Come on, guys! Hear me out!
Would you cool it already?
Okay, what do you want?
I was thinking about this last night...
So, if you were to eat human flesh,
would it taste good or bad?
Come on, Mista.
Don't talk about stuff like that.
Why the hell would you bring
that up out of the blue?
Get outta here! Go eat by yourself!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Scrunch
Kapow
You won't be heading anywhere.
In particular, you will never
arrive at the truth.
Why, you little brat!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Useless!
No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Episodio 38 Golden Wind Requiem
Y-You did it! At last!
Your Golden Wind evolved
with the arrow, and...
I couldn't see what it did,
so I don't really know how,
but you finally defeated him!
But... wait a sec.
Did he float up anywhere?
Hey, where is he? Where's his body?
Damn it!
Where is he?! Find him, Giorno!
Where is he?!
I'm just...
barely... still alive...
somehow...
But...
What was that?
My prediction clearly showed
my victory... and yet...
What in the world... was that Requiem?
I need to escape... into this sewer for now...
I still... have enough strength left for that...
I did it...
Was I just lucky?
You jackass!
I-I'm not g-gonna let you
s-snatch my precious c-coat!
It's not happening!
What? You wanna fight?
Well, do ya?! Don't mess with me!
I'll take you on anytime!
Come at me, ya dickhead!
What?!
Come on! Come at me!
I-Impossible!
This can't be...
You're never gonna get my coat!
I can't stand up!
S-Someone...
You ain't getting it...
I-I can't... Not here...
I-I'm Diavolo!
Not at the hands of a guy like him...
I'm fading...
Where am I?
Why am I sleeping on a bed?
I fell into the river, and then,
when I got into that sewer...
Let's see... Today's date is the 25th.
11:20 AM.
File number 68.
I, Dr. Monica Ultello,
will be handling this case.
We have an adult male,
between the ages of 30 and 40.
His identity is unknown.
Judging from the state of his skin, it's been about 48 to 54 hours since his death.
I will now begin the autopsy to
determine his cause of death.
Hey, woman... What are you talking about?
Although his body was found near the river,
Where am I? What am I doing here?!
he had barely any water in him,
so he couldn't have drowned.
Hey, woman!
I can't move...
M-My fingers...
My body...
What in the world is...
Hey, woman! Are you listening to me?!
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing?!
Why won't my body move?!
A-And this pain...
I-It hurts!
The cause of death is a stab
wound reaching his liver.
There are no marks indicating hesitation,
so we can rule out suicide.
Next, I'll dissect his abdomen
and check inside, just in case.
His liver is very healthy.
It's a very nice color.
I-It was just a dream?
Am I just dreaming?
But...
I-It's happening again.
What time is it? Where am I?
I was in the Tiber River in Rome...
And that feeling...
That unimaginable pain I experienced
in the autopsy room...
I-It was too real to be a dream...
Hello, sir?
Are you all right?
Why are you hunched over like
that? Are you not feeling well?
Jump
Hey, stop that!
What in the world is this?!
Something's wrong!
I-I couldn't possibly die
in such a stupid manner!
Don't tell me that this is...
Golden Wind Requiem's—
We have to find him!
I can sense that he's still alive!
I can't relax until we know for sure!
No, there's no reason to look for him.
What?
Everything's already over.
I wasn't able to clearly see
Requiem's ability myself,
but I know deep in my heart that it's true.
He won't be heading anywhere ever again.
In particular, he'll never arrive at the truth...
He'll never even arrive at
the truth behind his death.
Why are you hunched over, mister?
Does your tummy hurt?
Eternally.
B-But he's alive...
His end is that there is no end.
That's... Golden Wind Requiem's ability!
H-How many times am I going to die?!
Wh-When am I going to be
attacked next, and from where?!
S-Stay back!
Stay away!
S-Stay...
Stay the hell away from me!
So we finally did it?
We're the ones who won?
Hey, come on! Let's hurry
back to the Colosseum.
Bucciarati might've gotten his
soul back, but his body is hurt.
He's probably wondering what the hell
happened to us at the Colosseum!
Right.
Giorno, come on!
We're going back to the Colosseum!
Let's heal Bucciarati's wounds and head home!
Yeah...
Let's go.
I'll be right there.
Giorno, that's how it should be.
Don't worry about it.
What we've accomplished up to
this point is an absolute victory.
Fate is a sleeping slave.
And we've set that slave free.
That's what our victory is.
Giorno Giovanna
Golden Wind Requiem
Just hear me out!
Taking time to really think
about what you're eating
is connected to whether or not
you're living a happy life.
That's why I think it's really important.
So, there are animals
that are carnivores, right?
You know, like lions, cats, and vultures.
You won't find meat from carnivores
like that at a restaurant.
Why is that?
Because it's too smelly to eat!
It's disgusting!
Listen up, guys!
Cats are too disgusting to eat.
Are we on the same page so far?
I'd never eat a cat, even if some culinary
expert said it was the best thing ever!
On the other hand, have you
heard of a fish called "sweetfish"?
Sweetfish don't eat bugs.
They only eat algae.
They're vegetarian.
Usually, fish guts are too bitter to eat,
but sweetfish guts are delicious.
It's because they're not carnivores.
So with that logic in mind,
all the meat we consider delicious
is from herbivorous animals!
Cows, pigs, and chickens!
The better their feed,
the better they taste!
Which leads us to this conclusion...
Humans would taste gross
because they eat meat!
Well? How do you like the
opinion I came up with?
I see. That's actually rather convincing.
That whole thing that comes up in
novels about human flesh tasting good
is a flat-out lie!
I, uh... I actually eat a lot more vegetables
and fruits than meat, though...
Then you might actually be pretty tasty!
Narancia, don't egg him on!
Hey, you're late, Bucciarati.
You know Leaky Eye Luca, who's in
charge of the airport, right?
His dead body was just discovered.
I've been ordered by the
capo Polpo to check it out.
I hate that guy. He deserved to die.
He had no qualms about tormenting the weak,
and he sold drugs to kids.
He probably got high and
hit his head or something.
Narancia, you may feel that way deep
inside, but don't actually say it.
Think about the world we live in.
Do you want me to look into this?
You're going to be a capo someday.
You don't need to trouble yourself
with such trivial matters.
No, I'll be looking into this myself.
By the way, Fugo...
Oh, right. You have a guest.
He's been waiting for you all morning.
He's a civilian who runs a
flower shop in Monsanto Plaza.
I've looked into him already.
He's an ordinary, responsible gentleman,
but he lost his only
daughter six months ago.
Mr. Bucciarati... As you can see,
my legs don't work so well,
and I came here without my wife,
who usually accompanies me,
so I apologize for coming here alone.
Do you pay your taxes?
I beg your pardon?
Do you always honestly pay the taxes
you owe to this country on time?
Of course I do...
I don't know what you came
here to talk to me about,
but a civilian like you shouldn't be here.
If you properly pay your taxes,
you should go talk to the police or
anyone else who deals with the law.
The moment you start talking
to me, you'll end up in
far deeper debt to the organization
than you can even imagine.
I, just like everyone else in this country,
have worked hard for my family,
believed in the law,
and raised my child with proper morals.
She was my only daughter.
She had turned seventeen last September.
I apologize if I sound overbearing,
but I'd like to continue this
conversation with you in private.
If you want to continue
this conversation...
They all trust me greatly,
and I also trust them.
And you're asking me to interrupt their
meal and tell them to go outside?
I can't do that.
This happened a few months ago...
My wife told me that my
daughter had a boyfriend.
I heard that he was a young sculptor
who was just getting started.
That was fine and all, but despite the
fact that he was older than my daughter,
he never came to introduce
himself to us, her parents.
That got to me.
And shortly after...
my daughter jumped off the roof
of his apartment building,
holding a strange rock sculpture he had
made, and plunged into the courtyard...
I'm terribly sorry for
losing my composure...
Why do my tears hurt so much?
My daughter was my hope...
My daughter shone with youthful beauty...
I want you to avenge my daughter!
Please make that man pay!
Hang on a second.
Are you saying this was murder?
Are you implying that this boyfriend
pushed her off the roof?
If a murder happened in this town,
I would have heard about it.
The police refused to look into
it further and ruled it a suicide.
Even my lawyer!
But there's something that
only her family knows...
My daughter would never commit suicide!
Both my wife and I can say
that with confidence!
Please! I want you to settle
this once and for all!
Please make him, the bastard who's still
living his life as usual, experience
these tears of despair that I'm crying!
Life is full of hardships.
I feel for you, but I can't agree to this.
Are you trying to imply that we're some
assassins who would lynch just anyone?
Everyone in this town relies on you.
I'm just asking for the rightful punishment!
The rightful punishment?
Florist, earlier, you asked
if we could talk privately.
That was because you knew how
dangerous this conversation is, wasn't it?
But what you said about something
only her family would know...
I can't take that lightly.
To think that no one involved
with the law was moved by
those words in the past six months...
I find that rather unbelievable.
I can at least try to make
this boyfriend talk.
I'll only ask for that payment once
we confirm that he's actually guilty.
Does that work for you?
Mr. Bucciarati!
Mista.
I'd like you to look into this.
Sure.
Bad luck
What the heck...
is this rock?
Kill me
Mista, make sure you put that back.
Uh... Did I knock this rock... off of its stand?
Was it always here?
Be careful when you stand up.
Make sure you don't hit that rock.
Mista, Bucciarati says we
can drive you partway.
Right...
Mista, here's the address
to the apartment building.
Here's a picture of the boyfriend.
Find him and make him talk.
You can get a little rough
with him if you need to.
Make sure you get a confession.
You've got a tape recorder, right?
Yeah... But how far should I go?
I mean, if he actually ends up being
a murderer and killed that girl...
We aren't assassins.
Make it so he can't walk for four or five
years, and leave the rest to the police.
I'm sure that'll satisfy the
florist's need for revenge.
Menacing
Hey, where are you going?
Hurry up and get in the car.
I'm gonna leave you behind.
Mista! Do you want a ride or not?
Are you taking a piss?
I'm not! Yes, I want a ride!
I'll be right there!
What's been bothering you, Mista?
Well, there's something that's been
bugging me about the florist's story.
He mentioned that when his
daughter jumped off the roof,
she was holding some kind of rock, right?
Did he mention what kind of rock it was?
A rock?
Like, the shape of it...
How big was the rock?
The boyfriend is a sculptor, right?
He said it was a strange-looking rock.
Yeah, but what exactly did this
strange-looking rock look like?
He only said it looked strange.
What are you getting at, Mista?
Wait, that stone back there...
S-Stop the car for a sec, Fugo!
Stop the car!
Why?
Just stop the damn ca—
Why do you want me to stop the car?
E-Er, never mind...
I was just seeing things.
It's nothing.
Are you all right?
How much wine did you have earlier?
Hey! I'm not drunk!
Sorry for saying something stupid!
I'm terribly sorry for all the trouble!
That's his apartment building, right?
You can drop me off here.
Oh, for crying out loud...
Shouldn't someone else go
with Mista on this job?
Should I accompany him?
No, I'll go with Mista.
I just remembered the rumor about Stand
users gathering in this town for some reason.
You take care of the investigation
of Leaky Eye Luca.
Understood.
So the guy's apartment is
on the seventh floor...
And above that is the roof.
His name is Scolippi...
The courtyard...
So this is where the florist's daughter...
That's a Stand!
This incident involves a Stand user!
And what the hell is this rock?!
Bucciarati!
Episodio 39
The Sleeping Slave