Passione is a pretty big gang organization.
First, there are groups made up of
six to ten underlings, like my team.
Then there are capos like
Polpo who command those teams.
They reign over a particular
region, making it their turf.
These teams include specialty teams, such
as an assassination team and a drug team.
Despite being from the same gang,
I really don't want to involve myself
with those teams or their capos.
And the one who stands
at the top is the boss.
The boss only has contact with the trusted
subordinate he considers his right hand,
and we have no way of
knowing who or where he is.
Gang members in this
city hate standing out,
as it can quickly lead
to their assassination.
So even the capos will dress
normally to blend in with the crowd,
and some even have cover jobs.
That goes double for our boss.
He won't reveal his identity to anyone.
If we go snooping around,
we're detected immediately.
I know plenty of guys this has happened to.
So, Giorno, in order for us to
get close to our mysterious boss,
we need to be acknowledged.
We can't defeat the boss unless
we earn the acknowledgement
and trust of someone close to the boss.
So first, we're going to get stronger.
We have to climb up
to the position of capo.
Of course, the two of us can't do that alone.
A team we can trust...
That's what we'll need to defeat the boss.
Episodio 05 Find Polpo's Fortune!
The news of the incarcerated Polpo's
death spread among the other capos.
According to our intelligence
team, it might've been suicide.
That's not his style.
Polpo was in a special cell.
Murder isn't possible.
Maybe he was plotting to betray the boss.
There aren't many capos
as trustworthy as him.
That's even less believable.
More importantly...
Yeah... The problem is his successor.
How do I look?
Rome 10:05 a.m.
I just heard that the capos are freaking out.
Apparently, Polpo committed suicide.
Huh?
Hey, watch where you're going!
I'm fine.
Suicide? That fatso?
I told you to watch where you're going!
So I dunno if Polpo was sad because he was in
prison or if his obesity made him depressed,
but he apparently wasn't very strong mentally.
He put his own gun in his
mouth and blew his brains out.
You sure it was suicide and not murder?
It was suicide, for sure.
From the... autopsy, they call it?
Any expert can tell if it
was a suicide or murder.
Hey, there's a light up ahead.
More importantly, have you heard
the rumors about Polpo's fortune?
Rumors?
I don't know where the end of the universe is,
and I don't know jack about that, either.
Before Polpo went to prison,
he converted some of his
fortune into jewels and gold
and hid them somewhere.
He has a hidden fortune.
It's too much to even deposit in the bank,
and he kept it secret from the organization.
No one was stupid enough to look
for it while Polpo was alive.
But now that he's dead,
that fortune doesn't belong to anyone.
It's free money.
It's said to be worth about five billion lire.
Five billion?
If I had that much money,
I'd be heading to Monaco or
Japan with a girl on each arm.
Nah, I'd rather work my way up.
If I can climb up to capo with that money,
I can taste honey that's even sweeter.
But who knows where it's hidden...
No one knows?
Nah, and this is just what I'm thinking...
But Polpo was such a fatty,
he couldn't even go outside on his own.
Do you think he could hide a fortune
worth five billion on his own?
He must've had someone do it for him.
Someone who's good at
keeping their mouth shut...
Though I'm not sure anyone
like that actually exists.
But Polpo liked Bucciarati.
Bucciarati? That's one of the
thugs from Naples, right?
Yeah. If anyone could've hidden it, it's him.
And now that Polpo's dead,
Bucciarati should be making his move...
to get the five billion lire
that's just been freed up.
I'm sure that even Bucciarati wants money.
Hey, Zucchero!
That bastard Zucchero actually left!
Did he seriously believe that?
If you're actually going to trail
Bucciarati, I'd be careful.
Apparently, he and his
subordinates are Stand users.
Naples 11:26 a.m.
Hey, Fugo.
It's such a nice day outside.
It wouldn't hurt to skip out
on studying for one day.
I'm just not feeling it today.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your strawberry cake.
Listen, Narancia.
Set it there.
Yes, sir.
You're amazing.
It's hard to ask someone
to teach you something
when you haven't really
even been to grade school.
But you even learned your multiplication tables!
You can do this. Just do as I've taught you.
You've got a good head on your shoulders.
Okay, ready? What's six times five?
Six times five... Six and five...
Thirty?
Correct! See? I knew you could do it!
You're basically halfway there!
I see! Six times five is thirty! Okay!
Hey, what's the deal with this?!
What do you mean? It's strawberry cake.
Yeah, I can see that by looking at it!
It's obviously not chocolate
cake or cheesecake!
That's not the point here!
There are four slices of cake!
Do they want me to die?!
Again with this, Mista?
You moron!
It's bad luck to choose one from four!
Choosing from five is fine.
Choosing from three is fine.
But when you choose from four,
something bad will happen!
When I was a kid, another
kid adopted a kitten from
a litter of four that was
born in our neighborhood,
and then the cat scratched
his eye right out of his head!
Of course, he beat the cat to death later.
That's just an old wives' tale.
If you think about it rationally,
when people eat a cake one slice at a time,
someone's going to have to
take one of the last four slices.
That's the thing, though!
This is when the restaurant should be more
considerate and just bring us three slices!
Talk about shitty service!
Jeez... Don't eat it, then.
But I want some strawberry cake!
I did it!
I did it, Fugo! How's it look?
You're finished? Let's have a look.
What is this?
Am I right?
Crunch
You stupid delinquent!
Are you messing with me?!
How many times do I have to
teach you this before you learn?!
You shit-for-brains!
Oh, boy. He's lost it now.
You just said six times five was thirty,
so why the hell is your answer even less?!
Hey, Abbacchio, are you gonna eat that cake?
What?
Did you just call me shit-for-brains?
It's not good to look down on others.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you, Fugo.
You bastard...
What the hell are you guys doing?!
I could hear you all the
way from the entrance!
You're bothering the other customers!
This is the new member
I told you about yesterday.
Let me introduce you.
This is Giorno Giovanna.
I'm Giorno Giovanna.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm sorry, Fugo.
No, I should apologize.
Please forgive me, Narancia.
I'll study even harder, so teach me again.
Hey!
I'm the one who brought him
here, so be respectful!
Mr. Bucciarati.
What is it?
There's a phone call for you.
All right, thanks.
Make sure you guys properly
greet Giorno! Got it?
Giorno, I'll be right back.
Take some time to get to know these guys.
All right.
Giorno, was it?
Why don't you have a seat?
Let's have some tea and chat.
Here you go, Mr. Bucciarati.
Thanks.
This is Bucciarati.
All right.
Is something wrong?
No.
Bucciarati! Bucciarati, do you have a second?
Oh, hello, Ms. Menini.
What's the matter?
I'd like to ask a favor.
Could we talk outside?
Of course.
Well, drink up.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Fifteen? Ha, you're two
years younger than me.
Thank you for the tea.
What's wrong?
You just thanked me for the tea that
I so generously poured for you.
Since you already thanked me for
it, you'll just have to drink it.
Or do you not want to drink
it since it's not very hot?
Maybe he doesn't want to drink it because
he doesn't want to be one of us.
What the hell are you guys doing?!
It's nothing.
He went to the trouble
of pouring this tea for me.
No freakin' way!
What did you guys do?
Gross! He actually drank it!
D-Dude, you're hilarious!
Did you seriously drink it?
No, there's no way he could have!
Hey, how'd you do it? Where'd you hide it?
Hey, come on. Just tell me! Okay?
Who knows?
You're all keeping your abilities
secret, too, aren't you?
So he's a Stand user?
What I did with the liquid in the cup is...
I used my ability to change one
of my teeth into a jellyfish,
which is 98 percent liquid, to suck it up.
Is it, like, some ability to move things?
Open your mouth.
There's no hole in there, is there?
You actually drank it for real?
I'm not sure what it is,
Was that your favorite or something?
but there's something about Giorno Giovanna
that makes him hard to dislike.
If you guys tell me about your
powers, I might tell you mine.
You're cautious. I respect that.
Does Bucciarati know?
Yeah.
They're not exactly a team yet,
but we don't have any time to wait.
This has to be decided now.
Quit screwing around. We're going out.
Huh? Where?
Follow me and you'll find out. Hurry it up.
Bucciarati! How are you?
Oh, Mr. Bucciarati!
Hey, Bucciarati.
Come by my shop again sometime!
I will!
Hey, what are we going to do about a car?
We got a loaner.
Since a certain someone
destroyed our last one.
As I suspected, the citizens trust him.
Hey, I told you that wasn't my fault!
Bucciarati, this is my friend,
and she's in a bit of trouble
because her son is beating her.
Right?
I see. That's rough.
I'll give him a talking-to.
What's your son's name?
Thank you.
He's usually such a sweet boy.
But lately, he's been getting into drugs...
Bucciarati, I've been living in
this neighborhood for fifty years.
But lately, I've been so anxious.
Who's making them sell those drugs?
I'm so scared.
Hey, you're going to protect
us, aren't you, Bucciarati?
You're on our side, right?
Yeah... I'll take care of it.
I'll figure it out.
We're going cruising on a yacht?
That's awesome!
When did you get a yacht?
We're going to rent one.
Huh?
Aw, it's just a rental.
Say, Bucciarati...
Whatever you do, please don't
rent that one with the number 4.
It'll sink. I know it.
Oh, come on... If that were the case,
it wouldn't be floating there now.
Shut up!
Then you can ride on that one!
We'd like to rent a yacht.
Of course! You can use whichever one you like.
Other than 4!
All right. Sir, I'd like the one on the far left.
All right. Let me get you the key.
For now, I'd like to rent it for three days.
How much will that cost?
Oh, I could never ask you
for money, Mr. Bucciarati!
Use it as long as you'd like.
Thanks.
Ring me up, pops!
This feels nice.
Hey, Narancia... Hey!
Huh?
Well, uh, you know...
You bought drinks, didn't you?
Would you sell me one?
What? You always say that, but you never pay!
Oh, who cares? Gimme one!
Come on, hurry! Gimme!
You're so helpless.
You want a cola or Sparite?
I'll take a co— Actually,
a Sparite, since it's clear.
Here you go.
Thanks. Could you hold this magazine for me?
Thanks, and thanks again...
Huh? What's wrong with this thing?
It just stopped working!
Why'd it stop?
I just bought it!
Damn it! How dare he sell
me something like this?!
That stupid old guy from the electronics
store is gonna regret this!
Hey!
Come on, Bucciarati! Hurry up and
tell us where this boat's headed!
Fine. We're far enough
away from the shore now.
We're headed to Capri.
Capri?
We're not going there as tourists, are we?
Correct.
Then why are we going there?
This morning, the capo
Polpo committed suicide.
What? Suicide?! Polpo did?
No way!
But why?
It doesn't matter why he died.
Polpo was a capo who did
things that'd get him killed.
But what does he have to do
with why we're going to Capri?
Polpo actually has a secret fortune.
It's worth...
ten billion lire!
T-Ten billion?
I'm the only person who
knows where it's hidden.
I'm the one he ordered to hide it.
That ten billion now belongs to us!
With that money, we can
claim the rank of capo!
A-Awesome!
He's definitely a man
who's going to the top.
Just like I thought,
he's going to become a capo!
He earned this opportunity
by working diligently enough to be
acknowledged and liked by a capo.
Amazing.
Seriously? This took a
sudden turn for the awesome.
Where is it?
Where'd you hide that kind of
fortune on Capri, Bucciarati?
I can't tell you that yet.
Rumors of his hidden fortune have
made the rounds in the organization.
No one can find out before
we secure the money.
B-Bucciarati!
Hey! Something's wrong!
Did something happen, Narancia?
Narancia!
What the heck are you doing?
H-Hey, come look at this!
There's only one shoe left...
Give that here, Giorno!
I don't quite understand what's going on.
Where did Narancia go?
You guys didn't see it?
To me, it looked like Narancia
got pulled into this box.
What?
That's impossible!
He didn't randomly fall
into the ocean, did he?
Narancia, where are you?
Hey, Narancia! If you're just
fooling around and hiding... Hup!
Hurry up and answer us!
Narancia, where are you?
Narancia! Answer us!
Mista?
What are you doing, Mista?
Where did you go, Mista?
It can't be...
Come on, Mista!
Why are you messing around now—
Fugo?
Hey, Fugo!
What?
What's going on?
Abbacchio, Giorno, stay close to each other!
We're being attacked!
There's someone hiding
somewhere on this boat!
This is a Stand attack!
But why now?
The money.
Someone found out that I
knew where the money was,
and they're trying to steal it.
Which means they're from the organization.
Does that mean they've been quietly tracking
us ever since we were on the shore?
Looks that way.
They probably grew impatient because
I wouldn't just say where the money is.
They intend to get rid of everyone but me,
then make me cough up the location.
And they can take their time, since we're
on the ocean with nowhere to run.
Are you saying Narancia
and the others are dead?
I didn't say that.
But it's for ten billion.
They'd even kill someone from
their own organization for that.
No, Narancia and the others are alive.
They're somewhere on this boat.
I don't know if this person is
trying to use them as hostages,
but they're alive.
Giorno Giovanna,
how the hell can you be so sure about that?
I used my Stand to turn
Narancia's shoe into a fly.
The fly is trying to return
to its owner, Narancia.
If Narancia was truly dead, it wouldn't
be flying around searching like that.
Can you locate him?
He's alive... He's alive, but...
It's not going down into
the cabin or in the locker.
The fly's not trying to stop...
It keeps flying around that
area looking for Narancia.
What the hell is his ability?
Just shut up and listen.
Narancia is somewhere near
the entrance to the cabin.
That's a fact.
But for some reason, the fly
can't find him, so it's lost.
I think it's safe to assume that we'll
find the enemy wherever Narancia is.
Which means the enemy isn't just
randomly hiding behind something.
I see.
So if we don't figure out the
mystery behind the enemy's ability,
getting too close without
knowing could get us killed.
Correct.
But the fact that their ability requires them
to attack while hidden is a shortcoming.
If we can figure out the mystery behind
it, we'll be able to defeat them.
Abbacchio, your Stand...
might be perfect to defeat such an enemy.
Defeat?
Can you solve this mystery with your ability?
Hard to say...
Damn it, Abbacchio!
You'd better not be hung up on
stupid shit at a time like this!
Stupid shit?
No.
This has to do with my safety.
I can't just carelessly reveal my Stand ability
in front of a stranger that I can't trust.
Bucciarati,
I don't know what made you trust this guy,
but I don't consider him a part of the team.
If we don't figure out the enemy's
location, we're going to be killed!
And I'm saying that's just this
untrustworthy brat's hypothesis.
He just came up with it out of fear.
He didn't see anything.
Abbacchio!
The enemy is just hiding
somewhere in the cabin.
I'll find them and take care of them.
If we get close without figuring out
the mystery, we're going to get kil—
Shut your mouth!
You stupid little brat...
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream.
What are you talking about?
You can solve the mystery, right?
I'm counting on you!
Giorno!
What the hell are you doing?!
Roar
G-Giorno!
There's an enemy over there!
Shit!
Giorno's in trouble!
Abbacchio...
Giorno Giovanna... You're one crazy bastard.
All this to prove yourself...
What the hell is wrong with you?
Episodio 06
Moody Jazz's Counterattack