You gonna be able to track them, Melone?
Yeah.
I've managed to collect a blood sample.
Bucciarati's, that is.
Hey, when's this train
gonna get underway?
Please, just wait a little bit longer.
We have another driver on the way right now!
What? What happened to the first one?
Ugh, talk about annoying.
Especially that crying brat over there.
I knew I shouldn't have gotten on
this train with all these peasants.
Miss.
How's your health?
H-Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
This is my compartment!
You can read what's written
on the door, can't you?
Do you have anything with
your birthdate written on it?
Uh...
Oh.
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Born March 10, 1977.
Twenty-four years old.
Very... bellissimo.
A very good age.
Don't touch my things!
Get out!
Smack
So good...
What a magnificent slap.
If you have the energy to produce
such a strong slap, there's no doubt.
You are...
in excellent health.
"Health: excellent."
And judging by the taste of your
fingers, your blood type is O.
Right?
What's your deal? Are you a thief?
Who do you think I am?
My family—
Ah, I don't need your name.
I don't care about where you
were born or your upbringing.
What's important is your
current health condition,
your birthday, and your blood type.
A Pisces and type O!
Bucciarati is an Aries and type A,
and, according to horoscopes,
is a terrible match for you.
And that's so perfect!
Looks like you drink and smoke, as well.
Do you do any drugs?
If you're doing any drugs...
You're even more amazingly di molto great!
I-If you want money, I have it...
If you want more, I have a credit card...
Listen.
Could you be quiet and listen?
This next question is the
most important of all.
What's important here is your preference.
Which do you prefer?
Apparently the Indian Karma Sutra,
which was written 1,500 years ago,
has more than 48 positions in it.
And I think it's really important...
as the beginning that leads to
the birth of an excellent child.
Now, choose.
Babyhead!
H-H-Help me!
Help me!
Conception complete
3 minutes until birth
Analyzing the DNA from Bruno Bucciarati's blood sample.
Would you like to integrate the DNA into a body and nurture it so that it can be tracked?
Oh, yes. We're going to nurture it...
1: Yes. 2: No.
into something atrocious.
Di molto...
Episodio 17  Babyhead
As long as no one finds us,
we should make it to Venice
by tomorrow or the day after.
Man... Everyone seems super bummed.
I wonder if Bucciarati said
something harsh to Trish.
No... I think she's worried because
Bucciarati hasn't told her anything.
Trish is probably a Stand user,
but hasn't realized it.
And her mysterious father...
She has all sorts of questions on her mind.
But Bucciarati is forbidden to
speak about any of those things.
I'd like to look more into her abilities.
They'd probably offer some hints
about the mysterious boss.
She's very strong-willed.
She doesn't cry or complain at all.
Mista!
Tell Number Two and Number Three
to share the hamburger with us!
Huh? What are you talking about?
There's nothing to eat here right now...
Huh?
Where the hell did you get that?!
D-Don't tell me...
Why'd my hamburger disappear?
There's something under the seat.
Sh-Shit!
A turtle?
There's something on its back...
What are we going to do, Mista?
It looks like some kind of jewel... Is it a key?
This seems bad.
What just happened?
Mista, you were keeping watch
on the ceiling, weren't you?
What happened?
Huh? Me?
I-I haven't the slightest.
I wasn't watching at that moment...
Huh? Maybe the truck stopped...
Birth complete
Ow!
What happened?
Th-This...
D-Don't tell me I—
Thank goodness. Nothing happened.
That stupid asshole!
What the hell was up with
that creepy bastard?!
How dare he make me think
I was about to die?!
I wanna kill him, damn it!
That piece of shit!
Hello? Are you the conductor of this train?
Come to my compartment, right now!
What does "kill" mean?
Looks like they were born.
They're starting to learn from their mother.
Babyhead's child, that is...
And this is great!
They're already responding to their
mother's desire to kill someone!
Make us proud!
I'm telling you, some creepy bastard
attacked me here! He attacked me!
It's because you have that poor
excuse for a lock on the door!
There's even a bump on my head!
Ugh, I'm so pissed!
That piece of shit! I hope
you guys are prepared!
What does... "kill" mean?
I'm going to sue the hell out of
you guys! This is unbelievable!
What does... "piece of shit" mean?
Would you like to learn some more?
Okay, pay close attention.
This is Mr. Lion. He's the king of beasts.
The one with the long nose is Mr. Elephant,
and the one with the long
neck is Mr. Giraffe.
The one eating the grass is Mr. Zebra.
And...
Oh, what's this?
This is what "kill" means.
Do you understand?
It means to make them die,
or to get rid of them.
Next... Oh, we have some children's games.
A spinning top and baseball.
This is bowling, and these are ice skates.
Oh, dear! Look at how handy these things
are when you use them like this!
The ones who died are the pieces of shit.
You use "piece" when there's only one and
say "pieces" when there's more than one.
Do you understand?
But you can kill them in whatever
way your instincts tell you to.
However, you are forbidden
to attack this girl named Trish.
You need to capture her alive.
There is also a newbie
whose face we haven't seen yet.
They're with Bucciarati as well,
so you need to find them and kill them.
I have to pee.
What should I do?
What should you do?
I mean, just do it?
Babies pee all the time.
But it doesn't look like
the lock's been broken...
H-Hey, what is this?!
There's something leaking from
the ceiling of this stupid train!
I don't see anything...
I-It stinks!
What is this?! It's so dirty and gross!
Miss...
Mommy said that I stink.
She's also screaming that I'm "dirty and gross."
So it seems. And how does
that make you feel about her?
What a great mommy!
Yes!
Di molto! This is extremely wonderful!
You're learning so well!
I'm hungry...
What should I do?
Not yet. You haven't learned enough yet.
It's too soon.
Let me drink! Hurry and let me drink!
Hey, not yet! I told you, not yet!
I can't take this anymore!
I can't spend another second on this train!
I'll sue the train company and make sure
they take responsibility for all this!
I'll tell them the bump on my
head is a concussion, too...
Huh? I don't hear her anymore...
She was too good of a mother!
It's good that she taught him the desire
to kill first, but this is too early!
H-Hey!
Bucciarati's DNA is currently not moving...
It's idle somewhere up north.
What am I going to do with you?
I guess I can't deny your talents, though.
It looks like the automatic tracking
of Bucciarati's DNA has kicked in.
It's a hassle, but Babyhead's son is an
invincible, remote-controlled Stand.
Nothing can defeat you!
Melone
Babyhead
Let's just steal one already.
Are you stupid?
Word would spread in no time
and go right to the enemy.
Then they'll just be waiting to ambush us!
That's true.
Fugo's got a good point.
Then let's hear what
Bucciarati wants us to do.
Wh-What are you doing, Giorno?
If we steal only one,
we'll be caught immediately.
But if we steal a hundred...
If it isn't just a single
car that disappeared,
and if they're all found in
pieces at different locations,
the search for the missing
cars will be much harder,
and it should give us plenty
of time to get to Venice.
I see...
That definitely beats hitchhiking.
Whatever.
Giorno, you tell Bucciarati.
Here.
We're going to go get a car.
Please get down from the chair.
It's very dangerous outside right now.
Listen, Mr. Bucciarati.
If I were to ask you a dumb question,
would you be able to answer it?
It depends on the question.
What am I supposed to do if
I need to go to the bathroom?
You aren't suggesting that
I use a diaper, are you?
I see... That's a very good question.
Good. I'm glad you understand.
Let's make the closet a toilet.
Please, go ahead.
Go ahead?
You said you had to go to the bathroom.
I don't know where it leads underneath that,
but I'm sure the turtle will be fine.
It might actually get nutrients from it.
I have no idea what you're trying to say...
Bucciarati, we've procured a car.
All right. Once we confirm
that we're safe, let's head out.
Understood.
That bike... When did it show up here?
Where's the person who was riding it?
Giorno, is something wrong?
Trish?
What the hell?!
Trish!
I-Impossible!
Zipper—
Shit... It's a Stand, and
a remote-controlled one!
But this power isn't remote-controlled. What's—
Bucciarati, please be on your guard.
A strange bike has appeared.
Bucciarati?
Don't tell me... Bucciarati!
Where's Trish? Trish!
I had the turtle in my
hands this whole time...
I'd know if they came outside.
Could the enemy have already
used some kind of attack?
Golden Wind!
Di molto!
I've captured the boss's daughter, Trish,
and Bucciarati as well.
What should I do now?
Di molto! Well done, Babyhead!
Get away from there immediately, of course!
I'm currently inside a turtle...
There's one human waiting at the exit of the turtle.
I've never seen him before.
He's going to find me on my way back. What should I do?
Someone you've never seen?
That must be the newbie.
If he finds you, you're going
to have to get rid of him.
Roger.
I will get rid of the newbie who's waiting at the turtle's exit.
But make sure you do it quietly
so you aren't found by the others.
Capturing Trish takes top priority.
I'll have them head over
there as well, just in case.
I thought I felt a presence there, but...
No, you were correct.
Everyone! There's an enemy here!
We're being atta—
D-Did it take... my throat?!
Are you done yet, Mista?
Don't rush me!
Is something wrong?
Nah. Giorno's waving.
I'm pretty sure Bucciarati's telling
us to hurry up and get the car.
I just told you not to rush me!
The attack was successful. It's very quiet,
because I stole part of his throat.
Di molto! Well done!
Impossible! I destroyed the cabinet,
but it's still not showing itself?
And how am I not able to see
it the moment it attacks me?
Where is it hiding, and how is
it carving out pieces of me?
Carving out pieces... Which means...
Shpang
So you've carved away his leg and eye, too?
Di molto! Well done!
Now, come back, Babyhead!
The attack was unsuccessful.
Obviously, he's figured out what I am. What should I do?
What?
The newbie outside has removed the key from the turtle's back.
Apparently, when someone removes the key, only living things can leave.
My body is floating upward.
What should I do?
I'm not sure what you're
saying... Living things?
You're a Stand! It doesn't matter
if you're living or not.
That's true, but right now,
I have the eye that I stole from him.
His eye is living.
I knew it... It was that cabinet.
I see now...
It's not that I couldn't see the enemy.
I'd seen them all along!
This ability chops up humans and
reconstructs them into something else!
Melone.
What should I do?
Don't panic! Who cares if he
figured out your ability?
The newbie hasn't been able to breathe for
a while, and he's missing a leg, right?
Just defeat him already and steal
the turtle, along with Trish!
Roger.
Golden Wind!
It's dodging by splitting itself apart!
Which means...
G-Guys...
I need to somehow... let them know...
That had some effect!
No, that was just a rock.
Sh-Shit...
Trish is going to get taken...
At this rate, Bucciarati will be eliminated!
I-It's strong...
Is it... invincible?
I will leave the newbie's corpse here.
As planned, I've quietly captured Trish.
Di molto! Good!
I'm heading back to the train
you're on now, Melone.
Reconstructing humans into objects...
Your ability gave me an excellent hint.
Your ability is similar to my Golden Wind.
They're very much alike in the way
that they both recreate something.
Due to the hint you gave me,
and almost being killed,
it would appear...
that I've grown a little.
M-Melone, did you hear that?
I totally forgot earlier, but now
I know the newbie's Stand ability.
What about the newbie?
His button has become an eye!
In his hand! It became an eyeball!
Hey, Babyhead, what are you talking about?
What's this about the dead newbie?
He inserted the eye into his face!
Rumble
He did the same with his throat and leg!
His ability is to create life!
He created his own parts!
His ability is the exact opposite of mine!
Hey, who the hell are you talking about?
You're not getting away! Golden Wind!
The newbie... He...
He's been revived!
A-Are you listening, Melone?
He made parts of the motorcycle into roots!
I can't separate them!
I have to get rid of the
parts that are stuck!
I need to get away from the bike!
Did it turn into a rock again?
This isn't good. He's going
to try to pick up the turtle.
I'll kill him before he picks it up!
Calm down, Babyhead!
Let him pick up the turtle.
What do you mean?
The moment he picks up the turtle,
tear him apart for good.
Oil's pouring out. That's not good!
Make sure he can never get up again!
I got him!
It was only a little bit, but how
dare you freak me out, you bastard?!
Now, I'm going to rip your head—
I've learned a lot from your ability
to turn humans into objects.
I'm not sure if it's fate or if our
Stands were attracted to each other
due to their similarities that we met.
But because of you,
my Golden Wind was able to grow.
Wh-Where did it go?
I just tore off your wrist. Where did it go?
Tore off?
That's incorrect.
I intentionally let it go.
I'd like to give you a little advice.
You should probably use your hand to
defend yourself, rather than attack me.
D-Don't you dare underestimate me!
Take this!
What?!
The hand that I cut off has already
become another living creature
and invaded your body.
Yes.
As you can see, it turned into a piranha!
Episodio 18
Head to Venice!