Episodio 16  The Thankful Death Part 2
Pesci! What the hell are you doing?!
Pesci!
Hurry up and stop the train!
B-Bro!
Stop the train!
Bro!
I-I don't know how to stop it!
Now you and your aging ability
will both disappear.
Then my crew will return to
normal, and Trish will be safe!
You bastard...
Bucciarati!
Bro!
What?!
Prosciutto!
W-Well done, Pesci!
Excellent work! That was quick thinking!
That was close...
I almost didn't make it, but thank
goodness I managed to hook him!
Now my hook will never let him go!
B-But this is definitely
the weight of two people!
Bucciarati must be hanging on, too!
I seriously thought I was
done for, Bucciarati.
I called you a failure of a capo,
but I take that back now.
I apologize for my rudeness.
You are able to make decisions impartially.
You're even able to risk your own life.
The boss made the right decision,
leaving Trish in your hands.
I'm actually astonished.
However, Bucciarati...
You're an unlucky capo!
Now, fall into the hell of
150 kilometers per hour!
Zipper Man!
Did you forget?
You're still aging as we speak!
Too slow!
You know... I was saved by that
line your little bro sent out.
He wasn't aiming for me.
Could I actually be the unlucky one?
There was no way Mista
should have been alive!
I fired three bullets straight into his head.
The fact that he's alive
is as messed up as someone
saying the sun rises in the west!
I happened to let him know
that the energy from an attack on the line
gets sent back to the one who's hooked!
Impossible!
Bucciarati!
It's one person lighter now!
We must've thrown Bucciarati off!
We did it, Prosciutto!
Looks like the aging is wearing off.
Now we just have to deal
with the fishing hook guy!
Yeah.
Earlier, my Fisher Man's hook definitely
dug into Bro's right hand...
His pinky was on the right
side of the hook.
But right now...
The pinky is on the left side of the hook.
This is someone's left hand!
What the heck's going on?
Whose hand is on the other end?
How did Bro's right hand
switch to his left?!
N-Now that I think about it...
Bro also seems just a bit heavier...
H-Hey, you!
Make them stop the train!
I think everyone on this train is sick!
I'm starting to feel much better, but...
I've lost some teeth!
Th-The aging has stopped!
Hey, are you listening to me?!
Have the driver stop the train, quick!
It can't be...
Don't tell me the weight that
was flung from the line was...
It can't be!
It can't be! It can't be true!
Don't tell me that Bro...
Are you listening to me, you dumbass?!
I'm talking to you! You, right there!
My bro, Prosciutto!
What should I do? What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
No way! The guys inside the turtle
are going to come out, too!
Wh-What should I do? What should I...
What the hell are you even saying?!
I'm telling you to make them stop the train!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up, damn it!
You some kind of mammoni?!
Fine. I'm starting to feel better,
so I'll tell them my—
Wh-What's going on?
The aging hasn't stopped!
Bucciarati, y-you're...
Impossible...
Don't tell me... Don't tell me he...
What?!
Thankful... Death...
Bro!
You were right, Bro...
You were totally right.
You said we should never
release our Stand ability once we've gotten
a hold of them, even if we lose a limb...
Bro...
With the mess his body's in,
th-there's no way he can survive...
He's going to die any second now,
and yet he isn't releasing his Stand's ability!
We have to get Trish,
no matter what, right, Bro?
We can't turn back now...
I get it now, Prosciutto!
I understand your resolve
not as mere words,
but within my heart.
Once we think of killing someone, Bro,
the deed has already been done!
That's the first time I did someone in.
But it wasn't as big of a deal
as I thought it'd be.
And now, there's no one left
to call me a mammoni.
Pesci
Fisher Man
I'm going to settle this once and for all
before Bro's ability disappears!
Bucciarati! You need to hurry
up and remove that hook!
Yeah.
You opened up your hand with a zipper.
He can tell what I'm trying to do?
I'll read all of his actions!
I'll make the hook travel from his hand
down his wrist and to his forearm!
The hook's traveling further up your arm!
The hook is out again!
It's no use. Whenever I try
to get the hook out,
he reads my moves
within a few centimeters!
And he's powerful!
I'm not going to lose track of your body!
And I'm going to get Trish and make sure
Prosciutto's will is seen through!
Bucciarati! The bastard down there!
If we finish him once and for all,
Giorno and the others will stop aging
and take care of the fishing line guy!
I know, but that's proving
quite difficult to do, too!
I'll make you suffer the same
agony my Bro is going through!
Bucciarati!
He's hanging on to something.
In that case... You can just go up!
You're heading right for
those electrical wires!
Get chopped in half!
I felt an impact, but he didn't
get chopped in half or fall off.
I feel a heartbeat through the line.
Bucciarati is still alive.
He's entered the train!
That was close, Bucciarati!
At this point, we're gonna
have to face him head-on!
Yes... But that's going
to be difficult, as well.
We won't make it in time.
The hook has now entered my chest!
What?!
The distance between the hook and
your heart is now twelve centimeters...
Eleven centimeters...
I underestimated the situation.
The enemy that posed a
greater threat on this train
wasn't the one who could age everyone.
The one who's even more terrifying
is the guy using this fishing line!
So what are you gonna do?!
The hook's gonna dig into your heart soon!
Nine centimeters, eight centimeters...
Then I don't have any choice.
In order to defeat his ability,
I'm just going to have to show him
that my resolve is superior to his!
Zipper Man!
What the hell are you doing?!
Bucciarati!
He disappeared!
I can't feel his pulse or the
vibration from his breathing...
Why?!
How did I lose his presence?
How?!
How can you do something
so insane, Bucciarati?!
I know there's no other way...
But seriously, are you going to be okay?!
Quiet... down.
Wait until he goes away.
This is what it means to have
resolve... Number Six.
Damn it, I can't find him!
Bucciarati can go anywhere with his zippers!
Could he be heading here
from s-some direction?
No, wait. Calm down...
Jumping at shadows is a sign of weakness!
That's what Prosciutto would tell me!
Be more confident, Pesci.
It doesn't matter if
you're on a moving train.
I'm sure you can find him
by sensing his heartbeat.
That's what he'd say!
There's no way Bucciarati
can move quickly right now!
He must still be somewhere near the hook!
H-He's extending the line even further!
Quickly, pull yourself together and run!
For now...
he's lost sight of me.
I can make it through this
as long as I don't move.
The fact that I'm not
doing anything right now
shows my resolve.
His heartbeat, his pulse...
Look for those two things.
Borgh
Got one! But that's not him!
The weight isn't right.
It must be another passenger!
This is... It's weakened,
but that's the sound of a heart!
N-No! He's going to find your heart!
How could you do such a thing?!
He said he wasn't going to do anything,
but he chopped his heart in
half to stop it from beating.
This is insane!
How long can humans live when their
heart and breathing have stopped?
D-Damn it! It's not there!
I don't sense anything
else moving in that room!
D-Did he move somewhere else
using his zippers after all?
Y-You're reaching your limit!
Where the hell did he go?!
Don't tell me that Bucciarati
actually managed to finish off Prosciutto...
Once the aging stops, the rest of Bucciarati's
guys will step out of that turtle!
God damn it!
I'm not gonna let that happen!
W-We did it! He gave up on this cabin!
Your resolve made him search elsewhere!
You managed to make it through!
Hurry up and zip your body
back together! Hurry it up!
Un...believable...
How unlucky...
Bucciarati! Pull yourself together!
My only expertise is controlling bullets!
I don't have enough energy to move
stuff that's bigger than me!
He was more stubborn than I thought...
He's... won...
Stop, you damned train!
What the heck?!
B-Bro!
This was definitely a difficult path
that I wouldn't have been able
to traverse without some luck.
The path leading closer to you, that is.
You're going to pay, Bucciarati...
You got close to him!
Your resolve won out, Bucciarati!
...right in front of Bro,
before he's gone for good.
What the hell?!
I'm surprised you were able
to see through that attack!
His eyes and face...
They look as if they've come through
ten years of endless bloodshed.
I feel such intensity and
calmness from his eyes.
Trickery won't work against him.
Do it... Victory is in
your hands... Pesci...
Do it... I'm watching... over you...
I will murder you!
What?!
I knew you'd do that!
Going up someone's arm to get to
their heart was a surefire plan
I've been using because I was less confident
and I thought I'd miss otherwise!
When I'm confident I won't miss,
I go straight for the heart!
Right now, I'm going to go
straight for everything!
I'm gonna murder you!
I'll rip your heart out, Bucciarati!
You're supposed to say that
after you've actually done it.
In the world of gangsters, that is.
Did I... lose?
Am I... going to die?
But... I'm not... just going to die!
Go ahead... and take her... and run...
I'll let Trish live...
He's got the turtle!
Wh-Where am I?
But before I die...
I'll leave your heart in despair!
The despair of losing your crew!
I'm going to smash this turtle to pieces!
Holy shit! That's not good!
Earlier, I saw nobility and resolve that was
hardened like a diamond, shining in your eyes.
But you've fallen.
Now you're just a piece of shit.
Fallen? Fallen, you say?!
The only ones who are going to fall
and get crushed are these bastards!
You won't make it in time!
I hope you enjoy hell, Bucciarati!
You're going to fail, no matter what,
when you're a piece of shit.
Arrivederci.
"Goodbye"
Prosciutto –Dead
Stand Name: The Thankful Death
Pesci –Dead
Stand Name: Fisher Man
As I figured, we won't be able
to continue riding this train.
Yeah.
There's no way they haven't
contacted the rest of their crew.
I'm sure they told the others about
our destination and the turtle.
We'll have to use another form
of transportation from here.
There's something I want to ask you.
Are you willing to give me an answer?
I haven't been given permission
to answer any of your questions.
Our mission is solely to be your bodyguards.
You are going to answer me.
Who am I?
What the hell is this?
What's this on the ground?
Why can I suddenly see such bizarre things?
Why is my life in danger because
of a father I don't even know?!
As I thought...
The boss's daughter is a Stand user.
Answer me!
Bruno Bucciarati
Zipper Man
It's currently 6:34 PM.
I got here twenty minutes
after the train stopped.
Prosciutto is dead next to the tracks.
Parts of Pesci's body, which has been
torn to pieces, are on the riverbank.
Judging from the scene, the one who
disposed of them is Bucciarati's Zipper Man.
I see. Where are those guys and the girl?
They're long gone.
You gonna be able to track them, Melone?
Yeah.
Everything the two who have fallen managed
to do will make tracking them possible.
I've managed to collect a blood sample.
Bucciarati's, that is.
Episodio 17
Babyhead