You're not leaving me with any choice.
My name's Formaggio.
How do you like that?
And that?! And that?! And that?!
I'm sure he plans to follow
me all the way back.
But...
I just have to make it back
without getting followed.
I'm going to follow the orders I was given!
Did you hear that loud noise?
I wonder what that was.
Come back for now, Li'l Bomber!
That bastard is somewhere nearby,
but I should get away from here.
With all these people gathering, it'd be
a bad idea to attack with my Stand.
Huh? The bleeding's stopped already.
I thought he cut me really good, too.
Huh?
Where'd this knife come from?
This isn't mine.
My knife's not this big.
Where'd mine go?
These shoes aren't mine, either!
They're way too big!
Where the hell did my shoes go?
There's something
weird about this seat...
A-And this steering wheel.
I-I can't reach!
My foot won't reach the pedals,
and this seat is huge!
I can't see through the windshield!
What the hell?! This car isn't mine, either!
Where'd it go? Where'd the
car I came here in go?!
I can't get back without it! Damn it!
Is he actually that stupid?
Get a damn clue! You're shrinking!
The effects of the wound I gave
you are finally starting to show!
W-Wait, these are my shoes and knife.
Which means...
Did you finally figure it out, you moron?
But it's too late now.
You won't be able to drive like that!
S-So this is that stalker guy's Stand ability?
You're gonna tell me where
the boss's daughter is.
The battle's already begun.
No one can turn back now!
Episodio 10  Hitman Team
Hey, did you guys get my mineral water yet?
I'm thirsty.
I'm about to die from thirst.
I'd actually like to have lunch soon myself.
I mean, I'm fine, but I need
to feed these little guys.
Feed us!
Narancia is indeed taking a while.
This is why I was worried about him going.
Drop it, Fugo. How many times
must you bring this up?
I'm not going to drop it! After I—
I-I apologize.
Anything cut by my Tiny Feet becomes small.
It does take a little while for the
ability to go into effect, though.
The clothes and bandana you have
on now are shrinking with you.
Your shoe and knife, which were separated
from your body, have stopped shrinking,
which means that the more you shrink,
the fewer things you'll be able to use.
O-Oh, yeah! I need to get a hold
of Bucciarati and the others!
Ow! What the hell's with
that automated door?!
I'm still shrinking?
This door...
I've become so light that it won't open!
Exactly, you moron.
Still...
I have to get to that phone as soon
as possible so they can help me!
It opened, damn it!
It's useless!
It looks like you haven't realized this, but
your clothes and wallet are shrinking with you.
You need a telephone card or
coins to use the pay phone!
It only takes coins that are the right size!
Narancia's Height: 62.5cm
This guy might be smarter than I thought...
This isn't good.
Having his friends find out my
ability is the last thing I need.
And if Bucciarati finds out about this,
he'll move the boss's daughter somewhere else!
That definitely can't happen!
I'm not gonna let that happen!
H-He's here! That bastard's
gotta be around here somewhere!
Where are you?
Are you hiding under the phone?
Come out here, damn it!
This is perfect.
Are you over here?
In a few more minutes, he'll shrink
down to the size of a cockroach.
Where are you?!
Narancia's Height: 58.0cm
His Stand's size and power will
get so small, it'll be powerless,
and then I'll be able to
torture the shit out of him.
Then I'll win!
I guess I don't have a choice.
He shouldn't be able to find me,
but I just have to wait a little longer...
I finally figured it out, you bastard!
You're in my right ass pocket!
Now I've got you!
The ability to become smaller?
Were you in my pocket this whole time?
Damn it. But you sure are tiny...
Wait... How did he figure
out I was in his pocket?!
Shoot him dead, Li'l Bomber!
T-Turn back!
Wha—
A b-ballpoint pen?!
Narancia's Height: 53.0cm
Damn it! Where'd you go?!
What the hell did you do?!
That stalker bastard! Where are you?!
That was a close one.
When my Tiny Feet shrinks
something other than myself,
it takes a while because
of the energy it needs,
but when I turn things back to normal size,
I can do it instantly, like I
did with that ballpoint pen.
The repulsion it created in that moment
was enough to send me flying over here.
But how'd he figure out
that I was in his pocket?
Did I move around too
much and tickle his ass?
I-Impossible!
I hid immediately! How'd it find me?!
There you are! You're not getting
away, you stalker bastard!
It's coming after me!
Th-This is bad! Tiny Feet!
Wh-Where'd that bastard go?!
That was way too close.
If the air pressure from the tire hadn't
sent me flying, I would've been done for!
But I'm sure it won't find me down—
Y-You can't be serious! Shit!
This Stand's ability isn't
just shooting endlessly!
It's somehow finding me,
and it's definitely following me!
And it's not like it's seeing or
hearing my movements.
That wouldn't explain how it
figured out I was in his pocket
or how it knew where the tire's
air pressure sent me flying.
I found you! You're down in that drain!
I-It can even find me underwater?!
Tiny Feet!
D-Damn it! Think, think,
think, think, think!
I can't die here!
The Hitman Team has nine members.
Formaggio is one of them.
2 years ago / Naples
I'm planning to address the trash
problem at next week's assembly.
Are you sure it'll be okay?
Don't worry. I'm just going to tell the
Minister of Tourism the right answer.
It's the same thing as usual.
I always worry that you might
be pushing yourself too hard.
Dear, don't you think you're
drinking too much today?
What the hell, Pesci?
Are you drinking milk again?
B-But my stomach sorta turns
when I drink espresso.
That's why you're such a mammoni, Pesci!
Just by drinking that milk, it's possible
you're making us lamer by association.
Why do you think we even
bring you along, anyway?
You need to correct things like that first.
O-Okay...
So, Formaggio, how are things going?
That's all yours, Pesci.
A little gift from me to you.
Looks like things went well.
Yeah, the job's basically done.
Now we just have to watch it happen.
Let's get this over with
and watch a soccer match.
Narancia Ghirga
Li'l Bomber
It was delicious.
Thank you very much.
We'll be waiting for your return.
All right, let's finish things off.
That was wonderful.
I'm glad I went with the white tod—
What's the matter, dear? Are you in pain?
Hey! What the hell are you
doing parking here?!
Get outta the way!
W-Wait, what's that coming out
from underneath the car?
Th-Th-That's blood!
All right, let's go home.
What's the matter, Pesci?
Did your knees give out?
We're back!
How'd it go?
Perfectly!
The guy's been blown to bits.
But you ended up killing the chick
he was with in the process, too.
I guess this job was perfect
for your useless Stand ability.
Whatever, man. If you got a problem,
take care of this yourself.
As much as I'd love to,
the leader wants me to conserve
Melone, how much was this job?
my ability until we absolutely need to use it.
Twenty million lire.
Damn, that's cheap!
Ghiaccio, calm down.
We'll talk about money later.
More importantly...
Where are Sorbet and Gelato?
Are they playing hooky?
Maybe they're getting it on somewhere.
They're a couple, aren't they?
And you call my Stand ability useless?
No, something's definitely wrong.
Gelato's one thing, but Sorbet would
never miss out on a chance to get rich.
He's always made sure to
show up to claim his share.
Once an organization is established
and starts to mature as a group,
there will always be people within
that group who want to rebel.
When smuggling cheap drugs
coming from Central Asia
to various countries in
Europe as well as America,
they make a profit that's
tens to hundreds of times more.
Which means it's not the least bit strange
that there will be those
who show up and try
to take over the boss's territory,
even at the risk of their own lives.
Did you find them?
No, there's no sign of them.
They must've been dealt
with because they were
trying to find out who the boss was!
It's definitely possible.
They're two crazy bastards.
Polpo's in control of all the gambling,
and the jerks selling the drugs
are also making a fortune.
But the only thing that we, the Hitman
Team, get is our pay from the boss!
This ain't fair!
We're the best there is in the
whole damn organization!
We deserve way better!
He suffocated?
Yeah... Just Gelato, though.
Sorbet's corpse isn't here.
"Punishment"
Punishment...
A few days later, a bunch of packages with
no sender were delivered to the team.
Seriously? Again?
Who the hell's the sender?!
Frames?
They're not paintings, though.
Is this what they call
modern art or some shit?
There's something weird in them.
Hey!
Th-That's the same color nail
polish that Sorbet always wears!
I-I've seen it before...
He and Gelato use the same shade!
Get the frames out and line them up.
There were a total of
36 of these art pieces.
Oh, hell no...
You can't be serious... This is...
I don't want to see any more!
Shut up!
That's...
They were pieces of Sorbet's body,
chopped up and preserved in formalin.
When they put his face together,
they saw that it was distorted in fear.
He was likely cut into pieces by a
very sharp knife, starting with his toes.
It was a rather intense
way of getting killed.
That day, the Hitman Team
came to a new understanding.
D-Do you think that Sorbet
was sliced up right in front of Gelato?
Yeah. And he was so overcome
with fear and despair
that he choked on his
own gag and suffocated!
This was a silent message from the boss.
All of you...
Forget all about Sorbet and Gelato.
From then on, they ended up
getting the cold shoulder.
They never tried to find out
the boss's identity ever again.
At least, not until...
they found out that the
boss had a daughter.
Damn it! I'm not going to
die in a place like this!
We're gonna kill the boss and
take over his drug route!
We're gonna claw our way
up from this hellhole!
It's riddled with holes?
He shot that rat to death? Why?
C-Could it be...
It went the other way.
It's looking around for me.
Breathing?! So that's it!
Narancia's Stand, Li'l Bomber,
detects its target when they breathe!
Mosquitoes find animals to suck
blood from by searching for
the CO2 that they exhale.
This is the same thing!
So that's how he found
out I was in his pocket!
Come to think of it, when all those
randos showed up in the alleyway,
he stopped searching for me.
There was a chance he would've
shot one of those randos!
It had detected my breathing!
There you are!
He shot again!
Looks like he can't tell the
difference between me and the rats.
In that case...
Look at those creepy little shits...
Th-These numbers...
and this movement pattern...
The ones that are breathing must be rats!
Their speed is the same!
They're all going the same direction!
A threat... You were only a threat
when I didn't know how you worked.
How were you finding me?
Now that I know that, you're more
harmless than a mosquito,
Narancia!
I win, Narancia!
I'm gonna get the hell outta here and
wait for you to shrink into nothing!
H-How?
The same movement...
All of them are moving the same way,
but there's only one rat
who's breathing really hard...
Are you tired? You're out of breath.
Is there something heavy on top of you
that's making it hard to breathe?
I think it might be worth it to shoot
the shit out of that fatty there!
Shit!
Yes! A clean shot!
Th-That was close...
If I hadn't returned to my normal
size, I would've been done for!
If time hadn't passed to the
point of you becoming so small
Narancia's Height: 13.2cm
that your Stand power
was rendered useless...
I would've been a goner!
I-I didn't get him!
Did I become so small that Li'l
Bomber's power also shrank?
My attacks won't work anymore!
Episodio 11
Narancia's Li'l Bomber