That's perfect. That spot's just fine!
Bang
Booom
Yee-haw!
Well done, Mista!
As long as we move upward,
their attack won't begin.
I see...
I think I understand how they survived
so long after betraying the boss.
You got the footage, didn't you, Secco?
The desperate looks on their faces as
they were fighting for their lives?
Good!
Good, good, good, good, good, good,
good, good, good, good, good...
Well done, Secco!
The more curious someone is,
the stronger they become mentally.
Humans are far more curious than any other
creature, and that's why they evolved.
I can't wait to see it...
I can't wait to see guys like him die.
Oh, right. Forgive me, I'd forgotten.
You get a treat for taking
such a good picture.
How does two sound?
Three, you say? You want three sweet ones?
You little glutton.
All right. You can have three.
Here it comes, Secco. Here comes three!
Oh, my bad.
Good!
Good, good, good, good, good, good,
good, good, good, good, good...
You're such a good boy, Secco!
Now, go!
You go to Bucciarati and the others, Secco.
You and your Stand, Sanctuary.
Episodio 30 Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 1
What are we going to do, Bucciarati?
We can't go back out to sea.
If that mold's range is extended by
the corpses, as Giorno guessed,
then instead of tracking down the user,
we're better off finding a car and
getting out of this village.
Our number one priority
right now is to get to Rome.
Giorno, how's Narancia's treatment going?
It's hard to treat him in this village.
There's living mold in his wounds.
All right, Mista, climbing up is fine.
We're going to go up those
stairs and get ourselves a car.
That's a bit cruel, Bucciarati.
He didn't even ask Narancia
if he was okay or not.
Not to mention, earlier,
when you were trying desperately
to get up from the boat,
what did he say?
He coldly ordered you to throw the turtle.
What are you so mad about?
Of course he said that. I was the
one who went down into the boat.
It's good that we made it out alive,
but because of me, we almost died.
Besides, if Bucciarati hadn't
told me to throw the turtle,
I might've dropped it into the ocean.
I know that!
What I'm saying is that
he's cold to everyone!
Say... I don't really understand
how girls feel, but...
Were you hoping he would
ask you if you were okay?
I already know how Bucciarati is,
but you're dying to know more about him.
Excuse me? I'm dying to what?
Well, getting to Rome is what's
most important right now.
You can figure out your feelings later.
I'm really not doing so great right now.
Let me rest for a bit.
The only way we can go is up right now,
but if we should ever have to go
down any lower than where we are...
We'll be fine.
This village is built on
the side of a mountain.
All the roads are uphill.
And outside the village,
there are cars still running.
That means the mold's
range hasn't expanded yet.
We just need to acquire a car and
get out of this village quickly.
We need to hurry to Rome at all costs.
Which car should we take?
One with a corpse next to it, because that
corpse should have the key to that car.
It was just the mold breaking
that corpse's hand apart.
I'll watch our rear.
You hurry up and get a car.
Right.
Mista, I take that back.
Something... Something is wrong.
Hurry and go up!
R-Right!
What are you doing, Mista?!
I told you to go up!
I already am, Bucciarati!
But...
We're sinking!
We're moving away from the wall!
What's going on?
The whole staircase is being
pulled into the ground!
This must be a different Stand
user than the one using the mold!
There's another one after us!
This isn't good!
We need to hurry and climb up!
If we go down any further,
the mold will attack us!
Jump onto the wall!
My gun!
It's not sinking...
The staircase itself is sinking
into the ground, like it's melting!
What's that?
The enemy!
The enemy's down below,
and he's coming for us!
Mista! Climb onto the wall!
Zipper Man!
Zuboom
He's fast... This guy is fast.
And this is strange...
The ground feels solid when I'm
touching it with Zipper Man's hands.
This is a solid stone staircase,
but I'm sinking into it...
And this thing is moving around
freely underneath the hard ground.
This isn't good! I can't tell where he is!
Where is he coming from?
Can you hear me, Six Bullets?!
Come back to me!
Yee-haw!
One coming at us from beneath the ground,
and a man-eating mold Stand...
They're both making the most
of the other's Stand ability.
This duo is too compatible, more so than
any other team we've encountered before.
What are they, bound by the
red thread of fate? Damn it!
I found one, Bucciarati.
A corpse that's still holding the car key.
You bastard!
I just caught a glimpse of our enemy!
He jumped from the stairs
and dove into the wall!
Th-This is...
Run, Mista!
It's fast! At this rate,
we might make it to the car,
but we won't have time to start the engine!
I'll hold them back! Keep going!
Don't stop, Mista!
The ground is still hard!
The bullets are going to ricochet!
If the sinking ground is
still hard somehow,
our best chance is the
moment I get pulled under.
This guy's the powerful, close-range type.
His range is small.
I should be able to see it as
soon as it tries to pull me in.
That's when I'll get him!
There! It showed itself!
Now!
Take this!
Mista!
I see...
I figured a powerful, close-range type
might be able to deflect some bullets.
But you see...
If you're going to deflect bullets,
my Bullets can do that, too!
The first three shots I fired should...
What?!
He's not going to finish me off?
So he thinks he can kill me at
any time, now that I'm hurt?
Hurry and pick up the key, Bucciarati!
Start the engine!
What the hell are you doing?!
Hurry up and get in the car!
If we can actually get out of
this village by car, that's fine.
As long as we can all head for Rome.
Where are you going, Bucciarati?!
Wh-What?!
So you're going to track us from
underground, no matter where we go?
What a terrifying ability.
But do you have any idea where I'm headed?
Apparently you didn't, huh?
You had no idea where we were.
Arri, arri, arri, arri, arri...
Arrivederci!
Squish
Cioccolata
Green Tea
Arri, arri, arri, arri, arri...
Arrivederci!
My...
My face!
What?
Cioccolata!
Three days ago... You heard, right?
The Stand that the boss sent into
the airplane... Notorious Chase...
Hey, Secco. Aren't you tracking
them down right now?
Why are you calling me?
Hey, Cioccolata... This is important.
Very important!
Chase... Is that thing...
Is it alive? Or is it a dead Stand?
What brought this on?
It's a simple question!
Answer me. If Chase was here,
would your Green Tea's mold
grow on it? On the dead Stand?
Notorious Chase...
Are you talking about the one where
the user was killed, but his hatred
was so strong that the
Stand somehow survived?
Who knows?
I'm curious about him, but I have no
idea if the mold would grow on him.
But I do know for certain that my Green
Tea will destroy any living creature.
The mold doesn't grow on inanimate
objects like rocks, right?
Forget about that! Quit wasting time
and film those guys dying already!
That's just it, though, Cioccolata!
Look up the hill. Look at the road.
Hey, Secco...
Why is there a car leaving the village?
Is the one driving the car one of them?
Why did you just let them go?
Hey, Cioccolata... It's just unbelievable...
He hit me in the face.
That Bucciarati guy...
He didn't have any mold growing on him.
Even though he jumped down!
I can't believe he attacked me there...
It's totally unbelievable!
His body won't grow mold!
What the hell is going on?!
I haven't the slightest.
I totally thought...
that you had plummeted.
You scared me, Bucciarati.
Did you hang on to the wall with zippers?
I guess it might've been a close call.
It doesn't look like the mold got you at all.
Mista, rest for a bit.
I closed your wounds, but if you move
now, they'll start bleeding again.
I'll look out for any cars
that might be following us.
Right...
Bucciarati, your wrist... Did you hurt it?
Please, let me see it.
Are you listening, Bucciarati?
If the mold got to you, you're in danger.
Please, let me see it.
That's...
Th-That's impossible...
Your skin is so cold...
A-And your pulse...
Giorno, did you just say something to me?
I couldn't hear you.
What's... going on?
Impossible...
It simply can't be!
O-Oh, yeah...
Something similar happened before.
I thought it was just my
imagination back then...
When we were leaving Venice.
Apparently, I hurt myself.
Looks like there isn't much time left.
I'm losing more and more
feeling in my skin...
Or...
Maybe I never had any to begin with.
That's impossible! Don't tell me, back then...
When you saved Trish from the boss in Venice...
Bucciarati, don't tell me... back then...
It's strange.
I've accepted this as fate.
Just a tiny bit of fate, of chance,
that Heaven had granted me.
When you healed my wounds in Venice,
it appears the life force you gave me
allowed me to move for just a bit longer.
Why... Why didn't you say anything?
My Golden Wind completely
healed your wounds back then!
I'm sure it can fix whatever
you're going through now, too!
Giorno, I'm sure your Golden Wind
knows more about that than anyone else.
That nothing can be done for those
whose lives have already ended.
By that time,
my life...
had already ended.
You won't tell the others about this, right?
That's impossible...
But that's impossible, Bucciarati!
Y-You're—
Quiet, Giorno!
Listen. What's that sound?
Am I just hearing things?
There's no car following us.
I hear it. It's getting closer.
It's getting really close!
What?!
Above us! It's a helicopter!
He dropped some mold on us!
Wh-What the hell just happened?!
Bucciarati, we're descending!
This road goes downhill!
The mold is going to get us!
Giorno, Mista! We're jumping out!
Grab on to me!
Climb up! Climb up, even if only a little bit!
Subconscious...
In a way, Stand abilities are
the users' subconscious abilities...
If there's any guilt in their heart,
they might subconsciously hit the brakes...
But whoever this is enjoys cruelty.
Actually, he lives for it.
That's how his ability became this.
This guy doesn't have any brakes at all!
He has no limits on how evil he can be!
Hey, what's wrong?!
I-I'll go get a doctor right away!
Hey, don't! Don't go down that way!
I'll bring a doctor here right away!
Hey, what's going on?
The mold...
It's spreading instantaneously!
That's impossible. There are
three million people living in Rome.
This is nothing like that fishing village!
And there are members of
the organization in Rome.
This would be a hit to the boss, too.
This guy doesn't care.
He's enjoying this!
At this rate, everyone in Rome will die!
No, this guy's not going to stop,
even if it spreads further than that!
There's something else!
At this rate, the mold's killing range
will spread to the Colosseum
faster than we can get there.
Mista! Is that helicopter
within your gun's range?
It doesn't matter!
We have to hit it, no matter what!
Make sure you take it down!
Got it! I won't let you get away!
Go, Six Bullets!
Yee-haw!
The guy in the helicopter
wanted me to shoot at it...
So that the guy who can move around
underground could safely get to us!
All right, Secco was able to splash
down safely... or should I say land?
Now they're cornered.
And whoever Bucciarati and
his men were meeting in Rome
will be dealt with by Green Tea.
Th-That bastard's coming
from the top of the hill!
And we can't go back down!
Mista, concentrate on the helicopter!
We can't let it escape!
I'll deal with this guy.
I-It's no use, Bucciarati!
It's already too far away!
I won't be able to hit the fuel
tank or the propellers from here!
No, Mista.
You never know until you try!
It's no use! They won't reach!
I know the Bullets' range better than anyone.
The helicopter got away!
The guy underground is coming for us!
The bullets hit their target, Mista.
Now, the two of us are going to go take
care of the man in the helicopter.
Let's go after the helicopter!
Go after it? The helicopter?
What?! What is this?
We have to take care of him before the
mold's killing spree reaches the Colosseum!
Bucciarati,
we can leave the guy beneath
the ground to you, right?
Go, Giorno!
Run, Mista!
Episodio 30
Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 2