No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Episodio 39 The Sleeping Slave
Bucciarati? This stone is
definitely shaped like...
Hey! Are you the sculptor?!
Who the hell are you?!
Don't you dare try anything!
I didn't kill you because
I was ordered not to,
but now that I know you're a Stand user,
there's no guarantee that I won't add
another hole between your eye sockets!
Who the hell are you?
How do you know Bucciarati?
The florist's daughter falling
to her death is concerning,
but why did you follow
me from the restaurant?
Daughter?
Are you a police officer?
No, the police wouldn't—
Listen up, you sick bastard!
I'll be the one asking questions here!
You just need to answer!
Just concentrate on that.
Got that? Don't even think about
saying or doing anything else!
That also includes lying to me. Got it?
All right... I'll ask you
one question at a time.
First off, are you in a gang?
Do you belong to some organization?
I can find out later if I look into it, of course.
N-No... I'm just a sculptor.
I'm not famous, but I
make a living off of it.
Then how did you become a Stand user?
I don't even know what a Stand is.
If you mean this ability...
It just started happening
while I was still a child.
Was it the same for you?
Hey!
Next question. Why did you
follow me from the restaurant?
And how do you know Bucciarati?
Bucciarati...
Bucciarati... Is that his name?
Let me see him, please! He came
with you to this building, right?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You didn't answer my question, you moron!
I-It's probably not an answer you'll like...
But this rock moves on its own,
regardless of how I think or feel.
It's been like that ever since I was a kid.
It's a power that I have no control over.
The rock didn't follow you.
It was following him... Bucciarati.
Oh, is that so?
Do you want me to make it so you
can never hold a chisel again?
Sorry to break it to you, but Bucciarati's
far away from here, you dumbass!
You're the one who's lying.
Bucciarati should be in
this apartment building.
Let me see him. His life depends on—
Don't mess with me!
Why did you kill the florist's daughter?
What are you after—
What the hell are you doing?!
I told you to not try anything funny!
The rock has left...
What?!
One of the greatest sculptors in
history, Michelangelo, once said...
"I don't have any thoughts when
I take hold of a marble slab.
Every block of stone already
has a statue inside it,
and it is the task of the
sculptor to discover it."
What the hell are you babbling
about, you bastard?!
You're going to die if you don't hurry
up and bring that rock back here!
Michelangelo was saying that the ultimate
statue is not created from an idea.
It already dwells within
the stone as its destiny.
He was an artist who could see
that destiny as he sculpted.
It's not that I sculpted that rock
into the shape of Bucciarati,
and neither did your bullets.
That is the shape of destiny.
The statue had a hole in its
chest that was gushing out blood.
I don't know if it's in a few
days or in a few months,
but that's going to be how
Bucciarati eventually dies.
We're all slaves to fate.
That's the meaning behind my
ability, Prophecy Stones.
This is your last chance!
Bring the rock back here now!
If you die, so will your Stand!
You get that, don't you?!
If he touches my Prophecy Stones,
he can die without suffering.
I wanted to see him so I could
at least hear his last words...
Wh-What the hell is this guy's problem?
Is he mocking me?
How the hell can he be so calm, damn it?!
Fine! You want your brain splattered
onto that rock so badly?
Look! There are three shots left.
This is how you use destiny!
You're apparently trying to
do something to Bucciarati,
so bring that rock back here right now!
You're the one who doesn't
have time or chances!
I told you. There's nothing more I can do.
Bring it back here right now, God damn it!
The florist had a hard time walking, right?
He doesn't know it yet,
but it's an early symptom of some
disease in one of his internal organs.
He'll most likely survive, though.
When his daughter died,
her organs were preserved.
He'll receive them as transplants.
The girl found out from the rock
that she'd contract the same
disease in a few months.
She understood that and believed it.
She decided to die while she was
healthy for her father's sake,
rather than die in pain later.
So she accepted the rock, and...
The rock allowed her to
die without suffering,
and in a way in which her
organs weren't crushed.
You have some nerve saying that when
you're the one who killed her!
Wh-What?!
It's a misfire, Mista!
That bullet was a dud!
That's impossible!
That bullet is Number 5's responsibility!
Aw, why me?
I cannot die yet.
Because the rock hasn't carved my death yet.
Y-You think you're going to get
two duds in a row, you jackass?!
You caught a glimpse of destiny just now.
You no longer have any
intention of shooting me.
Am I wrong?
Wh-What's with this guy? Damn it!
What the hell is he talking about?
Is he still messing with me?
Hello, Fugo?
Tell Bucciarati that this
sculptor is a Stand user!
What?
This bastard keeps mentioning Bucciarati,
but I can't really tell
what's going on by myself!
What are you talking about, Mista?
You still haven't met up with him?
Huh?
Bucciarati headed to that
apartment building a while ago.
He followed you right after
you got out of the car.
Hello? Mista? What's wrong?
What?!
Bad luck
Prophecy Stones
Scolippi
Wh-What's the number,
Fugo? I have to find him!
What's the number to the phone
Bucciarati has right now?
Are you all right?
The one you're calling
right now is Bucciarati's.
Hello, Mista? Hello?
Hurry, Bullets! Find Bucciarati!
Mista? Hello?
Hey, wake up, you sculptor bastard!
How can I stop that rock?
Hey, wake up, would you?!
Answer me, God damn it!
What do I need to do to stop that
rock from getting to Bucciarati?!
P-Please... Tell me.
I'm starting to understand what you told me.
But what the hell am I supposed to do?
I can't let Bucciarati touch
that rock, no matter what.
I can't.
Please, tell me.
It'd be better and easier...
if you two didn't defy the rock...
No one's been able to do it before,
but if you're able to destroy that rock
or change its shape, then...
We found him, Mista!
We found Bucciarati!
We got a report from
Number 1 that he found him!
Bucciarati's on the seventh floor!
The stairs! Bucciarati used the stairs!
What?!
Th-This isn't good!
The rock! The rock is on the stairs, too!
The rock is right in front of Bucciarati!
Stop him, Number 1!
Tell him not to touch that rock!
It's no use, Mista!
Number 1's bullet doesn't have enough
power left to fly over there.
Bucciarati!
Yee-haw!
Bullets?
We did it!
That was close!
Its shape is falling apart!
That's great and all...
B-But I have a feeling we
might've made things worse...
Bullets, what in the world is going on here?
Is that a Stand?
And its shape...
Run, Bucciarati!
Zipper Man!
Don't attack it!
It's bad news if you touch it!
Run down here, Bucciarati!
Mista!
You can't touch that rock!
If you lay even a finger on it, you'll die!
What do you mean?
I'll explain the details later!
Is that rock a Stand?
Hurry and get downstairs!
Get out of this building and
get as far away as possible!
What? This happened in
the elevator earlier, too...
Sh-Shit! These stairs are dangerous!
We need to find another way down.
Going down these stairs is a bad idea!
Go up, Bucciarati!
Wh-Where is it?
It's not here! Damn it!
Where did it go?!
Mista, what's going on?
Sh-Shit!
Above you, Bucciarati!
Bucciarati!
Wh-What's this face on this rock?
If we can destroy the rock
or change its shape...
Mista!
If I just smash it into the pavement
from here, it should break into pieces!
Damn it!
You're not getting away!
That's impossible! Mista!
Damn it... What that
sculptor bastard said...
turned out to be true...
If you don't appear in the rock,
then it's not your time to die yet...
What the hell have you been doing, Mista?
You left the tape recorder
on the car seat, you dumbass.
Hey... It's you, Fugo...
What was this rock?
Mista, what chain of
coincidences led to this?
Uh... You should be fine now.
I, uh... don't even know
how to explain all this.
Anyway, about the florist's
daughter's death...
The sculptor was sort of the suspect,
but not exactly the suspect...
I hurt him enough to land him in the
hospital for a couple of months, though...
I still have no idea what the
hell you're talking about.
Was he an enemy or not?
Was it suicide or not?
Explain it all in a more orderly fashion!
That's just it, though...
It's really, uh... hard to sort
everything out in my head.
Simply put, we destroyed the
rock, so everything's over now.
Hey, Bucciarati, I'll look into
the incident with Leaky Eye Luca.
No, it'd probably be quicker
to look into it myself
than have you try to explain what happened.
It's a job I can do on my own.
Fugo, try to get a decent explanation
out of Mista so we can explain
what happened here to the florist.
Bucciarati, I'm willing
to do anything for you,
I'm not sure how I should say this...
but do you really think I can
understand what he's saying?
You can stop thinking now.
We'll just use Abbacchio's Moody Jazz.
Over...
Everything is over, you say?
If you had just accepted Prophecy Stones,
everything would've ended peacefully...
We're all slaves to fate.
We cannot change what has
already taken shape.
I don't know who they are, but now
they're going to face a difficult path,
and some of them will lose their lives.
But...
Are they all like this?
He jumped from up there to destroy
the rock for his friend, Bucciarati.
The path filled with hardships
that they're about to walk
might have some meaning.
Their hardships may end up
being someone else's hope,
and might be the beginning
to some greater meaning.
I can't wish for their safety, but I
pray that they are sleeping slaves.
Sleeping slaves who will find
some meaning once they awaken.
Hey, hurry up!
Who's gonna heal Bucciarati's
injuries if you don't hurry up?
Hey, Giorno!
Whoa, be careful, Trish.
Thanks. Something suddenly
appeared near my feet...
Menacing
Trish?
Hey, Trish! Wh-Where'd you go, Trish?
Trish!
Hey, Giorno! Where the hell is Trish?!
Unbelievable... Trish is right there, Mista.
Mista, Giorno, I'm right here.
I didn't trip on this rock.
It's what was in its shadow.
Don't leave me behind.
If you leave me behind,
I don't know how many days it'll
take me to get to the Colosseum.
Polnareff?!
Mr. Polnareff.
You're still alive.
But if all our minds were switched back,
then your soul... and the turtle...
My body is dead.
But the moment my soul got sucked out,
I was able to hang on to this turtle Stand.
I can't leave this key, but I decided
to live here for a while as a ghost.
Well, it's great and all that you're okay,
but it's not over yet.
We're going to the Colosseum
to heal Bucciarati's wounds.
Bucciarati? But his soul...
Hey, what are you doing?!
Oh, uh, sorry!
I was just thinking that you're right...
I think I might actually smell weird.
So this is what I smell like?
Maybe I'll start using cologne...
Really?
I might've said something weird back then,
and maybe it's because I was panicked,
but it doesn't bother me anymore.
It almost even feels nostalgic.
Really? Really?
Yes. But your fingers are still weird.
What are you going to do with that?
Those who carry on the will of those who
have passed must keep moving forward.
I won't destroy this arrow.
Keep the arrow inside the turtle.
That will do, Giorno.
That is the duty of those who have survived.
Let's go
to the Colosseum.