Episodio 02  Bucciarati Is Coming
Giorno Giovanna.
His father is DIO Brando.
DIO always saw women
as mere tools or food,
so it's unknown how Giorno's
mother was able to give birth
to Giorno fifteen years ago
without being killed.
Giorno's mother was a very beautiful woman,
but she was far from a model mother.
After Giorno was born, they lived in Japan,
but she would often go out
at all hours of the night,
leaving young Giorno alone at home.
You sure you should leave
your kid home alone?
Isn't he, like, two or something?
Oh, it's fine.
I'm not about to lose my freedom
just because I had a kid.
Shiobana
Giorno would wake up in the middle of the
night, and his mother wouldn't be there.
How terrifying and despairing that
must be for a child of one or two.
There was no point in crying,
so Giorno would just sit there, trembling.
When Giorno was four,
his mother got married.
She married an Italian, and therefore,
Giorno also became an Italian citizen.
Um...
What are you doing over here?
Come on, Haruno.
Come take some photos with us.
You mother's waiting for you.
But as you'd suspect,
when Haruno's mother wasn't around...
You're always looking at me,
trying to figure out what mood I'm in.
You annoying little brat!
But it was actually the opposite.
What's the matter?
Oh, the bread.
Here you go.
Jeez, you're such a gloomy kid.
The one who got him into the habit
of trying to read others' moods
was this man himself.
This made Giorno
the perfect target for the local
kids to take out their anger on.
Whoa, what's wrong, Giorno?
Why'd you trip over nothing?
Hey, you kids. Hurry up and get home.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Go back to Japan, you little freak.
He never fights back, does he?
He's so creepy.
He started to believe that he was the
lowest scum to walk this Earth,
and that it was only a matter of time until
he would grow up to be like the rest of the
twisted people who lived in this town.
But a certain incident would
save Giorno from this fate.
Damn it, where did he go?
Find him! Don't let him get away!
He can't get far with those wounds!
You don't think he went into
someone's house, do you?
Keep your eyes on the ground!
There should be blood.
You go straight ahead. We'll go this way.
Hey, kid.
Have you seen an injured man around here?
He's tall and has black hair.
He went that way.
That way?
He won't be able to move
fast with those wounds!
Let's find him!
He felt no fear.
He just felt that the man
on the ground also seemed alone
and lonely, just like him.
Come on!
Coming!
Thankfully, the man was hidden behind
the grass, which was suddenly taller.
This was due to Giorno's
Golden Wind ability,
but Giorno didn't know he had this ability
yet, so he did it subconsciously.
Around two months later...
I'll never forget what you did for me.
Not long after,
Giorno's father stopped hitting him.
Damn it!
Why does he care so much about Giorno?
Come sit over here, Giorno.
Come on, don't be shy.
The mean kids changed their tune.
I know it's not the best seat, but...
The man was a gangster.
Here you go, kid!
This is... too much.
I think there's been a mistake...
The scoop of chocolate is my treat!
Thanks...
Don't sweat it! That guy always
takes really good care of me.
The man would always just
quietly watch over him.
Despite Giorno being a child who always
tried to read other people's moods,
the man treated him with
respect as a human being.
Giorno learned how to trust others,
a natural trait that should have
been learned from his parents,
from silent interactions with a stranger.
What was that?
A gunshot?
We shouldn't get involved.
Talk about bad luck...
U-Um...
What is it?
The man acted somewhat cruelly,
determined not to drag Giorno
into the world of gangsters.
Hey, wait up!
Hold it!
You're the one who killed
my dad, aren't you?!
You little shit! Damn it!
Damn it!
Your dad was scum.
He broke the rules of my turf by selling drugs.
He even sold them to women and children.
That's why I killed him.
How? Why?!
Why can't I shoot?
You're...
You're a piece of scum, too!
Giorno didn't think the man
was scum in the least.
Bizarrely, the gangs that committed
crimes and broke the law
were what straightened out Giorno's heart.
In a city where politicians were corrupt
and the police didn't protect the weak,
Giorno Giovanna found his reason to live.
Rather than looking up
to a player in Serie A,
he wanted to become a Gang-Star!
This taste... is the taste
of someone who's lying!
My name is Bruno Bucciarati.
Answer me.
Your questioning has already
turned into torture.
Does your head feel wobbly,
as if it's about to fall off?
Though I'm pretty sure you have
no idea what I've done to you.
My body has a zipper?!
Giorno Giovanna.
If I wanted to, I could roll
your head around like a ball
while I ask you who did Leaky Eye Luca in.
I don't think I could withstand
another one of his attacks.
He'll tear me apart!
I only noticed this ability a few months back,
but I've never used Golden Wind
to attack another human.
When Golden Wind hits something,
it can give it life.
Any object can change into any living thing.
But...
Even I don't know what'll happen if
it attacks another human being!
Answer me, Giorno Giovanna!
I don't have any other choice!
Useless!
Bagyah
What?!
Rumble
Y-You're...
a Stand user!
Rumble
So you could see my ability!
A what user?
So you're the one who attacked Luca!
Didn't Golden Wind hit him head-on?
Then he should at least
have a broken bone or two.
You bastard...
Wh-What?
What did you do to me, you bastard?!
What the? I was just trying to stand...
I'm overflowing with power!
I can feel more and more power rising in me...
It's as though my body's been
filled with the gasoline of life.
What?
Its movements look slow.
Whoosh
Could it be that I ended up like
this because of your ability?
Whoosh
You're a fool if you have a Stand
that grants your enemies power!
Take this, Giorno Giovanna!
What? I can see myself...
What am I doing back there?
The handle's not bent!
Did I misunderstand what's going on?
I just thought I was moving
with incredible power...
But my body's actually still over there,
and my consciousness just jumped out,
and that's what's over here?
Crap! I have to dodge!
I-It hurts!
A very sharp pain is gradually hitting me!
It's not that Giorno's slow... It's that
my consciousness went berserk!
Useless!
It appears that when I have Golden
Wind give a living being extra life,
they go berserk... or at least,
just their senses do.
I don't know why I have this ability,
Boom
but I'll definitely be
taking advantage of it.
Bruno Bucciarati
Hey, what the hell are you guys doing?
I'm gonna call the police!
I'm sorry for all the ruckus.
Please rest assured that we'll make
sure not to involve any civilians.
So this is Giorno Giovanna's Stand?
No... It doesn't seem like he
even knows what a Stand is.
But this ability...
It appears as though both of our
abilities only reach a few meters.
And here I thought you were just some brat
who wasn't affiliated with any organization...
Giorno Giovanna!
You're the one who attacked
Leaky Eye Luca, aren't you?!
My boss wants to know why you attacked him!
You wouldn't believe me if I told you
it was an accident, would you?
So I'm going to be disposed of, right?
And you came here fully prepared, right?
When you're going to dispose of someone,
you're always prepared
for the possibility that
you could end up being
the one disposed of, right?
He's going to kill me... He's serious!
This brat is actually going to try to kill me!
He's intense enough
that he'd actually do what
he says he's going to do!
Kabaam
Zipper Man!
So that's his Stand?
Kashink
Now I know for sure that my
Zipper Man is more powerful.
I wasn't told that I need to
bring the suspect back alive.
I wouldn't mind taking care of you here.
But I've had my fill of dealing with
your dangerous powers today,
so I'm leaving.
I'm going to keep my distance for now,
but I'll take care of you eventually.
He can even pass through a solid
wall by putting a zipper on it?!
This isn't good!
Letting him out of the
cable car is gonna be trouble!
If I lose him now, it won't
matter that I have Golden Wind!
If he's going to come after
me 24/7 with that ability,
there's absolutely no guarantee I'll survive!
I'm going to lose!
I can't let him get away!
If he tells his friends about me,
this will end up out of my control!
I have to stop him right here, right now!
For the sake of my future!
O-Ow!
Be more careful, damn it!
He disappeared!
Where could he have gone in that instant?
Don't tell me he can even
enter people with his zipper!
What are you going to do about this?
I'm covered in garbage!
But that's the only thing I can think of!
That must be how he got that eyeball
and those fingers inside me!
Bucciarati went into one of these guys
to hide, like wearing a costume...
And that's how he's planning
to head back into the city.
Better get my broom...
They're all heading in different directions.
I don't see a zipper.
Which one is it?
Which one is he hiding in?
What the hell's your problem,
you stupid fly?!
Jump
A tooth?
I gave life to the tooth that
broke out of your mouth
and had it be reborn as a fly.
The fly would return to you so
I could tell where you were...
But this isn't good.
I just got done saying we wouldn't
involve any civilians...
But my bad. That was a lie.
Still, he ended up hitting
himself with his own power,
so I hope you can just deal with it.
Giorno Giovanna, I can see your
ability is not to be underestimated.
You leave me no choice.
This will be dangerous,
but it seems I'll have to take care
of you right here, right now.
I can't let you escape.
I'm pretty determined about that.
Let me escape?
You don't have to worry about that.
The only thing you have to worry about
is what you'll do once your body parts
have been zipped apart all over the ground.
This battle will be decided
by who hits the other first.
What's the matter?
Come at me, Giorno Giovanna.
Useless!
Thud
Just your senses will go berserk.
"You hit me first, so how?"
I don't blame you for wondering that.
This isn't my arm.
My Zipper Man's ability allows two separate
things to be connected with a zipper.
This is that kid's arm.
I switched it out with mine.
Because, of course, I'd rather avoid the
danger of being hit with your ability.
That's why your Golden Wind didn't work.
What are you trying to do, Giorno Giovanna?!
I'm ending you right now!
Unbelievable... He ripped off his own arm
to extend his range a bit further
and strike a moment faster...
Golden Wind!
I-It's happening again!
Just my senses have gone berserk!
H-He's going to get me!
The destructive power of Giorno Giovanna's
Stand ability isn't too great...
But in this case,
that actually makes things worse!
If I have to experience that slow
pain not once, but multiple times...
I'll probably die from the shock of the pain!
Don't!
Stop!
He went out of range?
What are you doing, Giorno Giovanna?!
Why did you stop attacking me?
Why didn't you finish me off?!
Because you're a good person.
You're in a gang, but you're a good person.
You hesitated for a moment before attacking me,
so I decided I wouldn't attack you, either.
When you saw the arm you
took off of this kid,
you were shocked to see the state it was in
and stopped attacking for a moment.
You were shocked that he'd
been shooting up drugs.
How old is he?
Thirteen.
If you were just some gangster who
wouldn't have hesitated or been shocked,
I probably would've been rolling
around on the ground in pieces.
But you seem different.
That's why I stopped.
There are people in this city
who would sell drugs to kids.
They're unforgivable.
That's what you believe.
But the one selling those drugs is your boss.
You can't help but feel conflicted about that.
That's why your heart ached
when you saw his arm.
So what? That's got nothing to
do with me eliminating you.
I've been ordered to find the one who
attacked Luca and eliminate them!
Just because you stopped attacking me
doesn't mean I'm not going to kill you!
No...
You won't kill me now.
What?
You won't kill me. I know it.
Why do you say that?
Because you're going to join me.
I plan on defeating your boss
and taking over this city.
What?!
In order to get rid of gangs
that sell drugs to children,
I'm going to have to become
a gangster myself.
Are you saying...
that you're going to join our organization?!
Are you serious?!
Do you even know what that means?!
What a great view...
Yes. If I'm going to take over this city,
I'll have to join the organization that
rules it and work my way up.
Bucciarati,
I'm going to become a Gang-Star!
Episodio 03
Meet the Gangster Behind the Wall