Episodio 21 The Mystery of Emperor Crimson
Damn it, Narancia!
Who do you think you are,
trying to eat all the chocolates yourself?
Give them back!
I bought them with my own
money, so give them back!
Narancia, I swear...
There are only three left!
What a greedy little shit.
We've all been waiting for these,
and we're hungry!
The ladybug brooch is moving
from the top of the tower.
I can feel it.
It's heading to the charnel house below
to try to cross through there.
Bucciarati must've put the brooch
somewhere on the boss's clothes.
Sorry, Giorno, but could
you grab that water?
I'm a bit thirsty.
Also, you should be careful.
We've been ordered to wait
here on the boat for now,
and not set foot on the island.
Right.
Huh? Eh?
Y-You ate them, didn't you, Mista?!
Give them back, damn it!
And what the hell do you have on your mouth?
Huh?
Ah!
"Ah," my ass! You little shit!
S-So sweet!
When did you stuff them in your mouth?
By the way, I didn't thank
you yet, did I, Giorno?
For grabbing the water.
Something's... bizarre...
I don't know what,
but something's strange.
Hey, you bastard!
Didn't you hear that the boss ordered
us not to set foot on the is—
...land?
Huh?!
This isn't normal.
Something weird is going on!
This isn't good! Bucciarati!
Where do you think you're going, Giorno?!
Is that you, Giorno?
Bucciarati!
Yes, I know he's on the move.
I know exactly where the boss is because
of the brooch you put on him.
Right now, he's at the bottom of
the stairs to the charnel house.
He's right by the pillar that's about
two meters away from the stairs.
But wait, Bucciarati!
Something is wrong!
Bucciarati, your mission to
act as Trish's bodyguard
has now come to an end.
Wh-Why, you...
He's trying to immobilize my arm.
Zipper Man!
But... Emperor Crimson has already...
...seen through it.
Your movements in the future.
The trajectory of your
movements in the future.
Within Emperor Crimson's ability,
this world's time disappears,
and no one remembers the movements
they made within this segment of time.
The clouds in the sky don't
realize they've broken apart.
A flame that's extinguished doesn't even
realize the moment it went out.
All that remains in this
world are the results.
In the world where time has been eliminated,
all movement becomes pointless!
I am the only one who can
react to these movements.
I can see every single
one of your movements!
This is Emperor Crimson's ability!
Th-This ability...
No matter who you may be,
everyone goes through their ups and downs.
You succeed, and you fail.
But if you happen to find the pitfall known
as the future that's right in front of you
and manage to not fall in,
you will never experience
a setback in your life.
You will remain in your best condition.
Don't you think so?
Now that I've actually met you,
I can tell that we are indeed related.
I can sense that you are,
without a doubt, my daughter.
Which means...
When you are awake, you will feel
the exact same way toward me!
Trish...
I must fill any pitfall
that threatens my path!
I will now sever this bond
of blood that binds us!
Trish!
Dogyuuuuun
Wh-What?!
That must be Giorno...
Giorno's Golden Wind's ability...
He planted the turtle's cells in
the brooch and gave it life,
and a turtle with Stand abilities was born.
Since our call was interrupted,
he must've sensed something was wrong
and activated his ability.
He always gives me courage...
I didn't think I could move
anymore, but... Not yet.
I still...
have to keep moving a little bit more.
My mission's done? You're wrong, Boss.
It's still ongoing!
As for Trish...
I will protect her on my own order!
If he can read all of my attacks,
and I can't even realize
that he's dodged them,
then his ability surpasses
all others in its invincibility.
But...
This ability doesn't allow him to
read one's movements for long!
It's only a short time.
It seems to be around five to ten seconds.
Distance...
For now, I need to get
as far away as possible!
I need to get far enough that
the boss can't find Trish!
I beg of you to keep moving, body.
Don't let me waste this
chance that Giorno gave me!
Until I can get out of this basement...
It seems there was another traitor.
Must be the newbie.
Rumble
If my information is correct,
I believe his name is Giorno Giovanna.
Rumble
So he must've joined this organization with
the intent to betray me from the start.
It seems you thought you could escape
just by distancing yourself from me,
but it's nothing for me to escape
that turtle an instant sooner.
It appears that your efforts
were futile, Bucciarati.
How are you still able to move?
Sheer willpower?
If you just rest, you won't be
able to get to the first floor,
but you'll be able to die peacefully.
First, I'm going to eliminate Trish.
Don't you dare move, Bucciarati!
The chance that Giorno gave me wasn't in vain!
If this is going to be about
reading each other's moves,
I've already read yours!
I knew before you fell into the sewer
that you'd probably use
your ability to escape!
Now, Zipper Man!
Emperor Crimson!
That was close...
But within Emperor Crimson's world,
your efforts are still futile!
Take this!
You're finished!
It wasn't you that I was trying to attack!
It was this pillar!
Zipper, close!
What?!
As I thought...
Your ability is invincible...
But it appears that you can only
read movements for a short time.
You're not reading ahead of time.
Just try and read my future
movements, Boss.
Try to figure out what I'm going
to do in a few seconds.
Try to see beyond time.
You should be able to see me
after I've reached the first floor.
Bucciarati! Trish!
This wound...
What happened in the basement?!
Where's the boss?
He should still be around...
Somewhere close by.
I don't know the whole situation,
but there's no way
the boss is just going to
let Bucciarati go after this!
Bucciarati...
N-No...
Bucciarati!
His pulse...
I-Impossible! It's gone!
I created the parts needed for his recovery!
Bucciarati, please breathe!
So this must be Giorno Giovanna.
His unknown ability gave Bucciarati
the chance to escape.
However...
I will not let them get away!
This is impossible!
I know I created the parts!
There's no way he shouldn't have a heartbeat!
Giorno, it's me.
Call Abbacchio and the others.
Get out of here.
That voice...
I told you to call Abbacchio and the others.
Get out of here!
Out of this church!
Hurry!
B-Bucciarati!
Th-Thank goodness!
You're okay!
Hurry! Hurry up and call the others!
B-But...
We can't figure out who the
boss actually is right now.
We need to get out of here, Giorno!
While we're still far enough from him!
They're within my range!
Here I go!
I'll explain later! Hurry up, Giorno!
Golden Wind!
Giorno's over there!
Hey, Giorno, you bastard! Come back here!
How are you gonna make up for disobeying
orders and stepping onto the island?!
Bucciarati's here, too!
H-How the hell did you get so injured?!
Why do you still have Trish with you?!
What's going on here, Bucciarati?
I'll explain everything later.
Right now, we need to get out
of here as fast as we can.
I commend you, Bucciarati.
I commend your precise and
keen decision making.
Even though I have the
ability to eliminate time,
if I were to face all six of those Stand users,
one of them would end up
learning my true identity.
For the moment,
they've managed to escape
my Emperor Crimson.
But this is not the end.
I will never...
let you escape
from Venice!
Now I understand why the boss is feared by
everyone and how he ruled over all of us.
We can't defeat the boss... not now.
As for his identity...
Assuming it even has one,
we'll need to find his
ability's weakness first!
Emperor Crimson
What...
What the hell's going on, Bucciarati?
We need an explanation.
What the hell are you doing?
All right. I'll just come out and say it.
But I can't explain everything right now,
because there's no time and
danger's right around the corner.
The reason I brought Trish back
is because I betrayed the boss just now.
I'll be leaving you guys now.
If you go with me,
you will also become traitors.
Wh-What?
I-I don't think I heard you right...
Wh-What did you just say?
He said... he betrayed the boss.
B-But why?
You probably shouldn't hear any more,
because you guys have
nothing to do with this.
I think you should explain.
Some of them might want to follow you.
We need people on our side.
What the hell is your deal, Giorno?!
First, you go into the church
without permission, and now—
Bucciarati!
What's wrong? Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I lost a lot of blood, so I got a bit dizzy.
That shouldn't be possible...
When I created his parts, it should've
also replenished the blood he lost.
Did I miss a wound?
I guess I've used up a good deal of energy.
Does he not feel pain? There was no
blood coming from the wound, either.
Was I just seeing things?
I'm sorry.
You had me worried for a sec!
For real.
Bucciarati, please...
Yeah, Bucciarati.
We want to know the details.
The boss had us act as her bodyguards
so that he could kill his daughter
with his own two hands.
Because she shares his blood, she could
have figured out his true identity.
I found that out and...
I couldn't forgive him.
I couldn't just come back
pretending I didn't see that.
That's why I betrayed him!
How could you?
Are you insane, Bucciarati?
You know exactly what happens to traitors,
no matter who it is.
The boss never lets anyone get away!
Hell, Venice could already be
surrounded by the boss's elite guard!
You're right, and that's why
I'm going to need help.
If any of you are willing to accompany me,
come down these stairs and get on the boat.
But I will not order any
of you to come with me.
I won't even ask you to come with me.
I did this all on my own.
So you don't need to feel
obligated to come with me.
This may come off as arrogant,
but I'm going to say it anyway.
I did this because I believe I'm right.
I have no regrets.
Despite the world we live in, I want to
continue on the path that I believe in.
If we can just find his weakness...
Though we're only fleeing for now,
I will defeat the boss, no matter what.
I will find his weakness, no matter what!
I understand your reasons, and what
you did was right, Bucciarati.
But I'm going to be blunt...
I hate to say it, but no one's
going to get on that boat.
How could you let your
emotions take over like that?
I owe you my life, but going with you
now would be a different matter.
You've lost sight of reality.
No one can survive in this world
on expectations alone.
We can't survive without the organization.
Fugo's absolutely right.
What you did is basically suicide.
No matter where in the
world you might run to,
you'll never find a safe haven again.
Besides, I pledged my loyalty
to the organization.
It's not like I pledged my loyalty to you.
That being said...
I never had a home or place I wanted to go.
The only time I'm ever at ease
is when I'm with you, Bucciarati.
Abbacchio...
Y-You can't be serious, Abbacchio!
If we actually manage to defeat the boss...
Considering my skills,
I'd say I'm next in line to become a capo.
Bucciarati's smart.
He never goes into a fight that
he has no chance of winning.
We're gonna strike it rich for sure.
Mista! Not you, too!
What are you going to do, Fugo?
You've all l-lost your minds!
We're going to be completely isolated!
Where are you going to run to?
No, you won't even make it
out of Venice alive!
Narancia,
what are you going to do?
I-I... d-don't know what to do...
Tell me, Bucciarati...
What should I do?
Do you think I should go?
Are you scared?
Yeah... I'm r-really scared...
B-But just order me!
If you order me to go with you,
I'll be more confident!
Nothing scares me, as long
as you order me to do it!
No.
This is one thing I can't order you to do.
You need to decide for yourself.
You need to choose your own path.
B-But I don't know what to do! I don't know!
But let me just give you this warning.
Don't come with me, Narancia.
You're not cut out for this.
Are you serious about this?
You'll be killed, without a doubt.
There are some things in this world that
you just can't do, even if you're right.
Our job has always been dirty.
How is this any different?
Even then... I can't lie to myself.
Let's go!
Once the boat takes off,
you're officially traitors!
Why? You're insane!
All this for a woman you just
met and barely talked to!
You don't even know what
kind of music she likes!
Trish was abandoned by
the people she trusted...
I was also abandoned before.
I was abandoned by my dad
and the friends I trusted.
We're sort of alike...
It's none of our business what
the boss does with his daughter!
Trish and I are sort of alike!
All he had to do was close his eyes!
I just don't understand!
Giorno, give me the turtle.
Let's put Trish inside it.
Okay.
Bucciarati, please turn around.
Bucciarati!
I'll go! I'll go, too! I'm coming with you!
Don't order me not to go with you!
Trish is me! She's me!
The wound on her arm is my own!
Narancia... Not you, too...
You fool... You're going to be killed.
I can't go along with
such a foolish betrayal.
I can't become a righteous idiot...
You took way too long to make your decision.
You'd better not hold this
against us later on.
Narancia, I have nothing but
respect for your courage.
I guess Fugo didn't come after all.
That was his choice to make.
Bucciarati!
I... I want to protect Trish!
I'll defeat the boss with you!
Yeah.
Squalo?
We have some traitors... in Venice.
The names of the traitors are
Bruno Bucciarati and Giorno Giovanna.
The boss's identity: Unknown
Stand name: Emperor Crimson
Has the ability to eliminate a certain amount of time.
Because of this, he can predict the future. Invincible.
They can be taken dead or alive.
This is straight from the boss!
Special Program
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure: Golden Wind
determinazione