Because you're going to join me.
I plan on defeating your boss
and taking over this city.
What?!
In order to get rid of gangs
that sell drugs to children,
I'm going to have to become
a gangster myself.
Are you saying...
that you're going to join our organization?!
Are you serious?!
Do you even know what that means?!
What a great view...
Yes. If I'm going to take over this city,
I'll have to join the organization that
rules it and work my way up.
Bucciarati,
I'm going to become a Gang-Star!
Pass! Pass!
Thanks!
Thanks.
Fine.
I'll report back saying I couldn't
find the one who attacked Luca
and introduce you so you
can join the organization.
However, if they find out at any time
that you're going after the boss...
I'm not going to save you.
Traitors can't be saved.
You'll have to deal with your own failure.
Otherwise, I'll wager on your golden dream and
the honorable, golden resolve it took
to go so far as to rip off your own arm,
Giorno Giovanna.
Episodio 03  Meet the Gangster Behind the Wall
Our organization oversees
every industry in Naples.
Passione... That's the
name of the organization.
Passione means "passion," but that's not
actually related to the boss's name.
No one actually knows the boss's name,
nor does anyone know what he looks like.
We receive orders from a number of his capos.
Giorno, the capo who'll be deciding
whether you'll join the organization
is a man named Polpo.
He's in this building.
But this building...
Loom
It's a prison.
Correct. Polpo was convicted
of a certain crime
and won't be out for fifteen years.
But he gives me orders from the inside
and commands the organization.
He can leave this place whenever
he feels like it, but he doesn't.
There's simply no reason to.
But why?
You'll understand once you go in.
Giorno Giovanna, you're going to be
interviewed by him, and you have to pass.
It's basically like any other job interview.
What the interview actually
entails will depend on his mood,
but whatever you do, don't let him
find out your true intentions.
All right.
Oh, yeah. The Stand ability...
That's what you called it, right?
I never asked how you ended
up with that ability,
but are there others with it?
That'll also be answered
once you get inside...
If you pass, that is.
First, place your belongings, watch,
and everything in your pockets into the tray,
then proceed to the next
room for a body check.
Stand right there and raise
your hands over your head.
Once you go through that gate,
please continue straight down the hall.
N-28 is where Polpo's cell is.
The room is divided with reinforced glass,
but you'll be able to talk to him.
Touching the glass, giving him anything,
and receiving anything from
him are all forbidden.
You have fifteen minutes.
Once you pass through, the gate will close.
If something happens, please yell.
I'm going to meet him directly in his cell?
Not in some visiting room?
You don't know who he is?
That left arm of yours...
Is it injured?
That's no bed...
Gwooo
It's just on your right hand,
but the fingers are slightly red,
like you were holding something.
Like lines that would be
left after holding a bag.
Which would mean that you were holding
a bag in your right hand up until now.
Why's that?
Well, uh... You're right.
I was holding a bag in my right hand,
because as you observed, I hurt my left arm.
I envy your ability to be
so reckless with your body.
Would you like some wine?
I have some exquisite Chianti Classico.
It pairs perfectly with some Scamorza
cheese and caviar on a cracker.
I've been told that I'm not allowed
to give you anything or
receive anything from you.
They're just saying that.
What people say and what they do...
are vastly different.
That's the best and worst thing about people.
The only downside to being
in this cell is.... well...
Polpo...
The fact that I can't admire Michelangelo's
great painting in the Sistine Chapel.
It's not that he doesn't
need to leave the prison.
Things would just be the same
for him whether he left or not.
With that body, he might
actually be safer in the cell.
More importantly, how did
he get through the door?
Bucciarati's told me all about you.
So you want to join our organization?
Hmm... Giorno Giovanna, was it?
Well, why don't we get
this interview started?
What the hell was that?
Did my eyes play a trick on me?
For a moment, it looked like he took a bite
out of his finger along with the cracker...
No... Maybe Polpo is also a Stand
user, just like Bucciarati.
Either way, I can't let him
find out that I'm one, as well.
What do you think is the
most important thing
when it comes to choosing
someone, Giorno Giovanna?
Is it what they're capable of?
Oh? And what exactly are you capable of?
I borrowed a few things when
she was patting me down.
I thought these would be useful for your test.
Of course, I'll be returning
them to her when I leave.
Do you have anything else?
Other than that, the only skill I have
is being able to completely
fold my ear into my head.
That's rather amusing.
But, you see...
There's something else
that's far more important,
and that's trust, Giorno Giovanna.
The most important thing when it
comes to choosing people is trust.
In comparison, being smart or
being talented means as much
as this piece of cracker between my teeth.
This test is all about seeing
how trustworthy you are...
with this lighter's flame.
Take it, and make sure the
flame doesn't go out.
Whoa, there.
Be extra careful to make sure
the flame doesn't go out.
Fuller, the 17th-century theologian, said,
"He's my friend that speaks
well of me behind my back."
In order to join our organization,
you'll have to show how trustworthy
you are when we can't see you.
For 24 hours, you will hold on to that
lighter without letting the flame go out.
If you can do that, I'll approve
of you joining the organization.
Simple, right?
The lighter has plenty of fluid in it.
All you have to do is sit quietly
in your room until 3 PM tomorrow
and make sure the flame doesn't go out.
If you're a careful man who'll work
hard to make sure it doesn't go out,
the flame shouldn't go out.
Which means you're someone we can trust.
However...
If you're a man who is
taking us too lightly,
and you fall asleep,
sneeze, or knock it over,
or a sudden wind blows the flame out...
It means that you're untrustworthy,
and I can't allow you to
join our organization.
Now, take the lighter.
This is your entrance exam.
You have 24 hours.
I'm looking forward to seeing you come
to visit me again tomorrow at 3 PM.
For 24 hours...
All visitors must go through another body
check when they go through the gate.
Once you're told that you
can leave the facility,
please continue to the next
room and grab your belongings.
Wait! Polpo didn't tell you anything?
What?
I'm going to pat you down now.
Let me remind you that it's prohibited
for you to accept anything from him!
Shit! I was under the impression
that Polpo bribed all these guys,
giving me permission to take
the lighter out of here!
Visitor, put your hands
up and proceed forward!
So Polpo's test for me
has already started...
And...
I have no choice but to go through with it!
I have to pass this test
and get into Passione!
Koichi Hirose
Reverb Act 3
Visitor, hurry forward!
Just like I hid her ID in my hand
where no one could see earlier,
Put your hands up and proceed forward!
I will conduct a body check!
I'll hide this flame!
You're free to go.
There are no problems here.
You may leave this facility.
However...
Please open up your hand.
Let me remind you that it's prohibited
to accept anything from him.
Visitor, open up your hand!
I'm going to check it.
A flower?
A real flower?
Very well. I'll allow you to take that out.
You are permitted to leave this facility.
I turned the lighter into a flower
and hid the flame within it.
That was too close.
But is this flame Polpo's Stand ability?
The wind's definitely bad news!
Hey, Giorno! Perfect timing!
Could you push the shutter
button on the camera?
No.
Sorry, but could you help me out here?
I finally made it back to my dorm.
Th-That was close...
Now the lighter won't fall over,
and even if the air moves,
the flame will be protected.
Now, just as Polpo said, I just need to
watch over this for the next 23 hours.
I know.
I'll make sure my window
is locked, just in case.
I need to make sure it doesn't randomly
open and allow the wind to blow in here.
What?
Who's opening my door without even knocking?
Th-That's—
Looks like he's out.
Now's my chance.
It's that Japanese guy again!
His name was... Koichi Hirose!
How did he find out my address?
Looks like my suitcase and
belongings are long gone.
But my passport might still be around.
It's probably harder to sell someone's ID.
I feel like a thief, sneaking into
someone's room like this, but...
No! He's the thief here!
What's so wrong with trying
to find what belongs to me?!
His passport? Shit!
It's in the documents case
on top of my desk because
I'd planned to return it to him!
At this rate, Koichi's going
to see the lighter's flame!
Then he'll probably put it out!
He'll think it'll set the place on fire!
What should I do?
I have to hurry up and retrieve that lighter!
Golden Wind!
I used Golden Wind to turn
the light cord into a snake.
That bread is pretty delicious.
Good job biting into it!
Now I'll pull it up with the cord...
What? Shit!
I can't believe this.
He found the lighter.
This isn't good.
I have to make sure he doesn't
blow the flame out!
Oh?
This mark! The mark symbolizing Japan!
I found it! It's my passport!
I-It's burning!
Thank goodness...
Huh?
That's strange. I could've
sworn I saw a lit lighter...
That was close.
He almost extinguished the flame.
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream!
And to take my first step toward that dream,
I have to protect this flame, no matter what!
Whoa, that was close.
Sorry about that. I was cleaning the stairs.
I'm glad it was just a slight mist and
the water didn't actually hit you.
This must mean we've both done
good things in our daily lives.
Your daily actions are very important.
If you weren't careful, you'd probably be
wearing that bucket of water on your head.
Seriously? This isn't good.
The flame...
I wonder if I can ask
Polpo to let me try again.
No...
If he were that forgiving,
he wouldn't have tested me with this.
Flame?
Is that lighter not lighting up anymore?
Is it broken? Is it my fault?
No, it wasn't you.
I'm actually trying to
process what happened...
But from what I can see,
it doesn't look broken.
The lighter is still letting gas out.
What did you just say?
Whoosh
Yes, there's still gas coming out.
Is this the switch?
Did you try pushing it?
No... It shouldn't be able to light.
But look at this fine craftsmanship!
This whole test depended on
if the flame was lit or not.
It's a very impressive lighter.
If I were able to just light it again,
there's be no point in this test!
I was startled by the size of the flame,
but it looks like it's working fine.
See?
By the way, since you have that lighter,
you're not smoking cigarettes, are you?
Something's wrong.
It actually lit up again...
There has to be something wrong!
What the...
That couldn't be his Sta—
You relit the lighter, didn't you?
I'll give you one more chance.
You have two possible paths.
Th-That's...
The first path is to live
and become a chosen one.
Your only other path is death.
A Stand!
That's gotta be Polpo's Stand!
There's no doubt about it!
You relit the lighter!
This is your fate!
No way! You bastard!
What the hell are you doing?!
This soul...
did not belong to one
who should be chosen.
One who should be chosen?
H-Hey, are you...
He's dead. He's uninjured, but he's dead...
Was it because...
That Stand pulls people's souls out
and kills them with an arrow?
Is that it?
But does "the one who should be chosen"
mean someone who can join the gang?
You relit the lighter, too, didn't you?
I'll give you one more chance.
You have two possible paths...
Episodio 04
Joining the Gang