Doppio...
Did you forget that I gave you a portion
of my Emperor Crimson's power?
Now is the time to use it!
You have Emperor Crimson's arms and Eulogy!
Calm down and look carefully for movements.
And then try to predict the future
movements that will occur around you.
Look carefully and predict the
future movements that will happen
Episodio 27 Emperor Crimson vs. Metallic
ten seconds from now.
B-Birds!
Birds went flying, just like what I saw!
B-Boss! I just saw him!
He was blended into the footage of ten
seconds from now that Eulogy showed me!
It looked like a person had blended
into the rocks in the background!
B-But I can't see him right now!
I can't tell where he is by looking directly!
That's Risotto.
He's somehow hiding his appearance.
Could it be...
He normally isn't visible, but you can
see him because you saw the future.
Look a few seconds into the future to
see how he's going to attack, Doppio!
Th-There he is!
H-He moved!
Wh-What?!
Th-This is awful, Boss!
In ten seconds, s-scissors are
going to c-come out of my throat!
Calm down, Doppio.
What you saw wasn't you dying.
Risotto is the assassin that no one
in the organization could find.
You should expect a little bit of damage.
You need to see how he's going to attack you
a few seconds in the future!
The fact that he gets close to me
means that it's definitely not
a remote-controlled Stand.
Th-This footage showing that there'll
be scissors inside my throat...
Does it mean this future
is unchangeable, Boss?!
Correct.
Now that you've seen that footage,
you're going to have to prepare yourself.
It's true that you're going to have
scissors shoved down your throat.
But see through it!
See through how he's going to attack you!
If you can see through his methods,
you'll find his weakness!
And then, get within two meters of him
and strike him with
Emperor Crimson's arm, Doppio!
Damn it!
There you are! Take this!
You're sloppy.
But then again, in all my
years of being an assassin,
you're the first one to ever land
a blow this close to my location.
How truly interesting.
How did you know?
I'm curious about your ability.
But still... you're going to die!
I-Impossible!
How did he get the scissors under my skin?
He hasn't laid a finger on me,
and I haven't opened my mouth.
H-His Stand hasn't even touched me...
But the scissors are opening on their own!
A-At this rate, he's going
to chop open my throat!
Stab!
I need to get them out!
Those movements...
I thought I'd be able to slice open his throat,
but it's as if he knew I was going
to place those scissors there.
He just put his hand to his
throat and defended himself.
There's something going on.
I need to be more careful...
so I can finish him off
completely in my next attempt.
God damn you!
Damn it... I couldn't tell.
The boss is going to be upset with me.
I still don't know how he's invisible.
B-But this damage...
I-I'm losing strength in my legs...
Th-That's—
What's the matter, Doppio?
Were you able to see his attack?
B-Boss!
You couldn't see it?
Then move away from there immediately.
Figure out exactly where he
is by having him chase you!
Y-You bastard!
I've made up my mind.
I'm definitely going to see
through him next time.
Damn it.
I'm going to get within two
meters of him, no matter what!
You just saw Emperor Crimson's
next footage, didn't you?
What did you see?
I'm asking you a question, Doppio!
My right foot, Boss.
For the next move, in a few seconds,
it's going to be scissors again.
It went flying off.
My foot is going to go flying off.
What did you say, Doppio?!
H-He's coming! I saw a glimpse of him!
Get away from there right now!
Why didn't you move immediately
after seeing the footage, Doppio?
Risotto Nero, the assassin.
While his movements are careful,
he's already made preparations to kill me.
I can't get my legs to move.
I'm not sure if I can run.
Razor blades, scissors...
He was preparing for me
to lose all this stamina!
Shit. Doppio won't be able to win now.
It's going to take me at least
ten seconds to come out.
This isn't good.
The damage he'd endure from losing
his foot would be less than ideal.
I need to minimize the damage somehow.
I'm telling you to move away from there now!
You're going to be killed!
But, Boss, if I may interject...
That's exactly why I shouldn't move.
I've used up my stamina.
That's why it's easier
to tell if I don't move.
All I've been thinking about is
where he was attacking me from
with the razor blades and scissors.
But I was going about it the wrong way!
There you are!
His ability...
is to use the iron within
a living creature to create
iron razor blades within their bodies!
The fact that this frog and I are
so worn out gave me the answer!
You use your Stand ability
to use the iron within a living
creature to create razor blades!
And given that the razor blades came out
of the frog before they came out of me...
That's the direction you
were approaching from!
Th-This bastard...
Looks like the prediction was correct.
Someone's foot went flying off.
And the mystery behind the enemy's form
is slowly becoming apparent, Boss.
Huh? Boss?
That's strange. I could've
sworn I was holding a phone...
Where did I drop it?
I mean, that's a frog...
Oh, there it is!
How the heck did I drop it down there?
It's underneath all these rocks,
and now it's covered in sand.
Oh, jeez. And I need to report
to the boss immediately, too...
D-Did it break?
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
Yes!
As small as they make electronics these
days, I guess they're pretty sturdy!
Hello? Praise me, Boss.
He can't move anymore.
Impossible...
Well done, Doppio.
My Doppio...
Am I going to be the one to finish him off?
Or should I wait until you get here, Boss?
I want to make sure that Risotto
Nero is finished off for good.
I'll take care of him myself.
Get closer to him, Doppio.
Get within two meters of him...
And then, I'll go there.
Until then, get closer to him.
You got it! I'll get closer to him, Boss!
Inside the wound where
his foot was severed...
They're wriggling.
Risotto's Stand is inside his body!
You have precognitive powers, don't you?
You had a decent idea of what would
happen and how I would move.
Otherwise, there's no way you could've
predicted my position or my attack.
It's true that, at first, you were a beginner
who couldn't do anything on your own.
But... who are you right now?
Your personality is now
filled with confidence.
And what's that look on your face?
Those eyes don't belong to a young man.
It's as if there are two of you.
Shink
Could that be what's going on?
No, that's not it.
There's no doubt about it.
I'm much closer than I realize...
to the one I'm after right now!
Two years.
It's been two years since we were
basically pups who had been
collared, shaking in fear.
You're definitely something more
than what we've been looking for.
I'm certain of it.
I want to know what you are.
I want to see your true form.
I want to know what you are when
I kill you... no matter what!
Risotto Nero
Metallic
Solido Naso... That's probably
one of the boss's aliases.
Otherwise, he wouldn't hide
his daughter so quickly.
We came all the way here,
but it's just a waste of damn time.
Damn it.
But if we're able to get his daughter,
we might find out who the boss is!
Right, Bro?
We haven't been able to make a move
ever since what happened
to Sorbet and Gelato.
I wonder who's guarding his daughter.
Pericolo's not a Stand user,
so maybe it's Polpo.
Then maybe we should head
toward Naples and ask him.
Don't get ahead of yourselves.
It's times like these that you should
remain calm before doing anything.
I understand how you feel,
but you need to lock away what
happened to Sorbet and Gelato.
Failure equals death.
I'm excited, but...
The one who gets too excited in
this situation is the one who dies.
The foot I chopped off!
I was right. Risotto Nero...
I can now see your powers! Magnetism!
You're controlling your Stand at
that distance with magnetism!
You took control of the iron inside me
and made me spit out those
razor blades and scissors!
The way you make yourself disappear
is by covering yourself in iron powder
and camouflaging yourself to
match the scenery around you!
Correct.
You may have figured out what
Metallic is, but it's too late.
Because you are already complete.
Iron.
You can find iron anywhere in this world.
Of course, it's in sand,
as well as spring water and plants.
And of course, iron is also
found within humans, as well.
Stab Stab Stab
What are you doing, Doppio?
You predicted his movements!
I will not allow you to
receive further damage!
Th-This is... B-Boss!
You saw through my ability,
and my foot got chopped off.
But you are already complete.
There's nothing you can do about that.
Large amounts of iron can be found in
vegetables like spinach and meats like liver.
It's an important substance
that's within your bloodstream.
What happens when all the iron within
you leaves your body at once?
To put it simply, your blood turns a
horrible shade of yellow and you die.
The iron in your blood
captures the oxygen
that enters your body when you breathe,
and carries it throughout your body.
Without that, the precious oxygen doesn't
reach your fingertips or your brain.
Which means, now that you've
been robbed of so much iron,
despite how hard you're breathing,
oxygen isn't entering your body.
Your body is going to become
a corpse before you actually die.
Now, then...
I wonder what I should do next.
Should I wait until you croak, or...
We seem to be out of time anyway,
so should I just go over
there and finish you off?
B-Boss...
That's...
They're near the mansion!
It's Bucciarati!
He finally showed himself!
Narancia's also there, and...
Abbacchio's there, too!
What? Abbacchio's there?
We're out of time.
Doppio, finish him off with your next move!
Predict Risotto's movements in the footage!
I'm already looking!
Risotto will come around
my right side, and then...
He disappears! I can't see him!
I-It can't be...
What do you see, Doppio?
What do you see?
I'm gonna turn the tables, damn it!
I'll finish him off, Boss!
A few seconds before what happens
in this footage happens...
I'll blow off his head instead!
Just like I chopped off his foot earlier!
H-Here he comes!
Don't do anything else, Doppio!
There's nothing else you can do.
Listen well, Doppio. This is important.
Don't waste any more energy.
I'm heading there right now.
It'll be a few more seconds,
but I'll deal with Risotto.
A few seconds?!
But it'll be too late!
He's going to attack me any second!
Deal with it!
If my full abilities get there,
I can just erase the time
you saw in the footage!
But I'm the one who's going to be attacked!
So I'll finish him off!
Doppio! This is the only way!
This is the only way you're going to survive!
Your body can't take any more.
I won't allow you to waste any
more energy on my behalf!
You're going to finish him off?
Risotto Nero is not someone
you can find twice!
But what if I can, Boss?
If I know where he is...
If his ability is going to try to steal
even more iron from my body...
H-Here he comes! He's attacking!
He should have the strength to pull...
He should have the strength
to pull the iron from my body!
The scalpel is pointing in the
direction of the magnetic force!
You're right there, Risotto!
I figured that's what you'd do.
Magnetism pulls at the iron.
If you can figure out which
way it's being pulled,
you thought you could figure out my location.
However, unfortunately...
What you sensed was
the magnetism that Metallic is producing
in the foot you chopped off.
I left it there.
I learned from my mistake of
letting you chop off my right foot.
I need to make the best of that situation.
There's barely any oxygen left in your body.
You are complete.
You shouldn't even be able to move an inch.
You're different from before.
Now you're brimming with confidence.
The excessive physical changes to your body,
and the way you're talking to yourself...
It all makes sense now.
I finally figured out who you really are!
Yes, this had already been confirmed
in 16th century Germany.
There are people in this world
who have multiple personalities.
In some cases, it doesn't
just affect them mentally.
Their body... Their physique can change,
as well as their way of speaking.
I had just thought that you were the
boss's most trusted subordinate.
But you...
To think that you...
I can't wait.
I can't what to see what your
face will look like once you die!
There's nothing else you can do.
I'm keeping my distance.
You have no strength to resist.
There's nothing you can do!
I've won!
I'm going to chop off your head!
This is the end! Take this!
Metallic!
Wh-What?
Risotto,
I told Doppio...
that you were no longer
an enemy he could handle.
Don't tell me...
I knew it. The enemy was already here.
But I shot right through him!
I hit him good, too!
Y-You...
If the blood in my body
that's been robbed of iron
isn't going to carry oxygen
throughout my body...
It's the same thing as if
my body wasn't breathing.
Which means that the only thing
Li'l Bomber can track right now...
How many enemies are there, Narancia?
Just one!
There's only one person
breathing on that cliff!
...is your breathing, Risotto.
I see.
This is the same thing that happened in
the footage that Doppio saw, but...
I was winning...
I would've won...
But you had thrown the scalpels at them...
Boss...
Episodio 28
Beneath a Sky on the Verge of Falling