Episodio 26 A Little Story From the Past ~My Name Is Doppio~
This is a little story from the past.
Summer, 1965
We're going back to the summer of 1965.
Prisoner 696! What's going on here?!
Prisoner 696!
Did you eat something bad?
She's pregnant?
This is a women's prison on a remote island.
There are only women here!
Not to mention, this prisoner
was sentenced to ten years
for bank robbery and assault.
She's been here for two years already.
Push! Just a little bit more!
When could she have gotten pregnant?
She wasn't big earlier today.
And now...
Hey, you! Who the hell's this kid's father?!
He's... dead...
For over two years... now...
You can't be serious.
A barnacle growing in your knee
would be more believable than that.
Looks like the baby made it.
Yes... But something's strange.
The baby's eyes have been
open ever since he was born.
And he's not crying at all.
This goes without saying,
but we can't raise a baby here.
We'll find someone to take him.
Where are you from?
Sar...di...nia...
A priest at a small church
there took the child in.
Time passed, and the boy
became known as someone
rather cowardly and a bit slow.
June, 1985
Well, I'll be going now.
See you later, Mr. Frog.
Hey, watch it!
Oh, it's you.
Walk closer to the edge, you dumbass!
Don't you dare tell the priest about this.
Th-That was close...
But I'm glad you didn't get squished.
Do you like frogs?
I like frogs, too.
I hate bugs, though.
I also don't like guys who smell.
I hate everything that's not beautiful.
Are you from around here?
Y-Yeah...
Say, it's a bit hot out.
Want to get something to drink?
Well...
That's not a bad idea.
Then I want sparkling water.
Hard water from France.
I hope you're treating.
You want to become a sailor?
Yeah...
Well...
You're a simple man.
That's probably best for you.
Oh?
He walked all this way?
Good on him.
It might be a good idea to get him a car.
In order to build a garage next to his room,
the priest started digging
into the floor with a pick.
What's this?
A corpse?
No, it's...
As he carefully picked at the concrete...
The person he discovered was a woman.
It was the woman who gave birth
to the boy the priest took in.
Sh-She's alive...
She couldn't move nor talk,
but somehow, she was being kept alive.
How many years had it been?
The woman had no sense of time.
Hatred? Love?
Her heart was dark.
This hair color...
That night, the whole village burned,
with strong winds carrying
the fire to every single house.
No one knows how it started.
Seven people died, and others went missing.
On the list of the deceased were
the names of the priest
and the boy he'd taken in.
Olbia, Sardinia: Present Day
Why, you!
Hey, kid! Look out!
Shut up. I know.
There's a truck coming, right?
You bastard!
Where the hell do you think
you're walking, you dumbass?!
O-Ow...
Aw, man... Ow.
Guess I had the wrong idea.
Looks like you're down on your luck.
Having a bad day?
Or have you been having
a streak of bad luck?
I'd say so. I've had one problem after another.
Why not let me tell your fortune?
I'll make it cheap.
Huh? Nah, I'll pass...
Sardinia is your home, isn't it?
And it's been a while since you've
been back here, hasn't it?
I wouldn't call that fortunetelling.
You can tell I'm a traveler
just by looking at me.
Anyone could figure that out.
You're... living with a secret.
Light and shadow,
what's inside and what's out.
You could probably call
it two separate lives.
But you take advantage of that secret
and have an unyielding personality,
which has earned you nothing but victories.
What?
Oh, please forgive my rudeness.
There's something about your face that is
very intriguing to someone in my field.
Please, let me tell you your fortune.
I'll make it 20,000... no, 10,000 lire.
Everyone has their secrets.
That's a pretty broad statement.
You're looking for someone.
You're currently looking for
someone very important to you.
Seriously...
Everyone spends their
lives looking for someone.
A beautiful girlfriend or a good friend...
But I guess it's nice to
hear these things at times.
How do you go about doing it?
With that crystal ball?
No... I've already begun.
I can tell just by looking at the shape
of the mud splatter on your pants.
It's been said for thousands of years
that in Romani fortunetelling,
the best results come from looking at the
shape of something that formed coincidentally.
Because that is the symbol of fate.
Your daughter...
Yes.
The person you're looking
for is your daughter.
You came back to Sardinia to find the child
of the woman you left fifteen years ago...
Huh?
Huh? Er... Something's strange.
You're rather young...
I know what I just said,
but this is strange...
Whose child? Mine?
But you have one. I'm sure of it.
Let me see your palm!
Hey!
Please! My pride as a fortuneteller
is on the line here!
Let go of my hand... Don't touch me...
I won't ask for payment...
Actually, I'll pay you!
20,000... No, I'll pay you 100,000 lire!
Please!
You're friggin' annoying! Don't touch me!
What good would it do
for you to see it, huh?!
Considering you're about to die!
Your face... Your age...
It appears you're not a Stand user.
You have the wisdom to see people
for who they really are,
and you made that your business.
That was your greatest failing.
No one in this world is allowed
to know who I really am.
But I now know that you are indeed
an excellent fortuneteller.
Out of respect for that, I'll be sure to kill
you instantly so you don't feel any pain.
So answer my question...
This man's name is Risotto.
He's a traitor.
He is also looking for my daughter
and trying to find out my true identity.
I want you to tell me where he is right now.
Where he is?
I can't tell that much...
But I'm sure you'll encounter him soon.
He's here in Sardinia...
He is filled with vengeance,
and you will certainly encounter him here.
I see. Very well.
That's plenty.
I knew it!
I was right! Light and shadow,
what's inside and what's out.
Two personalities!
As long as you bear this secret, the death
of people will bring you good fortune,
and you will never lose your splendor!
What a beautiful palm!
I've never seen a hand like this before!
Huh? Something's wrong.
It suddenly looks strange.
The lifeline is totally different...
I see!
This is my own hand!
It changed before I even realized it!
Emperor Crimson.
You...
I'm so glad you weren't squished.
It's dangerous to be on the sidewalk.
Go on, shoo.
Be careful. Go on.
Huh?
Where to, sir?
Costa Smeralda, please.
You got it.
And now for our next story,
the investigations involving the site of
the crash off the Olbia coast in Sardinia.
However...
Driver, do you have a cell phone?
Mine broke...
No, I don't. Sorry.
I see...
C-Could you stop for a sec, driver?
I'll get out here! This is fine!
I'll get out here.
That's the building.
There's no doubt about it.
I just have to keep an eye out over there.
Costa Smeralda in Sardinia.
This area was forgotten by history
until about half a century ago,
when a certain millionaire from India was
enamored by the scenery of this coast,
where the winds and cliffs met,
and started living there.
Hey, wait a sec!
There seems to be an extra
digit on your meter...
So you actually think I rigged the meter
because I wanted more money?
Is that what you think? Huh?!
N-No... But 800,000 lire to get from
the city to here seems a bit...
I don't have that much.
Like hell a guy on vacation doesn't have money!
I know you hid some in your pocket earlier.
I saw you hide an envelope in your pants.
Don't—
Come on, let me see.
Don't touch me... I-I'm getting a headache...
See? I knew it.
You friggin' idiot!
Those who have seen what
they shouldn't have seen
don't need to exist in this world!
Y-You bastard...
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
Hey... Did you just hear a phone ring?
Huh?
Where did it come from?
Hey! I asked you a question!
That phone's busted, so there's
no way it could've rung!
H-Hell if I know! What are you—
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
There it is again! Where is it?
Where is it?
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
Hey, what the hell? You have a car phone!
Hello? Yes, this is Doppio.
Boss... Yes, I just arrived.
It's the spot in the photo.
I just need to keep an eye
on this place, right?
Huh? The driver didn't see
what was in the envelope,
so I don't need to finish him off?
If I may interject, Boss,
I believe he saw the photo that
he wasn't supposed to see.
Right. I'm very sorry, Boss.
Yes, I'm about to start watching the building.
You're about to watch the building?
No, my Doppio.
Take a good look. Slowly... Naturally.
Don't do anything suspicious.
The one who's being watched...
is you, Doppio.
Th-That's Risotto! The traitor assassin!
He appeared just like
the fortuneteller said!
Apparently, due to the plane crash,
he came to notice the existence of this
photo of Sardinia that was at Trish's house.
We need to take care of him first.
Otherwise, he'll interfere
once Trish arrives.
I'll be the one to finish him off.
We need to get close to him without
him figuring out my true identity.
Risotto's ability is a
mystery to me, as well.
Draw him out about two meters away from you.
Then he'll definitely be within
Emperor Crimson's range.
You can do it.
I'm hanging up, my Doppio.
Yes, I understand, Boss.
Beep.
What's this? My head... It hurts.
O-Oh, yeah. I don't have time
to worry about a headache.
I just had a call from the boss.
My mission is to keep an eye
on that building and... uh...
What was it again?
Get closer?
Right! I have to get closer!
But to what?
I won't get closer to you.
Look over here.
Wh-What the?!
But I think I've seen him before...
Wh-Who is he again?
Move your hand.
Otherwise, I can't see your face.
I-I don't have any money!
B-Blood!
Why does this always happen to me?!
Maybe I just imagined it.
The ignorance and fear in his
expression are not an act.
If he was from Passione,
he wouldn't act like this.
Not to mention, he's more
unguarded than a baby.
He must be a civilian.
Please don't!
Stop fussing. I'm just
going to pick up my knife.
I don't care about you anymore.
I-I don't feel so good... My head hurts...
T-Two meters...
That's right.
There was just one thing you
did that seemed like an act.
When you fell,
you reflexively hid the envelope
so I wouldn't see it, didn't you?
It's right under your left shoe.
What are you hiding?
If I'm satisfied with what I see, I'll leave.
What is your deal?!
I-I don't have any money! Just let me go!
It wasn't murderous intent or hostility,
but your expression there seemed fake.
Stand up, move your left leg, and show me.
I told you to stand up! Stand up!
Oh, so it's just an envelope.
There's nothing in it.
Your trembling certainly isn't an act,
and I can tell you're a
coward who can't lie.
But now... I'm even more interested in you.
You're definitely a Stand user.
You heard that sound, too, didn't you?
Just now, you glanced over toward that sound.
That's the sound of scouting.
It's carefully scouting the area.
That sound and shape...
is Li'l Bomber!
They've finally made it here!
And who are you to show up to
such an important location?
It must mean that the
boss trusts you greatly.
But there is true fear in your heart.
You're a walking contradiction!
Shut your trap!
You're the one who's about
to be shaking in your boots!
I see.
Since you're running toward me,
you must be a close-ranged power type.
Your range is around two to three meters.
As long as I know that,
I know how I'll kill you.
What... the... M-My throat!
Th-These are...
actual razor blades?!
T-Two meters, damn it!
I'll shove these razor
blades right up your ass!
I told you, I know how I'll kill you.
Impossible! I'm not done yet, damn it!
H-He disappeared?
That's his... That's his assassin ability...
But how...
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
There's a phone ringing somewhere!
I can't believe it!
There just happens to be a
pay phone in a place like this!
Click!
Beep!
Hello?!
My Doppio...
Wh-Where are you, Boss?
Are you nearby?
If you are, please come quickly!
I cannot.
I cannot go there until you
get close enough to him.
Because everything will be over
if he happens to see me and
then manages to escape.
B-But—
You need to get closer. You need to
get within two meters of Risotto!
Boss! I don't know what his ability is!
He could attack me again at any second!
Doppio...
Oh, Doppio...
My adorable little Doppio...
Did you forget that I gave you a portion
of my Emperor Crimson's power?
Now is the time to use it!
Episodio 27
Emperor Crimson vs. Metallic