Wh-What? My body suddenly...
All my strength is...
It can't be... My eyes are blurring, too...
Am I finally out of time?
I knew this moment would come...
But now?
I must go.
Go? Wait... I know Bucciarati
and his crew have a goal.
Where is he trying to go?
I'm sure the boss wants to find that out.
Pardon me.
Can I lend you a hand?
It's totally up to you, though.
What? You're still here?
I'm fine.
Go run along somewhere.
But... and excuse me if
I'm being presumptuous,
but I think it might be hard for
you to cross that road alone.
I really don't mind lending you my shoulder.
I mean, if you don't mind...
Well...
That might not be such a bad idea.
How far would you like to go?
Um... Just to the entrance of the Colosseum.
The entrance of the Colosseum...
Episodio 33 His Name Is Diavolo
There's no time. Just to the other
side of the road... Please...
Look out!
You stupid-ass drunk!
Are you okay?! Where were you look—
What? Why is Bucciarati so cold?
Sorry about that...
This is a guardrail?
Did I run into it?
Could it be that...
Bucciarati can't see anything?
He also ignored that car horn
when he tried to cross the road.
Does that mean he can't hear, either?
That wound on your throat...
Were you hurt during that scuffle earlier?
Actually, it looks like that wound
is from this morning or last night.
It's not bleeding anymore.
That's a strange place to be wounded.
He can somehow see it clearly.
But it's under my collar...
He's looking right at it!
At the wound that Risotto gave me!
Oh, you picked that up for me.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Well... Ready to go?
Okay... Let's go.
He can hear me, too.
But something seems off,
for just being hurt in a fight.
What's going on?
That's Guido Mista!
Damn! I took too much time.
Of course he'd show up.
Is something wrong?
We haven't finished crossing yet.
No, um...
Sorry, the cut on my neck
started bleeding a little...
He's heading this way!
I apologize for being selfish,
but I'm in a hurry.
I need to hurry up and cross.
No!
Don't stand up!
I mean... There's another car coming.
Let's cross once it passes.
No, that's on the other side of the road.
We can cross.
Come on.
Let me cross.
N-No... Mista's coming!
I'm just going to have to
eliminate him right here...
Right now!
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
I wonder what that sound was.
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring,
ring-a-ling-ring-a-ling-ding...
What the hell are you doing?
What did you just say?
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring,
ring-a-ling-ring-a-ling-ding...
Why am I getting a call right now?!
He's going to figure out who I am!
You're...
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
You friggin' dumbass!
Why the hell are you calling me right now?!
Do you want him to find out?!
Trish!
Don't come outside yet!
The danger's not fully gone.
Get back in the turtle!
You don't understand. He's here!
I started getting that feeling again.
The same thing I felt in Sardinia...
Who... are you?
The person in front of me...
You're...
Rumble
Trish!
I can feel him! He's nearby.
The boss is nearby!
He's nearby?
You don't know exactly where, though?
He just suddenly appeared...
But I don't know where.
Thank goodness. You're safe.
Well done. You did excellent work.
This is why you're my most trusted
and number one subordinate.
Don't worry.
Bucciarati is looking at you right now,
but he doesn't actually see you.
What do you mean?
I don't know how this happened,
but Bucciarati is already a corpse.
His heartbeat has stopped,
and he's not breathing properly.
He can't see, and his eardrums
ruptured in his battle with Secco.
All he can see right now, Doppio,
is the shape of your soul.
All he can hear is the energy of your soul.
He can't see objects like guardrails,
and all he can see in cars are
the souls of the drivers.
What's wrong, Trish?
Did something happen?
My daughter's soul and mine
have a similar scent.
That's what I gave you just now.
All Bucciarati sees is
the form of my daughter!
Get Bucciarati to lead you to
whatever he was seeking.
Have him take you there!
Trish...
Sorry... I'm tired, so I spaced out a bit.
But thank goodness you're safe, Bucciarati.
Yeah... More importantly,
was there a young man nearby?
Oh, I saw him rush off somewhere in a hurry.
More importantly, Bucciarati,
let's hurry to our destination.
You're right. I hate to bother you,
but could you lend me a hand?
I can't seem to gather enough strength...
Yes,
of course.
Diavolo
Emperor Crimson
It's rather small, but Trish, I have
a house in the suburbs of Naples.
Once all this is over...
if you don't have anywhere to go...
You can live there.
There's a school nearby,
as well as a great restaurant.
It's close to the beach, too.
You've had nothing but horrible
things happen to you,
but you still have a chance
to enjoy a new life.
Thanks. But more importantly
right now, where should I head next?
Go up those stairs...
Upstairs?
Don't turn your head, Doppio!
Keep going as though you
haven't noticed anything!
There's someone here.
Upstairs, behind one
of the stone pillars.
Someone is watching you!
It appears that his goal
was to meet with someone.
But who could it possibly be?
I haven't the slightest idea...
Boss, how do you know they're here?
And if I don't turn around and look,
I won't be able to tell who they are.
Look at Bucciarati's eyes.
That should be enough.
He's reflecting in
Bucciarati's eyes right now.
Don't move!
Stop right there.
Take even a step up those
stairs, and our deal is off.
You're right! There's someone
hidden behind one of the pillars!
My name is Bruno Bucciarati!
I came this far because I
trusted you when you said
you had a way to defeat the boss!
I know that.
But before we get to that,
who's that next to you?
There's nothing about them
anywhere in my records!
And there shouldn't be!
Trish doesn't belong to the organization,
and I only met her a few days ago.
But as you can see, she's one of us.
Trish? That sounds like a girl's name.
Sounds like?
This isn't good... He's
going to find us out, Boss!
Calm down. Listen to me.
This is what you're going to say:
"Do you have a problem with me being
a girl?" Go on, say it, Doppio!
Do you have a problem with me being a girl?!
I guess I said something I shouldn't have.
It's a bit dark in here,
so I couldn't see you well.
Is she a Stand user?
Of course! But enough questions!
What I want to know is, who are you?
Let's just get to the point of this meeting!
No, not yet. I want to see her Stand.
Trish! Move slowly.
I have no data on you,
but if you show me your Stand
from there, I'll trust you.
B-Boss...
Who the hell is he?
He's definitely got experience fighting.
He's even thinking about a Stand's range...
Who could he possibly be?
I really have no idea...
Well? Hurry and show me from that spot.
Move slowly, as if you're
lifting up your skirt.
That's... It can't be!
Why does he have that?
That arrow... There's no doubt about it.
That's the arrow from back then!
Wh-What's this ominous
murderous intent I feel?
It feels like someone's pointing
a knife right at my heart...
I've felt something like this before...
Don't tell me—
No, wait... That's right.
There is one person I can think of.
He used the arrow to track me down...
He's—
In Egypt, I dug up the arrows that
awaken Stand abilities within people.
I knew the moment I saw them
that these arrows had some mysterious power.
An old woman named Enyaba
who had two right hands
told me she'd tell me how the arrows
worked in return for shooting some.
I figured one would be more than enough,
so I sold the other five for a handsome sum.
Come to think of it, that old woman
said something rather bizarre...
The arrow chooses people,
and those people are attracted
to one another like magnets.
In the 90s, me and my old friend
Jotaro Kujo were investigating
these arrows that brought
out one's Stand abilities.
We heard about a young man who
had dug up the other arrows,
and we split up to be more
efficient in searching for him.
Jotaro went to America and Asia.
I went to Europe and Africa.
And I managed to find out
that one of the arrows was
in a region of Italy where drug-related
crimes had suddenly skyrocketed.
I investigated an unusual
region where drug crimes
involving young people and their
victims had increased twenty times,
and I knew I was finally close.
But...
My organization was nearing
perfection after just a few years.
My subordinates swore
their loyalty to me.
I had men hiding in all branches of society.
I had a notion that someone
was trying to track me down.
In the end, I would finish them off myself.
That's the most surefire way.
I'd already decided that.
But I ended up making two big mistakes.
My first mistake was that this crime
organization was already complete.
Communications, the government, the press...
Society itself had isolated me.
And my second and greatest mistake...
Silver Chariot!
I guess I'll tell you,
since you're going to die.
The man who had unearthed the arrows
had powers far more sinister
than I could have ever imagined!
The moment that anyone
sees Emperor Crimson...
Boom
This ability...
Time... It...
...they are no longer in this world.
Is there no hope...?
I'm certain that I killed him!
To think that someone I had eliminated
in the past would show
up again with an arrow!
Bucciarati! The one next to you is—
Wh-What? Bucciarati!
Where'd the person next to you go?!
They disappeared! Don't tell me...
Where did they go?!
Where did the one you brought here go?!
T-Trish...
I'm asking you who the hell
that person next to you was!
I didn't hear or see anything fall,
but a piece is already behind me...
No... These movements...
Time just skipped!
Just like what happened in Venice!
We moved further up the stairs
before we realized it!
We're not gonna make it!
The man waiting for us at the Colosseum
just entered the boss's range!
This is a test.
I've accepted this test to stand
victorious against my past.
A person grows once they are able
to defeat their weaker self.
Wouldn't you agree, Jean Pierre Polnareff?
You're...
Rumble
Diavolo!
It appears that no matter how
much I tear apart the past,
it still manages to wriggle up
like a worm from under a rock.
This is surprising.
No wonder I couldn't think
of anyone who opposed me.
How did you get here?!
But in the end,
it doesn't matter how you survived after
I scattered your remains in the ocean.
What's important, Polnareff,
is what you were trying to
tell Bucciarati and his men!
Don't you dare set foot on those stairs!
I'm up here! You're down there!
Why won't you fight yourself, Polnareff?
Because you no longer have
the mental capacity for it?
Or are you no longer physically able to fight?
What are you going to use that arrow for?
This is impossible. I'm sure
it was a kid down there!
Diavolo... When did you get so close to me?
You're the one below me, Polnareff!
As long as you are below in Hell,
it doesn't matter what you
plan to do with that arrow!
There! Silver Chariot!
I see your Stand ability
hasn't lost any of its power.
And it seems you've learned...
You've figured out how to see when time
has skipped by counting drops of blood.
I see. In just a moment's
difference in number...
Your timing is genius, too.
If I had been any closer,
I would've been gravely injured.
This is the worst...
I can't believe the first person
to get here was Diavolo...
I won't have another chance. But I must...
I must protect hope at all costs!
You're already within my range!
You won't escape this time!
Emperor Crimson!
Now, once the passage of time resumes,
you won't be able to see how
many drops of blood there are.
I've just defeated my weaker
self from the past!
Take this! The passage of time will resume—
Wh-What is this?
The arrow... The Stand...
I don't know what it's doing, but...
Take this!
This arrow... What is it doing to Chariot?!
There's some kind of
power behind this glow!
Time, resume!
Impossible! What did you do?
The arrow does more than
just draw out Stand abilities?
This is my gamble to keep
the arrow from Diavolo.
I didn't want to show him that,
but I don't have the power to fully
control the arrow any longer.
You won't get away!
Stab
That arrow is our hope...
The one who can fully control that arrow
will be the one to control the world.
I-It happened again!
It skipped! Time skipped again!
Trish! Where's the boss?
You spent years uncovering some
incredible secret about the arrow.
I guess you held out a
pretty long time, Polnareff.
But unfortunately for you,
I have the arrow now!
It appears your heart has stopped.
But the life you lived
was not a complete waste,
Jean Pierre Polnareff.
You have been ever so useful... to me.
Giorno!
L-Look over there! It's Bucciarati!
Hey, he looks really hurt!
Bucciarati!
Be careful! The boss is somewhere nearby.
So you've come...
What?
Who are you?!
How long have you been standing there?!
Episodio 34
The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 1