Something's wrong.
It actually lit up again...
There has to be something wrong!
You relit the lighter, didn't you?
No way! You bastard!
What the hell are you doing?!
This soul...
did not belong to one
who should be chosen.
One who should be chosen?
H-Hey, are you...
He's dead. He's uninjured, but he's dead...
You relit the lighter, too, didn't you?
I'll give you one more chance.
You have two possible paths...
So it indiscriminately attacks anyone
who happens to see the lighter relit.
Th-This is...
This bastard... He's dragging my soul
out of me through my shadow!
I'll give you one more chance.
You have two possible paths...
Episodio 04  Joining the Gang
The first path is to become a chosen one.
It's no use... It's stronger
than Golden Wind.
The old man died after his soul
was struck by that arrow.
So what's going to happen to me
if my Stand is attacked?
Your only other path is death.
Th-This arrow...
If I actually get stabbed by
that arrow, I'm dead for sure!
I've got no choice!
Even if Polpo is one of the capos,
if he's going to stand in my way
and even kill an innocent old man
like he was a piece of trash...
I have to defeat him!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Golden Wind...
Only your senses will go berserk,
and all movements will look slow.
It's gone! That's impossible!
It shouldn't be able to control
its own movements right now.
Even if it were able to move,
it should be extremely slow.
It shouldn't be able to disappear!
It has to be around here somewhere...
It has to be!
I have to find it before the
slowed-time effect wears off,
or it'll attack me again.
What?!
F-From within the shadows?! Sh-Shit!
Its movements are slower,
but it's still just as powerful!
I can't move at all!
The shadows! It's in the shadows!
It can only move within the
shadows, but at amazing speed...
Looks like it can't follow
me into the sunlight.
But the sun's going to set on the
other side of the school soon.
Once that happens, I'll have nowhere to run.
What'll happen if I force
it out into the sunlight?
It's definitely worth trying.
But how am I going to drag it out?
What should I do? It's waiting right there.
It's waiting there patiently
for the sun to go down.
Hey!
What are you doing, Giorno Giovanna?!
Koichi!
Who's that guy collapsed
at the bottom of the stairs?!
What did you do to him?!
Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
That wasn't me!
That Stand right there atta—
The wrong idea?
I saw you talking to that old man!
I was watching from the window!
You were... watching?
Then... did you see the
lighter being relit, too?
Huh?
Don't step into the handrail's shadow, Koichi!
Get out of the shadows!
Sh-Shit!
You saw the lighter being relit, didn't you?
You have two possible paths.
Wh-What's going on?
The first path is to become a chosen one.
Your only other path is death.
This arrow is...
Golden Wind!
It hurts so much...
This hurts like hell, but now...
it looks like I was able to drag
you out into the sunlight.
I turned part of the handrail
into morning glories and let them hang down.
Now you're out of the handrail's shadow!
So close!
There were more shadows nearby,
so it managed to escape.
But it looks like if I can drag that
thing completely out into the sunlight,
I might be able to win.
Wh-What was...
What was that Stand?!
As you saw, it's trying to attack us.
The old man who relit
this lighter was killed.
Because we saw it being relit,
both you and I are now its targets.
That's not what I meant.
That arrow... It's from the Bow and Arrow!
I didn't know one was in Italy, too...
What are you doing, Giorno Giovanna?!
Is it because of you that another
Stand with the arrow appeared?!
It'll take too long to explain everything...
But I don't know anything.
Do you know something about that Stand?
And about that arrow?
Why did you save me?
Telling me about that
arrow is more important!
The sun's going to set!
Why did you save me?!
Don't you dare assume that I feel like
I owe a thief like you anything!
The lighter being lit is
because of something I did.
There was nothing I could've
done for that old man.
I feel awful about it.
I believe what I did was right,
but I feel dark and gross inside.
But despite that,
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream
that I believe to be right.
Two years ago, I was shot with a similar
arrow and gained my Stand ability.
If the person shot with the arrow doesn't
awaken to that ability, they will die.
Awaken to the ability?
That's it!
That's what it meant by the "chosen one"!
Someone whose Stand awakened!
And that must be the motive
behind Polpo's test!
I don't know about the origin of the arrow,
but I've met a Stand very
similar to this one before.
It's a long-distance
remote-controlled Stand!
Long-distance and remote-controlled?
It can only carry out simple commands,
but it won't stop attacking
until it's fulfilled its motive.
Our best option is to find the
Stand user and take them down.
Sadly, that's not an option.
The user is in a jail cell.
We can't get to him.
Anyway,
that thing won't be able to leave
the school building's shadow,
so let's head into the sunlight
while it's still available.
Then, before the sun goes down,
we'll lure it into the shadow
of something that can move,
and then we'll get rid of that shadow.
That way, we can drag it into the sunlight.
Got it!
I-It's gone!
I've got you!
Wh-What?!
You saw the lighter being relit, didn't you?
The crows!
It hid in the shadows of those crows
and moved over there in them!
Th-This thing...
It's useless!
Sh-Shit!
While in the shadows, its power
and speed are much higher!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
My Reverb Act 3's ability is to
make Stands or people heavier.
I've made its hands heavier,
so much that it won't be able
to lift a finger from the ground.
It should let go.
I made the entirety of its hands heavier!
It shouldn't be able to
bend its fingers anymore!
It's strong...
It's determined to not
let go, no matter what.
You have two possible paths...
I-It's no use!
Any damage inflicted upon the
Stand goes right back to the user!
At this rate, Giorno's
legs are going to break!
Act 3! Undo 3 Freeze...
No.
Don't do that, Koichi.
This ability that makes things heavier...
Don't you dare undo it.
This is perfect.
This is exactly the ability
that I was looking for!
But your leg's going to shatter!
Wh-What?
That tree...
Golden Wind is an ability
that continuously gives life,
so that tree continued to grow,
lived the extent of its life,
and is now starting to wither.
Ability?
But that tree's at least ten meters away...
So you got to the tree's
roots by digging that hole!
Bam
Y-You did it! The shadow's gone!
It's been dragged out into the daylight!
You told me there were two paths,
but sadly, you only have one.
Koichi, could you move
to the right a little?
Huh? Like this?
Hmm...
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Bask in the sunlight.
That's it.
That's your one possible path.
Still, I have to wonder
if I'm going to be able to join the gang now.
What to do...
Polpo
Shadow Sabbath
That arrow...
The fact that the Arrow
is also in Italy means
that there'll be even more victims!
I need to hurry up and tell Jotaro!
Wh-What are you doing?
Did you just say there'll be more?
We defeated Polpo's Stand,
which had the arrow.
You saw it for yourself.
Defeated? You've got this all wrong!
I'll admit that we managed to escape
its attacks because of you,
but that Stand only stopped
attacking because of the sunlight.
The user isn't hurt at all.
They're perfectly fine!
So Polpo's alive?
Not only that, but long-distance
remote-controlled Stands
basically don't affect their users at all.
He probably hasn't even realized
there's been a battle here.
What?
So he has no idea at all?
He doesn't know I'm a Stand user, either?
Chill out, would you?
If he noticed anything, it was probably
that his hand felt a bit heavier,
but he'd have no way of knowing
that you and I are Stand users.
Hey, could you move your finger?
Sorry, but I still can't
let you make your call.
I'm begging you...
This isn't just one enemy.
They're an organization.
If you tell someone,
the organization might find out.
Enemy?
Organization?
I'll tell you and only you, Koichi.
The Next Day
Someone gifted me a special-order pizza.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's see, you were...
Giorno... Giorno, uh...
Giorno Giovanna.
Ah, yes. Sorry about that.
My head goes blank when I eat.
Perhaps it's because all my
blood goes to my stomach.
This might sound sudden, but are
you a religious person, Giorno?
I'm not sure... but I'm not
very passionate about it.
What I'm about to say may
contradict God's teachings,
but I'd like you to listen carefully.
If the most important thing
in this world is trust,
the most despicable thing you
can do is insult someone.
Listen well... To insult
or betray someone's trust
not only hurts their reputation,
but puts them in a very sticky situation.
We will not fight others or risk
our lives over money, power,
or having our seats taken
at a theater or on the bus.
Fighting is truly foolish.
Only idiots bother with it.
But...
I will risk my life over being insulted.
I believe that God forgives even murder.
Don't forget that.
Congratulations! I will allow
you to enter the organization.
You did bring me the lighter still
lit, as I trusted you would.
You pass.
That's our Passione organization's badge.
It proves that you passed.
You'll be working under
Bucciarati for a while.
How about it? Why don't we celebrate your...
Did that brat actually protect
the flame for 24 hours?
Or did he relight it and
become a Stand user?
I couldn't care less about that.
Young, clueless guys like him are easy to use.
Either way, we can use him however we want.
Oh?
I could've sworn I closed that...
The blood does flow to my
stomach after I've eaten...
You met him again?
I'm sorry, Jotaro.
But I can't help thinking
that he, Giorno Giovanna, isn't as
dangerous as you think he might be.
What makes you think that?
Well...
Well, I'll tell you that in person.
Is that all right?
All right.
If that's what you want to do, that's fine.
I'll be waiting.
Thank you.
I'll talk to you later.
Jotaro, back then, I really did think...
Does this Giorno kid really admire that?
Is he sane?
But I can feel it...
I can feel that he has a righteous heart.
I can tell...
Because I observed three members of
the Joestar bloodline back in Morioh.
The three who exude righteousness from
their hearts, as if it were their life energy.
I could see the same thing in his eyes.
Without a doubt, the blood that flows in
his veins carries the will of the Joestars.
So I'm going to keep this to myself
for a while, like he asked...
The golden dream that Giorno
Giovanna possesses.
Well, then, maybe I'll
go do some sightseeing.
The Next Day
Come with me, Giorno Giovanna.
What was that noise?
Well, whatever.
When someone insults you,
even murder is forgivable?
I see. What you told me is very important.
You insulted that innocent old man's life.
So I changed one of your guns into a banana.
You should savor your
last meal as best you can.
So... Where are we going?
I'll introduce you to my team.
They're all Stand users.
Episodio 05
Find Polpo's Fortune!