It doesn't look like anyone's following us.
Bucciarati, are we not leaving Venice?
The boss has his own personal elite guards.
I'm sure they've already
learned of our betrayal.
They're probably... going to
be coming after us next.
But we don't know what kind
of abilities they have.
Correct. If we try to cross
the sea unprepared,
they might strike us there.
Let's wait and see for now.
Understood.
Mista!
We're hungry!
I'm starving!
Feed us!
Our guts are running on empty!
Calm the hell down!
I know this is really bad timing,
but could we stop by a
restaurant or something?
Well...
I guess we need to refill our guts, as well.
Episodio 22 The "G" in Guts
You guys have heard of vegetarians, right?
Are they allowed to eat, like, cheese?
Probably not.
I mean, milk and eggs come
from cows and chickens.
That means they probably can't have
cake that uses whipped cream, either.
What?! They can't have cake, either?
I wonder if their bodies actually
function better, then.
Then what do those guys do
about shoes or handbags?
Those are made from leather.
Well, if they're vegetarians
because they feel bad for animals,
they probably wear sneakers
and carry backpacks instead.
Man, they're intense.
So would you have old ladies dressing
like basketball players, then?
They'd never let them into a
restaurant looking like that.
Giorno, being all scared won't
make anything happen.
Let's just eat for now.
Yes, I know...
Still, we need to be on our guard.
For example, there's a possibility
someone could've poisoned our food.
Y-You bastard! What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Huh?
What are you gonna do about
this, you little shit?!
You think you can pay for this?!
This suit cost four million lire!
Let's take this outside!
Smash
You must be an enemy!
What?!
You an enemy?! Huh?!
Well, are you?!
You an enemy?! Take that! And that!
Hold it, Narancia, Mista.
I don't think this guy's an enemy.
He's unconscious.
He's totally just a random civilian.
What? Are you serious?
Crap! What am I gonna do?
Yeah, this stain's gonna
be hard to get out.
A single drop of wine on a
white suit really stands out.
I can't pay for this shit!
Well, the location of the stain
might make it look like a button.
If he puts a button there, he can hide it.
While we're at it, let's get him to make
sure there isn't any poison in our food.
That's a great idea!
Hey, that's enough.
More importantly...
What's going on with Bucciarati right now?
After that battle with the boss,
Bucciarati's heart definitely stopped.
And when he got hurt back there,
there wasn't a single drop of blood.
What about now?
But right now isn't the best time to find out.
I'll keep this secret to myself for now.
So, Bucciarati, what are
we going to do now?
The boss's Stand makes time disappear,
and the boss is the only one who
can move freely in that state.
He's invincible.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Anyone's attack becomes
useless before that Stand.
However...
That'll change once we find
out who the boss is!
Because if we find out the boss's identity,
we might be able to assassinate him.
And to do that, we need to find out
who he really is.
But how are we going to find him?
The boss is the type of guy who's
gotten rid of any trace of himself.
Trish.
There must be some kind
of hint involving Trish.
Everyone was after Trish, and the
boss was trying to eliminate Trish.
Right?
A-About that...
I don't really want to involve
Trish in this anymore...
Th-This feeling sucks.
Trish doesn't know anything!
If she finds out her actual father tried
to kill her, she'll be in shock.
Bucciarati, please!
Let's not talk about the boss's identity
and stuff like that in front of her.
There's no need for that, Narancia.
I've already known that... for a while.
T-Trish...
I remembered something when you said
he got rid of any trace of himself.
My mother had mentioned that
she met my father in Sardinia.
Sardinia...
When I was little, my mother told me
that they had met while she was vacationing,
and he told her he'd be right back...
But then he disappeared forever,
leaving nothing behind,
not even a photo or his name.
Before he became the
boss of the organization...
Fifteen years ago...
Then was he born and raised in...
I'm not sure about all that, but...
Sardinia. His past and true
identity should be in Sardinia.
Why are you telling us that?
We might end up killing your father!
No, we are determined to defeat him!
You defeating him or not isn't my problem.
But... I want to know!
I want to know who I came from!
I'm not about to die
before I find that out!
Hey, Narancia.
Looks like she's way stronger than you thought.
Fine.
Sardinia...
That's our next destination
after we escape from Venice.
That's where we'll find out
who the boss really is.
I was under the impression
that Trish was like me,
but I guess she'd already made up her mind.
I just followed on a whim,
so I still don't know
if there's any hope in this trip or not.
Huh?
An enemy! There's an enemy nearby!
There's a shark in my soup!
Li'l Bomber!
Giorno! Get Trish inside the turtle!
Abbacchio, cover the right!
Mista, guard the left!
Where, Narancia? Where are they?
Inside the soup!
They were somehow already in it!
Where are they now?
But they were there!
There was something like
a shark in my soup!
I don't see anything strange about it.
Does that mean we lost them?
Swoosh
Narancia!
What happened?!
Narancia! Were you attacked somewhere?
Where did they get you?
Narancia, what's wrong? What's there?!
I'm asking you what's wrong, Narancia!
Hold it, Mista.
I don't think Narancia can talk...
What? You can't talk?
What's wrong, Narancia?
What are you pointing at?
Water? You want a sip of water?
H-Hey! Th-This is bad! Look!
Narancia's tongue! It's gone!
On top of that, I don't
think he's breathing!
This isn't good.
I can use Golden Wind to
create parts for his tongue,
but it'll take time to finish.
Hey, come on! He's about to suffocate here!
Mista, do you have a pen?
A pen?! Y-Yeah, I have one...
Stab
Looks like he's breathing.
I'll give life to this pen to
create parts for his tongue.
That way, he can breathe
while I create his tongue.
I see...
So that's Giorno Giovanna.
Now I'm starting to understand the
information the boss gave us.
We're going to have to be the most
careful around that newbie kid.
Yeah... I'm a bit surprised
he saved Narancia.
I thought my Crush would
be enough for this job,
but apparently, I'm going to need your
help eliminating all five of them,
Tiziano.
As the boss's elite guards,
we're going to have to defeat him here.
Are you ready, Squalo?
All according to plan.
As long as we can lure them to
water, Crush is invincible.
Our plan will decide everything.
We'll take care of them
one at a time, Tiziano.
Yeah, Squalo...
We'll use Narancia.
Crush
Squalo
Are you all right, Narancia?
Yeah...
You guys saved me.
What did you see?
How did the enemy Stand attack?
It... c-came from the soup...
Narancia, don't force it.
I-I'm fine. I can talk.
Hey, Narancia, what's the enemy like?
Where'd he run off to?
He was...
He was like a pebble!
He was huge, and he ran into the restaurant!
Huh? Huge like a pebble?
But earlier, you were saying
it was in your soup!
You're contradicting yourself.
Huh? Did I just say that?
So, then... is the enemy about this big?
Nope.
Huh? No, wait!
Then, like, this big?
U-Um...
No? Then, like, this big?
Yup, exactly.
So something this big was in your soup,
and it went running into the restaurant?
Yup.
Huh? What?
We can't get a clear picture
of this enemy at all.
Does that mean it was really fast?
Nope! It was slow!
What?
Huh?!
If it was huge and slow,
why didn't we see it?
Did you actually see a Stand?
Of course I did... n—
You keep contradicting yourself!
You're not trying to act tough
because the enemy got you, are you?
I... I...
Answer me, damn it!
You didn't actually see anything, did you?
Of course I did...
not...
So you didn't actually
see anything, after all!
This is no time to screw around!
There's no one suspicious nearby.
Apparently, it's a remote-controlled Stand.
That must mean that the user
is watching us from somewhere.
In that case, we should
leave here immediately.
Let's follow the channel out to the sea.
Yeah, Giorno!
Let's do it! Let's use the channel!
Yes, Narancia. That's what I just...
Narancia?
Narancia, why do you keep
covering your mouth?
Let me see it.
What the hell? It's completely normal.
Yup! I'm totally fine!
There's no problem at all, Mista!
So, what are we going to do, Bucciarati?
Are we going out to sea?
No. Let's not follow the channel just yet.
This is our chance.
We're going to use it to defeat that enemy!
The boss wasn't expecting our betrayal,
which means there probably aren't that
many members of his elite guard here.
If we defeat him now,
I'm sure we'll be able to get through
the seas of Venice just fine.
I see. You have a point. I agree.
Yeah, I agree.
Very well, Bucciarati.
If you say so.
Abbacchio, could you use your
Moody Jazz to replay what happened?
Yeah, sure.
Where do you want to start?
From when the soup was still on the table?
Yeah.
What the hell, Narancia?
Guys! The enemy's right over there!
Over there? You mean inside
the restaurant's bathroom?
Narancia, you damn well better
have seen something this time!
Yup, I did!
After them. We'll settle things
with this enemy here and now.
Come on, Giorno. Let's go.
Right...
Well done, Narancia.
None of his friends realize
that there's another Stand
besides Crush, which travels
from liquid to liquid.
Yes, they don't realize that my Stand,
Talking Mouth, is attached to
your tongue and making you say
the exact opposite of what you mean.
All right, I'm gonna go kill
the rest of them. Grazie.
Schwing
S-So that's what was going on! Damn it!
They were using me to get everyone
near the water, one by one.
How dare you underestimate me?!
I don't sense anyone here...
Let's at least figure out
what the enemy looks like.
Moody Jazz!
Transform into whoever was in here a
few dozen seconds ago, and pursue them!
Narancia!
Seeing who the enemy is
through Moody Jazz is fine,
but don't pursue them!
If it gets into water,
they don't stand a chance!
In that case, I'll do everything I
can to keep them away from water!
Over here...
Moody Jazz is transforming.
Water's bad news! Don't look in there!
Look at me! Look in here!
What the hell? That's disgusting!
Come over here, Abbacchio!
Look in here!
What are you talking about?
Have you turned into some kind of pervert?
We're trying to investigate because
you said you saw the enemy in here!
Did you really see them in here?
Of course, I—
Seriously, what is your problem?
Bucciarati, there's a chance Narancia
was just seeing things in here.
We might be better off looking at
the table if we want to pursue them.
Yeah.
Cut the crap, Narancia!
I'm not gonna let you take us all down!
Narancia, what happened to your finger?
Did you snag it somewhere?
Here, I'll stop the bleeding.
That bastard's going to try
to use my blood to move.
N-No! S-Stay back, Giorno!
Yeah! Fix me right up, Giorno!
There's definitely something strange.
Is something wrong with
the inside of your mouth?
They attacked your tongue earlier.
Does that have anything to do with it?
Great job, Giorno! You're so intuitive.
Just a little more...
Just a little more,
and Giorno will figure it out.
But you're bleeding really badly.
First, let's take care of that wound.
Now, let me see it.
No! You can't touch the blood!
Come on, Narancia.
This is bad! Stay back!
Hurry!
Li'l Bomber!
Damn it...
Narancia,
you seem to be under attack by something,
but there must be some reason
you can't tell us the truth.
Yes! He figured it out!
Was there something left in your
mouth from the first attack?
Like, an ability that makes you say
the opposite of what you mean?
Yes! That's it, Giorno!
Sh-Shit! There's water from the pipe!
Giorno!
Episodio 23
Crush and Talking Mouth