Any luck?
Try checking Interpol or even
the Sardinian police records.
Do these fingerprints match any records?
It's no use. There are no hits.
Even if the boss had a previous record,
odds are he made sure it was erased.
But it has to be somewhere...
That's why he tried to eliminate
his own daughter and fears letting
anyone know what he looks like.
Why don't we look through
the records of the dead?
The boss might've faked his own death.
Let's give it a shot.
We can't let him get away with this.
A moment ago, just for a little while,
I felt the same thing I felt in Venice.
The one who got close to Abbacchio was...
my father.
This man finished Abbacchio
with his own hands.
Are you saying that the boss is here, Trish?
Yes.
I don't know where he is
right now, but he's nearby.
Bucciarati!
Not right now!
If we don't find out the
boss's identity for sure
and kill him, we're going to lose.
We have to track down his identity first!
No hits.
It's no use... The boss is meticulous.
It's impossible to track
him down any farther...
That's not true!
You have already tracked him down.
What?
All that's left now is to
find a way to defeat him.
Episodio 29 Get to the Roman Colosseum!
I've been waiting so long
for people like you, who'd do everything
they could to track this man down!
Screech
Someone tracked us down instead!
Giorno, cut the connection, quick!
Wait! Don't cut me off!
I'm on your side!
You want to defeat Diavolo, don't you?
Diavolo?
Please believe me.
I knew deep in my heart that someone who
wanted to defeat Diavolo
would eventually show up.
That's why I always kept this line open.
I've been waiting for so long...
I waited for years, filled with hope.
I'm on your side!
I don't know about that.
Diavolo?
Just because you said that name
doesn't guarantee that you're on our side.
Giorno, cut the connection.
His Stand is able to skip through time!
Did you know that?
Though I'm sure that
you're in a hurry to find out
who he is because you know that.
He's on our side...
This guy's on our side.
No underling of my father's could've
survived knowing his Stand ability.
Be quiet, Trish.
We can't reveal more
about ourselves just yet.
All right. Let's hear what you have to say.
First, tell us your name.
My name doesn't matter.
My body is already in a state
that prevents me from fighting.
What's important is whether or not
you are actually able to defeat him.
His ability to erase time has no weaknesses.
I'm sure you're planning
to assassinate him,
but you are certain to fail!
Are you saying you know of
a way to defeat the boss?
His Emperor Crimson is invincible!
But I do know of a slight
possibility to defeat him.
It's just a possibility, though.
You will have to obtain that possibility.
Obtain it?
Come to me. Come to Rome!
If you do that, I can give
you this possibility!
Do you really think we'll go to you?
We don't even know if we can trust you.
I'm sure at least some of
you know what this is.
Screech
That's...
the arrow!
At least, it looks just like it!
Why do you have that?
I'll tell you that later.
You must come to my
location to retrieve this.
He doesn't know the true
way to use this arrow.
This arrow doesn't just awaken
Stand abilities in people.
There is hidden wisdom within it.
I will tell you what it is.
Come to Rome.
This arrow will defeat him.
It is your last and only hope!
Bring, ring, ring, ring, ring...
Hey, you there!
What the heck do you think you're
doing, answering my phone?!
That call's for me!
Give it here! You stupid brat!
Hello? Yes, this is Doppio!
It's strange, Doppio.
What is, Boss?
Bucciarati and his crew.
They've lost Abbacchio, so they should
be at a loss as to what to do now.
But that's not the case.
They've fled with no hesitation whatsoever.
They're on that boat with a goal in mind.
Look into it.
Return to Abbacchio's last
location and look around.
Something's not right.
Look around?
But what am I supposed to look for?
Fear is born
from an unexpected past.
This is what I've been fearing
ever since I found out that I had a daughter.
There's nothing suspicious, boss.
The statue's been destroyed, but that it.
I know it. I can tell.
Those traitors... There's no doubt about it.
They figured something out
that I don't know about.
They figured something out?
What could it be?
They didn't have that kind of time.
It's something that I'd never expect!
That's enough, Doppio.
Go after them immediately.
You have to track them down yourself.
Yes, sir!
Also...
Cioccolata and Secco...
Have them stop Bucciarati and his crew.
I didn't want to ask for help from such
filth, but I have no other choice.
This is the last time.
Listen well, Doppio.
One must destroy their fear.
The moment is now.
We must get through this
right now, no matter what.
That is what it means to be alive.
Who the heck is this guy
waiting for us in Rome?
Can we really trust him?
Who knows? But Bucciarati
decided we're going.
What other options do we have?
Let me tell you a little
story from the past.
In Greenland, there's a place called
Cape York where only Inuit people live.
It's famous for having a crater
created by a meteorite.
It's said to have fallen tens
of thousands of years ago.
In 1978...
Two men from a team that was surveying
for natural resources within the crater
contracted an unknown illness.
They both ended up with blisters
all over their bodies,
and eventually, they died
looking like tomato sauce.
On top of that, one of them suddenly shot
a jolt like a stun gun from his finger
and accidentally burned a few
fingers off the doctor treating him.
In later investigations,
it was discovered that a virus,
which was tens of thousands of
years old, had been trapped
within the meteorite inside the crater.
That virus may have flown
here on the meteorite.
A virus?
What about it?
I tracked it down!
This arrow is made from the same material
as the meteorite found in Cape York!
Centuries ago, a man who craved
absolute power like that of the gods
found out about this rock and created
arrows from it. This is one of them.
This killer virus culls lifeforms.
This is a theory called "viral evolution."
Most people who contract this virus will die,
but some possess something
that lets them survive.
And as if it were rewarding them,
the virus gives them a new life ability.
This has already been proven,
with your own bodies.
So that's what Stands are...
That is the root and
principle of that arrow.
I see. I understand that now.
But what's this secret way of using the arrow
that we're supposed to retrieve?
I can't tell you that until
you come see me in Rome.
On top of that, I can only
tell one of you what it is.
Because no one else can ever find
out about this secret power.
But once you find out that method,
I guarantee that it will take
you to another dimension.
It is the only way to
defeat Emperor Crimson.
There's no guarantee that
your story is true.
But if the boss hears about this,
he's definitely going to eliminate you.
I'll trust you.
How do you want to meet?
Come to the Colosseum in Rome.
Once you get there, you'll know.
It doesn't matter what time.
I'll be waiting.
Everything will be revealed there.
Come on! Get up, damn it!
Shut up! I'm gonna take a piss!
Seriously!
I'm gonna do it!
This isn't the damn bathroom!
There's no toilet here!
This is it, right here.
Damn, that feels good!
I'm gonna do it!
Let's go up on land once those drunks leave.
Then we'll acquire a car immediately.
From there, we'll be in Rome
within 45 minutes.
All right, got it.
Perfect timing.
The moon's hidden behind the clouds, too.
Look, Mista.
There are some drunks
sleeping over there, too.
Damn it! Was there some
kind of party tonight or what?
Come on! You're gonna get in trouble.
Come here!
Let go of me!
I said I'm gonna do it,
so I'm gonna do it, damn it!
You can't! This isn't a bathroom!
See? It's right here.
Hey.
How the hell am I supposed
to reach like this?
How am I supposed to open my fly?
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Don't touch me!
Splash
What'is going on?!
That's a Stand attack!
What?!
They were waiting for us!
There's an enemy here!
Listen well, Secco.
The thing you have to worry about
most is running out of battery.
Finding out later that it didn't record
pisses me off more than anything else.
You sure it's recording?
Excellent.
Eulogy Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
You are able to see what happens in the future
as though you're watching footage on a TV. You
are also able to see beyond the time that's been
erased, and the future seen in the footage is
never wrong.
Eulogy
Predicts the future a few dozen seconds ahead.
You are able to see what happens in the future
as though you're watching footage on a TV. You
are also able to see beyond the time that's been
erased, and the future seen in the footage is
never wrong.
Cioccolata, 34 years old. A former doctor.
About two years ago, he let a
patient die due to a simple mistake.
Once he was laid off from the
hospital, Passione took him in.
He could be considered a failed elite,
but the boss found out his true nature
after he became a Stand user.
It wasn't malpractice.
He had killed patients on purpose.
He diagnosed countless people
who were perfectly healthy
as being sick and operated on them.
He'd reduce the anesthesia so the patients
would wake up during surgery, as well.
Ever since he was a young boy,
he had always gotten top grades.
When he was fourteen, he volunteered
to take care of the elderly.
However, in reality, he was administering
unknown drugs to the
elderly people he looked after.
Also...
Your family hates you.
No one's going to come visit you.
He would say things like that every day,
driving people to suicide.
On his bookshelf at home,
he had 25 video tapes of the
expressions the elderly made
when he told them those things.
After driving nine elders to suicide,
he decided he'd become a doctor.
The thing that Cioccolata loved
most was to observe people dying.
The reason he became a doctor was so
he could observe people's pain and death.
While watching someone die,
he felt superior to the rest of humanity,
and felt as though he truly understood
the psychology of the human race.
Cioccolata's one and only partner was Secco.
The only thing known about him is that
he's Cioccolata's former patient.
For some reason, they got along,
and Secco only follows Cioccolata's orders.
Even among the various Stand
users that exist within Passione,
this duo stands out as a pair of monsters.
That's who Cioccolata and Secco are.
It appears that their
destination is Rome, boss.
I just received word that they
arrived at a local fishing village.
Listen well, Doppio.
Have Cioccolata stop and eliminate
Bucciarati and his crew.
But... you must catch up to
those two, no matter what.
Those two... yes.
It's rare that I ever feel repulsed by others,
but Cioccolata is the worst piece
of shit on the face of the earth.
He'll probably make a mess
of Rome before he's done.
So you think he'll go berserk?
That's why you're going to
catch up to them, Doppio.
You must take control in the end.
You must not let those two
find out what Trish knows,
nor what Bucciarati and his crew
are looking for in Rome.
You're the only one I can trust.
Do you understand? You're number one.
I understand, boss.
That is what I live for.
Sorry, was that call too long?
Thank you very much, little girl.
Um, hewwo?
What the hell is that, Mista?!
When did that get on you?
Rumble
I have no idea!
Just hurry and find the user, Narancia!
Find out where the enemy is!
Li'l Bomber!
This isn't good! There are a ton
of civilians already down!
The enemy's range is basically
the whole village!
They actually involved innocent people in this?
This is going to make
looking for the user...
Damn it! I can't tell them apart!
Explain the situation, Mista!
My hand just suddenly bubbled up.
I have no idea when this shit got on me.
It's almost like mold...
It's making my skin rip open...
It looks like it's coming out
from underneath my skin!
The same thing came out of the villagers,
and their bodies have fallen apart!
Th-This isn't good, Bucciarati!
We can't go up on shore.
There's no way we'll make it up
the stairs to the parking lot.
We're better off getting away
from the shore on the boat for now.
Are there any signs of
breathing on the shore?
There's no one on the shore!
Wait, Bucciarati!
Until we know what attacked,
it's too dangerous to move.
I know that if we go up on shore, we're gonna
be attacked by whatever this thing is!
Giorno!
Fwoosh!!
It's on me?!
This is...
Wh-Where the hell is it attacking from?!
M-Mista!
Grab on to me!
Mista! Don't stretch out your hand!
This Stand has something like a switch
that gives it the chance to attack!
Chance to attack?
What does that mean?
As soon as I lowered my hand,
the attack began!
Come to think of it,
it first bubbled up on my hand
after I reached into my boot to get my gun.
That drunk jumped down from
the stairs and got attacked.
Splash
The other one had gone down the stairs...
And Narancia had jumped down into the boat.
Fwoosh!!
Menacing
So the attack begins when our
bodies move down to a lower location?
B-But...
Menacing
Guuush
At this rate, you guys will be...
He's not going down.
He's not boarding the boat
to save the other one.
I guess he's already figured out...
exactly how...
my Green Tea works.
Mold...
I've read about this before...
There's a particular type of mold
that inhabits the inside of a bug.
When that bug moves to a lower location,
it propagates inside it and kills it.
Entomopathogenic fungus
and caterpillar fungus.
This is very similar to that!
If you move to a lower location from where
you originally were, it reacts and attacks!
This is a Stand!
Why in the world would it work like that?
To expand the Stand's range even further!
Just as the mold spreads
from within the dead bug,
the corpses produce more corpses.
If the people move a bit further before dying,
the mold's range just keeps growing.
That's exactly what they want.
Because the Stand ability is
the user's unconscious will.
Climb up, Narancia!
Get off the boat and back on shore!
Mista!
Hurry up! Move forward more!
My foot!
Throw the turtle, Narancia!
Throw it toward Mista!
Plop
Okay, Narancia.
That's perfect. That spot's just fine!
Bang
You and the turtle are in
the absolute perfect spot!
Booom
Yee-haw!
Well done, Mista!
As long as we move upward,
their attack won't begin.
They made it back up.
All of those bastards made it back onto the
shore without a single one of them dying.
Interesting.
Good. Excellent.
Episodio 30
Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 1