All we need is someone to head to the
island first and get rid of the guy.
It's perfect for situations like this.
I'll be going, too.
Mista! He's already on the radio!
Shoot!
Bazoo
Damn it! This isn't good!
It'll be bad news if this
truck gets away right now.
Episode 08 Six Bullets Appears, Part 2
Guido Mista's way of life ever since
he was little was to live
it as simply as possible.
He loved to sleep and found
joy in looking at branches
in the morning sun,
watching the clouds go by,
the scent of wine,
and having a bite of cheese.
Whenever he spotted cute girls,
he would talk to them,
even if they shot him down.
If he ran out of money,
he would jump any jerk
badmouthing movie stars
in front of the cinema and take their money.
At times, he'd get his ass whooped so
badly that the police had to intervene,
but Mista lived a very
happy life nonetheless.
Being simpleminded could
be taken as an insult,
but Mista always felt that
overthinking things invited fear
into one's heart, which was bad.
When Mista turned 17,
he learned from a certain incident
that people have pre-determined destinies.
When they're young,
people may find themselves
at a standstill or taking the
long way around at times,
but they ultimately end up traveling
the path they were destined to walk.
On a clear summer night, Mista was
wandering around like he usually did.
Mista!
Hey, wanna go have some fun?
Sorry, we have plans.
Ciao!
Sure.
No! Let go of me!
Shut your mouth!
There's no point in resisting!
Shut up! Quit your screaming!
The woman being punched in
the parked car was half-naked.
She was bleeding from her nose and
mouth, and about to lose consciousness.
For a moment, Mista hesitated
to get involved, but...
Y-You bastard!
Because he's so simpleminded,
his body acted on its own.
You bastard! What do you think
you're doing to our bro?!
You little shit!
No matter how close you may be,
there is no guarantee
you'll hit your target just
because you pulled the trigger.
When you're panicked or in a hurry,
you end up pulling the trigger even
if your gun isn't facing your target.
Both of the shots the hooligan fired
went under Mista's arm and
disappeared into the darkness.
The hell?!
S-Stay back! You hear me?!
Three, four, five, six shots!
Unbelievably, they all
faded into the darkness.
Then his panicked friends started shooting.
At this point, this is
nothing short of a miracle,
but not a single shot hit Mista.
Meanwhile, Mista was astonished at his
own state of quiet concentration.
What the hell's going on?
Wh-Who is this guy?!
Bro!
Wh-What are you—
After stealing one of the
guns and some bullets,
Mista calmly loaded the cylinder,
and pulled the trigger as calmly
as a nurse inserting a shot
into a patient's arm.
He pointed the gun at their faces
and shot four perfect shots.
Of course, this was his
first time killing someone,
but he didn't hesitate or feel any remorse.
In a helpless situation, Mista made the
decision to cut through the shadows.
Eat lead!
The driver of the truck must be its owner,
because...
his right leg isn't injured.
I wasn't planning to kill you, but...
O-Ow!
Damn it! You shot me twice,
you piece of shit!
Quit moving! I'm going to aim
properly this time, damn it!
How could I say something so lame?!
That's not what I meant!
I was supposed to ask how
that bastard didn't die
after I shot him in the head!
Did the bullet just happen
to miss his brain?
That was so charming of you, Mista.
Your name is Mista, isn't it?
I heard that you have even
more friends on Capri,
but you're the only one who's seen my face.
Isn't that right, Mista?
After that little trap you
set for me with the radio,
I wound up getting shot twice
in that surprise attack,
but if I face you head-on
with my Stand, Arts & Crafts,
I can easily deflect a bullet
from a puny little pistol.
By the way, I was a bit too busy to count,
but how many bullets was that in all, huh?
You fired four on this truck...
And I'm pretty sure you fired two back
at the watchhouse in Marina Grande.
Right? I counted correctly, didn't I, Mista?
Now I can get close enough to beat
the shit out of you safely, right?
Shit. I need to reload!
Wh-What the?!
Y-You're kidding me!
My left hand won't let go!
Whoa!
Hey! How long are you gonna keep driving?!
Stop the damn truck, you dumbass!
Yeah... Someone stop it, please.
Someone stop this truck! This thing is...
Think about it for a sec.
Why was I nice enough to let you
know that you were out of bullets?
Did you think it was because I'm a nice guy?
Mista...
I only told you because I knew you
could no longer escape from this truck.
The driver also can't let
up on the gas pedal,
nor can he let go of the steering wheel.
I told you because you
won't be able to reload
with your left hand stuck to the truck.
Those are the bullets that the
bastard's Stand deflected.
They've stopped in mid-air,
like they're fixed in place
and moving in conjunction with the truck.
Fixed in place...
He must've used his ability to affix
the bullets into place mid-air,
and to affix the driver
and me onto this truck.
His ability is to fix something
he's touched into place.
The bullet I shot at him was also affixed to his skin at the opening of the wound
and hasn't actually penetrated his head.
That's why he hasn't died!
To tell you the truth, Mista,
I'm ecstatic that you attacked me.
So much that I'm willing to forget the
fact that you shot a bullet at my head.
I mean, it was up in the air if Polpo's
fortune actually existed or not.
It's just a rumor among
some thugs, after all.
But the fact that you attacked me
means it actually exists!
I'm overflowing with hope
and motivation! All right!
I can passionately steal the ten billion
from that bastard Bucciarati!
I told you it would be easy for
my Stand to deflect your bullets!
Yee-haw!
Wh-What?! Another bullet
showed up from the shadows?
He fired two bullets in a single shot?
Is that Mista's Stand?
But...
I can still deflect it somewhat!
Hell yeah!
Well done, Six Bullets
Number 6 and Number 7!
And now that we've thrown you from the truck,
there's nothing more to worry about!
Ow! You shot me again, you bastard!
But... you're not getting away.
This is for ten billion!
You're not getting away!
There is a way to defeat him.
But he's strong... That's a fact.
Will I be able to do it?
Sale
Arts & Crafts
Blood...
A vehicle...
The enemy and Mista are in a car,
heading toward the top of the island.
Will I be able to catch up with them?
Either way, I need to find
a car to chase them in.
Four bullets?
What the hell's going on?
I only have four bullets!
Why do I only have four left? Seriously!
Mista, it's because you dropped some bullets!
You dropped them, dummy!
Four is unlucky.
Don't put all four in there.
It'll just be bad luck.
I-I can take my hands off the wheel!
Yes! My feet can move, too!
Now I can finally stop!
Don't you dare stop!
Huh? B-But you told me
to stop the truck earlier!
And what I'm saying right now is more
correct, at least when I'm talking to you.
Listen up. I want to go
back to Marina Grande.
My buddy's back at the marina.
There has to be another way back there.
I won't harm you. I'll even
thank you if you take me back.
Got it?!
That bastard stops the bullets at the surface
of his skin so they don't penetrate his body.
The ability to fix things in place...
How am I supposed to beat him?
If I can just shoot into his mouth...
The inside of his body should be defenseless.
He might actually die.
But I only have four bullets left.
Damn it, talk about unlucky!
Three would've been much better.
Now that I've seen his face and know who
he is, I don't need to do anything dangerous.
It'd be much safer to meet back
up with Giorno at the marina.
I have extra bullets with
the rest of my things, too.
Th-That bastard!
Impossible! He scaled the cliff already?!
Hey, stop the truck!
Huh? Now what?
Stop the truck, I said!
Hurry it up!
Th-That's the guy from earlier!
Mista...
There's no way in hell I'm going to
let you tell your buddies who I am!
I'm not letting you get away, Mista!
He can affix rocks in the
air, just like the bullets?
He climbed up here
like he was using a ladder?
Why the hell did you stop
the truck, you dumbass?!
Huh?
Drive!
Huh? Wait, what?
Full speed ahead!
You'll be sorry if you stop!
If you want to settle things
right here, right now...
Let's do this!
Driver, don't you dare stop the truck!
Just gotta tap it slightly with my finger...
Even if it's just slightly,
if I tap it over and over,
it'll just keep building up force
in the place where it's affixed.
I can't hit it too hard.
It'll throw off my aim, and my enemy will
figure out which way it's going to fly.
And then... I let it loose!
Bam
What?!
It came back to you, Mista.
Those three Stands of yours that you
just fired lost control and flew off.
Just a little at a time...
You just keep tapping it with
just a little bit of force.
Just like tapping an SOS in Morse code.
The aim's not perfect, so I can't use it
on things that move around too much,
but I can definitely use it on you right now!
Th-This really sucks...
Talk about bad luck.
Four is always the absolute worst for me.
Ever since I was a kid...
There are just some
misfortunes you can't see.
Still, other than that, it's a good number.
I only have one bullet left,
but this means the worst is over, right?
Now the number's one, damn it!
Number 5! Number 6! Group up!
We're all gonna group up on this last shot!
This is the the last of them,
so give it your all!
Yeah!
Stay put, Mista!
Don't you try to shoot me again, you dumbass!
Just look at this distance! No matter what
abilities your Stand uses on the bullets,
or how many you fire,
I clearly have the upper hand.
I have plenty of time to defend myself!
You've realized by now that it's impossible
to beat me, haven't you, Mista?
If I told you...
that I only have one bullet left in this chamber, would you believe me?
I'm telling you the truth.
I only have one bullet left.
If I shoot it and you somehow
manage to deflect it,
I'll be out of bullets.
You'll find out anyway, so I
might as well tell you now.
If I miss this last shot,
you'll see that I'm out of bullets!
Though messing up is hypothetical right now...
I'm definitely going to shoot you
with this one, final bullet!
What are you pointlessly
rambling on about, Mista?
It doesn't matter to me how
many bullets you have left.
Whether you fire a single bullet or
a hundred, you can't defeat me!
It's not pointless at all.
You're definitely going
to let your guard down
now that you know I only
have one bullet left.
This is pointless.
He's gonna use his Stand!
Leave it to me!
Let's go! We only have one target!
Give it your all!
You're aiming for the inside of my mouth.
Am I wrong?
He opened his mouth on his own!
He's not going to defend himself!
We'll just have to charge right in!
I knew it.
Ow!
I knew you were aiming there...
At the inside of my mouth!
That's what any normal person would think...
That I shouldn't be able to use my
ability to affix things inside my body.
It's a pain in the ass to guard myself,
so I opened my mouth for you!
Impossible...
He can even affix things inside his
mouth to guard against the bullet?
Damn... This really freakin' hurts!
But... it looks like you weren't lying
about that being your last bullet.
I see you're not shooting again.
You done now, Mista?
If you're finished...
The launching power on this baby...
is more than ready, Mista!
Take this! Release!
He really did let down his guard.
He let his guard down because
Mista was out of bullets!
We just wanted to get closer to him,
because the closer we get,
the better we can aim!
Wh-What?!
Wh-When did they—
Shit! They're too close!
Here we go, boys!
Aim!
Arts & Crafts! Defend!
The bullet split in two?!
It won't matter if he gets
one more clean hit on me,
but... he's not aiming for that, is he?
That's not good.
Don't tell me... he's aiming for that!
That's—
I aimed for the same wound.
If I shoot another round at the
one that's stopped in your head,
it's going to push it just enough
to dig further into your skull!
I mean, if you're invincible enough to
withstand that too, I'm sorta screwed, but...
We did it!
Yes!
Come on, Number 3.
I keep telling you to not
bully Number 5, jeez...
He's still somewhat alive,
even though he's got a bullet in his brain.
Guess your Stand really is invincible.
Bucciarati told me not to kill you, but...
Hey, we're going back!
Back to the marina!
What do you want?!
What the hell is with you guys?!
Damn it.
Who the hell do they think I am?
Telling me to stop, then go...
I'm not a freakin' taxi, you dumbasses!
How dare you threaten me?!
I'll let you off the hook for now,
but next time I'm gonna let you have it!
I'm terribly sorry, but I'm chasing someone.
Could you take me to the top
of the island in this truck?
Quit wasting time! I'm desperate here!
You're gonna drive! Got it?!
Y-Yes, sir...
Episodio 09
The First Mission from the Boss