All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 17: The Lovers, Part 2
You made a nice bridge, Jotaro.
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
Hey, Jotaro. My back itches.
Scratch it!
A little lower.
Lower...
Yeah, that's it.
Don't dig your nails in so much.
Mr. Joestar?
Hey, what's wrong?
I-It feels like someone's tickling my back...
I can't concentrate on my Stand like this!
Mr. Joestar!
Wh-When did all of these people show up?
Mr. Joestar, keep your voice down!
People are staring!
Everyone will think you're nuts!
I-I'm not yelling for the fun of it!
Oh, no!
Poor man...
Let's give him some change.
What is this?
It's not easy having an older relative like that.
You said it.
Kakyoin, go buy the TV.
Let's get out of this crowd.
R-Right.
Are you the owner?
Eh? Yes...
I'd like that TV.
I can't believe Kakyoin's
Hierophant and Polnareff's Chariot
have shrunk themselves
and entered Joestar's body.
They're trying to fight me?
I can see it!
I can see where they'll exit
the artery wall that leads to
the brain stem, and The Lovers.
Over here!
We only have minutes left before the flesh bud
eats through Mr. Joestar's brain!
Hurry, you two!
There we go.
All right!
Now, Mr. Joestar!
Hermit Purple!
Th-This is...
These tentacles are part the flesh bud!
We finally got to the brain stem,
but the flesh bud's already grown so much.
Damn it!
It's him!
L-Look!
He's using his scissor-like hands to
knead Mr. Joestar's brain cells
into a gooey mash, so he can
feed them to the flesh bud!
If we can't beat him and sever
all the flesh bud's roots quickly,
it'll grow big enough to eat through his brain!
All right! I'll cut them apart!
No, not cut... I'll grate them!
Like a daikon radish!
Swish! Swish! Swish!
You bastard!
Now's our chance!
Slash
We did it!
N-No, that wasn't enough!
That thing's pretty fast, Kakyoin.
But I've already seen through his moves.
If that's the best he can move,
he's no match for...
Polnareff!
Who are you talking to?
H-Huh?
Polnareff, that's not me.
And what you cut wasn't the Stand.
Its form is breaking apart.
Wh-What?!
I'm The Lovers!
Polnareff!
It was disguised!
It used the brain cells...
Mr. Joestar's brain cells!
He was using the mash of kneaded brain cells
to disguise himself as my Hierophant Green!
And what you defeated was merely
a dummy made of brain cells!
You were completely fooled, you idiots!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Shine those shoes right, Jotaro!
I'm in such a good mood right now!
I need you to shine my shoes until
they're as bright as I feel right now.
I want the sunny sky to
reflect right off of them.
If you want, you can use
your uniform to shine them.
Actually, why not lick them clean?
Hey! You bastard!
What are you writing?!
Punched in the gut
Hit with a rock
Stole my wallet
Stole my watch
Walked on, like a bridge, over a dirty river
I'm writing down everything you owe me.
Made me scratch his back
Made me shine his shoes
Kicked me
I'm going to make sure you pay it.
I can be forgetful, so I'm writing it all down.
Jotaro, you bastard...
Well, whatever. It won't matter in the end.
Whoa! Kakyoin, look!
Look at that dummy's head!
The one I just cut open!
Wh-What in the world...
He's splitting into two!
Listen up.
In this world, the one
who knows himself best wins!
In Aesop's fable,
the tortoise beats the hare,
because the tortoise knew his own
psyche and abilities better than anyone!
The same goes for me.
I know that I lack the power or speed necessary
to mortally wound either of you.
Everything begins
once you've acknowledged your own weaknesses!
Emerald Splash!
Did it work?
M-More dummies made out of brain cells...
They're multiplying!
B-But a person can only have
one Stand. Only one is real!
Wh-Where's the real one?!
Right here!
Emerald Splash!
So close! I was right next to that one.
The more we hit the wrong ones,
the more it multiplies!
No, no...
It's me...
It's me! It's me! It's me! It's me!
It's me, after all!
Polnareff, that's enough!
Withdraw your Stand.
I can't bear to watch you get hurt
for the sake of my brain.
Damn it!
I can't stand the thought
of leaving things like this.
Withdraw your Stand!
You're going to get killed!
Not to mention...
There's no more time...
Don't give up until the very end, Mr. Joestar!
I can't tell!
I can't tell the difference!
Which one is the real one?
Which one is the Stand?!
Which one is it?!
The weakest of all is also
the most, most,
most, most, most, most,
most, most terrifying of all!
Say, Jotaro. Take a look at this gold bracelet.
It would make a girl happy,
if you were to give her something like this.
Jotaro,
see that space in the glass?
Use your Stand to sneak through and steal it!
I told you to steal it, you dumbass!
Hurry it up!
Or...
I don't mind breaking the glass and taking it myself.
Are you okay with them catching me
and beating the shit out of me?
Joseph would definitely die from the pain.
Hurry up!
The salesman's looking the other way!
This guy's shoplifting!
You bastard...
The Lovers
Dan of Steel
This guy's shoplifting!
Hey, salesman!
Sir! Please don't let him get away!
Sure!
You bastard...
What? A thief?
Who is it?
That guy?
That Asian kid?
Back where I come from,
they chop a thief's fingers off!
Hey, Jotaro.
You better not use your Stand against civilians.
Bastard!
Take this!
Despicable!
You thief!
Get out of our country, asshole!
We'll let you go at that.
You can keep your fingers!
That was great! Well done!
Because of the commotion you caused,
I was able to get my hands
on something even better!
Jotaro!
What the hell are you laughing about?
What's so funny?
I'm laughing in anticipation
of the fun that's to come.
I'm laughing because I have much more
to look forward to now, and I'm excited!
I'm so excited for the moment
when I get to pay you back.
Why, you...!
You seem to misunderstand.
Old Man Joestar will die within seconds.
That's the reality you're facing.
Nah. You don't know us very well.
You don't know Kakyoin.
What?!
"Everything begins once you've
acknowledged your own weaknesses," eh?
I see...
I'd have to agree with that.
To know yourself is an important lesson...
But you clearly don't know
your enemies well enough.
You haven't done your research.
Didn't you realize?
My Hierophant...
can spread its roots along the ground,
so I can inspect every single one of you!
Something's suddenly touching me!
You're the Stand!
Emerald Splash!
Bang
We did it!
Well, well, well, well...
That injury means that
Kakyoin's on the attack now.
I wonder if I'll still have my chance
at payback once he's done.
He's realized he's out of his league!
He's trying to escape into the artery!
He's trying to escape!
He's trying to get out of Mr. Joestar's brain!
Huh? He's leaving?
All right! That's great!
Mr. Joestar, hurry! The flesh bud!
Right!
Over Drive!
The flesh bud is disappearing!
I-I'm saved...
Now we can be more
buddy-buddy with Mr. Joestar.
Polnareff, you know...
Oh! B-But wait...
If it's leaving my brain,
that means the Stand...
...is going back to its user, Dan of Steel!
That's not good! Jotaro doesn't know that!
What's wrong? Why are you stepping back?
You're not going to tell me about
what's happening to my grandfather?
Hey, hey, hey...
What are you so panicked about?
Where are you trying to go?
You aren't trying to run away, are you?
Not after all this...
Please forgive me, Jotaro, sir!
I admit defeat!
I'll change! I'll lie on the ground and lick your boots!
I did an awful thing!
You can hit me as much as
you'd like! Hit me! Kick me!
But please, spare my life!
Lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick...
Soon...
The Lovers will soon be back!
This idiot, Jotaro, doesn't have a clue!
This time I'll invade your brain from your ear!
Kakyoin's several hundred
meters away. Just you wait!
I'll give you pain that will make
you wish you were dead!
I-It's here!
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
Now! Go in!
I figured you were planning something like this.
Don't you know that my Stand, Star Platinum,
possesses excellent
eyesight and precise reflexes?
Are you sure you did your research on us?
I-I-I'm not planning anything!
Your Stand's power...
"Your" Stand? Just "your"?
N-No! I-I meant your majesty's
Stand is more powerful
and more just than any other!
I didn't stand a chance, so it came back!
P-Please look!
That attack broke my arm and my leg!
I can't fight anymore! I can't move!
Well...
As for what you owe me...
I guess I'll take your
arm and leg as payment.
Do you swear that you'll
never appear before us again?
I-I do! I swear!
I'll go to some deserted island!
I'll go to the ends of the Earth
and never come back!
You're not lying, are you?
The next time I see you,
I'll punch you one thousand times.
I'm not lying! I'd never lie!
Get out of here.
Let's play soccer over there!
But then I can't play!
Jotaro!
You fool!
Take a look at that girl over there!
My Stand, The Lovers,
just went into that girl's ear.
He's heading for her brain.
Don't you dare move, Jotaro!
I'm going to stab you in
the back with this knife!
I'll make sure you never move again!
Just try to attack me
with your Star Platinum!
That girl will surely die!
You would never kill such
a young child, would you?
Good grief. Fine, try it.
Hey! Don't you understand?!
I told you not to—
—move? Move...
Huh? Huh?!
What's the matter?
Weren't you going to stab me?
Like this?
M-My body won't move! Why?!
Wh-What's this thing wrapped around me?!
So you didn't notice?
Kakyoin tied Hierophant's tentacle
to your Stand's leg as it escaped.
You must be totally oblivious
if you didn't realize that
you left a trail all the way to here.
Please forgive me!
Ask for forgiveness from Enyaba,
the woman you killed.
We never had any intention of
forgiving you in the first place.
D-DIO paid me in advance...
I-I'll give you that.
Good grief.
You truly are the lowest scum in history.
You can't pay back what you owe
with money.
Here's your receipt.
Jotaro Kujo
Next Episode Preview
I have this feeling like
someone is staring at us,
so I keep looking back.
Are you sure you're not just being paranoid?
I can't help but feel that presence, too.
I really can't shake the feeling
that someone's staring at us.
Something's strange. Something...
Episode 18
The Sun