That's... Giorno's brooch?
C-Could that brooch be...
forming his left hand?
Giorno's not out of the game yet!
If I can protect that left hand,
Narancia and Mista's wounds
can also be healed!
B-But how am I going to do that?!
Episodio 25 Spicy Lady
B-But if I scream
or move faster than that
brooch, I'll be killed first.
It's unfortunate for Giorno and the
others, but I can't do anything...
And I'll also be the one
attacked after the brooch.
I have to hide.
I have to use this opportunity
to hide in the closet...
This is...
the switch to make the seat recline.
If I push it, the seat will lean back.
That thing will probably attack
this seat before the brooch.
Th-Then I can grab the brooch
and head into the cockpit...
B-But I can't!
I can't make a wager like that!
It's far too dangerous.
I need to just hide in the closet...
What's wrong with me?!
Do I even realize what I'm doing?!
Unbelievable.
I didn't want to take the risk,
but I still pushed the button!
Now I just have to do it.
The path to the cockpit is wide open!
Move...
slowly...
Just like the tai chi that
the Chinese practice...
It's only about two meters to the brooch.
I can't rush.
If I rush, I'll die!
It's heading back this way!
Because it finished destroying the
seat... and it stopped reclining...
But there are more seats to recline.
Why did it... grab on to
my leg and not the seat?
L-Liquid?
It reacted to the speed of
these liquid drops falling?
B-But why are my boots wet?
All I did was push the reclining switch!
How did my boots get wet?
I knew it. I should've left the ladybug alone.
I should've just stayed out of this!
S-Save me, Bucciarati!
M-My boot just fell over next to my foot.
It's like it went through my foot...
Wait, what?
What just happened?
Now, pick up that brooch, Trish.
Wh-Who's there?
Is someone there?
I've always been here,
ever since you were little.
I've always been by your side.
Trish, please pick up that brooch.
That's the decision you've made.
You've already made up your mind
to protect Giorno's left hand.
Hesitation leads to weakness.
And... please, give me orders.
Wh-Who are you?
I am you.
I'm also the one who got the
thing off of your boot just now.
I am your ability.
Now, if you've made your
decision, please pick it up.
You and I are going to protect
Giorno's left hand!
Trish, if we're able to protect it,
we'll open up a new future
for Giorno and everyone else.
And your future, as well.
What's going on?!
Pick it up, Trish!
I'm finished!
How the heck am I supposed
to protect this thing?!
This is your ability.
I made the seat softer.
Wh-What just...
Made it softer?
I literally slipped right through the seat.
And it somehow damaged that thing.
The fleshy part of that thing ripped.
That thing managed to stop Mista's
bullets and catch up to this plane.
It has the ability to destroy
things that are fast.
But if it hits things that aren't
moving, it takes damage.
Are you... me?
Was I the one who just did this?
The thing with the boot, too. Was that—
What's important right now, Trish,
is that you picked up the brooch.
Your strong determination
overpowered any hesitation.
You are becoming stronger,
both mentally and as a person.
And you are able to make anything
in this world softer, more elastic.
Making things softer...
means they become harder
to break than diamonds!
I-It's coming again!
This time, stay still.
I'm starting to understand that
you're me, but I have to hide!
Make the closet door soft!
Please make it in time!
Damn it! Stay the hell away
until I close this door!
I-It managed to find me on the other side
of the door, even though I'm hiding!
I-I'm done for!
I'm starting to understand that I'm a
Stand user and have Stand abilities...
B-But...
This thing's invincible!
The user is already dead, too.
No one can defeat this thing!
Trish, I asked you not to move.
We have to head to the cockpit,
where Bucciarati is,
but we went in the opposite direction.
What are you talking about?
Giorno's brooch is developing
into his left hand and moving.
I had to run away!
But your ability...
All it does is make things softer!
It's taking all I have
to evade these attacks!
I-It's going to get me!
I-It attacked the clock again?
What?
I made the clock more elastic.
As long as you don't move faster than
the second hand on that clock,
it'll continue to respond to the second hand
and give priority to attacking
the clock over and over.
When I said not to move,
I just meant to move slowly.
Move slowly.
Slower than the second hand.
At super slow speed...
But with the strength of a vise.
We're going to rip this thing apart...
and kill it.
You bastard! Just go to hell already!
You piece of shit! Quit latching
on to this world, damn it!
It's falling apart into tiny
pieces and disintegrating!
This Stand that just kept pursuing
its targets, like a vengeful spirit,
is becoming so small and disappearing...
Y-Your name...
Do you have a name?
What should I call you?
Spicy Lady.
I see...
That's a fitting name.
Trish Una
Spicy Lady
Now Mista and Narancia's
wounds can be healed.
But Giorno Giovanna...
He is a strange person.
Not only is he able to give things life,
but his actions also helped you mature.
I'm going to go make sure
the engines are okay.
Bucciarati, I have some news to break to you...
The problem has already been solved.
Giorno has actually already...
Don't say another word!
I-I mean... Slowly...
Come here slowly, Trish.
Our altitude is 7,000 meters!
6,800...
6,600!
It's no use. It just keeps falling!
And I don't know why!
I figured out why we're falling, Abbacchio.
But what are we supposed to do?
What are we supposed to do about this?
Bucciarati, what are you—
I told you not to move!
D-Don't tell me...
Th-Th-That's... But that's impossible!
Giorno said that thing has
the ability to catch up
to things that move and take them in.
The engines on this plane...
Just now, that thing...
Trish, don't turn around.
Don't panic, no matter what.
Slowly walk this way.
Th-That's...
No! Th-That's impossible!
It's no use! We just keep falling!
At this rate, we're going to crash!
Actually, the engines are
likely to explode before that!
Th-That thing should've been torn
into pieces and disintegrated...
W-Wait, the engines are
right behind the closet.
Oh, no...
If even a tiny part of this thing
melded into the wall of the closet...
There's a possibility that it
took in the engine's energy.
And now...
We need to make an emergency
landing, Abbacchio.
The Tyrrhenian Sea is in front of us.
We need to make an emergency
landing on the water.
It's the only choice we have!
An emergency landing?
Even if we're able to land safely,
what are we supposed to do after that?
This thing will still come after us!
It's invincible. It's too powerful.
It's an invincible ability!
Now, slowly, Trish...
Slowly, like a slug. Don't panic.
Don't run, whatever you do!
If you rush, it'll attack you!
Wh-What the?!
What are you doing?!
It's going to catch up to you!
Yes, it certainly will!
If I do something as lame as moving slow,
it's going to catch up to me anyway!
Get in the cockpit, Bucciarati!
Have you lost your mind, Trish?!
It's going to destroy the door!
Th-The door...
Th-This is...
What the... Don't tell me you...
An emergency landing?
Bucciarati, we need to do the opposite.
If we all want to survive
and get to Sardinia safely,
we need to... destroy this plane!
Wannabe!
Spicy Lady!
T-Trish... This is...
When did you obtain Stand abilities?
Th-The walls and glass
are all soft like rubber.
If that thing is going to
prioritize speed in its attacks,
then crashing would be faster.
A plane crashing is way faster
than this parachute!
Yes! You stupid bastard!
We took pretty severe damage,
but now that the plane has crashed
into the waters near Sardinia,
that means the boss's men can't
confirm whether we're dead or alive.
Right?
The organization's lost track of us.
That means we've got some time now.
Time to track down the boss's
true identity and find him!
No, Abbacchio.
It appears that our damage is going to
grow just a bit... just a little bit more.
I'll get rid of that thing.
I have to use my zipper.
Wh-What?!
Don't tell me...
It's completely invincible.
There's no way to kill this thing.
We can only chase it out with
speed, just like Giorno did.
B-Bucciarati, you can't mean... D-Don't do it!
You're going to wrap that
thing onto your arm?!
Don't! Are you going to take
yourself out of this, too?!
No, Abbacchio.
No one else is going to get hurt.
Giorno's Golden Wind ability
is safe right here.
Wh-When did you...
Arrivederci.
"Goodbye."
Stand name: Notorious Chase.
Complete annihilation: impossible.
Forced to track the crashing
waves of the sea forever.
At times, it attacks ships that happen to
move faster than the waves and sinks them.
Eventually, these waters would be known
to local fishermen as the "Tyrrhenian Belly"
and considered ominous.
Now, let's lay low and find
out who the boss really is.
We're going to track down my father's past!
The private jet hijacked from
the Marco Polo International Airport
crash-landed in the Tyrrhenian Sea,
fifty kilometers northeast of Sardinia.
This mystery has yet to be solved.
No passengers were found on board.
I thought I'd made it disappear,
but one's past wraps itself around
one's true peace, never letting go.
Unbelievable. This is why blood
relations are so troublesome.
It wouldn't be concerning
if it involved a stranger,
but once blood relations are
involved, things become tricky.
But that's all it is.
It's just a blood relation.
If I can get rid of that,
I'll be able to remain
in the prime of my life.
Several days ago,
after Pericolo secured Trish,
the traitors who were after her scoured this
apartment that Trish and her mother lived in,
but none of them noticed.
Every morning of her life,
Trish awoke in this house...
And...
Every day, she looked at this picture
that her mother had lovingly put up.
But this date... There's no doubt about it.
It's fifteen years ago.
This portrait... Even I almost missed it.
To think that such a thing existed...
Their plane crashed... but they're alive.
I can feel it...
My daughter's Stand abilities have awakened.
I can also tell that she's alive
and heading to Sardinia.
And if it was Abbacchio's Moody
Jazz that was flying the plane,
that means he's also alive, at the very least.
I can't let Moody Jazz go
to the spot in this picture.
Trish might not realize it right now,
but she'll surely remember
the existence of this picture.
And if she goes to Sardinia, she'll figure out
that the person who took this portrait
of her mother when she was young
was me!
I can't let Moody Jazz's ability replay that!
I'll have to go there myself.
I have to do it myself.
I can't let any of my subordinates
attempt to handle this.
Oh, y-you were home.
I knocked, but...
I'm here to clean your room.
P-Pardon me, I'll come back later...
Huh?
Why was I here again?
O-Oh, right! To clean! I'm supposed to clean!
Now, time to get to work.
Episodio 26
A Little Story From the Past ~My Name Is Doppio~