Hamon will travel even better down here!
Underwater...
Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
Jo--
JoJo!
H-He did it!
It's not over!
I can't believe he outswam
Hamon traveling underwater!
He's like lightning.
My Overdrive only scraped his head.
It'll take a solid punch
to send Hamon directly into him!
Lord Dio!
I thank you for giving me life and
the supreme honor of fighting this man!
He is made of the stuff of heroes.
Now we fight without
the burden of water!
Now we face each other using skill,
technique and spirit alone!
Hold nothing back!
Show me everything you have!
Even as Dio's puppet,
he hasn't lost his pride!
But it has been twisted into
a love of violence!
Your blood will be one with my body!
Another hair attack?!
Bring it!
I'll give you a dose of Hamon!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 6: Tomorrow's Pluck
Overdrive Barrage!
JoJo!
T-This is bad. Hamon can only be
projected from the extremities!
He can't cut Blueford's hair
with his arms tied up like that!
I-I want to help him,
but we have our own problem!
Tarukus! H-He's gonna...
I-It's tearing through my clothes
and into my skin!
Struggling only makes it worse!
His hair is draining my blood!
Here's your coup de grace, pup!
I'll slice off your head
and bathe in a fountain of blood!
Try this instead!
Metal conducts Hamon, too!
Metal Silver Overdrive!
G-Good show!
He turned blocking the sword
into an attack using Hamon!
My heart resonates...
Heat enough to burn...
My blood's beat is razor-sharp!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
Yes! There's the sound
of flowing Hamon I'm so used to!
S-Something is different about Blueford.
Now that I know his past
and personality...
This is for the best.
He is a zombie
trying to spread his vile kind.
He has to be destroyed.
I am the Black Knight Blueford.
This pain is nothing to me!
You're a mess, Blueford!
I can't believe his bloodlust
still drives him in that state!
What?!
What are you doing, Jonathan?!
Dodge or counter!
Why aren't you moving?!
What in blazes?
What are they thinking?
You said this pain just now.
Pain.
You feel pain.
T-The flowers!
They're blooming at his feet.
Black Knight Blueford's body
is being ravaged by Hamon.
But pain has returned to him.
The pain of being human.
As Hamon destroys his zombie form,
it is restoring his noble human soul.
That's why I stopped fighting you.
And that's why you stopped your sword.
His face is no longer twisted
by rage and hatred!
He looks like a son
peacefully talking with his mother!
You believed I would stop my attack.
Your trust kept you
from counterattacking.
Is your faith in humans so strong?
This pain means I'm alive.
If I can feel pain,
I can feel joy as well.
This is humanity.
I am filled with an odd tranquility.
I feel no bitterness.
Here, at the end, I have met
a marvelous man of true compassion.
I shall now return to my queen.
Companion of a world 300 years
younger than mine,
tell me your name.
Jonathan Joestar.
Jonathan, I grant you the word engraved
into the sword given to me by my queen:
Luck.
And for your future, I grant you this:
Pluck!
Sir Blueford!
What irony.
What a twisted fate.
Why did I have to kill him
in order to save his soul?
He left the world with hate,
but he had a proud spirit.
His noble heart was bent
to terrible insanity!
The mask caused this!
And I'll stop Dio, the man behind it!
JoJo! Behind you!
Tarukus!
W-What the...?!
How could he heartlessly stomp the armor
of his dear deceased friend?!
Blueford, you spineless dog!
I admired him,
but cunning was his game...
...while I chose to be
a master of slaughter!
I crush, kill and destroy
using brute force alone!
Let me hear your anguished cries!
Nice catch, JoJo!
The cliff is crumbling!
These leaves...
JoJo!
Yes, sir!
Life Magnetism Overdrive!
Grab on, Speedwagon, Poco!
Humans create a weak magnetic field,
making them living magnets.
An Overdrive can increase
that field's power.
Sending the field into the leaves,
they created a magnetic sheet!
Amazing!
You have a lot of tricks!
Are you guys, uh, human?
Were you sent down from heaven?
I've been wondering that, myself!
I'm totally baffled!
And Baron Zeppeli,
you're the biggest mystery of all!
Where did you learn to do this?!
I came across a mysterious man
at a port town in India.
He was young and shabby-looking,
but called himself a doctor.
I was in for a shock.
He took a gangrenous limb
and healed it with light from his hands.
It was the power of Hamon.
I felt that Hamon might be the key
to fighting the evil stone mask.
So I traveled far up Tibet's Salween
River in search of the doctor's master.
His name was Tonpetty.
Stranger from a distant land,
I can see your future.
Is it your desire to train with me?
To do so would alter your fate.
You will be destined to die.
I accept that.
I have a purpose worth
risking my life for.
I can't share Tonpetty's prophecy
with anyone, even JoJo.
Y-You all right?
T-That sound.
Is that Hamon, too?
I-It's not!
It's Tarukus!
H-He's insane to leap in
to attack us from that height!
This glider is made of pure Hamon.
Touch it at your own peril.
What's that?!
T-The old knights' training ground!
Jump for it before
Tarukus knocks us down!
That lunatic!
He slammed straight into the wall!
That'll destroy even a zombie.
Unlike Dio, he can't regenerate,
so he should be finished.
H-He's a machine!
He lives only for fighting.
His bones should've been
powdered by that!
He's climbing up!
Our goal is to destroy Dio,
but he insists on getting in our way.
We will eliminate Tarukus here!
JoJo, take the boy
somewhere safe inside!
There's something strange
about this door.
C-Careful! These ruins
are where the knights trained to kill.
They say it's full of traps!
Jonathan! Something's coming!
- Oh, no!
- JoJo!
W-What is this?!
Tarukus!
The Lair of the Two-headed Dragon.
A chain death match after
300 years of boredom sounds perfect.
The Lair of the Two-headed Dragon,
an ancient sparring ground!
Home of the chain death match!
I killed 48 here.
You could call this sport my specialty.
S-Stop, Baron Zeppeli!
It's just too thick!
Y-Yikes!
He's ruined his hands!
U-Unfortunately Hamon cannot
be used for destruction.
Bricks I can handle, but not this door.
JoJo is the same.
He cannot break the chain holding him!
The key to the collar on your neck
is right here!
The doors can't be opened
from the outside during a match.
The key to my collar is on yours.
That means that taking the head
of your opponent...
...is the only way out of here!
Overdrive!
T-The chain is touching the ceiling
so Hamon won't flow into Tarukus!
My left humerus is cracked.
I can use Hamon energy to fix it.
But to do that,
I need to get this collar off!
I can't breathe!
JoJo!
D-Damn!
I wet my pants!
I-I have to get away from these guys!
They've brought disaster to my town!
Baron Zeppeli, that lever!
The door can be opened from the inside!
JoJo will fight on his own.
But his battle with Blueford
has left him weak.
I don't care how!
We have to find a way to join him!
I don't see any way in!
It's too small.
They could never fit through.
But...
...maybe I could.
Blast it!
We can't get the door open.
We'll have to use the cliff entrance
Tarukus used.
B-But that'll take too much time!
We've got no other option.
I'm always on the sidelines!
I'm powerless!
I can do nothing to help!
Look at me, Poco!
I said look at me!
Aww, he's scared!
He's quaking like a leaf!
Look! Look!
He's gonna cry!
U-Uh oh!
L-Let's get outta here!
S-Sis...
Taking it from those bullies again?
Come on, now.
Why don't you try standing up to them?
I-I'll fight them...tomorrow!
So when is tomorrow?
Um, tomorrow.
Poco...
What is the scariest thing to you?
Is it that sting you feel?
Is pain scary?
Don't you think growing up
being unable to do anything...
...would be scarier than pain?
I-I...
Relax, baby brother.
I'll do the laundry when we get home.
Poco!
A window!
Hey! Don't go in there, you fool!
Stop him! Tarukus would butcher a man
going in there, let alone a child!
Listen, kid! It's too dangerous!
Think what will happen
if those monsters win!
If that big JoJo guy dies,
they'll attack our town!
They'll attack Sis!
I have to be the one to protect Sis!
Sis! Tomorrow is now!
Stay back! It's not safe!
Keep out of this, brat!
Poco!
Pain isn't...
...what's scary.
I did it.
You did well, Poco.
Don't worry, you're not that hurt.
Now, Baron Zeppeli!
Go in there and crush him!
Baron?
You will be destined to die.
At last...
Is it time for the prophecy
to be fulfilled?
If it is fate, I will simply accept it.
Baron Zeppeli!
What did you just say?
Next episode
This is just too cruel!
You'll pay, Tarukus!
I'll stomp you!
JoJo, please, take up my torch!
Chapter 7: The Inheritor