Time, resume!
Stab
What?
Who are you?! How long have
you been standing there?!
Wait! Who are you?
What's that mark I can see on your neck?
Wh-What is this? What's going on?
Why did the arrow fall from my hands?
You! I told you to stop!
Show me... your... face...
Why am I sitting down?
He was on top of the wall
where Chariot melted...
Could it be... the arrow's...
M-Mista! Something's wrong...
Th-This feeling...
Everyone else is also...
What's going... on...
No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Eternal greatness exists only within myself.
Sing a song of sorrow in a world where time has vanished.
Episodio 34 The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 1
Wh-What? Did I fall asleep?
What... happened?
It's already dawn.
Yeah. I'm not sure why, but it seems like
we've been asleep for a few hours...
Wh-What is this?
Why are my hands all wet?
Is this blood?
Wh-Why?
Were we attacked?
Are you hurt anywhere, Giorno?!
Dash!
Giorno! Get behind the wall!
You're right out in the open!
If you're hurt, you need
to tend to your wounds!
I-Is Giorno hurt? I can't
seem to see him anywhere.
Hurry up and hide, Giorno!
Wh-Where the heck is he anyway?
I can't see him at all from where I am.
Could you tell me where he is, Trish?
If he's hurt, we need to go save him!
What the hell are you talking about?
Huh?
Nothing you're saying makes any sense.
Wha—
What the hell is this?!
H-Hey, what the hell is going on?!
Why do I have these things?!
N-No, wait! I'm missing something!
It's totally gone!
What I'm missing is way more important!
Hey, Giorno! What's up with
the blood on your hands?!
Where the hell are you looking?!
You! I'm talking to you!
Y-You're talking to me?
I mean, I was surprised earlier, but whatever
this blood is, I don't feel any pain.
It must be from when the mold attacked.
I had Giorno fix it for me, but the
wound hasn't completely closed,
so I think the blood is from my shoulder.
The mold's attack?
But you...
What... in the world...
happened?
Did I fall asleep?
I feel strange.
Rumble
Wh-What the...
Th-This face...
G-Giorno's body and my body...
No, wait. It's our souls, our minds.
Could it be that while we were sleeping,
Giorno and I, and Mista and Trish...
Each pair's minds have been swapped?!
Oh, no... I... I...
What's with this face?!
This body!
I stink!
My armpits...
smell so bad!
H-Hey, come on, Trish!
That's not the problem right now!
We were attacked by a Stand.
It's definitely not the
boss's Emperor Crimson,
Why me? No!
but our minds have been
swapped for some reason!
Damn it! Could it be another
one of the boss's elite guard?
No, Narancia.
The boss is already somewhere
near the Colosseum,
so I don't think he'd rely on
one of his subordinates.
Plus, Mista and Narancia mentioned an attack, but is that really what this is?
Our minds have been swapped,
but we're not hurt.
What could have...
H-Hey, Giorno.
No matter what happens,
I-I'm still older than you. Got it?
Oh, my gosh! I have hair
growing on my fingers!
And my nails are so gross and malformed!
And they have so much dirt under them!
I can't deal with this!
I knew it! That stinks, too!
Why? Why did I have to be Mista?!
H-How am I supposed to know?!
Probably because we fell
asleep near each other.
And is that really what you think about me?
Do I smell that bad?
Hey!
What the hell are you touching there?!
H-Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
I wasn't trying to touch it!
It's just itchy around the elastic...
Don't stick your fingers in my panties!
Okay, I got it...
If you spread your legs any
further, I'll kill you.
Okay, I get it! But you're wearing panties
to make your butt look firmer,
so everything's so tight and itchy!
You're even wearing a push-up bra.
Just so we're clear!
The next time you stick your hand
into my skirt, I'll kill you!
I'm going to
curse you to death!
Narancia!
Tch. Don't you get it? That's Giorno.
And so what, you're going to kill yourself?
Stop that!
Hey, guys...
I, um, have a question.
So, Bucciarati...
Um, so it's me and Giorno,
and Mista and Trish.
If we swapped minds with
whoever was closest to us,
then who did Bucciarati...
I've been watching him,
but he's not moving at all.
Is he okay?
Stay away from him, Narancia!
Huh?
There should be someone else
inside Bucciarati, too.
And we don't know who that is.
Is that what you're saying, Giorno?
It all comes down to what went down
at this Colosseum before we got here.
Who was near Bucciarati?
And what happened to the boss and the
man waiting for us at the Colosseum?
Narancia, scout the area with Li'l Bomber!
I've been trying... but...
Something's wrong. Li'l Bomber isn't...
M-My Stand ability...
Appear! Li'l Bomber!
It's no use! Li'l Bomber won't come out!
D-Don't tell me our Stands—
No, Narancia. That's not it.
Take a closer look.
Li'l Bomber!
I-It's so fast! It's so fast,
I couldn't even see it!
But what the hell?!
I don't know what's going on,
but I feel so refreshed!
I don't know what's going on, but...
...we're so full of energy!
My Stand is still with me,
but it seems to have powered up!
I destroyed six iron
railings in a single shot!
My mind is on point!
What in the world is this Stand ability
that can swap people's minds?
What's the purpose of this?
This Stand user...
As much as I don't want to
believe it, are they our enemy?
There's no one else nearby.
I can't tell if any of them are the boss.
Everyone around the Colosseum...
is fast asleep.
Even with my radar, I can't
really tell how far it reaches.
No, wait...
Some of them are moving just a little bit.
Some are even waking up!
Man, that was a great dream.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
I assaulted some female cop
and even handcuffed her.
Tweet, tweety tweet.
Arooo!
Waaah! Waaah!
So all the passersby got swapped, too?
Yeah, it looks that way.
There's confusion everywhere.
What a weird ability...
Hey, Giorno. What are you doing?
I should be able to sense a soul's
energy through the ground.
But I can't... Who is it?
Who did Bucciarati swap with?
Narancia... I mean, Giorno.
If you're thinking that the boss
and Bucciarati got swapped,
there's one thing that's clear.
That's not it.
That's definitely not the boss's soul.
If it were him, I would
be able to sense him.
But the strangest thing is that I'm
certain the boss isn't nearby, either.
The boss disappeared somewhere.
Bucciarati...
You're saying we won't know
about him until he wakes up?
Until then, we can't take
our eyes off of him.
It hurts...
Without question, the enemy is Diavolo.
Got it?!
I-It hurts...
But listen to me, Narancia... No...
Are you Giorno Giovanna?
Golden Wind!
No... I'm not speaking from inside the turtle.
It's me. I'm the one speaking.
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff.
I was the one who arranged to
meet you here at the Colosseum,
but Diavolo backed me into a corner,
and I could no longer fulfill my promise.
Who swapped with who
Mista                Trish
Giorno         Narancia
Bucciarati
Turtle         Polnareff
Who the hell is this guy? Who's "Polnareff"?
Let me just say this first...
I only did this because Diavolo
left me with no other choice.
This strange phenomenon that's
happening to all of you right now...
is a part of the arrow's power,
the arrow I was supposed to give you.
I'm desperately hanging on to my
soul... so I can tell you this.
The arrow?
So you're saying this was
caused by that arrow?
To be more precise, it's because my Stand,
Silver Chariot, took hold of the arrow.
My body is already dead upstairs.
The reason I was able to swap souls
with this turtle and survive is
because of that arrow.
There's definitely someone in the
hallway on the second floor.
There's a dead guy who's been
knocked out of his wheelchair!
It's only my body? Where's Diavolo?
Hey! If everything you're saying is true,
your Chariot can return
us to normal, too, right?
No... I currently don't have the power
to control Chariot or make it disappear.
I don't even know where it is right now.
Chariot has basically gone berserk.
Your own Stand went berserk?
How irresponsible can you—
No. More importantly,
what happened with the boss?
What happened to him?
Where is Diavolo right now?
I don't know.
Diavolo was right in front
of me, but he disappeared.
All of you, listen very carefully.
The arrow is not your enemy,
nor is it your friend!
What I'm about to explain to you is hope!
Such a trivial... trivial coincidence
happened two years ago.
After I was incapacitated by Diavolo,
I somehow managed to survive
and hid in a small farming village.
That's where the trivial thing occurred.
The arrow we had retrieved in Egypt fell
between the wall and some furniture.
It's truly an insignificant thing.
Normally, one would just stick their
arm back there and pick it up.
But for my body, it was an arduous task.
I thought about just leaving it there,
but I figured that Chariot
could get it for me.
That's when it happened.
Chariot hurt its finger on the arrow.
It was mere coincidence.
The arrow draws out Stands from
those who have potential.
But if it happens to pierce a Stand...
I don't know how old that arrow is,
but I'm starting to understand what the
person who created it was thinking.
There's more to the power of a Stand!
Something that goes far deeper!
Suddenly, the birds in the sky fell,
bugs hid beneath leaves,
and cattle laid on the ground.
And the farmers started
sleeping in the streets.
I felt a slight change, but a much
bigger change had taken over Chariot.
I had a bad feeling, so I immediately
took the arrow away from it...
before it could go berserk.
Everything went back to normal,
as if nothing had happened.
Then I realized that if someone who had
enough power were to use this arrow,
they would have the power to control
the minds of all living creatures!
But I currently don't have
that kind of power.
And that's why I waited...
for someone like you who was
searching for Diavolo's true identity.
Though, in the end,
Diavolo was able to outdo me.
So this controlling minds thing...
Do you mean the thing going on right now?
It's just swapping souls?
No.
Remember when I said that this
was just a part of its power?
I can't control it, so I wasn't able
to see its potential beyond that.
But it definitely exists!
Go retrieve the arrow!
Stop Chariot before the boss can,
and reclaim the arrow!
The only way to defeat Emperor Crimson
is for you to use the arrow
to its full potential!
So in order to take back the arrow,
you're telling us to kill Chariot.
Am I assuming too much?
That's fine.
Once you take the arrow,
Chariot will be destroyed regardless.
Besides, I've already been finished off.
There's one other unbelievable and
important thing that I need to tell you.
Are you the girl called Trish?
Yes, though I currently have hairy knuckles.
I see...
The boss is a duo.
There was a kid who was somehow able to
transform into you and trick Bucciarati.
Diavolo and this kid were like
a well-coordinated team.
What? B-But how?
But that's impossible.
The boss trusts no one. That's how he
kept his identity secret for so long.
I'm not sure what happened, either...
But there was definitely a mysterious kid.
If it wasn't for that kid, there's no way
I'd have let Diavolo get that close to me.
Two... So the boss is a duo?
What's...
Giorno! Something's moving!
Nine o'clock. Uno signal.
It's a person!
There's a person heading in
from the gate on the right!
H-He's...
That face!
The boss! No... Diavolo!
Narancia...
Get Li'l Bomber behind him—
Giorno, wait!
The left! Look to the left, in the shadows!
So there it is!
That's my Stand, which the arrow evolved...
Chariot Requiem!
He's—
Th-This isn't good!
Diavolo was looking for Chariot!
He's trying to get the arrow!
Giorno, wait!
Don't attack just yet!
That Stand!
It's Zipper Man!
Th-That's Bucciarati!
It's Bucciarati's...
soul!
Episodio 35
The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 2