Quick
Dial
Redial
Call
Function
Silent
Memo
Good morning.
This is Kosaku Kawajiri.
I realize this is selfish of me,
but I will be around fifteen
minutes late to the office.
Yes. I have to discipline
my unreasonable son.
Yes, sir. I realize this would sound
highly trivial to anyone else. Yes.
I am terribly sorry.
Yes, as soon as I'm done.
Yes, I'll head right to the office.
Yes.
Yes. If you'll excuse me, sir.
Curse that Kosaku Kawajiri
being so apologetic.
Did you want to climb the
corporate ladder that badly,
despite how anxious you were?
The reason Josuke went into that house
is because he knew he'd have the upper
hand in a close-quarters battle.
I will admit that's true.
It's best that I avoid close-quarters
combat with Shining Diamond.
If I can figure out just where Josuke is,
I can shoot an air bullet from here, but...
Hey, you.
What do you think you're
doing on this property?
What? Are you saying you're
not on this property?
Don't get nitpicky with me,
Mr. Goody Two-shoes.
Is this your house?
How long have you been watching?
Hey, I'm the one asking the questions here.
I live next door.
I was thinking about sleeping past noon
when I was woken up by some kind of noise.
You make me suspicious.
Rio, from next door, said her
underwear gets stolen all the time.
And since everyone's
gone around this time...
I'm envious...
Huh?
Of all the free time you seem to have.
Hey, are you running away?
Damn him... Going after Rio like that.
Pisses me off!
He was an underwear thief after all!
These panties...
Th-They're Rio's...
P-P-Pan...
Woohoo! I'm so lucky!
Diamond is Unbreakable
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 38   Shining D (Diamond) is Unbreakable, Part 2
I-It's no use! The phone line's been cut!
Okuyasu is dead...
I'm going to beat the crap out of
Yoshikage Kira with my Shining
Diamond and defeat him.
I'm going to end this within a few minutes.
Hayato, stay along the wall there
so that Kira can't see you.
Where is he...
going to enter from... is the question.
Huh?!
Wh-What?
J-Josuke!
It's an air bullet!
There's one heading toward you right now!
It's about the same size as earlier...
B-But that's impossible!
There's no way he can tell
where you are from outside!
How does he know?!
Great...
I know, Josuke Higashikata...
I know the exact distance.
Three meters until impact...
I... I can tell...
We can tell where the ball of air is.
Yes!
You'll be able to dodge it!
No matter how many come through,
you'll be able to dodge them... now...
What?
I-It's going after Josuke?
Yoshikage Kira knows where I am.
Where is he? How is he seeing me?
There were no windows in that room!
The curtains are all drawn, too!
There's no way he can see you from outside!
It's automatic! It must be
automatically chasing you!
No, that's not right.
The version of Deadly Queen that's
automatic goes after heat
and is called Heart Attack.
But... It's not going after
the lit cigarette there.
More importantly, if it was
automatically tracking me,
the air bullet wouldn't be
able to go through the wall,
and Yoshikage Kira plans to do the final
detonation himself to finish me off.
It's a mystery, but he knows exactly where I am!
It's getting faster!
Find Kira for me!
Find out how he's watching me!
I-I found him!
H-He's right outside the gate.
Two meters until impact...
He's outside?
I can't figure out how he's able to
pinpoint your location from there, Josuke.
Hurry and run!
That bastard! I don't know
how he's watching me...
One more meter!
But I didn't want you chasing
me in the first place!
Shining Diamond!
All right, it's going to impact on Josuke!
Detonate!
Yes! It was a direct hit!
Deadly Queen!
My, my, that was close.
But I was on my guard.
Your willpower to try to
get one final blow in...
That's why I won't go near
you, Josuke Higashikata.
J-Josuke!
H-He's alive...
Hmph. It was a direct hit,
but he wasn't blown away.
There's a slight discrepancy
when I detonate by hand...
But the damage is absolute.
I can finish him off with the next shot!
W-We... We have to get away from here!
Y-You're pulling me the wrong way...
This is the opposite direction...
Not that way... It's the opposite direction!
I'm going to kill him!
We need to go in the direction
of Yoshikage Kira...
My Shining Diamond
can't fix my own wounds...
But once my blood has left my body and
hardened, it's just another object.
It's no longer part of me.
Therefore, I can gather it and
stick it onto other things.
So I stuck some inside a shard of glass.
The rain stopped, and the blood
stain on his jacket earlier...
should have hardened by now!
That's my automatic tracking bomb.
Sh
Shi
Shin
Shini
Shining
Shining Di
Shining Dia
Shining Diam
Shining Diamo
Shining Diamon
Shining Diamond
Jo
Josuke
Josuke Higashi
Josuke Higashikata
The shard of glass that I was
able to guard against...
It must be this blood stain...
This stain must have led that
glass shard right to me!
I-It was a direct hit!
It's embedded right into Kira's back!
That's...
Josuke Higashikata's Shining Diamond is
a Stand whose actions I can't foresee...
But the damage Josuke sustained
is greater than mine.
Just one more shot!
One more shot and I,
Yoshikage Kira, will be victorious!
I-It's here! Th-This one's big enough to see!
That must mean...
that this is his final shot.
This will be mine, too!
I-I don't think the same attack
will work twice on Kira!
He'll dodge it!
We'll just have to see about that...
By the way, Hayato, sorry,
but the lighter from earlier is in my pocket.
Could you get it for me?
It's a bit hard for me
to get it myself with
this pole sticking out of my stomach.
The smoke is useless now!
You can see the air bullet!
The air bullet isn't what I want to
use the lighter to see this time.
I'm going to look at something else... So...
Let's find out why he can see where I am.
Don't move, Hayato.
J-Josuke? Wh-What are you...
Stay still, Hayato.
He might not be watching...
He might be listening.
Kira had a cell phone.
Did he just happen to have it? No!
So then, who was he talking to?
Was it his boss from the office?
No, that's not right.
There's only one person that Kira
would be calling right now...
I'd completely forgotten about you,
old man in the picture...
The one who's trying to
protect Yoshikage Kira!
I have no idea when he got
inside my pocket, but...
So this was the answer!
Th-The air bullet passed through the window!
Get back!
It impacted!
Josuke... is running away three meters ahead.
Sh-Shit!
I-It passed him!
And he's now moving diagonally
right, then up... Three meters.
He hasn't figured out that it's Josuke
because he's using a raspy voice!
And now, he's running away
one meter to the left...
What?! How can you do that, you bastard?!
Right there. Detonate!
Yoshikage!
I did it! Josuke's been
blown away, hasn't he?
Yeah, he was gloriously blown away.
All the way to Hell, with my directions.
Though, I mean, he was
a ghost to begin with,
so it's more like he finally made it over.
Josuke...
J-Josuke!
Th-This must be some kind of mistake...
Something this horrible...
should not be happening in my life...
when I just want to live
as peacefully as a plant...
But what I mustn't forget
at times like these
is that it's in times like these,
horrible times like these,
that opportunities present themselves.
I've learned that in the past.
When I'm backed into a corner,
if I think things through rationally,
opportunities will make
themselves available!
I, Yoshikage Kira, have always done this.
There is no trouble that I was
unable to overcome...
Ever!
You're within my range...
Yoshikage Kira!
H-He's near him!
H-He finally got near him!
This is a close-quarters match,
and it'll be over in an instant.
Josuke's ability is greater,
b-but if Kira touches him,
he'll be turned into a bomb!
A-And the wounds in Josuke's
leg and torso from that blast...
Josuke, you shouldn't even
be able to stand right now.
Josuke Higashikata!
Bring out... your Deadly Queen...
Deadly Queen!
H-He's strong...
I'm going to be defeated...
I, Yoshikage Kira, am going to be defeated!
N-No... How could...
We were so close!
Josuke is stronger than him!
Is fate really on the side of that murderer?
M-My fists didn't hit him...
These air bullets acted like cushions!
B-But it wasn't my intention
to have it guard me...
I didn't have time for that!
Stray Cat!
I see... Stray Cat thought
it was being attacked,
so it instinctively blocked the attack!
This is my chance! This is that chance!
A opportunity has presented itself
at the worst of times, after all!
Deadly Queen!
Change that air bullet into a bomb!
I've won!
I've changed it into a contact bomb!
It'll explode if anyone touches it.
Josuke, with the damage you're
currently suffering from,
you won't have the strength to dodge this!
Yoshikage Kira!
It's a contact bomb?!
Josuke! It doesn't matter
if it's glass or wood!
Hit that and take cover!
I've won! This always happens
when life deals its worst to me!
Luck is on the side of Yoshikage Kira!
Wh-What?!
Th-The air bullet went off its course!
Y-You're...
You're...
O-Okuyasu!
You know, I always wonder
where all the stuff I scrape
away with The Hand goes.
Though I'm not really smart,
so whenever I think too much
about anything, I get a headache.
There.
What?!
I-I can't believe it... I-It's Okuyasu.
But his heart and breathing
had completely stopped...
I had a weird dream...
While I was walking amid the darkness
in that dream, I saw a light.
And I saw my dead brother...
My big brother, Keicho.
He asked me where I was going,
so I said that I was going to follow him.
I mean, my Bro was always reliable.
He never made any bad decisions,
so I'd have nothing to worry about.
But then he said I should decide for myself.
He said, "Okuyasu, you're the one who
has to decide where you're going to go."
I thought for a bit,
and answered that I was going back
to Morioh, and then I woke up.
It was a really sad dream.
Okuyasu...
Y-You've got some nerve,
dreaming at a time like this!
There's that lousy attitude!
Despite your wounds,
you seem pretty okay.
Shut up!
If you were alive, you should
have woken up sooner, damn it!
I-Impossible... Fate should
have been on my side...
I should have been given my opportunity!
Stray Cat! Shoot another shot!
Wh-What?!
Wh-Wh-Whoa... Whoa, there.
Y-Yes! Now Kira won't be able
to use his air bullet bombs!
Th-Th-There's...
There has never been any trouble that I,
Yoshikage Kira, was unable to overcome!
Look, Jotaro!
That loud sound must've
come from that house.
I wonder what happened. Was it a gas explosion?
L-Look! That man is injured!
Josuke and Okuyasu are there, too!
That kid is Hayato Kawajiri from the picture.
And that man is Kosaku Kawajiri.
It looks like everything's falling into place.
Any fate that would side with you...
Any opportunity that would come your way...
is nothing compared to the heart
of justice that's here right now!
It's definitely here! It's right here for sure!
Compared to that heart, you're nothing!
Episode 39
Goodbye, Morioh – The Heart of Gold