All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Your sword is terrifyingly fast.
It's amazing, but do you really think
you'll defeat me by the time
the flames on that table strike 12?
Aren't you being rather conceited,
Mister...?
Polnareff.
Allow me to introduce myself.
Jean Pierre Polnareff.
Merci beaucoup.
I appreciate your introduction.
But...
Monsieur Polnareff,
don't assume that my flames
always burn upward or downwind
as they would in nature.
It is called Magician's Red
because it controls flames freely.
In the beginning, this world
was engulfed in flames.
I expect nothing less from Magician's Red,
who controls the flames that
suggest the beginning of all things.
But, you say I'm being conceited?
You're saying that my swordsmanship
is mere conceit?!
Foom
In the moment they lined up,
he pierced five coins in a single strike!
No. Take a closer look.
That's...
I-I see... there are flames between each coin.
It appears you understand what this means.
It is not conceit.
My Stand has the power to sever even fire!
It can slash the very air and create gaps
between nothingness and nothingness.
Which means your Magician's Red is
powerless before my Silver Chariot.
When did he...
The card that my Stand has,
The Chariot, suggests conquest and victory.
I don't mind taking care of you
in this cramped little space,
but, Avdol, you'd be able to use your
flame abilities in a much more open space, no?
It would be fitting for my Stand to
defeat you under those circumstances.
A fitting victory.
All of you, outside!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 5: Silver Chariot
Wh-What is this place?
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
It's Tiger Balm Garden.
What?
Tiger Balm Garden,
a garden that exists along the hillside
of Hong Kong's Tai Hang Road.
Its unique taste and appearance
make it number one among
Hong Kong's bizarre zones.
I will make a prediction here.
First, Avdol,
you will be destroyed by
your own Stand's powers.
Avdol...
Jotaro, you need not interfere.
With such an open space,
I can control my Stand as freely as I please.
Come on!
Slice
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on. What's wrong?
You're not going to use your precious
flames to your heart's content?
If not, I'm going to take my turn.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
That bastard. He's mocking us.
With repeated stabs, he carved a
statue that looks just Magician's Red.
You know...
You fit quite well in this garden, Magician's Red.
Suuuuuck
Here it comes.
You're ready to show your true power?
Sounds like fun.
I'll take what you dish out.
Hey, hide behind something.
Avdol is going to use it.
"It"?
Crossfire Hurricane!
Is that all you've got?!
I told you that my swordsmanship can create gaps
between nothingness and nothingness,
and blow away flames!
Crash
Avdol!
The flames are so strong
that he's being burned, as well.
It's just as I predicted.
You will die, burned by your own flames!
Oh, good, good grief!
You're still going to come at me?
How unsightly!
What is this odd resistance?
What?!
Impossible!
How can flames come out
from the body I severed?
That's not the Stand.
It's the statue!
Your eyes were blinded by the flames.
What you cut apart was the statue
that Silver Chariot carved earlier.
I told you that I could control my flames freely.
The flames that you blew back toward it
melted its joints and caused it to move.
You are the one defeated
by his own Stand's powers.
And now, face this again!
Crossfire Hurricane!
I believe it's ten years too
soon for you to fight me,
a fortune teller, with predictions.
Such terrifying power!
Since his Stand took that head-on,
it must have melted. It's done for!
That's one hell of a burn.
Yeah, he's dead. If he's lucky,
he'll be in serious condition.
Actually, that'd be bad luck.
Either way, he won't be
able to stand for three months.
His Stand is destroyed and unable to fight.
Now, Mr. Joestar,
let us hurry on our journey to Egypt.
Indeed.
Boom
Wh-What?
His Stand is breaking into pieces!
Bang
He flew into the air while still lying down!
Bravo! Oh, bravo!
H-He's...
I don't believe it!
He's perfectly fine!
But why is his body floating in the air?
Take a good look with your inner eye.
That's...
Bam
Yes, this is it.
My Stand with its armor off: Silver Chariot.
You seem shocked,
and it wouldn't be honorable to defeat you
without explaining my powers first.
You could even call it a surprise attack.
Would you give me the time to explain?
Very well.
Let's hear this explanation.
My Stand did not break apart and disappear.
Silver Chariot was wearing armor.
That's what it just took off.
What was burned away by your
flames was just part of its armor.
That's why I was only lightly injured.
And with its armor off, it is lighter.
Did you see it lift me up?
That's right. That's how fast it can move now!
I see.
So you're saying that because
its armor was so heavy,
it had to take my Crossfire Hurricane head-on.
But that would also mean that it's naked now.
Now that it doesn't have its protection,
if it were to take that attack
again, it wouldn't survive.
Oui, precisely.
But that would be impossible.
Impossible? I'd like to test that theory.
Because I'm going to show
you something astonishing.
Oh? Go right ahead.
Line-up
Wh-What?!
His Stand just multiplied into six...
no, now there are seven of them!
I-Impossible.
There should only be one Stand to each user.
It seems that you are astonished.
These are shadow clones.
Shadow clones of my Stand that confuse
not only your eyes, but your senses.
Your senses can't follow its movements.
How do you like its swordsmanship now?
Silver Chariot
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Red Bind!
I told you that you wouldn't be
able to follow its movements.
Your flames can only grasp shadow clones.
Striking at random now?
You're getting a bit desperate, Avdol.
It's true; that'll just use up all his energy.
Crossfire Hurricane!
Non, non, non, non, non, non.
That is also a shadow clone.
Your attack will not work against my Stand.
Come on, come on, come on!
Avdol!
Such precision. Th-This is...
a Stand ability that has
been very highly trained.
For certain reasons,
I trained for nearly ten years.
Now, come at me again.
I will finish you with my next move.
In the name of chivalry,
you keep explaining your attacks.
You're rather honorable.
Therefore, I shall also
reveal a secret before beginning my next attack.
Oh?
You see, there are variations
to my Crossfire Hurricane.
It is a flame in the shape of an Ankh,
but it need not be singular.
I can break it up and make it fly in pieces.
Crossfire Hurricane
Special!
Just try and dodge it!
You waste your time, Avdol!
They formed a circle!
There's no opening!
Naïve! Naïve, naïve, naïve, naïve!
You're naïve!
I will again use this power against you!
Sever! Blow it back at him!
What?!
Kaboom
That's...
The hole that was made by the flames earlier...
I get it!
The first flames were used to dig a tunnel!
And then he shot the Crossfire Hurricane through it!
I told you.
I can break apart my flames
and make them fly in as many pieces as I wish.
Burning is a rather painful way to die.
Use that dagger to kill yourself.
I was conceited.
I couldn't imagine his flames
standing a chance against my swordsmanship.
I'll be a good sport and burn to death after all.
Since I was defeated by your powers,
it is only due courtesy.
It would be disrespectful to kill myself.
Even now, you remember to be chivalrous.
And you did not throw your
dagger when I had my back turned.
Despite having orders from DIO,
your proud honor shines through.
It would be a shame to kill you.
There must be a reason behind his actions...
Jojo!
Yeah.
Ugh. Those tentacles are so gross!
Jotaro, hurry up and get it out.
Shut up, old man.
Hurry! Hurry!
Good! Now that the flesh bud is gone,
we can be buddies. Ta-da!
Kakyoin, don't guys like him
who make stupid puns
seriously piss you off?
The boat that we had chartered
from the Speedwagon crew
yesterday should be at the harbor now.
What's wrong? Is there
something else you needed,
Polnareff?
I haven't thanked you for
freeing me from DIO's spell yet.
For that, you need to thank Jojo.
Don't need it.
It appears there's no one
to accept your kind thanks.
All right. I don't like to be pushy, either.
But there is something else.
Monsieur Joestar, I'd like to ask
you a very bizarre question.
A bizarre question?
Forgive my curiosity,
but even while eating,
you didn't take off your gloves.
Your left arm wouldn't happen
to be a right arm, would it?
What? My left arm, a right arm?
That is indeed a bizarre question.
What do you mean?
I'm looking for the man
who killed my younger sister.
I don't know his face.
But he has two right arms.
I lost it in a battle fifty years ago.
I apologize for my rudeness. Please forgive me.
If you don't mind, tell us what happened.
It's been three years now...
My younger sister was walking home from school
with a classmate one rainy day.
It was a country road in my native France.
On the side of the road, a man stood
with his back to them.
Mysteriously, even though it was raining,
the rain fell around him in a dome-like shape,
as if an invisible screen surrounded him.
Suddenly, as if cut down by a scythe,
her classmate's chest was sliced open.
And then...
My sister was shamed and killed.
That was all that man wanted.
Barely escaping death,
her friend somehow survived.
She said that she didn't see his face,
but both of his arms were right arms.
No one believed her testimony,
but I understood it!
Because I believed that man
may have a similar power to the
one that I had been keeping a secret.
He's definitely a Stand user.
I swore!
My sister's soul would not be able
to rest unless he atoned with his death!
I will use my Stand for retribution!
Menacing
Then, a year ago, I met DIO.
Blam
I see s-something in the crystal ball.
It's...
A vision. I didn't create it.
What's inside your heart is
being projected via my powers.
How about it?
Would you like to be friends with me?
Something is bothering you. You're in pain.
Stick with me,
and it'll disappear from your heart.
What's being shown in the
crystal is what pains you, yes?
Let me help you.
I have pain of my own...
My body cannot go out into the sunlight.
So please, help me, as well.
I shall find this man for you.
And then I was ordered to kill you.
I believed that was the right thing to do.
It's partially because of the flesh bud,
but DIO's also skilled at manipulating others.
Indeed. But according to what you just said,
it would appear that DIO has
found the man with two right arms
and has joined forces with him.
I've decided to go to Egypt with all of you!
If I go after DIO,
I'll be able to find the
one who took my sister's life!
What should we do?
I have no objections.
I'm sure you'd follow us, even if we said no.
Jean Pierre Polnareff.
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Stand name: Silver Chariot.
Silver Chariot
Powers: Fast and precise swordsmanship!
It's an honor.
Good grie—
Excuse me!
Would you mind taking our picture?
He's amazing.
I'm going to use this as my chance.
Thank you!
We want our backs toward the ocean.
You're annoying me! Ask someone else!
Now, now, now, now...
I'll take your picture for you.
Come, come.
You have very nice legs.
Let's get a full body shot.
Ooh, nice!
I'm going to take one more.
Très bien!
Just like the button,
I want to push, push, push
your hearts toward mine!
I don't quite understand his personality.
That was a very sudden change of mood.
More like his head and his lower
half are very clearly separated.
Good grief.
Next Episode Preview
Can't you do something about that uniform?
Students should act like students.
Bring it on! I'll take you!
Was that a Stand user?
If a Stand user inhales any cigarette smoke at all...
Episode 6:
Dark Blue Moon
By the way...