We made it to Venice!
I'm diving into the canal!
Mista! Please hurry up
and get out of the car!
G-Giorno! You... Your body's already...
I'm sure you already know this, Mista,
but our priority is to obtain the item.
Getting that thing will lead to our victory.
The disc is in there!
We're surrounded by water, so it'll
take a while for it to freeze.
That's why I drove into the canal.
Don't worry about me! Hurry and get out!
Got it, Giorno. But I don't
like your idea of victory!
Killing him, and the both of us
living to retrieve that thing...
That'll be our victory!
Like hell I'm gonna let you get away!
Just try and jump in, Mista!
I don't mind making a wager on whether
or not you can swim faster than my ice!
Sh-Shit! Driving into the
canal was a bad idea!
This guy has no weak point
when it comes to ice!
Episodio 19  White Ice
Turn the car into a plant, Giorno!
The hood of the car hasn't
completely frozen over yet.
Nurture a plant to life while you still can!
You're trying to grow vines
to use them as ropes?
That's not happening!
I-It's no use.
We need the right temperature
to grow a plant like a vine
that'll grow fast enough to reach the bank.
In this low temperature,
the only plant that'll grow is the
short grass you'd find in a tundra!
Who said anything about growing
vines that reach the bank, Giorno?
This is perfectly fine!
Short grass is exactly what I want!
But I need more! More! More!
If you don't want to die, get me more!
If you don't grow more,
we're gonna die, Giorno!
Gotcha! Too bad you couldn't
grow it to the bank of the canal!
Well done, Giorno! It froze over!
Now you won't die!
Th-That bastard! He froze some
short grass to create a sled?
N-No... A snowboard!
Damn it!
He's not going to let me get away so easily.
Of course not...
White Ice! Undo the ice temporarily!
Th-Th ice...
...melted!
Mista!
An extremely low temperature
is a world of life or death!
Nothing can move in extremely
low temperatures!
They can stop everything!
That's what makes my White Ice perfect!
It can even stop the raging
ocean if I want it to!
Hurry and get up on the bank, Mista!
Mista!
Gather up the grass that's
floating in the water!
The grass you were using as a snowboard!
While you can fire the
gun in your right hand!
Give it up, Mista!
Do you still not understand that
attacking me is pointless?!
Stab
Gathering up grass... I see.
Giorno, if you release your ability,
the short grass turns back into car parts.
Therefore, we can shoot them into you!
What?!
D-Did that do it?
No, it's shallow.
I think we can at least get away for now,
but Mista, this just bought us some time!
Let's get the thing quickly,
then get out of here fast.
That same strategy won't work again
the next time he catches up.
Please go, Mista!
The disc will show up somewhere
if we destroy the lion statue.
I'll retrieve it,
then hide somewhere in the city.
If I have a few dozen
seconds, I can do this.
But will hiding be enough
to get away from that guy?
It might just work, but it might not.
More importantly,
this guy's way too dangerous.
It'll be even worse if he ends up
running into Bucciarati and the others.
We need to end him now!
This is our only chance!
Wha— Mista! What are you doing?!
Your ability is perfect? That's impossible!
If you've completely encased yourself
in ice, how are you able to breathe?
There it is. I knew it.
Air's leaking out.
He's breathing from there,
the back of his neck.
Take your positions, Six Bullets!
Number One and Number Two,
go around and flank him!
Wah, he's looking over here!
He's gonna do another ice attack!
No, first, he's probably going to go up for air.
Once he rises to the surface,
I'm gonna put a bullet in his head!
He's trying to go up to the surface!
Let's go, Bullets!
We're aiming for the moment
he takes a breath of air!
Mista!
Number One and Two are saying
they can't see the hole!
It must be due to his posture!
He's facing up right now!
The hole's hidden!
Sh-Shit! Let's scram!
Oh, shut up!
Stay in your positions,
Number One and Number Two!
How dare you do that to my forehead?!
Mista!
What the?!
You shot some fish that were swimming around?
What the hell are you trying to do?!
He looked down! We can see it!
It's the hole! Now!
Here it comes!
We can do this!
Gwooom
We did it! Bullseye!
Th-That sound...
That sound... It can't be!
So you found my breathing
hole and went after that...
Mista!
But extremely low
temperatures stop everything!
Gases turn to liquids, and liquids turn to solids!
Take a closer look.
Can't you see the air that's stopped?
The bullet, Mista!
That's the sound of a ricocheting bullet!
What?!
White Ice... Gently Weeps!
Mista!
I'd already created a wall of frozen air!
It uses up quite a bit of my Stand's power,
but now nothing can shoot a bolt into me!
Anything that comes near me will stop!
This is a lesson I learned from you, Mista!
Giorno was right.
This is all my fault...
This is my responsibility.
If only I'd prioritized getting that thing...
It's not under any trash cans or benches.
I can't find anything of importance,
and they wouldn't hide it
out in the open, anyway.
But considering how much Mista is hurrying,
I just realized it must
be in the immediate area.
Where is it? This photo should be a hint...
Shit. This is the worst possible scenario.
Mista's currently acting out of despair.
He's decided to take responsibility for
this, even if it costs him his life.
But the only ones who can open up a path
in the darkness are those with resolve.
Things are getting interesting.
We're going to have to
make some sacrifices,
but my resolve, as well as Mista's,
will open up a path in the darkness!
Ghiaccio
White Ice
What the hell is this?
It was embedded in there?
In one of the cuts or gaps in the statue?
Damn it! If I'm close enough,
I should be able to shoot into
the hole in his neck again!
If I can just get close enough
to aim through the wall of air...
Mista's getting reckless.
He's willing to take responsibility
for this at the cost of his own life.
But this isn't just determination
resulting from him being cornered.
It's resolve!
We need resolve right now!
Resolve doesn't mean sacrifice!
A computer disc!
I knew it! The thing you were trying
to get was something to tell you
how to get to the boss!
I did it! Now we can find
out who the boss really is!
All that's left now... is Trish!
Right after I finish you bastards off!
Come at me with all your futile attempts!
Let me finish you off!
Mista!
What the hell are you doing?!
Having resolve is the
ability to open up a path
we need to follow within the darkness!
Guido Mista: arrested at 17 for murder.
The result of the trial:
they did not see his
actions as self-defense,
and he was sentenced to
15 to 30 years in prison.
My happy-go-lucky youth...
Is this really my fate?
Mista always had an optimistic view of life,
but in this moment,
he didn't know what to do.
Damn it.
Get up. You're being released.
You're the one who bailed me out?
Yes. I saw the incident on the news and
decided you acted out of self-defense.
It means you are incredibly skilled
with a pistol and full of life.
But a guy like you probably
wouldn't last two years in prison.
That's why...
You pulled some strings.
Do you belong to some organization?
Come with me.
There's an excellent ristorante nearby.
I like the way you eat.
The bruschetta here is great, too.
Do you still have some room?
Yeah.
Pardon me.
Yes, sir?
Could I get some bruschetta for him...
I should get some for them, too.
Could I get four orders of bruschetta?
No, make that five.
I guess I'll get an order for myself.
Right away, sir.
So, continuing our conversation...
I'm in.
I think you and I will get along great.
So, I'm in.
On one condition, though.
Treat me to some dolce, too.
Does this place have strawberry cake?
You sure are an odd one.
I guess this must be fate, too.
This isn't so bad.
Everything worked out in the end.
Mista learned that people have
predetermined destinies.
When they're young,
people may find themselves at a standstill
or taking the long way around at times,
but they ultimately end up traveling
the path they were destined to walk.
I can see it! I can see the path perfectly!
I can see it for sure this time!
It's there, Giorno!
I see the path I need to
take through the darkness!
Yeehaw!
Batoom
Bam
Shank
Crack
You guys don't seem to understand.
The air is frozen because of the
extremely low temperature.
Just like this.
If I put air that's been frozen
solid in my suit and melt it,
the air turns back to normal!
If I take it in like this...
Just like a diver who has
an air tank on their back,
I don't need a breathing hole anymore!
The hole!
He deflected the bullets!
Six of them! O-Oh, no!
I hope you have the resolve for this, Mista!
It's over.
Yeah, my resolve is there, Giorno.
If you hadn't given me your resolve,
I wouldn't have been able to see this path.
The path toward the resolve to be
willingly shot by my own bullets...
I-I can't see!
The blood's frozen to me and hardened...
The path through the darkness
isn't the path for the bullets to
get through your wall of ice.
I-It was to splash your face with my blood!
Shit! I can't get it off!
Hey, the metal pole from earlier!
Mista, your bullet carved it into a—
Ow! That hurts!
Something... Something... Something...
Something lukewarm is—
You asked me if I had the resolve for this...
Well, let me show you!
But you'll have to show
me some resolve, too.
The resolve to be filled with holes
and depart for the next world!
Th-That bastard's still standing!
He's hell-bent on shoving
me back even farther!
Is he insane?! He's determined to finish this!
Shit! I need to get this out of my neck!
You're crazy! The bullet's
gonna come flying back!
You're not gonna last!
I have to make it through.
Starting now, I'm showing my true resolve!
Steel yourselves, Bullets!
White Ice... Gently Weeps!
Y-You can't take any more, Mista!
You're going to lose consciousness!
We're also...
...going to disappear!
N-Not yet!
I'm still conscious! I can still shoot him!
Y-You did it!
It went all the way in!
You're... wrong...
The one with stronger resolve... is me...
Guido Mista...
I'll commend you for... pushing me this far...
But the one who took better advantage
of all the spurting blood... was me!
I froze the blood that spurted
out of my neck to support me!
Now my neck won't get
pushed farther onto the spike!
I'm totally secured!
The spike won't go any farther in!
Also... Haven't you forgotten something?
The bullet you shot last is still...
Straight into your head!
I win!
There's no wound?!
Wha—
Mista...
Your resolve is shining upon the path,
even brighter than this rising sun.
And it's shining on the path...
that we're meant to take!
What the hell?!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Useless! Useless!
Recently, I... started noticing...
that despite Giorno Giovanna...
being a newbie...
things always seem...
to play out exactly how he says.
The resolve I showed just now
was also partly Giorno's.
It was making its way into my
heart before I even realized it.
It almost feels like he's my capo,
even more so than Bucciarati,
and he kept me moving.
What the hell is his deal?
Well, I guess that doesn't matter right now.
It's not my style to think
too much about stuff.
Mista, we safely retrieved
the disc, thanks to you.
Hurry and fix me up. I-I can't breathe...
I wouldn't have been able to show
that resolve without your ability.
Hurry and fix me up, before I actually die...
Of course. But I'd like to
clear something up first.
Golden Wind doesn't exactly fix things.
It creates parts of your body.
I'll give life to the bullets
embedded in your body
and plug up the arteries and
other parts that were destroyed.
Just shut up and do it already.
Since I'm not exactly healing you,
your pain will remain.
Please don't complain to me later.
Ow!
O-Ow! Be more gentle!
Be more gentle, damn it, Giorno!
I told you, I can't.
You're a gangster, for crying out loud.
Please quit fussing.
There are about 18 more wounds,
so you'll have to remove some of
your clothes for me to plug the rest.
Bucciarati! I'm picking up two signals...
It doesn't look like there's anyone else.
Proceed, but carefully.
I'm assuming it's Mista and Giorno.
I'm sure they're bored out of their minds
waiting for us since nothing's happening.
Ack! Giorno!
There they are! Hey, Mista! Gio—
Be gentler! Gentler, damn it!
Don't take off my clothes!
I'll feel it more!
Well, Narancia? Did you find those two?
Huh? W-Well, u-um...
No! Huh?! Suddenly there's
something in my eye?
Giorno, no! Don't! N-No more! I-I can't!
I can't see! I can't see them clearly!
Be gentler, damn it!
Risotto's whereabouts are unknown.
Currently searching airports, train stations,
and the area around Naples.
Curse you, Risotto...
You must be heading to Venice.
If Bucciarati and his crew put
an end to you, that's fine.
Regardless, I'm not worried.
Episodio 20
The Final Mission from the Boss