I think I used my head too much.
My shoulders are sore.
They feel so heavy.
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 18: Von Stroheim's Revenge
It's dawn.
Caesar and JoJo should be back
before too long.
Madam Lisa Lisa...
Which blouse do you like?
Suzie Q, thank you.
White is always nice,
but something colorful can be fun.
I'll let you decide.
Let's see, then...
How about the white one?
But I really do like this design.
Did JoJo and Caesar
pass their final exams?
Somehow I'm worried.
I have a bad feeling.
Let's go with
the refreshing white!
Suzie Q...
Yes?
Send Caesar and JoJo to my room
when they arrive.
I'll tell them.
I really like the clean design
of this one.
Which is better?
Which to choose?
White!
Then again...
This is nice, too.
Oh, what to do?
The colorful one
will do nicely, Suzie Q.
Good choice, madam!
I'll just leave these here.
I'll clean up the broken glass later.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Hey.
Suzie Q.
What are you screaming about?!
Be quiet, dummy!
W-Who... Who are you?!
There's a stranger on the island!
You're calling me a stranger?!
It's me! Joseph Joestar!
JoJo?!
No way!
You always had a mask on before.
What a surprise!
You haven't seen my face
in all this time?
And so? Am I handsome?
Weird lips.
Even with these weird lips,
if we were to fall in love...
...you can kiss them all you like!
In your dreams!
Blech!
What's up?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Oh yeah, Madam Lisa Lisa wants you
to go to her room.
But she's in the bath,
so wait half an hour.
Got it. I planned to go anyway.
They know about the Stone.
You mean Madam Lisa Lisa's Stone?
Don't worry about it.
You don't want to get involved.
Um, JoJo...
Hmm?
You're actually pretty hot.
That's odd.
My shoulders have loosened up.
One ring neutralized at 6 a.m.
The other dissolves in six days.
The news I have is important,
but Lisa Lisa is taking a bath.
So I'm supposed to wait half an hour.
If I was told to wait, I'll wait.
Where to spend half an hour?
I think the best place is here
by Lisa Lisa's door.
Would it be wrong if I peeked
through the keyhole?
Nice!
Suzie Q?
What's she doing in there?
When did she go inside?
That was fast.
I thought she was on the docks.
What the...?
The knob is covered in slime.
So, Suzie Q, have JoJo and Caesar
returned yet?
Suzie Q?
Suzie Q!
Where did you put the Red Stone?!
Who are you?! Where is the Stone?!
N-No!
S-Something's inside Suzie Q!
You have reduced me to nothing
but a brain!
But I challenge you to one last fight!
I put the Stone on the boat
that just left.
I am here to stop you from chasing it!
You will not follow that postal boat!
The woman I am inside of
is still mostly alive!
You will have to kill her
in order to destroy me completely!
Can you do that?
Are you capable of that?
Esidisi!
JoJo!
You never give up, do you, Esidisi?
Oh, Caesar!
It's about time.
You...
You survived your bout with Esidisi?
You're a lucky one.
JoJo! What were you doing
with our coach?!
Cool it, meathead.
It's not like that. Look at Suzie Q!
Huh?
What's going on?
It's Esidisi.
His brain and blood vessels
have taken over her body!
Damn him!
Save me, Caesar!
Please...
Everyone picks on me...
...but you won't, will you, Caesar?
Don't fall for it.
She's not the one talking.
Esidisi is using her.
Caesar, the Stone is on a postal boat.
Leave this to us. Go after the Stone.
If the Stone reaches a train in Venice
we have no idea where
in the world it might go.
You're not going anywhere!
You have to kill me first, wiener heads!
A male voice!
His blood vessels are controlling her
from within!
Come on!
Bring it!
Use your Hamon and kill me!
It would be easy to destroy me
in my current state!
But you know that this girl's heart
can't take a Hamon shock like that!
Are you willing to take
this girl's life?
If you can, then hurry up and do it,
fools!
Hey!
I'm not soft, Esidisi!
I only have to end the life of one girl
and I can save the entire world.
I consider it a necessary sacrifice.
A-Are you serious, JoJo?!
Time to go to pieces, Esidisi!
N-No!
JoJo!
I'm really gonna do it!
Damn it! I can't hit her!
This bastard!
I thought he'd pop out of her,
but he's unfazed!
Enough of your bluffing.
You could never kill this girl.
The Stone has likely already
arrived on the main island.
You're too late.
A-And now...
W-What is he doing to Suzie Q now?
S-Stop this, Esidisi!
And now I will explode this girl's body,
and cover you all
with blood as hot as lava!
H-His blood is boiling hot!
S-Suzie Q's body is falling apart!
If this keeps up, it's not just Suzie Q,
we'll all be in trouble!
V-Very well.
JoJo, use your Hamon on Suzie Q!
C-Come on!
Don't make me do this!
I still have nightmares about
chopping von Stroheim's leg off!
A plan!
We need a plan!
I-I'll do it, then.
N-No, Coach! Let me do it.
W-Wait! I thought of something!
Remember Hell Climb Pillar!
We'll try that! It's do or die!
Let's go for it!
You and me! Two types of Hamon!
Two types?
I-I see.
I-It might just work.
Got it?
JoJo! Caesar!
I understand.
JoJo, follow my breathing.
Now!
JoJo creates a burst of positive Hamon!
Caesar focuses negative Hamon
on Suzie Q's heart!
At that point, the Hamon is
negative positive zero!
You've forced him out.
JoJo!
No. It's all right.
Let the sun take care of it.
That low-down scum.
Hiding away in a girl's body like that.
No, Caesar. You don't understand.
I fought with him, so I know.
He threw away his pride and did all he
could to get the Stone for his allies.
For thousands of years
he lived his life to its fullest.
Whether it was good or evil,
I respect his life.
JoJo...
Suzie Q...
While Esidisi controlled you,
you must have been semiconscious.
Answer this.
Where is the Stone headed?
Switzerland.
Saint Moritz.
A package.
An envelope with
Madam Lisa Lisa's crest.
The address is...
Switzerland?!
Are Kars and Wamuu there?
I just checked.
A cargo train for Switzerland
left ten minutes ago.
The Stone has to be on that train!
Saint Moritz
Venice
And we have to beat that train
to Saint Moritz!
In order to keep the Stone
out of the wrong hands,
we might have to do some dirty work.
We might break the law.
Some of us may end up dead.
I won't.
I wasn't ready before,
but I won't lose now.
I'll eradicate them.
Caesar!
Right. We're out of here!
Hey, Suzie Q! Look over here!
This is goodbye, Suzie Q!
But I'll be back in Venice one day!
Really?!
Yeah!
Heal those ugly wounds before then!
Later!
JoJo, you just make sure
you come back here in one piece!
Don't be pushy!
You may be an old lady first,
but I'll return!
You stupid jerk!
I'll be back soon.
Saint Moritz, Switzerland
Drive the damned car!
What's with your arms?
Something's wrong with the wheel!
Esidisi hasn't called.
He said he learned
the Stone was in Venice.
Has something happened to him?
Hey, JoJo.
JoJo!
JoJo, wake up!
5:00 p.m.
6 days until remaining ring dissolves
Huh?
JoJo, we've caught up!
They're in customs.
It's less than an hour from
the border to Saint Moritz.
I'm glad we caught up.
Look sharp, JoJo.
Listen, I'm just saving up my strength,
that's all.
Let's hurry up and get that Stone.
Then we need to plan for the
fight with Wamuu.
Wait until we cross.
What the hell?
Knock it off!
If you want to go on, just pass us!
German soldiers!
What are they doing
on the Swiss-Italian border?
You're looking rather spry.
My, how you've grown, Mr. Joestar.
W-What did you say?
What was that?
G-Get back here!
Who are you?!
I don't know any German soldiers!
Look at the train!
So many soldiers...
We found it, Colonel!
That crest! It's the package!
And we know what's inside!
The Red Stone of Aja!
W-Why do the Germans want it?!
We are taking the Stone as a specimen
for our research.
For the past three weeks,
we have been watching you in Venice.
We started when we lost
our team in Rome.
We saw your training. We saw Esidisi.
And we knew you were chasing the Stone.
Our base is a lodge up ahead.
Follow us.
We want to ask you about the Stone and Kars.
Let us work together, eh?
We are not complete strangers, JoJo.
Hey! What are you blabbing about?!
Don't think you know me, bastard!
So the Germans are here.
C-Coach?
We have no choice.
At least Kars doesn't have the Stone.
At that time, the German army
was marching across Europe.
March 13, 1938: Annexation of Austria
March 15, 1939: Annexation
of Bohemia and Moravia
They wanted to ensure their rule
was permanent.
September 28, 1939: Division
of Poland with Soviet Union
The power of the mask and Red Stone
would solve their problem perfectly.
The Germans needed the ultimate power
of immortality to conquer the world!
Five hours later - 10:00 p.m.
I'll read the heat inside.
The fireplace is lit.
Four lights on the wall,
two on the ceiling.
Two on the desk...
No, three.
Four humans standing by the wall.
From the right, their heights are
178 cm, 174 cm, 181 cm, 178 cm.
One human is by the fireplace.
He's 183 cm tall.
Five humans, all male.
One, two...
That's four.
And five.
So you're Kars?
You're fast.
In just a few hours, you heard
about your friend's defeat,
then learned that we had obtained
the Stone,
and have come for it.
And this brutal, calculated assault...
None of my men made a sound
before they died.
I'm sure there were five men
in this room.
So, why can't I sense your body heat?
Hey, rifle heads!
Do I have to wait forever for food?
Kars!
It's mechanical!
You're...
...von Stroheim!
Next episode
We should attack now!
That building is the address.
That was mean of me.
This is German science!
No machine can stop me!
Chapter 19: A Race Toward the Brink