All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Previously, on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
The building in this picture, huh?
I've been repairing roofs in Cairo for forty years,
but I've never seen this place.
My daughter's condition has worsened.
She'll only last three or four more days.
I can feel it.
DIO is near here.
Let's go.
If we keep asking around, we'll find him.
Man, it's super hot today.
I haven't had a bath since yesterday.
My good looks are going to waste.
What the hell, man?!
Do you want something from me?
How dense are you?!
I'm telling you to get out of my way!
You're a foreigner.
Don't sit here like you're a beggar!
Who the hell gave you permission?
Ah, are you a needy foreigner?
This isn't much, but here you go.
Hey, this is...
Y-You bastard! How dare you?!
Th-This is my territory, damn it!
Territory?
Hey, Polnareff!
Don't sit there.
And give that money to him.
Is this guy a beggar?
Sorry. My friend doesn't
know much about this city.
You should have just said so in the first place.
I'm a beggar who can't speak in
public for professional reasons.
This city has a beggars' association.
Each beggar has an established territory
where he's paid to sit and do his work.
That may seem strange,
but without rules like this,
there'd be chaos in the streets.
Huh...
Even worse, you hurt my pride!
I wonder if I'd earn more if I
dressed up like a needy foreigner...
Maybe I'll start doing that.
By the way, I thought you looked familiar.
Aren't you Avdol, the fortune teller?
I heard that someone was trying
to kill you, so you fled to Japan.
I've been looking for you
to ask a favor, since you hear
much and remember it well.
I'll pay well.
We need to find the location shown in this picture,
and we're in a bit of a hurry.
Fwoosh
I'm done with work for the day.
I can find the place from
that picture in three hours.
Wait right there.
Hey... Where did Iggy go, anyway?
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 38  The Guardian of Hell, Pet Shop, Part 1
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
Menacing
There's no doubt about it.
That's the mansion.
I found it in two hours.
There's nothing in this city that I can't find.
Huh?
Crash
Iggy then thought to himself...
That bird is a Stand user like me.
A Stand of ice dropped that thing.
And he's protecting this mansion.
He eliminates those who try to enter it.
Wh-Which means that bird
will come after me next!
Since ancient times,
the Egyptians had been hunting
using falcons that would glide
through the Nile Valley.
The falcon was called Horus,
and was highly regarded as the
guardian deity of the royal family.
Its eye, which can spot small
animals several kilometers away,
is called the Eye of Horus.
The Eye of Horus is a design
symbolizing fortune and glory.
His name is Pet Shop.
His Stand suggests the
god of the heavens, Horus.
Iggy thought to himself...
I-It appears that I've stumbled upon
the mansion Joestar and the others
want to find, where that guy DIO lives.
And...
It was that Stand's power that
dropped that chunk of ice.
So he's not a guard dog, but a guard bird.
Menacing
Y-You've got to be kidding me.
I've got nothing to do with this DIO guy.
I was dragged to Egypt against my will
and ended up traveling with
Joestar's gang. That's all!
Like hell I'm going to fight!
I just want to live comfortably,
fall in love with a hot bitch,
and live a peaceful, carefree life.
Like hell I'm going to do something as
dangerous as fighting this violent jerk
when I'm not gonna get anything out of it!
I'm just gonna act like a dumb mutt
so he'll think I've got nothing to do with this.
Those eyes...
I can't tell what that bird's
thinking from his eyes.
I don't think I'd lose to him in a Stand battle,
but I've worked hard to act like an idiot.
I've got nothing to do with this!
Hurry up and go back to
the mansion, you birdbrain.
Oh, it's a bird.
What's with that bird?
I-It's not even trying to dodge!
I-I can't stop in time!
I-I'm gonna run it over!
Wh-What was with that bird?
I-It was able to go under the car,
despite how low it is?
A bird that didn't even try to flee,
but actually charged toward the car...
Wh-What a crazy bastard...
Anyway, it looks like he's lost interest in me.
He only attacks if you try to enter the mansion.
If Joestar and the others actually find this place,
they'll have a hell of a time trying to get in.
Well, it's not my problem.
Chibi! Buchi!
Chibi! Buchi! Where are you?
Hey, have you seen my two dogs?
Their names are Chibi and Buchi.
Shut up! Don't ask me, I'm a dog.
It's not like I can talk. Are you stupid?
Th-That collar...
This is Chibi's collar!
Why is Chibi's collar under the gate?
And there's blood on it!
Chibi and Buchi...
Does he mean those two big dogs from earlier?
Chibi! Buchi!
Hey, you're not...
You're not trying to get
under that gate, are you?
You'll be killed!
Chibi! Buchi! Are you here?
Chibi! Buchi!
This isn't my problem.
I don't care if some human kid dies.
Survival of the fittest is the law of nature.
Buchi! Chibi!
Idiots die. The careless die.
I'm don't want any trouble.
See ya!
Chibi! Buchi! Where are you?
Come back!
Bam
He's eating them! No!
Good grief.
I can't just stand by and
let a boy who likes dogs
get killed!
Bang
Horus
Pet Shop
Chibi! Buchi!
Damn it! I guess I'm gonna have to fight.
Stare
It seems this is the first time that
Pet Shop realized Iggy
was a Stand user like himself.
You birdbrain! Come at me! I'll kill you!
The average speed of a falcon's descent
is over 300 kilometers per hour.
There is no organism that can move faster.
A falcon rips out its prey's vital organs
with its razor-sharp black talons while hunting.
Even traveling at 300 kilometers per hour,
it can still pinpoint its prey's vital organs.
What? Did he just smile?
It looked like the corners of its
rigid beak just edged up a little!
A smiling bird?
Wh-What is this?
Something's not right...
The air's gotten awfully cold...
I-Ice is coming out of the ground!
C-Crap!
My feet got stuck to the ground
while I was busy looking up!
My Stand's feet are also rooted by the ice...
Crap!
Icicles?!
But seriously, Avdol...
Do you think that sunglasses guy
can really find DIO's mansion?
If he can't find it,
then no one else can.
He understands the complex geography
of Cairo better than anyone else.
Believe in him and wait.
You say that, but...
We looked around for three
days and couldn't find it.
It's hard for me to believe that
he could find it in three hours.
You're getting repetitive, Polnareff.
Honestly. Can't you just calm down a bit?
I know it's hard not to feel anxious,
but all we can do now is rely on the
knowledge of those who live here.
Jeez. I haven't seen Iggy for a while, either.
Where the hell did that stupid mutt run off to?
Iggy hates being part of any group.
I'm sure he's close. He'll show up eventually.
Aren't dogs supposed to like humans?
What a shitty, cynical little mutt.
I managed to get away from him.
That thing's ice took the
skin right off my paw pads...
Damn it! I should have
just let that human kid die.
That bird's Stand is no joke.
The ice it makes isn't normal.
There's something more to it.
I've got to hurry up and
get the hell out of here.
Talk about holding a grudge!
Iggy has disappeared.
Where did he disappear to?
Damn it...
That ruthless bastard doesn't hold back.
But in the end, he's still just a bird.
This place reeks, but I guess I've gotta deal it.
I'll hide out down here for a while.
Wh-What the hell is this bird?!
Bam
Hey.
Talk about gullible.
What you thought you killed was actually
just The Fool's shapeshifting sand!
All right! You must be pretty
stupid if you fell for that.
Look at all that blood.
You probably shouldn't move around.
I never had any interest in you
or your master DIO, anyway.
Let's just call it a draw.
You got to shoot me up
with those ice missiles, too.
Wh-What the hell?
Do you think you're Bruce Lee or somethin'?
Hey! I said I won't go near
your mansion anymore!
Let's stop this already. Okay?
So that's your Stand's actual design...
He used that thing to freeze
the wound and stop the bleeding!
C-Crap!
H-He blocked the exit with
ice when I wasn't looking!
The ice is coming this way!
Shit!
Ice is running all over the tunnel!
I-I've got to get out of this tunnel!
He blocked this exit, too!
He's planning to finish me off.
Talk about excessive!
This goes way beyond holding a grudge.
He's a machine made to hunt and kill!
Not to mention, if he catches me,
he'll eat me alive!
What?! M-My foot!
I-I can't get my foot out!
Next Episode Preview
Man, this is really not my day!
That stupid dog.
That birdbrain is really pissing me off.
It wouldn't be strange if there was a Stand user
in charge of guarding the mansion.
I'm gonna have to do this...
If I don't, he's going to kill me!
Episode 39
The Guardian of Hell, Pet Shop,
Part 2