All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Previously, on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
C-Crap!
He blocked the exit with
ice when I wasn't looking!
The ice is coming this way!
Shit!
Ice is running all over the tunnel!
I-I've got to get out of this tunnel!
What?! M-My foot!
I-I can't get my foot out!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 39  The Guardian
of Hell, Pet Shop, Part 2
Hey, the sun's about to set.
Despite how confident
that beggar sounded about finding DIO's
mansion from the photo within three hours,
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
it looks like he was wrong.
Eh, Avdol?
It's occurred to me that
it might be better if he didn't find it.
It may be
that he did find it,
and that's why he hasn't returned.
Hey...
There could be a Stand user that prevents
people from getting close to the mansion.
It might have been too
dangerous to ask that beggar
to find the mansion for us.
Hey, now...
M-My leg...
My leg...
It got chopped off by that icicle.
If I didn't abandon my leg,
I would have been finished.
I-I should hide here for a while.
I need to hide here and get him off my tail.
I'll have the Speedwagon Foundation
make me an artificial leg.
God damn that birdbrain!
You're not going to get away with this.
I will get you back for this. Damn it!
That noise...
It's the sound of something
diving into the water.
I-It can't be...
It is not impossible for a
bird to dive underwater.
Birds use lungs to breathe,
just like humans and dogs.
But they also have air sacs that store air,
located in five to six places
in their chests and abdomens.
Air Sac                                       Lungs                          Air Sac
Because of these air sacs,
birds are able to fly at an altitude of
six to seven thousand meters,
where humans would fall comatose.
Even if they were being strangled,
because of the supply of
oxygen in their bodies,
birds could survive a few minutes.
This means that a bird can stay
underwater much longer than a dog.
S-Something's coming closer through the water.
That's impossible!
I don't want to believe it,
but the sound heading
straight this way has to be...
It couldn't be!
It can't be!
That asshole bird!
It actually dove into the
water to come after me!
That bastard... Where'd he go?!
I-It's coming! It's coming again!
His ice. One... two... three.
Th-Three shots are coming!
Bash
I deflected them!
Stab
I-I did it. Serves you right!
Th-The water's stopped dripping in...
And the icicle's starting to
freeze over again from the root.
Wh-What the hell?
I-I get it.
He's freezing all of the water
surrounding this area!
The airway's been cut off!
B-But he's not trying to suffocate me.
He's trying to crush me!
It's no use. It's gonna collapse!
This power's ridiculous! I can't hold out!
There's infinite water around
me that he can freeze.
Damn it!
I thought I was hiding in the water,
but instead, I've been cornered!
I-I'm just going to have
to dig my way out.
Man, today is really not my day!
My front leg gets ripped off,
and that damn bird is too strong!
I'm at my limit. I'm going to be crushed.
I have to hurry up and dig a hole to escape.
Huh?
What's that? There's some kind
of hollow space inside...
It's the birdbrain!
Open
He's gonna shoot an ice missile!
Crap! The Fool is behind me!
I don't have time to defend.
There's no way out, either!
I know! I-I'll just have to do this.
If I don't, he'll kill me!
I'll let him crush it
on purpose,
and let the air pressure
launch me forward!
I-I did it. I defeated him.
Stupid birdbrain. Serves you right...
B-But I'm done for.
I've lost a lot of blood,
and I don't have the
strength to swim to shore...
I-I'm gonna drown.
And here I thought I'd live
a life free of trouble...
Damn it,
I messed up...
I can't believe it!
I was just passing by and you
happened to drift by on the river.
That bird got you, didn't it?
Just like he got my dogs...
It's okay.
I don't think that bird's close by.
Don't die! Hang in there!
I'll patch you right up.
The bastard bird, Pet Shop,
and his Stand, Horus: dead.
Bastard Bird
Pet Shop - Stand: Horus -
Dead
Horus
Pet Shop
Damn that Iggy! Where the hell did he go?
He's gotta stop making trouble for us.
I'm worried. We haven't
seen him for quite a while.
That stupid mutt!
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Is someone following us after all?
No... I thought I heard a voice calling for us.
A voice?
I-Iggy?!
Iggy!
What in the world happened?
Iggy's been badly injured!
Hey... He's missing a front leg...
D-Did he get run over by a car?
He's not the kind of dog
that gets into car accidents.
You were attacked by the
enemy, weren't you, Iggy?
But it looks like someone treated his wounds.
And with perfect surgical technique.
It wasn't Iggy's voice.
Someone was calling to us in human language.
It appears that Iggy had
a run-in with the enemy.
I saw a boy holding him as he lay dying.
The one who treated him is a doctor
from the Speedwagon Foundation.
Just like the one
who treated my eyes.
Y-You're...
Kakyoin!
It's Kakyoin! Hey!
Kakyoin, are your eyes okay now?
I'm glad you're all safe.
It's great to see you!
Have your wounds healed?
Yes. I'm fine now.
It left a few scars, but my
vision has completely returned.
That's good to hear.
Jotaro...
Hey, Iggy. Where are you going?
Iggy, who had no interest
in humans or Stands,
is apparently trying to lead us somewhere.
I'm not sure what happened while
he was fighting the enemy's Stand,
but he seems rather angry about
how much pain he endured.
Just where is he trying to lead us?
Hey, Iggy, hold on.
Th-That car...
It's the luxury car that beggar was riding in.
Th-This wreckage is...
What did this? There's a huge hole,
like something gigantic pierced it.
It's just as I feared.
I knew I shouldn't have asked him...
Is this the work of the
Stand user that Iggy fought?
It seems there can be little doubt.
Iggy!
Hey, what is this?
I'm in a cold sweat all of a sudden.
This overwhelmingly oppressive feeling...
Where's Iggy
t-trying to take us?
I already know. This atmosphere is...
This dark sensation...
Th-This mansion is...
The one from the picture.
Who would have thought you'd
be the one to find it, Iggy?
The mansion that stood before Jotaro,
projecting an abnormally sinister energy,
housed the cause of all they've been through,
their destiny: the embodiment of evil.
They had journeyed long
and far to reach this place.
They traveled through many lands,
encountering DIO's countless
Stand-using assassins.
It was, indeed, a series of life-or-death battles
that were no simple task to survive.
Tears, laughter, sadness, rage, and happiness.
They experienced many
emotions on this journey.
In order to save Jotaro's mother, Holly,
it has indeed been nearly fifty
days since they left Japan.
All to defeat DIO, and end
this hundred-year-old destiny.
Joseph thought to himself.
He was determined to reach his goal
and save his daughter Holly, no matter what!
Kakyoin thought to himself.
In order to save Holly, and to conquer
the weakness in his own heart,
they would defeat DIO, no matter what.
Avdol thought to himself.
There was evil this world that must not
be allowed to prosper,
and so, must be destroyed.
Polnareff thought to himself.
He would make DIO pay
for manipulating him with
a flesh bud to make him
act against his own righteousness.
Iggy thought to himself.
The reason he had to endure
all this absurdity was
because of that bastard DIO.
So he was going to pay him
back for it, no matter what.
And...
In other words, if we beat the shit out of DIO
right here and now, it will all be over.
He's here. There's no doubt
about it, this presence is his.
Rumble
He's inside this mansion right now.
Which means that we...
...have finally reached the
last stop on our journey.
Are you ready?
Bam
The gate's open.
We can just walk in.
But it was closed yesterday...
Just as I can sense his presence,
he is aware that I have arrived.
Entering this mansion carelessly
would be like being swallowed by the enemy.
Now...
What to do...
The door opened! Watch out!
Hey, look at this corridor.
I don't see any end to it.
It's not real, is it?
It's some kind of trick or illusion, right?
Polnareff, don't go through that door.
We should see at least one
or two Stand users before DIO.
What the?! Something's coming!
Who the hell's that? Is he a Stand user?
Welcome.
Master Joestar, we have
been awaiting your arrival.
I am the butler of this mansion.
Next Episode Preview
Allow me to wager
that Star Platinum's first
attack against me will...
Jotaro, blast him!
Take that corner at full throttle!
If we don't defeat you,
we won't be able to proceed.
Exactly! That is indeed correct.
Episode 40
D'Arby the Player, Part 1