All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Tokyo
Tokyo, Hong Kong, Singapore...
Hong Kong
Singapore
And now
Calcutta
we're about to cross India...
But, well, I'm a little worried.
My image of India is a place where people
only eat curry and you
could fall ill at any time.
I'm worried that my body may not
be able to handle the culture gap.
That assessment is rather distorted.
You needn't worry. It's a nice
country, where simple people live.
I can guarantee it.
Well, we're in Calcutta. Let's go.
Honk
Hey, give me a tip!
Let me carry that for you!
Want a tattoo? You're so pretty.
Need some anti-venom?
It won't hurt your stomach.
I'll show you a hotel!
Calcutta, India.
In the 20th century,
its population is 11 million.
An immense energy swirls about the city!
I stepped in some cow shit! Damn it!
I don't need any.
My wallet's already been stolen!
Seriously, no thank you.
Tip! Tip! Tip!
If you don't give me a tip,
you won't go to heaven, Mister.
Hey! Don't put your nose on it!
A-Avdol! Is this India?
See? Isn't it a great country?
This is what makes this country so wonderful!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 10: The Emperor and the Hanged Man Part 1
Here, have this.
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
This is chai.
It's delicious.
Chai.
A popular drink in India.
A sweet drink made by boiling
black tea, sugar, and ginger with milk.
At last, a little peace.
It's just a matter of getting used to it.
Once you get used to it,
you'll see how wonderful this country is.
I like this place. It's pretty great.
Seriously, Jotaro? You really mean that?
Talk about culture shock.
I'll like it once I get used to it, huh?
Well, they say that people
adapt to their surroundings.
Where's the john?
It's over there.
Polnareff.
Yeah?
What about your order?
I'll leave it to you.
It had better be something amazing.
Gorgeous, splendid food
that suits a Frenchman like me.
Which means we can pick anything.
Let's see, something he'll like...
Excuse me.
Oh, please wait, sir.
Please use this.
What's this stick for?
Hey.
The toilet's shaped oddly, but it's pretty clean.
A nice guy like myself can't
stand it when bathrooms are dirty.
Is something wrong?
D-D-D-D-Don't "Is something wrong?" at me!
Th-Th-Th-Th-The toilet...
The toilet...
Oink
There's a pig sticking
its head out of the toilet!
This toilet is unusual, even in India.
They accidentally made the
pig pen down below a little too high.
So when the pig gets hungry,
it sticks its head out.
Th-That's not what I'm aski—
Er, wait, what?!
That means this pig's food is...
That's why it's there?!
That's why you use this.
Here...
See? Now you can go while the pig's
recoiling from the blow to the head.
Our manager actually gets the
pig to lick his butt and always says
how great it is, because he gets so clean.
Please, take your time.
W-Wait! Don't leave me alone!
Gulp.
Menacing
I don't think I could ever get used to this...
I'll wait until we get to the hotel.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Crap.
H-He's gone?
I could have sworn I
saw something weird there.
I must have imagined it.
I guess I can't help it.
I mean, there was a pig in the toilet.
It's not surprising I'd see an illusion
of a monster outside the window.
So this is what they mean
by culture shock in India.
Wha...
What?!
Huh? Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
I can only see it in the mirror!
So this is the mirror Stand
that Jotaro heard about.
Th-This isn't good.
This really isn't good!
Silver Chariot!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Damn it!
Stand!
Where's the user? Who is it?!
The man with two right hands...
There are so many people...
Damn it!
What's wrong, Polnareff?
What's happening?
If that...
If that was the Stand, that means...
That means he's finally here!
Jotaro, the Stand user you heard
about that uses mirrors is here!
The bastard that killed my little sister!
The bastard that stepped all
over my sister's life, soul, and pride.
I can finally... I can finally see him!
The one you seek vengeance upon is here?
Mr. Joestar, I'll be traveling on my own here.
Wh—
Now that I know the guy
who killed my sister is nearby,
I'm not going to wait
for him to come after me.
I'd be at a disadvantage
if I let him attack me,
and it's not my style.
I'll find him first, and kill him!
Even though you don't know what
he looks like, or what his Stand is?
Knowing that he has two right hands is plenty!
And he knows that I'm after him, as well.
He should be worried that I'll
come for his head in his sleep.
See ya.
You'll go out for wool,
only to come home shorn.
What's that supposed to mean?
Just as it sounds.
Are you implying that I'm going to lose?
Indeed.
Can't you see that the enemy
purposely attacked to get you alone?
I will not allow you to travel alone, Polnareff.
Listen up. I'm going to make this clear.
I never cared about DIO.
I told you in Hong Kong that
I was only traveling with you
so I could get my revenge.
Mr. Joestar and Jotaro
should already know this.
I've been alone from the start!
I've always been fighting alone!
Such a selfish man!
Did you forget that you
were brainwashed by DIO?
Have you forgotten that
this all leads back to DIO?
Like you'd ever understand how
I feel after having my sister killed!
I heard that the last time you met DIO,
you got scared and ran away.
A coward like you would
never understand how I feel!
What did you say?
Don't touch me.
You were just lucky that
you beat me in Hong Kong.
Don't lecture me.
Why, you...
Oh, did that piss you off?
But don't forget that I'm a lot more
pissed off than you are right now!
You can just keep acting like
the mature one as always, Avdol.
Why, you—
Mr. Joestar!
That's enough. Let him go.
Now that he's like this, no one can stop him.
No, I'm just disappointed in him.
I didn't think he was that sort of man.
I did indeed run in fear.
That's also why I believe we will win,
and can say with certainty that you'll lose.
What?
Then I'll say this with certainty, too.
Your divination will be wrong.
Tromp Tromp Tromp
Get off.
I'm here to see a friend.
Go back yourself from here.
Please, make me your wife.
I will dedicate my life to you.
Just tell me whatever you wish of me.
So please, let me stay by your side forever.
Don't be stupid. You're still only sixteen.
I'm old enough to marry.
I love you.
Listen. I'm just a drifter.
I live each day like it's my last,
and one day, it will be my last.
Royalty like yourself can't
think about marrying me.
No matter how much we love each other.
Really?
You love me?
Yeah. You're the only one
I love in the whole world.
That's exactly why.
It's because I love you that I can't marry you.
You understand, don't you?
It's hard for me, too.
My chest feels like it could burst.
But I'll come see you once in
a while and hold you like this.
That's enough to make me happy.
Yes...
Later. Love ya.
It's not nice to eavesdrop.
I'm sure you'd like to say
I'm being as indirect as ever,
and that there're girls like her everywhere...
But she's an easy mark, and it's convenient.
She'd do anything for me,
even throw away her own life.
You know how I work, don't you?
Menacing
Mr. Centerfold.
By the way, about Silver Chariot's Polnareff.
Seems he's looking for you on his own.
What will you do?
He fell hook, line, and sinker
for your plan to lure him out.
Shall we kill him first?
Blam
Let's go.
With you and your Hanged Man,
and me, Hol Horse, with my Emperor,
We can kill 'em all.
Hanged Man
Centerfold
So he didn't come back after all.
What?
You saw him?
You're sure you saw a
man with two right hands?
Where?
Huh? That's weird.
I lost him. He was just right there, too.
What?
He was with that man right there.
Fwoosh
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Man, talk about a memorable quote.
Who the hell are you?
Hol Horse is the name.
I'm the user of the Stand
that suggests the Emperor card.
Lord DIO paid me to get rid of you guys.
Hey, country boy.
I don't need the self-introduction.
Do you know the man with two right hands?
Well, that was rude.
You asked, so I answered.
Well, whatever.
I came here with him.
He's nearby.
What?
Where is he?!
No point in asking that.
I, Hol Horse, will be taking care of you.
Trash like you always says that,
and it always ends up the other way around.
Oh? Was that funny?
Lord DIO said that Polnareff was
a man who underestimated others,
and that I'd have no problem beating him.
He was exactly right,
so I couldn't help but laugh.
If I can't see him until I defeat you,
then that's just what I'll do.
Bring it on.
You know Stratego, right?
The tank is stronger than the soldier,
and tanks are weak against mines.
See, it's pretty much the basics of battle.
My Emperor is stronger than you,
so I thought I'd let you know about
my Stand's abilities before we fight.
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Seriously, such a memorable quote.
What are you trying to say?
My Stand shoots.
A sword can't beat a weapon that shoots.
So, what? A pea shooter?
I'll kill you!
You underestimated me, Polnareff!
Blam
And now, you've lost!
Fwoom
If it takes off its armor...
It's nothing but a bullet!
What?!
I-Impossible! The trajectory curved!
C-Crap!
The bullet is also my Stand.
Underestimating me by
not even considering that
will cost you your life!
Polnareff!
Wha— Avdol!
I went looking for you because
I was worried, and look what I find!
You're too full of yourself, Polnareff.
W-Worried?
Damn you! Are you going to lecture me again?
The enemy knows everything about you!
You said you've lived life alone,
but from now on,
you won't be able to win alone!
What bad timing for an outsider to interfere.
Curve
Move, Polnareff! The bullet's coming back!
Magician's Red!
I'll burn it to cinders!
Damn that Avdol!
He went after Polnareff himself.
Where are you, Mr. Avdol? Polnareff?
I have a terrible feeling...
Hey, there's a weird fight going on over there.
The puddle...
What?!
Mr. Avdol!
Man, today must be my day.
My gun and Centerfold's mirror
don't do very well with Avdol's flames,
so we thought he'd be
our most formidable enemy.
Talk about luck!
There are no scary pieces
left in this game of Stratego.
Mr. Avdol!
H-He's just hurt...
It's just a minor wound.
See? He's going to start speaking...
He'll open his eyes at any moment.
Right, Mr. Avdol?
You're going to wake up, right?
Mr. Avdol, wake up!
Please! Mr. Avdol!
Impossible. This was too easy.
It was too quick!
That's what he gets for lecturing people.
Look at him now.
Wha...
What did you say, Polnareff?
Mr. Avdol was worried about you—
Who asked him for help?!
He likes to meddle in other people's business,
but he's slow as hell, so they got him.
Guys like him just get in the way...
That's why I said I'd do this myself.
You bastard...
He saved your life. How dare you...
It really annoys me!
Having people up and die on me...
Polnareff...
It just annoys me so much!
Next Episode Preview
He's got a bold face,
and yet he died so easily.
Come to think of it, she
was really good at sobbing...
Your sister, that is.
Are you telling me to hold back?
Don't fall for the enemy's provocation!
Mr. Avdol told you not to fight by yourself!
Episode 11
The Emperor and the Hanged Man Part 2