From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 23: The Warrior of Wind
T-That wind...
It's flowing toward Wamuu.
My ultimate mastery:
Atmospheric Rift!
T-That's wind?!
You're near the flame,
so I only know your
approximate location.
But now that you can't use Hamon,
I'll find you eventually...
...and cut you down.
Atmospheric Rift
is Wamuu's final weapon.
The pipes he uses to cloak himself
suck up huge amounts of air
and then compress it.
The air is then blasted out of
a paper-thin slit.
It is a razor made of wind.
But it creates a terrible amount of
heat and friction, even for Wamuu.
His body can't handle it,
so it's falling apart.
But that tragic figure
is truly breathtaking.
Victory is yours!
Take his life to salve your wounds!
JoJo!
I-It's close!
I'll have to use one of my tricks!
This one's called the Hamon oil trick!
His lungs are like
high-pressure oxygen tanks.
Those pipes...
If I can hit them...
...he'll suck in the flames and explode!
But this is the last ace up my sleeve.
If I mess this up...
I've got you now!
Blast it!
Take this, Wamuu!
A firebomb?
Pathetic.
I can sense things
that are away from the flames.
You're out of tricks.
And that cry gave away your position.
Now...
Atmospheric Rift!
Caesar!
Lend me your aid!
More fire?
I can sense things away from the flames.
And now I will cut you in half
to claim my victory.
JoJo!
H-He's finally won it.
Wamuu...
You lost the moment
I threw Caesar's bandana.
Don't you see I meant for you
to break the bottle?
Your ability to cut it so easily
led to your defeat.
The oil that was inside is now vapor.
And the bandana you sliced up?
The fire...
...it's still burning.
And I'm sucking it in!
Wamuu...
You were an admirable fighter.
But a powerful ally named Caesar
was with me this whole time.
H-He lost.
He lost!
Lord Wamuu!
JoJo, that creature can regenerate,
even after exploding like that.
Use your strongest Hamon
to finish him completely!
S-So it's finally over, Jo...Jo...
It is.
You paid me back for Caesar.
I did.
Then do it.
Finish me.
I will!
W-What is this?!
That smoke isn't from the explosion.
It's from your wounds.
The Hamon from your limbs
spread throughout your body.
I know how painful that must be
for your kind.
I cannot mend you.
But my blood can ease
your pain before you go.
Do you wish to shame me as I die?
Stop! I don't need your pity!
Pity?
Did you say pity?
So why did you ignore the bubble
that carried Caesar's bandana and this ring?
Was it pity?
It was because that man
was a proud warrior.
I wished to honor him.
No, JoJo, you don't...
I do, Wamuu.
A fight is a fight.
My grief for Caesar is my grief.
Somehow, I wanted to honor you in return.
My blood pays tribute to you.
I have lost, JoJo.
It seems that as a warrior,
you stand taller than I did.
Kill the bastard!
Hold!
What betrayal is this?!
What?!
You recreants!
Wamuu!
W-Why?
I am sworn to Lord Kars, but I will
not allow the vampires to attack you.
I told Caesar this as well.
It's not because I am sentimental.
To me, only the strong are real.
Victory alone is just and admirable.
I merely lived according
to my own code of honor.
To me, immortality was a trivial thing.
All that mattered
was living up to my code.
Now...
Drink the antidote for me.
Do it before I fade.
Will you see?
I don't need eyes, a horn, or words.
I will know.
The action is what matters.
I have no regrets.
I am glad I was able
to witness your growth.
Perhaps I lived these thousands
of years in order to
meet you at the end.
Fare...well...
Jo...Jo...
Wamuu merged into the wind.
JoJo immediately gave
his opponent a last salute.
Though he shed no tears,
they had shared a silent song.
They had shared an affinity.
Wamuu, kill him.
B-But Lord Kars...
With respect, he's only a boy.
A boy? That he is.
That's why he must die.
If these Hamon-users grow up,
they'll be deadly enemies.
And humans grow quite rapidly.
Can you do it, Wamuu?
Well, since you can't do it yourself...
...let me show you how.
This is how it's done, Wamuu!
Wamuu...
He was too pure a warrior.
That purity made him weak!
Hey, Wamuu just lost!
What a disappointment.
That fool was just posturing.
Your friends are so low,
it makes me want to puke.
Lord Kars...
H-He's drinking us.
Now only I remain.
However...
I alone always stand on top!
Look at Lord Kars!
Lord Kars is...!
He's ready to fight!
But Lord Kars, there's no reason
to fight one-on-one!
Who needs rules? Let us take them!
We'll turn them into sprays of blood!
I thought you'd do this!
I told you!
T-The Red Stone!
It's me against Kars, one-on-one.
But if you don't like those terms,
I'll just smash it!
I'm a man of my word.
One-on-one.
My promise still stands.
That's why I revealed my horn to you.
As for my underlings' behavior,
they're already dead, as you can see.
Lord Kars?!
All I want is that Red Stone.
However, Wamuu and Esidisi
were my comrades for 10,000 years.
I must honor both their deaths
and their pride.
I will fight you Hamon-users fairly...
...and finish this with my own hands.
And Lisa Lisa, after seeing you fight,
I won't think of you as a woman.
I will fight you with all my strength.
Come!
We fight over there.
The temple at Piz Berlina.
Champions once came here to drink the
blood of the fallen mixed with liquor.
They thanked the gods
for the joy of life.
It's not an arena,
but it will add to our fight.
C-Coach Lisa Lisa, you may be strong,
but you're still a woman.
He looks weaker than Wamuu.
I'll take him!
You won't.
I haven't lived my life so that
a stripling has to stand up for me.
You're 50, all right!
I will use my Brilliant Bone Blade.
I would offend Wamuu
if I didn't offer you a weapon.
Take your pick.
My scarf will suffice.
I see.
Then let us fight.
T-There's no violence in Kars's stance.
How can he fight without violence?
What's wrong? Not coming?
Then I'll have to make a move!
Kars disappeared with that light!
W-Where is he?!
Kars... I can feel something...
But it's coming from both
above and below.
Brilliant Bone Blade!
A crack in the pillar!
Snake Muffler!
This Satiporoja beetle scarf
is a perfect Hamon conductor.
It is a weapon and a life-detector!
It even picks up attacks from behind!
S-She did it!
That's my coach! Wonderful!
He didn't compare to Wamuu,
but barkers seldom bite!
Though you are better than me, coach!
Wha--?!
L-Lord Kars!
Kars is behind her.
Who is b-below her?
W-What the...?!
What the hell is going on?!
Kars wasn't the one fighting!
It was a double!
How utterly stupid.
Why would I fight one-on-one?
All I want is the Red Stone.
My goal is to be the ultimate life form.
I am not a warrior like Wamuu,
nor am I a romantic.
No matter what the method,
in the end...
...victory is all that matters!
T-That's why I felt no violence.
He never intended to fight me himself.
It's over!
Jo...Jo...
The Red Stone is mine!
Now all that's left is for all of you
to kill that annoying JoJo!
K-Kars!
You're going down!
Kars!
Out of the way!
I'll split your damned skulls!
Zoom Punch!
Your Hamon isn't working.
He's weakened! Now--
Rebuff Overdrive!
You look worn out.
Your breathing is ragged
and your Hamon is weak.
And you're all that's left of
the Hamon-users Lisa Lisa trained.
Will you last?
Will you last, JoJo?
S-Son of a...
Flay him alive!
C-Crap!
T-That light!
That face!
Listen up, vampires!
You're up against von Stroheim
and the German elite!
And we're the Speedwagon Foundation
Special Forces!
JoJo!
I-It's Speedwagon!
And Smokey from New York!
My right leg is a bit stiff...
...but my body has been repaired!
Now taste our anti-vampire weaponry!
Ultraviolet lasers!
The Speedwagon Foundation miniaturized them,
but he does like to brag.
Crafty little creatures.
Where is JoJo?
He's gone!
He's as quick as ever.
Take your eyes off him
and he'll hatch a scheme in no time.
You crossed a line
you shouldn't have crossed.
You said you'd fight fairly,
but you cheated Lisa Lisa!
And that act betrayed the memory
of Wamuu, your fallen comrade!
You can save your indignation, scum.
The end justifies the means.
All that matters is the Red Stone.
You have to save effort,
minimize danger,
avoid risks,
and move your pawns carefully.
That is the real battle.
And now I'll maneuver you
into my hands and to your death.
Let me tell you something, Kars!
I've never hated anyone as much as you!
You hate me?
Then show me.
One-on-one. We'll fight
one-on-one like you wanted.
Lisa Lisa is mostly dead.
But only mostly.
I did that on purpose. I left her alive.
Why would I do that?
She's another pawn.
JoJo, she's a pawn I can use
against you.
Bastard!
I've sewn her feet together
with this rope.
Why am I doing this?
Here's why!
Lisa Lisa!
Off you go!
She'd be a bad pawn if she fell!
If you let go, she'll splatter
on the ground and die!
J-JoJo! Lisa Lisa!
Lisa Lisa?
That Lisa Lisa?
Do you mean the baby on the ship
Granny Erina told us about?
T-That means that woman is JoJo's...
Now you're glued to that spot.
Welcome to real battle, JoJo.
I'll just walk up to you
and slice you down while you can't move!
Kars, you bastard!
I hope you rot in hell forever!
JoJo doesn't know.
He doesn't know that
that woman is his own mother!
Next episode
Are the vampires finished?!
I want to kill you at my leisure.
The fire is a gamble!
This child... This child...
Don't, von Stroheim!
No!
Chapter 24: The Ties that Bind JoJo