Let me see the key we obtained again.
Go to the drinking fountain with a turtle
and use this key.
Don't tell me he...
The Thankful Death!
Just the driver... It doesn't look
like anyone else is in here.
There it is!
Something took the bait!
Wh-What the hell is this needle-like thing?!
A d-different Stand than
the one that's aging us?
Bro, where did you go?!
Episodio 15  The Thankful Death Part 1
Why aren't you here?!
Bucciarati and his crew were on this train!
But I wonder who I hooked.
It's definitely not Trish.
The strength pulling on
this rod belongs to a man.
The needle dug into his left hand.
He weighs 68 kilograms!
I'll reel you right in!
Whoa, hang on a second...
Th-This needle's sinking in deeper!
It's so fast!
It's moving up my arm at incredible speed!
Th-This line...
This must be Mista!
The thing that tried to cut
the line was a bullet!
The gunslinger is Guido Mista!
You can't cut my Fisher Man's line!
I wonder where the impact that
hit the line will end up going?
I'm gonna reel you right in!
I need to get this line out or I'm finished!
Damn it! It's going to make
its way up to my brain!
Sh-Shit!
Six Bullets! Grab this hook and stop it!
I-It's no use! We're being pulled!
We can't stop it with our power!
Sh-Shit... I'm just going
to have to look for it.
I'm just gonna have to find it!
Find it!
We need to find it, no matter what!
What was that?
Was that Mista's pistol?
Who the hell are you even shooting at?
What if you hit one of the other passengers?
Or did you shoot in hopes
that you'd actually hit me?
It's no use!
The hook is about to travel
deep into your ear!
We have to aim lower or the ice
won't get blown out of the glass!
A bit lower! Aim a bit lower!
Over here! Blast right into it!
We found the ice!
Shatter it, boys!
What do you think you're doing?!
I knew that bastard would
be cooling himself, too,
to the point that he'd lose his mind!
Damn it!
How could you?! The ice...
He's all pale and screaming.
My ice!
Could this guy be...
It's him!
He's the guy with the line and hook!
That fishing-rod-looking thing is his Stand!
R-Run for it!
Ice! I need to find some ice,
or I'm going to die of old age, too!
H-Help me...
O-Out of my way, gramps!
Get your zombie hands off of—
My body feels so heavy,
I don't want to move...
I ordered the really fatty steak,
but now I don't want to eat it anymore...
Don't touch me!
Woohoo! We got his hand!
Call Mista over here now!
Mista!
Hurry up and get over here, Mista!
Mista, over here!
We found the enemy Stand user!
Six Bullets, all of you
come back to the bullets.
It doesn't really matter
if you answer me or not,
but I'm going to ask you one very, very...
simple question.
If you don't answer within two
seconds of me asking the question,
I'll shoot a bullet into each of your eyes.
"Uno, due..." I won't wait any longer than that.
Got it?
All right. Here's the question.
Where the hell is your friend?
Uno...
H-Hell if I know!
I don't know where he is, either!
Due... All right. Then die.
Hey... Please help me...
I've always loved fatty steak so much,
but now I don't wanna eat it anymore...
Hey! Get out of the way! You'll want
to eat meat again soon enough!
No, I can't eat anything anymore...
Or rather, you won't be able to,
Mista.
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Thankful Death...
Huh? Wh-What?
W-Wait! Are you...
You bastard!
It works even faster when
I directly touch you.
Its power is at full strength...
when Thankful Death touches you.
B-Bullets...
Th-This speed... Shit...
I-Is that you, Bro?
Are you my Bro?!
I-I didn't notice at all!
Y-You were there the whole time?
I-I can't believe you aged yourself to
blend in with the other passengers...
Bro! Prosciutto! You're so awesome!
S-Stop! Why are you so mad, Bro?!
You friggin' moron!
What the hell was that?! Huh?!
I didn't know he was going to ambush me!
What could I do?!
You still don't get it?
Pesci, you friggin' mammoni!
Please stop hitting me, Bro!
Listen up! The reason I'm mad is
because you're so weak-minded, Pesci!
Of course, they did blast away
your ice, so you were in shock.
This is aging me, too, so it's bad news.
But if it were any other guy from our team,
they wouldn't have made their
Stand go away when they were
that close to finishing off an enemy!
Even if they lost an arm or a leg!
You're a damn mammoni, Pesci.
You freaked out. You're such a baby.
It's not because of the ice.
You're actually scared
deep inside your heart.
Grow up, Pesci.
If you don't grow up,
we'll never get our glory.
We'll never defeat Bucciarati and his crew.
And just so we're clear...
Our team isn't some buddy-buddy
club with a bunch of losers
who just talk about killing people
while trying to cheer each other up.
Once we decide in our hearts
that we're gonna kill someone,
the deed's already been done!
Let's go, Pesci.
Here, have some ice.
You mentioned earlier
that you sensed another presence
in the driver's cab, didn't you?
I don't know how they're hiding in there,
but the girl's in the driver's cab!
Prosciutto
The Thankful Death
Don't worry about Narancia!
Save the ice in the glass for yourself!
You need to keep your body chilled.
Fanning air and the chill from
a cold towel aren't enough.
There's no effect unless you use ice.
At this rate, he'll be the first to die.
Narancia and the rest of us are willing to
risk our lives to follow the boss's orders.
You just need to think about your safety.
That's our job.
You're not here because you
want to be here, after all.
And as for the enemy who's
causing us all to age...
Mista will take care of him.
I'm sure... he'll do something...
Mista...
Where and how are they hiding?
I'm finally getting it.
I need to start thinking in
four dimensions to find them.
Bucciarati received something black at
the station platform from the boss.
That's it. That's what I need
to find in this driver's cab.
Hey, Pesci.
What do you think that presence
you felt in this driver's cab was?
You don't feel it now?
A-About that... Bro...
You shouldn't expect much from me.
I'm not the brightest.
Pesci, Pesci, Pesci, Pesci...
I believe in you.
If you're still concerned about
me yelling at you earlier,
you just need to be more confident.
Your Fisher Man is unbeatable
when you actually apply yourself.
Right?
That presence you felt earlier
is extremely suspicious.
It's do or die time, Pesci.
It's okay to be confident in your ability.
R-Really?
Yes!
Try to remember. It doesn't
matter how trivial it seems.
Did anything seem strange?
Like maybe something black?
Huh? Something... black?
That's it, Bro!
I meant to look under
the driver's seat earlier!
There was something weird!
S-Sorry... I guess I was just imagining it.
So, yeah... You shouldn't count
on me or my intuition, after all...
No, I don't think you're wrong.
Say what?!
Excellent work, Pesci.
The mystery's been solved.
I now understand everything thanks to you.
B-Bro? Wh-What are you...
Why is there suddenly animal
shit under the driver's seat?
I don't understand at all!
This isn't mouse shit, either.
If it were a mouse, it'd be dead by now.
This shit's not old.
It looks like it was just left here.
So what does that mean, huh?
Stand abilities don't only belong to humans.
And that means...
This animal is moving through the shadows!
Thankful Death!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
I-It's a turtle? It's a friggin' turtle?!
We found her! It's Trish!
I can see the others, too!
Just as I thought, they're all about
to die of old age, except for Trish!
That settles it!
I'll send even more of the
aging ability into the turtle!
Thankful Dead!
Wait a sec, Bro!
Isn't there... one guy missing?
There's someone missing in there!
Mista! Please get up!
This is all the ice I have left,
but please feel better!
I'm not sure if it's thanks
to my attentive nature,
or if I was just lucky...
But because I put that piece of ice
I'd picked up earlier into my hat...
Number Five... It seems you
were able to reverse the aging.
Thanks for stopping those bullets
for me... All three of them.
Number Five... I have one more request...
If you want to send one of us to Bucciarati,
I already revived Number Six,
and he went on ahead!
He took the ice in your pocket and
went to tell them that two enemies
were heading for the turtle!
That's perfect... I don't
need the ice anymore...
after all...
Mista!
It's Bucciarati, Bro!
Bucciarati's the one missing!
It doesn't matter if Bucciarati's
in there or not!
All that matters is that we take Trish alive!
Thankful Death!
What the hell?!
You're pretty intuitive... And fast, too.
I just have to defeat him, right?
The one in black!
That's right, Bucciarati!
If you defeat him,
everyone's aging will be reversed!
What the hell is Mista's Stand doing here?!
I personally blasted three
holes into his head...
So why is that thing here with an ice cube?!
Don't let that thing touch you!
If it does, you'll age way, way faster!
Get 'em!
H-He's fast...
Bro!
Don't worry about me!
Deal with the guys in the turtle!
Hurry it up! Kill the rest of his crew!
That was a little naïve,
wasn't it, Bucciarati?
After Mista went to all that
trouble to warn you...
Defeating me, even if it costs the lives
of your crew, to protect the girl...
Isn't that your mission?
You fail as a capo. Take this!
What?!
I will complete this mission,
and I will also protect my crew.
It won't be hard for me to do both
if I'm only facing the likes of you.
It's fast...
It's definitely fast...
Your... Zipper Man, was it?
It's definitely faster...
But you're the one who doesn't seem
to understand speed, Bucciarati!
I seem to be out of breath...
But the same goes for you, Bucciarati.
Since we used our Stands at full speed,
we both used up a lot of energy.
You didn't comprehend that and
tried to go as fast as you could,
even though you're still aging
despite standing still!
The more horsepower a car has,
the warmer it gets!
That's because you're burning calories.
You're a smart guy, so I'm
sure you can figure out...
what'll happen when your body gets warmer!
B-Bucciarati!
Th-The ice is starting to lose its effect!
So what are you going to do now, huh?
This zipper you gave me
is starting to close.
The zipper on my chin is already gone.
What's the matter?
Exhausted from your stiff shoulders?
Zipper Man!
I can see your movements!
You're too slow, Bucciarati!
I've got you! Now you're all finished!
And then we'll be taking
the boss's daughter!
I was aware of what would
happen if my body warmed up.
I was also prepared to get caught.
I will complete this mission.
I will also protect my crew.
One of the hardest parts of being a
capo is the fact that I have to do both.
Are you prepared?
I am.
Wha—
Y-You can't mean...
You bastard! You can't be serious!
Doing both is simple,
if I can get you off this train.
If I can just undo the aging,
my five subordinates will be back,
and we'll be able to protect Trish!
You bastard! Y-You can't be serious! Let go!
We're moving at 150 kilometers per hour!
Oh, come on, now. You're
the one who grabbed me.
Are you trying to die?! You bastard!
Episodio 16
The Thankful Death Part 2