M-Move, arm!
The Hamon will fill my head!
I have to do something
before that happens!
Lord Dio!
We'll find you a new body.
An excerpt from the December 4, 1888
edition of The London Press:
"73 of the 452 people living in Wind
Knights Lot went missing overnight."
"Investigators have one lead
based on witness accounts."
"Four outsiders were seen burning
a man's clothing at the cliff's base."
"One of them was seen smashing
a curious stone mask with a hammer."
Our work is done!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 9: The Last Hamon
Joestar heir Jonathan Joestar weds
Erina, only daughter of the Pendletons!
They plan to spend their
honeymoon in America.
Good heavens!
Look at the time!
They're about to depart!
Hey!
Hi, Mr. Speedwagon!
You almost missed seeing them off!
Sorry I'm late.
So where are they?
They're on the ship.
It's about to set sail.
What?!
Where can I see them?!
Father STYX...
...we expect much
from your mission to Mexico.
I'll do what I can.
Jonathan! Where are you?!
Gangway!
What weighs so much in this thing?
How should I know?
Some weird Asian told me to move it.
Hey. Did you guys hear that?
Quit flapping your gums and move!
We don't get paid till the job's done!
Ouch! What a bunch of louts!
Mr. Speedwagon!
Look! There they are!
Hey!
Mr. Joestar!
What a joyous occasion!
Make a happy life for yourselves!
I'll always be here for you.
If you need me, I'll come running!
Though I might just get in the way.
Mr. Joestar!
Bon voyage!
-Atlantic Ocean, en route to America-
One bird all alone,
separated from its flock?
Erina...
Is something wrong?
Why are you crying?
These are tears of joy.
Because I am with you.
Even back then, you strove
to be a true gentleman,
no matter the consequences.
And now the proud
Jonathan Joestar is in my arms.
I feel the same way.
When my heart was frozen in despair,
you came and warmed me.
I am happy to have saved a world
with you living in it.
I wish Dad could've met you.
Erina, let's go and eat!
Jonathan!
I was about to tell you
to watch your head.
I hope today never ends.
Crap, that's the engine room.
It sure fell into a filthy place.
I could just sell it,
but it makes me money.
Dear Lord...
You sure do like picking on me.
I couldn't. I've never had alcohol.
Try a little. Just a sip.
It's not that strong.
Give it a taste.
Here.
Y-You're...!
Jonathan?
No!
There's no way...
Dio is...alive...
Erina, go to our room and
don't forget to lock the door!
What's with this trunk?
The lock is open.
That's funny.
I can see a catch glinting inside.
That means...the trunk
is locked from the inside!
Stop!
You're...!
Is my new body here?
D-Dio!
Jonathan is worried.
There's something wrong.
JoJo, look.
See what has become of me.
There is a reason
I come before you in this state.
Why would I show you my weakness?
Because, JoJo, though I once
despised you, I now respect you.
I respect your courage,
your spirit and your power.
I realize that now.
Dio!
JoJo...
If it weren't for you,
I never would
have obtained the mask's power.
But because of you, the world
has slipped from my grasp.
If there is a god who controls fate,
I am sure he bound ours the tightest.
Our two existences are truly one.
I will take the body of
the only man I respect
and live in eternal glory!
That is the destiny laid out for me!
You will feel no pain,
that is my last gift to you!
His eyes...! No!
Live on as my body, JoJo!
Jonathan!
J-Jonathan...
Eri...na...
What a pity.
If you had just held still,
it would have been a painless death.
Torn from your fairy tale into hell,
unable to understand or even speak?
Did JoJo never tell you of me,
the mythical dweller in the dark?
I may not look like much, but surely
you remember me, Erina Pendleton.
No, it's Mrs. Erina Joestar now,
isn't it?
Dio!
The ship's full of monsters!
As you ordered,
I drained the life of one passenger.
And now most of the ship
has joined our family!
And now we go to America.
Isn't that right, Lord Dio?
I can't speak.
I can't even breathe.
Erina... Erina!
I have to save...
I can't charge my Hamon.
Behold, Lord Dio!
The sniveling whelp can't breathe!
He'll cause no mischief
with Hamon now!
This is what he gets for
crossing you, Lord Dio.
Now it's time to play.
Or shall I just wait a few minutes
for him to suffocate, hmm?
Listen, Wang Chan!
I'll tolerate no insult to JoJo!
He is the man who brought me
to my current state.
Show him some respect by severing
his head painlessly.
Yes, Lord Dio.
And now my dear friend's body
will become my future!
Jonathan!
He's up to something!
Stay back!
He might have one last trick
up his sleeve!
He can do nothing!
Surely Lord Dio overestimates him!
Now I'll scoop out what little brains
you have with my fingers!
Must...save Erina.
I'll have to use the last bit of Hamon
left in my body all at once.
A little will do.
Look out, Wang Chan!
S-Something broke inside of my body.
Something important.
N-No!
This... This is the end.
My last Hamon.
It was too weak to destroy
that zombie completely.
But it was enough.
W-What the...?!
JoJo must have done something
to Wang Chan's body!
He disrupted its functions
without destroying it.
He's made it cling tightly
to the machinery.
A-And the device it's clinging to...
...is the paddle's screw shaft!
The strength of a zombie is enough
to stop the paddle!
If the shaft stops, the steam inside
the piston will keep building up!
And after a while...
...the ship will explode!
Jonathan, this can't be.
How could this happen to us?
R-Run, Erina.
The s-ship will explode.
I don't know exactly what is going on.
It's too much for me.
I don't know if I should cry or scream.
Maybe I should just faint away.
But I can say one thing.
Erina Joestar...
...will die with you.
In the warmth of these lips, alas,
I feel the touch of death.
Jonathan Joestar is dying.
But we're together.
I want to stay like this forever.
Until the ship explodes
and everything burns.
Until everything is gone.
It's all right to cry.
But you...have to keep living.
It's like a storybook!
You want me to save a baby and run?
To me, that heroism is cruelty.
My only wish is to die with you.
That woman died to save her child.
My mother did the same for me.
Go with the baby. Hurry!
You plan to destroy the whole ship!
JoJo, you really never give up!
But neither do I!
I will live! No matter what!
Along with your body!
Zombies!
Devour Wang Chan's body
and restart the piston!
It's starting to explode.
Jonathan!
It's already exploding!
I have to protect myself
from the sun at all times!
So I am already prepared
in the event of an explosion!
Erina, take a good look!
Now that JoJo can't use Hamon,
I can safely steal his body!
Then I will step into that trunk,
my humble boudoir.
That little shelter can withstand
a blast made by a ton of dynamite!
Here I come, JoJo!
And I bid you welcome,
my new, eternal body!
Jonathan!
Dio...
Like you said, our fates might truly
be one in the same.
I feel an odd warmth toward you.
Now our lives are bound completely.
And they will vanish
along with this ship.
Fare...well...
...Erina.
Let me go, JoJo!
Release me!
Think about it!
You'd like a shot at eternity, right?
I can heal your wounds!
You can live forever with Erina, JoJo!
JoJo?!
He... He's...
He's dead.
Jonathan Joestar
Died February 7, 1889
passed away into oblivion.
His life was a piece of history
invisible to ordinary people.
They will never hear the tale
of his noble accomplishments.
But his descendants will.
The new life that was inside me
at that time will surely hear his story.
Erina Joestar was rescued
soon after near the Canary Islands.
And the book of the stone mask
closed for a time.
But this was only the beginning
of a new adventure.
Part 1: Phantom Blood -- Fin
Next episode
It was the fall of 1938.
Nice to see you, Speedwagon.
How did you know that, bastard?
Take him down!
I'm Joseph Joestar.
Call me JoJo.
Chapter 10: JoJo in New York