Hey, mister! This is the best deal
you're going to find in town!
That's exactly what the other guy said.
Then as a bonus, I'll give
you a tour of the city!
Seriously?
Hilarious!
Huh? What?
What's wrong?
My bag is gone!
What?
Here you go.
So, any changes lately?
Not at all, thanks to you.
I see.
Sorry to bother you.
This is what you want, right?
Yeah!
Oh, but this is all I have right now.
Then this is all I can sell you.
Naples: a city located in southern Italy.
It's a famous tourist spot so beautiful that
people say you should see it
at least once before you die.
Pardon us.
How do you get to Santa Chiara?
Oh, to get to Santa Chiara, go straight,
and then, at the first light—
See? I told you!
I told you it was over there.
My bad...
Thanks so mu—
Whoa, there.
Are you all right?
Th-Thank you...
Um, I'm sorry about that.
Be more careful.
Let's go.
Hey.
You dropped this.
Thank you so much!
No problem.
Hey, wasn't that guy super cool?
I should've asked for a picture.
Did those just come out of my bag?
What? They probably just
landed on it for a second.
Yeah, you're right.
You can't let your guard down in this city.
Pardon me.
Could I get a cone with a scoop of
chocolate and a scoop of pistachio?
Make that two.
You got it.
Episodio 01   Golden Wind
Hey! How many times do I have to tell you
that you can't run your business
here without a license?
Move your car!
Honestly...
You only moved one car length away!
So, whaddya say? It's faster than lining up.
What do you think?
I'll get you into the city real cheap.
Really? How cheap?
L-Luca!
Didn't I tell you that you need to pay
the protection fees you owe me
before doing any more business?
You can't be serious!
I told you that you need to pay
the protection fees you owe me
before doing any more business, right?
But...
Right?!
But I have a family...
P-Please stop!
You should think more about your
friendship with me than your family...
Got it?
I'm not the only one ignoring
you to keep doing business!
Well, who?
Who is it?
I-It's Giorno! Giorno Giovanna!
Giorno?
That kid's been making a fortune lately!
Well, I'll deal with him later.
Hey, you!
You can't run your business
here without a license!
Go somewhere else!
Buon giorno!
I'm finally here!
That flight was so long!
The air sure is different here!
Now, then, time to get to work.
Haruno Shiobana... That's an unusual name.
First, I need to get to my hotel.
I want to dump my luggage so I can
move around a bit more freely.
Let's see... Where's the taxi pick-up...
Whoa, that's amazing!
I know, right? That trick is amazing!
This shouldn't be possible!
How are you even doing that?
That's so gross!
How'd you stuff your whole
ear into your head?
Man, that was entertaining!
Thanks.
Don't attract too much attention
with your job here.
Looking for a taxi?
No, n-not really...
You sure?
I'm just finishing up my part-time job and
about to head home, so I'll make it cheap.
How about 180,000 lire to
get you into the city?
180,000? That's... about 10,000 yen.
That's way too expensive!
The basic rate is about half that!
Wow, you speak the language perfectly.
Huh?
Did you used to live in Italy?
No, I just had Rohan-sensei make it
so I could speak... Never mind that!
M-More importantly, you're saying you'll drive?
You look like you're only in
middle school or high school.
And I saw you give the
security guys something.
I'm pretty sure I saw some money.
What's that about?
Come on, now. You don't need
to worry about those things.
Okay, how about for 10,000 lire?
I won't even ask for a tip.
I'll take you into the
city for exactly 10,000.
Huh? 10,000 would be about... 500 yen?!
No, it's okay.
I'll just wait at the taxi pick-up...
Are you sure?
You'll really only charge 10,000?
Yup.
But you'll have to load your
luggage on your own.
Since I'm not asking for a tip.
Put your luggage up front.
You can sit in the back.
Just so you know,
you'd better not think of me as some
Japanese tourist who's not used to traveling.
Just get me to my hotel in earnest.
Yes. I'll get you there in earnest.
Or should I say...
I'll get your empty luggage there.
Huh? Wait... I didn't even get in yet...
Keep your mouth shut!
Don't tell me...
Hold it!
Ciao!
Reverb Act 3!
Too bad for you...
Didn't I tell you not to underestimate me?
You can run if you want.
As long as my luggage is safe, I don't care.
Look at that! Giorno actually screwed up!
That's what he gets for trying to trick
a Japanese tourist when he's
half Japanese himself!
Though people would never
be able to tell he's Japanese,
with that hair color and a
name like Giorno Giovanna.
It couldn't be...
Huh? It's gone! How?!
Is this some kind of egg?
I-Is it a Stand?! But that's impossible!
Would one show up the
second I get to Italy?!
That's not a Stand! The way that frog felt...
It's actually alive!
But seriously, how'd my suitcase disappear?!
He didn't have any time to hide it!
This is horrible!
This is only a hunch, but...
Excuse me!
Could I ask you some questions
about that taxi driver?
I think it's about time...
Are you Giorno Giovanna?
This is the first time we're meeting.
Do you know who I am, Giorno?
Leaky Eye Luca.
I heard that
even after someone stabbed a knife deep
into your face, you didn't stop fighting.
And because of that,
even though your wound has healed,
your eye is always watering.
Hey, why don't you have a seat right here?
Come on, sit down.
It's tiring having to look up at you to talk.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Fifteen?! Wow, you're just a kid!
Say, Giorno, there are three "yous"
to remember in friendship.
Three "yous," got that?
The first one is you don't lie.
The second one is you don't hold grudges.
And the third is you respect the other.
Sounds good, right? Those are
the three "yous" of friendship.
Can I help you?
Smack
I'm the one talking right now!
Who said you could ask
questions, you dumbass?!
I heard you've been working
part-time around the airport...
I, Leaky Eye Luca, haven't received
any of the gifts that you should've
given me out of respect yet.
How do you expect our
friendship to last like that?
Let me take a peek at your wallet.
Luca.
I already paid my protection fees.
I don't have any money.
To the security guards?!
That has nothing to do with me!
What's this? A photo of a family member?
Where's my money?
I want the money! Show me your wallet!
Luca...
Don't make me say the same thing twice.
I told you, I already paid,
so I don't have any.
Don't make me say it a third time.
You little shit!
What the hell is that creature?
It came back.
Smack it off!
This frog has nothing to do with this.
I won't smack it off.
I gave you an order, and I told
you to pay me a protection fee!
So you're going to disobey both of those?
You're going to tell me, Leaky Eye Luca,
"no" to both of those things?!
This is a living creature
that has its own conscience,
and it's thinking on its own.
You really shouldn't.
You're... You're...
I could never just smack it off.
Don't! It's harmless as long
as you don't do anything!
You're finished!
Whack
I told you not to.
It's not even that loyal to me yet.
It's just trying to protect itself.
It has its own life.
Any attack on it becomes an attack
on oneself, and it's fatal.
And...
I asked you not to make me say it a third time.
Making me say the same
thing over and over again
is useless.
And I hate that because it's useless.
Totally useless.
A piece of this guy's skin?
Yeah. I want you to get a sample
of it and send it to me, Koichi,
so the Speedwagon Foundation
can check its composition.
Its composition? Who is this guy?
His father, who died, was a bit special.
That's why we want to investigate.
It can be thin. I just need
you to get me a piece.
That's it.
I see...
I'll cover all your expenses for this trip.
What?! All of them?
Hmm...
I'm sorry if this sounds rude, but this
guy sort of looks like you, Jotaro.
The address on this picture
is somewhere around here...
How careless.
You don't need to worry about them.
No one around here is dumb enough
to try and steal their briefcase.
Oh... I guess this is a nice neighborhood.
Hey, can I sit next to you?
Would you like to come in for a meal, sir?
No, I'm going to sit next to him!
N-No, it's okay!
Hey, Giorno! Have some tea with me!
What? Wait, I'll pay for you!
You guys are too loud.
No, me! Me!
I like being alone. Go away.
Fine...
See you tomorrow, Giorno!
Ciao!
Th-That's—
Hey! Whose money is that?!
Are you using my money?!
You?! How'd you know I was here?
Give me back my passport!
Where's my luggage?!
It hurts me to say this,
but they're gone.
I sold them off, unfortunately.
So stop following me.
You're not getting away this time!
What's with this weight?
Wait... So that wasn't
a malfunction earlier?
Don't tell me... he has the same
kind of powers as me...
What did you just say?
It's heavy!
Golden Wind!
Life, spring forth!
Bring forth new life!
I think I just caught a glimpse of something.
Act 3!
That bastard disappeared.
That's impossible!
There's no way he'd be able to escape
3 Freeze's range that easily!
I'll say this one more time.
Don't even think about coming after me.
I hate saying things twice
when I shouldn't have to.
Because it's useless to say it twice.
I'll say this for your own good.
You shouldn't do things that are useless.
Knock him down, Act 3!
Th-The attack on the tree
came back to me...
I took something of yours,
but I can tell you held back
when you were trying to hit me,
when I see what that damage has done to you.
You're a good person.
There's no doubt about it.
Giorno Giovanna...
He's a Stand user!
Giorno Giovanna
Golden Wind
Hello?
Jotaro, it's me, Koichi!
Oh, Koichi. Did you get to Italy?
I found him!
The guy you asked me to find!
Haruno Shiobana!
That was fast.
Where do I even begin?
I immediately ran into him at the airport...
And, yes, it's safe to say...
He's a Stand user!
He goes by the name Giorno Giovanna in Italy.
You mentioned before that
Stand users are drawn to
other Stand users, right?
We seriously met by coincidence!
He's a student, but he
acts like a delinquent.
He stole my money and my luggage!
And it appears his Stand's ability is
returning his opponent's
attack right back at them.
Sorry about all this.
I'll get you a hotel and wire you some money.
Thank you.
Also, his hair was blond,
unlike in the picture.
After asking some people
who knew him about it,
they said that he didn't dye it.
It just suddenly turned that color.
Something about his dead father's genes.
Who's his father?
Are you and his father somehow related?
I'm the one
who killed his father.
His name is DIO Brando.
DIO?
You mean the one involved
with the bow and arrow?
Stab
I found out this year that
DIO may have had a child.
That's why I wanted to find out for sure
if Giorno Giovanna was really DIO's child,
and if he's somehow inherited his body.
But doesn't DIO's body belong
to the Joestar bloodline?
The fact that his hair turned
blond may be a sign that
the DIO blood in him, his Stand
power, recently awakened.
There might have been a trigger...
like a powerful Stand user being in that city.
A powerful Stand user?
Don't go near him anymore.
It's dangerous to take this further.
Understand?
Just one last question...
Is he our enemy?
Or is he a friend?
What do you think?
You're the one who actually met him.
What was your impression of him?
I'm not sure.
But, um...
He seemed like a very eloquent person.
Did you drop this?
No.
I see.
Guess it's mine now.
Let's say you found a bag
with 100,000 lire inside.
would you take it to the authorities?
No way. I'd totally take it.
Well, aren't you honest?
But what if I was a plainclothes
police officer and saw you take it?
I'd give you half and have you
look the other way... probably.
Wow, that's great!
And I'm sure that's actually what you'd do.
You're not kidding or bluffing.
I can tell! You're telling the truth.
You see... I can tell if people
are telling the truth or not.
I'm almost certain.
You know how your skin gets
shiny when you sweat?
That's how I can tell.
I think I'll have an even better
idea if I taste your sweat.
Who are you?
Leaky Eye Luca was found on the ground
near the airport after having
his own spade buried in the back of his head.
It's a rather serious injury.
He won't be regaining consciousness.
I'm trying to find out who's responsible.
Giorno Giovanna, no one knows why
Leaky Eye Luca was at the airport.
But the airport security guards
let me know that you were at the airport.
That's why I figured I'd come see
you and ask you some questions.
Are you actually a police officer?
Of course not.
Luca's no ordinary crook.
He's a gang member.
There are plenty of reasons
he might've been taken out.
He knew how to get people to hate him.
But that's not what his boss is thinking about.
The boss feels like his name was
personally tarnished since
one of his own was taken out.
That's why he told me to find out who
took him out and settle the score.
I'm asking you...
Did you happen to run into
Leaky Eye Luca at the airport?
No. I don't know who you're talking about.
You're not sweating.
All right, I'll believe you.
That does it for my questions.
Sorry to have bothered you, Giorno Giovanna.
What is that?
My hand was clenched the whole time.
That's Luca's right eye.
He's unconscious anyway, so I just brought it.
This taste... is the taste of someone
who's lying, Giorno Giovanna!
Well, well, well, well...
I said I was done with my questions,
but the situation seems to have
changed, Giorno Giovanna.
You told me a lie.
And now, I'm going to have to find
out why you lied to me, aren't I?!
What are you looking at?
Are you jealous?
Did you want to hit him, too?
My name is Bruno Bucciarati.
Answer me.
Your questioning has already
turned into torture.
Well? This is a pretty
creepy ability, isn't it?
Th-That's...
Those are Luca's fingers.
To tell you the truth...
Leaky Eye Luca was disposed of by our boss.
He said that there's no point
in him living anymore.
I took his fingers for torturing.
It's happening again! What the hell?
Is he also like that Japanese tourist?
Other than being able to tell if people
are lying or not, I can also do this...
I can put whatever I want in your mouth.
For example...
I can even put that fire
extinguisher in your mouth.
Though I'm afraid you'd die if I did that...
Talk!
You know who's responsible.
Were you told not to tell anyone?
Let's have you tell me who did Luca in.
There's no doubt about it...
He has a similar ability!
If you don't hurry up and tell me,
your torture is just going to get worse,
Giorno Giovanna!
This guy's bad news!
In that case...
I'll have to use Golden Wind
and dodge his attacks!
Episodio 02
Bucciarati Is Coming