What was it?
I've had this feeling ever since last night
that I'm supposed to do something...
Man, my shoes and bag sure feel heavy today.
Huh?
Th-This house...
Why?
I somehow ended up walking to
Rohan-sensei's house without realizing it.
The door's open...
I'd like to stop by and
thank him for yesterday,
but then I'd be late for school.
It's probably a bad idea.
He might still be asleep,
since he's a manga artist.
I really shouldn't just barge into his house.
It's a bad idea...
Rohan-sensei...
He's working so frantically.
But I wonder what it is...
I can't shake the feeling that
being here is actually terrifying.
What is it?
I'm glad you came.
I've been waiting for you.
You're right on time.
Huh?
However, could I ask you
to wait a little while?
Two more pages, and I'll be done
with the manuscript for next week.
I think I'll be done in about twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes?
Did he just say he'd finish
two pages in twenty minutes?
Did I hear him wrong?
Two totally blank pages of
manuscript in twenty minutes?
No way... And he said next week's?
We only just read this week's manuscript
yesterday, and he'd just finished it.
What?! You're not going to do pencils first?!
I-I can't believe it...
He didn't even draw that
complicated story in pencil first!
It's getting more and more complete...
And he's even drawing the backgrounds with it!
Wh-What was that just now?!
I couldn't really see it. What did he do?!
What?! H-He's doing the beta!
He's flinging ink around like shurikens,
and hitting exactly the right spots
without going out of the lines!
Th-This technique...
Aren't you supposed to fill in beta
by hand with a brush?!
Boom
He's already done with the beta!
It's only been about two minutes
since the page was completely white!
It's all thanks to you, Koichi.
The urge to work keeps welling up in me!
I want to draw so bad, I can't help it!
I just want to keep drawing!
This is the first time I've been able
to draw nineteen pages in one night!
I'm drawing a masterpiece right now!
Your experiences are amazing!
It's because I'm using your experience
as the source of my story, Koichi!
Huh?
What...
Hurry! I want your next reality!
Let me see your next page!
The more pages I take,
the more weight you'll lose,
but you don't care, right?
Because you're going to become
a masterpiece and live forever!
Flip
I-I remember now!
Heaven's Door!
Y-You're a Stand user!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Hey, now...
Episode 15  Let's Go to the Manga Artist's House, Part 2
I've managed to make a book
from a single panel rather
than an entire work!
This is amazing!
I'm growing as a manga
artist and as a Stand user!
I'm going read this now, Koichi.
Oh, my...
Those faces belong to Shining
Diamond's Josuke Higashikata
and The Hand's Okuyasu Nijimura.
How curious.
Why would those two be at my house?
There's no way Koichi would
tell those two about me.
How strange...
Huh?
I-It's Josuke and Okuyasu!
I'm not sure how they found
out I was here, but...
N-Now they can save me somehow!
Somehow...
I have to get them to save me!
Huh? Okuyasu and Josuke?
How did you know I was here?
Now, then...
Right now, I don't have any
interest in Josuke and Okuyasu.
I'm just going to finish up the
last two pages for next week,
and steal even more material from Koichi!
I'm so excited!
Huh? You were watching a
manga artist do his work?
This is where that manga artist works?
Rohan Kishibe?
Is he famous or something?
Have you heard of him, Josuke?
Nah. Even that bastard Hazamada
made fun of me for not
knowing what Perman was.
That wasn't it.
That wasn't what I wanted
to say to them just now.
But what was it?
Well, we were following you
because we were worried
since you were just wandering around,
but if nothing's wrong, then good. I'm relieved.
Thanks.
Do you want to come inside
and watch with me?
Nah, I'll pass.
I'd get nervous around somebody famous.
Same here.
I'm just satisfied knowing that you
didn't come here to meet some chick.
See ya, Koichi.
Okay.
I know I'm forgetting something.
I know I forgot to tell them
something really important.
I remember now!
I-I was going to ask for help!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
I'll head to school soon!
Sure!
Don't be late.
Got it!
N-No!
That's not what I wanted to say!
I can not attack the manga
artist, Rohan Kishibe
can not
It's no use! I can't ask them for help.
C-Can there be a Stand as terrifying as this?!
Heaven's Door is way too strong!
There's no way to attack it!
Scribble Scribble Scribble
Ah, I see...
At this rate, he's going to rip
everything out of me and kill me!
Stop
Someone's coming into this mansion!
What did you do downstairs just now, Koichi?
Huh?
Okuyasu!
Whoa, there! Don't you dare turn around.
Try anything funny, and I'll crush
you with my Stand, you little shit.
Okuyasu!
I don't know how you knew that
I was in danger, but I'm so happy!
It appears he figured it out coincidentally.
I just realized, but the wound on your hand
must have signaled him
that something was wrong.
It looks like you scratched it or
caught it on something while crawling.
I-I was so absorbed, I didn't even notice...
That's how you figured it out,
right, Okuyasu Nijimura?
Stand name: The Hand...
You have a complex regarding
your dead brother, Keicho,
and whenever you try to make a decision,
you wish that your brother were there.
Wha...
What? Who the hell is this guy?
Hey, Koichi, tell me what
this guy's Stand is!
W-Well...
I-I can't!
I can't say anything that'll put
Rohan Kishibe at a disadvantage.
If you see even one panel, you lose!
I want to tell you not to look!
Don't look at that manga!
Hey, I told you not to move!
Okuyasu, I wasn't interested in you,
but now that you're in
this house, I have no choice.
I'll have to turn you into material, too.
You bastard!
What?!
H-He's fast!
Okuyasu!
What the hell is this?!
Josuke Higashikata,
you're there, aren't you?
Ro
Rohan
Rohan Kishi
Rohan Kishibe
Hea
Heave
Heaven
Heaven's
Heaven's Do
Heaven's Doo
Heaven's Door
Okuyasu!
What the hell is up with this manga artist?
Oh, shut up.
Now, then... Koichi,
I have a question for you.
Huh?
Why do you think Josuke Higashikata
is hiding behind that door there?
Well? What do you think?
Why won't he come out, Koichi?
Josuke is hiding so he won't see your manga.
Yes, that is correct. You're pretty smart.
Okuyasu Nijimura there didn't
know about my Heaven's Door,
so I was able to trick him.
But unfortunately, because of that, Josuke
Higashikata now knows who I really am.
On that point, I feel I'm seriously,
no, without a doubt, put at
a very big disadvantage.
There's also another reason that Josuke
Higashikata is hiding behind the door.
What do you think that is?
In order to prevent that from happening,
I have to somehow drag him
out from behind that door.
He's in the middle of trying to figure
out how he's going to kill you!
That's also true.
But it's not the exact answer I'm looking for.
The correct answer is...
Josuke Higashikata is contemplating whether
he should flee this mansion alone or not.
Josuke would never do that!
Right, Koichi.
It was written in your files that
Josuke Higashikata's personality
would never allow him to abandon you two.
But you see, manga artists
have a habit of thinking about
every conceivable possibility
because of their job.
Like, what are all of the possible actions
that the protagonist can
take in this situation?
In this case, having Josuke run away
now that he knows who I really am
is truly troublesome to me.
Run... Actually, that might be a good idea.
He'd be able to get Jotaro,
and if Yukako finds out
what's happening to Koichi,
she'll be super pissed off.
Ah! We could win with her hair!
Though I don't want to see her!
Do that, Josuke! Hurry up and let them know!
You fools!
I explained that to you
so that it wouldn't happen!
Okuyasu! I already wrote that into your body!
Huh?
I'll allow you to explain what I wrote
in there to those two, Koichi.
No!
What's written there, Koichi?
B-But that's... No...
We can't run anymore!
You can't run away from this!
I'm asking you what's written there, Koichi!
If Josuke Higashikata makes
trouble for Rohan Kishibe,
I will commit suicide
by self-immolation
If Josuke Higashikata makes
trouble for Rohan Kishibe,
I will commit suicide
by self-immolation
S-Suicide?!
You'll commit suicide if
Josuke even tries to help us!
H-Hey, hey! I'll commit
suicide by self-immolation?
Don't be stupid! Like I'd die
in such a horrific way!
Huh?
But you will! He's invincible!
We can't defy him, no matter what!
Stop! My right hand!
So you've come out.
It's not that he came out,
but he was basically dragged out.
Ah... That's rather childish and simple,
but it might be quite effective.
This room is small and
there's nowhere to run.
If you can defeat me in a single blow,
Heaven's Door will disappear,
and Okuyasu won't commit suicide.
Josuke!
Closing his eyes is pretty simple,
but it might be a good idea.
As long as he doesn't see the manuscript,
Heaven's Door is powerless.
Just come charging straight in like that!
Which means...
I just need to open your eyes somehow.
Oh! He was able to withstand that.
This isn't good...
If he comes charging at me, I'll be finished.
If I were a protagonist in a manga,
what would I do in this situation?
seconds
How would I get him to open his eyes?
Go, Josuke!
Hurry up, Josuke!
I know!
There was something written in Koichi's file...
There! This is it!
I'm going to laugh at your hairstyle, Josuke!
That's from, like, twenty or thirty years ago!
You actually think that's cool?
How's that?
Looks like he gets angry if I say that.
It's sort of hard to believe,
but the file doesn't lie.
It's 100% true.
What did you say just now?
J-Josuke, calm down!
Just try and say that one more time!
You opened them...
Didn't you hear me?
It appears that you think
that hairstyle is cool,
but it doesn't look good on you at all.
It's lame!
Though a dirty little bird might
like to make your head its nest.
That's just a maybe, though.
Heaven's Door!
I've won.
Huh?!
What?!
Wh-What was that?
I-I know that I opened his eyes
and showed him the manuscript!
W-We're back to normal!
I'm certain that I showed it to him... Why?
Where the hell did you fly off to?!
Come back out here, damn it!
No, he totally didn't see...
He didn't see?
Do you mean that he's so worked up,
he doesn't even know what he's doing?
Where are you hiding, you dumbass?!
Get out here!
Yeah... He's the kind of guy that loses sight
of everything, even that manuscript,
when someone disses his hair.
I had no idea he actually got this mad.
This is way worse than I imagined.
What?
S-Something about Josuke's personality
that Koichi didn't know?
That means it's information
that's not in the file!
Why? Why does he get so
mad about his hairstyle?
There has to be a reason... Why?
I won't forgive anyone who disses my hair!
I won't keep quiet, no matter who it is!
The reason behind his hair...
I think I heard a little about it before.
That just might be why...
Huh? What are you talking about?
It has to do with when
Josuke was a kid, but...
This story is going to include my own
guesses about why this happened.
Apparently, when Josuke was four,
he passed out from an
inexplicable high fever,
and for fifty days, they weren't
sure whether he'd live or die.
Josuke...
He found out later that it
was right around the time
when Jotaro and Mr. Joestar
went to Egypt to defeat the man named DIO.
But at the time, they had
no idea it happened,
so Josuke's mom drove him
to a hospital in S City.
But on that day, Morioh was hit with
its worst blizzard in 18 years.
It's no use... What should I do?
Cars don't come by here often,
and there are no pay phones.
I should have called an
ambulance at the house.
I shouldn't have brought
Josuke out in this snow.
That's when it happened.
Wh-What do you want? Go away!
That kid is sick, right?
I'll push your car for you.
Huh?
Hurry up and
step on the gas.
Once you get moving,
don't stop. Just keep going...
Or your tires will get stuck in the snow again.
O-Okay...
Thank you!
His mom looked for that boy later,
but couldn't find a single lead.
Though the boy didn't personally
save Josuke's life,
the four-year-old Josuke
thought that what the boy did
made him his hero.
He's an inspiration that's
burned into his heart,
and his example of how to live.
So when someone insults that,
something deep in his heart snaps.
I don't know who he is,
but I admire him so much
that I copied his hairstyle.
And I won't forgive anyone who insults it,
because it's the same as insulting him.
I think that story might be the reason.
Though I thought Josuke was making it up,
so I wasn't listening very carefully.
Huh... I had no idea something
like that happened.
Rohan's holding a pen!
Bastard! You're going to try again?!
N-No...
I-I wanted to sketch this and write
a memo before I lost consciousness.
What a wonderful story! And I just
experienced something amazing.
I'm so happy.
I don't get to experience
something like this often.
If I can make it work in my own project...
I'm so lucky.
I'm so glad I moved to Morioh.
It's no use.
Until he dies, he'll keep trying
to use anything as material
for his manga, no matter how
horrible the experience.
At this point, you have to commend him.
Putting good and bad aside,
I have to admire that attitude.
He really is a super manga artist.
There you are, manga artist!
I'm not done punching you!
You sort of have to commend him, too.
Y-Yeah...
Sorry!
Rohan Kishibe's
Pink Dark Boy
— Notice of Hiatus —
Thank you for always
reading Pink Dark Boy.
For personal reasons,
we will be on hiatus
for about one month.
(From the Editors)
Rohan Kishibe's
Pink Dark Boy will be on
hiatus for about a month.
Rohan Kishibe's
Pink Dark Boy
— Notice of Hiatus —
Thank you for always
reading Pink Dark Boy.
For personal reasons,
we will be on hiatus
for about one month.
(From the Editors)
Episode 16
Let's Go Hunting!