Sanctuary!
Take this! I'm out of time!
As I thought... There's no mold growing on you,
even though you fell.
Cioccolata's Green Tea will
kill any living creature.
What the hell's going on with your body?
I mean, I guess I'll just have to pulverize
every last inch of your body
until you can't move anymore...
w-w-with my Sanctuary!
I don't think Ill be able
to defeat him quickly.
In that case... I'll lead him away
from here.
Episodio 31 Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 3
This should be far enough to
lose that underground guy...
There are accidents everywhere!
What's going on?
Look! Someone's unconscious
over there, too!
Hurry up and save them!
An ambulance!
Over here!
Under the stairs!
Wh-What's...
Wh-What happened to the mold?!
C-Cioccolata?!
The mold disappeared.
Giorno, Mista...
They must've taken care of
the guy in the helicopter.
Secco, it's me.
Did you take care of Bucciarati?
Something rather unexpected
has happened on my end.
I'm about to take care of Giorno and Mista,
but I've taken a bit of a blow to the head.
So there's something I want
to tell you now, just in case.
Listen carefully, Secco.
Their destination is the Colosseum.
I found that out from the
Bullets' conversation.
Apparently, someone's
waiting for them there,
and this mysterious figure
knows how to defeat the boss.
That's why Giorno and the others
are trying to get to them,
and why the boss is trying to
stop that from happening.
Listen carefully. Figure out this
mystery before anyone else.
You're the only one I can count on.
What's with him?
Wait, that phone call... Was it...
Cioccolata, you piece of shit!
Did you actually think
I'd feel sad over you?
You loser!
You're super smart,
you'd throw me sugar cubes and play with me,
and you have a lot of money.
On top of that, you're super
strong... Or so I thought.
That's why I thought I'd be
safe if I listened to you.
But apparently, you're weak after all!
I mean, you lost!
I don't like you anymore, you scum!
I hate your guts!
He knows!
He knows that we're trying
to get to the Colosseum!
He intends to figure out the secret!
I won't let you go!
Half...?
Take this! Zipper Man!
What?!
By the way, doesn't "Colosseum"
sound kinda like "kill them"
(koroseyo) in Japanese?
Don't you think so, Mr. Language Teacher?
I thought I'd ask before I killed you.
Up until now,
I thought we'd be out of danger as long as
we stopped the man in the helicopter.
But things are still getting worse...
The actual threat is this guy who
can move freely underground!
If I let him get to the Colosseum
before we get there...
He's going to go on a rampage!
You're... a bit annoying... Bucciarati.
You already know... don't you?
At close range, I'm faster
and stronger than you!
You're a nuisance!
I'll take care of you here and now!
You sure know how to think fast.
You got away again...
Just barely, though.
But your body really is weird.
What the hell is the deal with you?!
You have glass shards stuck in you,
but you aren't bleeding much at all.
Did you... see that just now, too?
Hey... What do you think that is?
It came from the second
level of arches, right?
There was something shining.
It happened earlier, too.
Hey, something just hid in the shadows.
Was that...
I saw it... I saw a glimpse of it!
The light was reflecting! Someone was
looking over here with binoculars!
The guy you're going to go
see is definitely there!
He was in a wheelchair, wasn't he?
I think I saw some prosthetics, too!
Is he disabled?
I'm going to find out this secret!
No matter what the deal with your body is!
I'm going to end you, Bucciarati!
Are you mocking me? You went into
the ground with your zipper?
Are you copying me?!
Do you think you stand
a chance against me
by going underground?!
Take this! Sanctua—
He's not hiding. He's moving.
These vibrations...
He's moving in some direction...
Y-Y-You copycat!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
You and your piss-stained zipper guy!
H-How dare you steal my technique?!
But the only thing that
copying me is going to do
is ensure that you basically
just doomed yourself!
I won't let you get to the Colosseum!
The surfaces are getting softer...
So he is pursuing me!
But this sound...
This sound that's heading right
toward me with no hesitation...
They say that sound reverberates
better in liquids than in solids.
It's just like being under water.
Does that mean he can hear
when I'm moving, too?
You got way further than I thought,
but you can't run from me anymore!
I can tell... I can even tell
how far you are from me!
He's 20 meters ahead and to my left.
He moved to the right. Just 10 more meters.
Just seven more meters...
Five meters...
I'm not going to strangle you.
I'll bury you alive.
You can die in this grave you
dug for yourself, Bucciarati!
You think you can escape my punches
when you're surrounded by walls of dirt?
Just two more meters!
A water pipe?
You cut it to try and trick me?
Seriously?
The fact that you're trying
these stupid little tricks
proves that you're feeling cornered!
You basically just admitted that you'd lose,
even with your abilities, when you
have to face off with my Sanctuary!
I don't know where you are, but I do know
that you're within 20 meters of me.
You're staying as still as possible
so I won't be able to find you.
Or what?
Are you trying to come up
with some kind of strategy?
I mean, you are pretty quick-witted.
But...
I'll make you lose your upper hand...
You and your quick wit...
That's a different sound than before.
What is this sound?
I'm hearing it from all directions.
The stone pavement inside the ground...
turns to mud because my
Sanctuary touches it.
But the moment it moves
away from my body,
it hardens again.
Say, Bucciarati...
There might actually be a chance.
If you stay perfectly still,
you just might make it...
I mean, there's that miraculous story
about the death row inmate
who survived three hangings
because of the rope breaking
or the gallows malfunctioning!
It's no use... I can't stay
underground any longer!
But it's not like I can run
along the surface, either!
I was prepared for this,
but if he doesn't make it here,
I'm going to have to destroy the arrow.
Our only hope... is for them
to encounter this arrow.
The only ones who can surpass Emperor
Crimson, who has the ability to control time,
are those who know the true
power behind the arrow.
And the one capable of that is not me.
It's them.
Twelve years ago, I acquired this
arrow after fleeing Egypt.
And the fear that this arrow brings
will never end until they come.
J.P. Polnareff
(36 years old, French)
The Colosseum in Rome
"Rome will exist as long as the Colosseum does;
when the Colosseum falls, so will Rome;
when Rome falls, so will the world. (A quote from a
certain medieval monk who saw the Colosseum)
This brief history... is rather ironic.
They joined a gang because
society had cast them out,
yet they're the ones trying to stop this
world from falling into the hands of evil.
But in the end...
Will Bucciarati actually
be able to make it here?
There's no point if he doesn't
come out the victor.
If he fails, I'll have to destroy
this arrow and its secret.
All I can do is wait for them to arrive.
Everything begins after that.
I've been waiting all this time...
just protecting this arrow's true power.
I-It's no use! I've reached my limit!
He moved! He couldn't take
it anymore and moved!
Twelve meters to the right. Bucciarati...
He's planning to hide beneath the Colosseum
so he can evade the barrage
of stone spears!
That's not gonna happen!
H-He's coming!
I can hear very clearly that
he's catching up to me.
I can feel the reverberations!
He's ten meters straight ahead!
Eight meters...
He's moving faster than me!
Zipper Man!
You know...
I knew he had something up his sleeve...
Bucciarati, is this the best you
could do in your desperation?
Though you are the only one who was able
to hide from my Sanctuary for even a second.
But now you're finished! I'm closer
than before. I'll find you soon.
The longer you hide,
the closer you come to your defeat!
Wh-What...
M-My skin...
Don't tell me...
Even the stone pavement
is turning into mud!
It stands to reason that your body
will start turning into mud the
closer I get to you underground.
I heard you! You're right there!
Now I've got you for sure. I can tell.
I'm 1.5 meters away from you.
So you've already made it to the Colosseum...
You were so close.
Take this! The secret will be mine!
Zipper Man!
To be honest, I don't really
know why, either...
But even after breaking some
bones, I barely feel any pain.
My heart has stopped, so I don't
bleed very much, either.
The damage to my body is minimized.
That's why I was waiting for this...
I'm sure my eardrums can handle the
damage they're about to endure, too.
I was waiting...
for you to drag anything and
everything into the ground.
Street lamps, street signs, parked cars...
And the tires on those cars.
Whoops. I guess you can't hear me anymore.
You bastard... N-Now you've done it...
But... This isn't a big deal.
I can still hear!
I could hear that tire popping!
I know where you are!
You're right there, Bucciarati!
M-My leg! Wh-Where am...
Wh-Why? Wh-Where is he?!
What did he do to me?!
How did I mistake a car for him?!
Your eardrums have been destroyed.
Your Stand that allows you to travel
through the ground...Sanctuary, was it?
Now that your ability's lost
its radar, your ears,
it's completely useless.
I figured it out, you bastard!
You're planning to destroy
my eardrums, aren't you?!
You think I can't travel through the ground
if my ears are destroyed, don't you?!
What a stupid idea!
Stay back!
Stay the hell away from me!
I won't take your life.
But now that you know about the man
waiting for us at the Colosseum,
I can't let you go, either.
I need you to stay put for a while.
You bastard!
You're trying to put me out
of commission, aren't you?!
Stay the hell away from me!
Just stop talking now.
This conversation isn't even coherent.
S-Stay away!
Score!
Th-The moment you attack me,
I'm gonna turn this kid into mud!
Then I'll throw him at you and run!
You don't wanna kill a kid,
do you, dumbass?!
Change of plans! For a while, I was
thinking about defeating the boss,
but I'll settle for just reporting this
to the organization and getting
a reward from the boss!
It's easier for me to just
work for the organization.
Hey, brat! Get me a taxi.
Raise your hand and flag
down a taxi for me!
You're going to get one for me!
Hey! Are you listening to me?!
You stupid brat!
Hurry up... and get me... a taxi!
Bucciarati! Why the hell are
you moving toward me?!
Can't you hear me?!
Your maximum range is two meters.
I'm very aware of that!
You're probably thinking I can't
get away because I hurt my leg!
Don't underestimate me! I'll kill this brat!
You couldn't reach me!
I'm out of your range!
You stupid piece of shit!
You just grazed my ha—
Wh-What the hell?!
A zipper! Shit, my throat!
I didn't need to even bother predicting it,
but in the prediction I saw,
there was no way that Bucciarati
would sacrifice a kid like me.
Shit! I need to undo this somehow!
Burnable Trash Pickup
Mon, Wed, Fri
Ah, Cioccolata!
Cioccolata!
I came here after tracing the
signal from Secco's cellphone.
But what's happening seems to be
different from the boss's orders.
To think that Secco had already lost...
Since they're a pair, that probably
means Cioccolata is also...
It also appears that
Bucciarati is here alone.
Where are Giorno Giovanna and Narancia?
Wh-What? My body suddenly...
All my strength is...
It can't be... My eyes are blurring, too...
Am I finally out of time?
I knew this moment would come...
But now?
Episodio 33
His Name Is Diavolo