Episodio 20 The Final Mission from the Boss
How much longer till we get there?
We're almost at Rialto Bridge.
It'll be at least another five minutes.
All right. Keep going.
Bucciarati, what was the
mission from the boss?
I'm reconfirming the mission
from the boss right now.
Are you all safe?
I thank you for protecting my daughter
Trish from the bottom of my heart.
I'll read it aloud.
"The information on this disc
was inputted the moment all of you
boarded the train at Naples.
Therefore, I'd like to warn you
that I have no way of knowing
how many more are after you,
or how many members you've
lost at this point in time.
The information on this disc is the
safest way for me to meet my daughter,
and also your final mission.
Let me also warn you that,
should you deviate even in the slightest
from the instructions on this disc,
it will be unforgivable.
If any of you do anything other
than what's instructed of you,
even if it's accidental,
I will consider it a warning
that you mean to harm me.
Here is your final mission.
You will now head to
the island of San Giorgio Maggiore.
The place you will take my daughter is
the top of the great bell
tower of the church there.
Once you take my daughter there,
your mission will be over.
Instruction one: there are no
stairs to the top of the tower.
Currently, there is only one
elevator that goes to the top.
The only ones allowed in the elevator
are Trish and one bodyguard.
Instruction two: the bodyguard is prohibited
from carrying any knives, guns,
cell phones, or anything else.
Instruction three: you must
land on the island within
fifteen minutes of retrieving this disc.
There is a tracking device in the
disc, so I know where you are.
Instruction four: the rest
of you will wait on the boat.
You are not allowed on the island."
That's all of it.
Bucciarati, we have arrived.
So the boss is at the top
of that tower right now...
Those are pretty detailed instructions.
He seems extremely cautious.
But I guess you couldn't
be a mafia boss otherwise.
Anyway, this means our mission ends here.
We all made it out alive,
so I guess all's well that ends well.
Yeah, just barely, though.
Let's live it up in Venice for a
few days before we go home.
I hear the food's great there.
They have good food here?
I just remembered I was hungry.
What kind of food do they have?
Well, they have squid ink pasta,
horsehair crab salad,
and I hear the carpaccio at the
Hotel Cipriani is fantastic.
Hey, you bastards!
Don't let your guard down!
The mission's not over yet!
Narancia, keep an eye on the radar.
S-Sure.
Bucciarati,
I volunteer to be her
bodyguard in the tower.
I'll take her to the top of the bell tower.
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Bucciarati's the capo, so of course
he's going to take her, you dumbass!
The boss didn't specify anyone because
he didn't know who was still alive!
Of course. I'll go.
All right, Trish.
The two of us will go onto the island,
as we were ordered.
I know.
It's our chance to find out
who the boss really is.
I'll find him, no matter what.
Oh, I know. Giorno,
could you give me that charm to wish
me good luck on this final mission?
Ladybugs are considered sun bugs.
They're symbols of life, right?
They're good luck charms, right?
Oh, that's right.
Yes. Ladybugs bring good luck.
This brooch that's been given life with Golden
Wind's ability will act as a tracking device.
Bucciarati.
What is it, Fugo?
I thought this was a good
opportunity to say this.
Why so formal? What is it?
I knew that you'd become capo someday,
and I know you'll be able
to complete this mission.
Of course he can.
Let's aim for an even higher
position in the organization!
Yeah... You're right.
Let's go, Trish.
If I can somehow get this
onto the boss's body,
Giorno will be able to track him down.
Right now, we just need
to find out who he is...
No matter what.
The elevator door is open.
There are only two buttons,
for the first floor and the roof.
It goes directly to either.
There are no other floors to stop on.
What's...
What's going to happen to me?
I suddenly got kidnapped by
gangsters just like you guys,
had my life threatened,
and now, I'm going to be taken to
a father I don't even know or love...
Where am I going to go now?
The boss is just concerned for your safety.
As for what will happen to you from now on,
this is what I think...
First, you'll be given a different name.
You might even need to have plastic surgery.
You'll be given a new identification
and family registry.
You'll be somewhere we won't know of,
some far-off country, where you'll live happily.
Your father has that kind of power.
Here. Let me give you a hand.
It's not like...
I-I'm nervous or anything...
I wonder...
if I'll be able to like my father.
No family worries about that.
Yeah...
You're right.
It's strange to even worry about that.
We're almost to the top.
Trish? Tri—
Wh-What?!
Trish... No... What's—
Trish and I should be the only ones here.
No one other than the guys
on my team knows we're...
No... It can't be!
Could the boss...
In order to make sure he stays
completely invisible...
Did he have us protect his daughter
in order to ensure that he could
finish off his daughter himself?!
Bruno Bucciarati was born as a
fisherman's son in a suburb of Naples.
His father wasn't the best
at dealing with people,
but he was an earnest and honest fisherman
who tried to protect his family
from the cruelties of this world.
Bruno.
Dad.
You need me to fix the net?
Got it.
His mother was very kind, and Bruno
loved his conversations with her.
He always looked forward to the bedtime
stories she read to him before going to sleep.
All right, go to sleep, now.
But...
It occurred when Bucciarati was seven.
So what are you going to do now?
Well... I want a change,
so I'm going to leave this town.
After ten years of marriage,
his parents divorced.
As for the reason, only his parents
would know the answer to that.
What are we going to do about Bruno?
After a discussion, Bruno's parents
had him make a decision.
Bruno, your father and I both love you,
but we're going to be living separately now.
Who do you want to live with?
Me or your father?
We want you to decide.
You want to leave this place with
me and go to the city, right?
You're very smart.
You want to go to a good school, don't you?
There'll be a lot more kids your age, too!
So, you want to live with
your mother, right?
You'll come with me, right?
I'll...
live with Dad.
Huh?!
What?! Bruno, you should
really think about this!
You like me better, don't you?
I'll stay here with Dad.
No...
Mom's strong...
She should be able to make it anywhere.
But...
All right, I'm leaving.
I'll come back once a month to visit.
Okay.
As Bucciarati had instinctively figured,
two years after his mother left,
she remarried a man from Milan.
He would end up only seeing his
mother at Christmas after that.
As for his father, because his
wife left him for the city,
he became determined to send
Bucciarati to a good school.
Dad, I think customers are
going to come by soon.
Oh, I guess it's about that time...
I'll reapply the nets.
All right. I'll let you handle this.
Up until then, he'd only been a fisherman,
but in order to earn money
for his son's tuition,
he started taking tourists and
other fishermen on his boat.
And the wheel of fate continued to turn.
Sirs, that island isn't good for fishing.
There are better—
Whatever, man.
We wanna go fishing over there.
Just shut up and take us.
Got it?
R-Right...
That evening, Bucciarati's father would
be rescued by the Coast Guard,
his body riddled with bullet holes.
He's been shot seven times in his arms,
shoulders, chest, and torso.
We got an operating room open!
Dad! Dad!
There are bullets still in his body.
Dad!
For now, please just wait
until the surgery's finished.
Be strong. Can you give us contact
information for the rest of your family?
Dad...
Forensics is coming by later,
so give them this as evidence.
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
Right.
H-How did this happen?
Good evening. Are you his son?
We found this at the scene.
Apparently, your father
witnessed a drug deal.
He was shot so that he wouldn't talk.
Your father is a very important witness.
We don't exactly want him to die, either.
I'm sure he'll be okay.
My father was shot because
of something like that?
Luckily, Bucciarati's father survived.
Despite being shot seven times,
none of the wounds were fatal,
and the boat that found
and rescued him
happened to have supplies
to treat his wounds,
allowing him to survive
until he got to the hospital.
He was graced by good luck all around.
But in terms of Bucciarati's life,
it might've been better if his father had died.
There are certain sticky
situations where you don't
have the opportunity to
choose the right path.
Fishermen have way too
much energy, damn it.
I'll keep watch! Just hurry up and do it!
You've got some nerve,
making us come here so late at night.
Go to hell already!
Wh-Who the hell are you?
A k-kid? H-Hey!
What are you doing under the bed?!
I-It's just a kid! Just
take the knife from him!
Th-That knife's dangerous! Put it down!
Riiiiip
Wh-What are you—
I'll protect you, Dad.
Don't worry. Take your time getting better.
At the age of twelve,
Bruno Bucciarati committed murder
and entered a territory
no one should set foot in.
I can't turn back now.
They'll keep trying to get
revenge and shut us up.
I can't trust the police, either.
The only one willing to
protect this father and son
was the organization that ran
the city from the shadows.
Bucciarati knocked on the
doors of that organization,
and in return for loyalty and
service to the organization,
they guaranteed their safety.
Believing the organization
was the true form of justice,
he worked hard there.
He made a name for himself
within the organization,
and eventually, the capo
Polpo took a liking to him.
Five years later, Bucciarati's father died
due to complications from his wounds.
Bucciarati loathed the white
powder of greed that had
dragged him and his
father into this situation,
and swore that he would never forgive it.
But...
I-I'm sorry! I won't bother them again!
I'll forget about that family!
Good. You can't regret anything
once you're dead, after all.
If you're also a gang member—
Those are...
Hey! What the hell are those?!
He learned that the organization's boss,
whom he thought was the true form of justice,
was involved in dealing
the drugs he hated so much.
In this city?
I thought they were prohibited!
And now...
The boss is now...
The most repulsive form of evil is
to exploit innocent people
who don't know anything,
and to use others merely for one's own gain!
A father did this to his innocent daughter,
all to cover his own ass?!
This is unforgivable!
You have once again betrayed my heart!
There... Trish is still alive.
All right. It's on him.
But, damn it, I can't see his face.
Boss, I was just going to
seek out your true identity,
but the plan's changed.
I'm going to get rid of you right now!
There's no time,
but the boss isn't expecting
me to betray him right now.
It will be...
an assassination.
I'll get ahead of the boss on his
escape route and finish him there.
This...
This hole...
I see.
It's a stairway to the charnel house that's
found in the basement of any church.
After he eliminates Trish down there,
thinking he's in the clear,
he'll go through there and exit
the other side of the building.
I managed to get here first.
Here he comes.
He came down the stairs!
Now!
You should just go home now,
Bruno Bucciarati.
If you step out from behind that pillar,
you're going to die.
Zipper Man!
I-It's going to break off!
So he knew I was after him...
But since he hid himself again,
I'm guessing he's not that powerful.
I'd like to ask you why.
What's the meaning of this?
I highly respected all the work
you'd done for me on this mission.
Were you so happy to become
a capo that you got greedy?
Or did you overestimate your
own powers and get cocky,
thinking you could actually surpass me?
When Trish wakes up,
I'm going to tell her that
her father didn't even exist.
Trish?
What about Trish?
My daughter has nothing to do with you.
You could never understand my true feelings!
Giorno?
Bucciarati! Yes, I know he's on the move.
I know exactly where the boss is because
of the brooch you put on him.
Right now, he's at the bottom of
the stairs to the charnel house.
He's right by the pillar that's about
two meters away from the stairs.
But wait, Bucciarati!
Something is wrong!
You're there!
Take this! Zipper Man!
The one who was in the pillar's shadow...
was me!
Wh-What...
What's going o—
I decided to show you... as a parting gift.
Since this is the end, I'll fill you in.
What you just witnessed and felt
was you in the future.
You from a few seconds from the
past witnessed yourself in the future.
This is my Emperor Crimson's ability.
I erased time and leapt past it.
I don't care who it is.
I will not allow anyone
to threaten my throne,
no matter what.
And now, you're going to have to disappear.
Bucciarati, your mission to
act as Trish's bodyguard
has now come to an end.
Episodio 21
The Mystery of Emperor Crimson