If only... My daughter,
if only you hadn't been born...
Fear truly does come from the past.
You have genuinely angered me!
What?
Booooom
You said you'd overcome this, did you not?
You were right, Trish.
Now you can surpass not only the past...
but their heads.
Trish!
No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Eternal greatness exists only within myself.
Sing a song of sorrow in a world where time has vanished.
Episodio 37 King of Kings
T-Trish!
No way! He...
He attacked! He went through
Trish's mind... and into himself!
I guess I don't need this body anymore...
or you.
H-Her soul!
It's moving away!
Trish's soul is...
disappearing into the sky!
The arrow!
The arrow belongs to me!
It pierced me!
The arrow's power...
This gift given to me by fate!
Now my Emperor Crimson
will sit atop the world again!
Did it pierce me?
I-It didn't!
Wh-What... Something is wrong!
No... I can't even grasp it!
E-Emperor Crimson's hand is translucent!
And it's crumbling!
What?!
Th-This is...
My soul is leaving her body...
This wind is...
I-It can't be!
Could it be that all you can predict, Boss,
are the movements of arrows and bullets?
You couldn't seem to predict
what I was going to do.
Y-You bastard...
You're the one who discovered
the way to destroy Requiem.
This thing behind our heads...
Or rather, this thing that's
behind every one of our souls.
It just needs to be destroyed.
You wanted to pick up the arrow,
so you didn't completely kill Requiem,
Don't... Don't, Bucciarati...
but if I completely destroy mine...
The ability of Requiem, the Stand
that lost control, will disappear.
Don't, Bucciarati!
Look at me! Think about who's truly worthy!
Bucciarati... Y-You're...
Who is the king worthy of
possessing this arrow?!
Bucciarati! The weak are not
worthy to possess the arrow!
All the souls that have been swapped...
will return to their original bodies!
Trish's soul!
I-It's Trish!
Mista!
Everyone, look!
You did it, Bucciarati!
It was a close call, but she's returning!
I'm leaving the rest up to you, Giorno.
B-Bucciarati...
Y-Your body's back at the Colosseum.
That body is—
Giorno, I was reborn.
When I met you back home in Naples...
When I betrayed the organization...
My soul had been fated to
slowly die, but it was reborn...
Thanks to you.
This is what true happiness is.
This is how it should be. Don't worry.
Please give everyone my regards.
How dare you?!
All for a stupid little girl!
You vile pukes that some
loser spewed into a toilet!
Who do you think I am?!
I, Diavolo, shall be the
one to possess the arrow!
W-We did it...
Way to go, Bucciarati...
That was a close one...
but Trish will be okay now.
Giorno... You need to heal us.
Bucciarati's still at the Colosseum,
but I'm sure he'll be here in no time...
Right?
Don't worry about it, Giorno.
I'm only going back to
where I was supposed to go.
I'm simply returning to how I once was...
That's all...
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Chariot Requiem
Benedict!
I don't remember who said it, but...
"We are all soldiers chosen by fate."
But there are truths I've learned
from this world, as well.
Fate has given me the ability to make
time skip, and to predict the future.
There's no doubt about it.
That's the undeniable truth.
The fate of this world
was supposed to have chosen my Emperor
Crimson to stand invincible at the top.
I am no soldier.
Damn it!
And despite that, somehow...
that arrow is not in my hands!
How dare you?!
There's no way...
There's no way that I, Diavolo,
would lose like this!
I need to retreat for now.
I need to hide from the arrow and await
the ideal moment for my counterattack!
Retreating here is not admitting defeat.
I have the ability to take
myself back to the top!
Don't let him get away, Giorno...
No matter... what you do...
If he gets away, he'll go into hiding.
He's planning to run away, Giorno...
I just felt it... He took a step back!
Wha—
He's holding the arrow!
The one who will control the
arrow after Requiem...
is Giorno!
It's no use... There's no way I
can escape from here after all!
I'll lose my pride if I flee from them.
I am a king!
My only goal is to remain at the top!
If I flee now, my pride will be lost!
There is... no next time!
He's not running away!
He's coming this way,
despite how pointless that is!
Golden Wind!
He did it!
The one who will go beyond the power
of that arrow is Giorno's Golden Wind!
No! You're wrong!
I thank you, my daughter!
Because of your insulting claim
that I was going to run,
I was able to keep my pride!
Thank goodness I didn't retreat.
If I had fled, I wouldn't
have seen this premonition.
This unexpected premonition
from Emperor Crimson Eulogy!
Golden Wind!
He did it!
The one who will go beyond the power
of that arrow is Giorno's Golden Wind!
B-But why?
It went through him...
but the arrow's on the ground.
I'm so glad I didn't run away. So very glad!
To be honest, my heart was filled with despair.
If my daughter hadn't ridiculed me,
I wouldn't have decided to advance on you.
And because of that,
I saw a premonition of the
arrow falling to the ground!
Giorno Giovanna...
You weak little newcomer...
This means that you weren't a suitable vessel.
He's already disappeared,
but remember what Polnareff said?
The arrow decides who
is worthy to wield it.
I know I'm repeating myself,
but I'm truly glad I didn't run away.
You've been rejected by the arrow!
Giorno, run!
You're finished!
I, Diavolo, will be king,
just like I've always been!
G-Giorno!
Mista, wait!
The thing that's peeking
through the crack...
Could that be...
Th-That's...
What am I looking at right now?
I cracked his head open!
Shouldn't I be seeing his brains
spilling out right about now?
What came out wasn't brains...
Th-This can't be!
And the arrow's being sucked into his arm!
The arrow—
Shit! You're finished, Giorno Giovanna!
Th-That's...
Giorno wasn't rejected.
He wasn't cast aside by the
arrow because he was unworthy!
No... In fact...
The arrow is forever Giorno's!
The boss can never have that arrow now!
Am I looking at reality?
I must be seeing some kind of mistake.
I should be looking at Giorno's corpse,
with his head cracked open!
This cannot be reality!
It's Requiem...
That's Giorno's Requiem...
Golden Wind Requiem!
Golden Wind has gone beyond
the power of the arrow!
What?!
The only thing that will survive
is the truth of this world.
Righteous actions born of truth
shall never be destroyed.
My friends may have perished,
but their actions and wills
have not been destroyed.
They handed this arrow to me.
So, are your actions born of truth,
or are they merely superficial, born of evil?
We're about to find out.
Can you avoid destruction, Boss?
Wh-What's going on? What's about to happen?
Don't tell me our souls are
going to be swapped again!
I don't know... No one does.
Giorno probably doesn't, either.
But given what just happened, I know that
Giorno has complete control of Requiem!
It hasn't gone berserk!
I couldn't see it... I couldn't
see the moment he attacked!
But I was able to predict that attack.
The reason it didn't fully hit me is because
I was able to predict the
hole appearing in my hand!
I can dodge his attacks,
though just barely.
It's true that this Golden Wind's
attack yielded tremendous power...
But... that's all it's worth.
It merely powered up.
It's a threat, but I can still predict it!
This is not something I can't overcome!
Fate has chosen me as the
one to stand at the top!
I am the king who has overcome all threats!
Don't talk to me like you have any idea
what's going on, Giorno Giovanna!
I won't even give you the
chance to regret your death!
Emperor Crimson!
Time shall be eliminated
for everyone but myself!
I can see it... I can see
his Stand's movements!
I can perfectly see what it's trying to do!
I can estimate what these pieces
of trash are going to do!
That should fully stop
Golden Wind's movements!
Even after time starts moving
again in a few seconds,
your eyes will never be able to see
myself or Emperor Crimson again!
The pinnacle of truth lies within my abilities!
Yes! I've won!
I'm just a moment quicker!
I've completely ripped out his
heart in my premonition!
The future has chosen the
actions of my Emperor Crimson!
This is the end!
Wha—
What?
Don't tell me this is...
Is the time that I disposed of
reversing... because of Requiem?!
N-No! Everything is returning to normal!
But my premonition still favors me!
Take this, Giorno Giovanna!
Wha—
What is this?
What am I seeing?
A-Am I dreaming?
Am I witnessing some kind of illusion?
No... that can't be true.
The only one who can move within
the time I've disposed of is me!
This is... Requiem.
What you're seeing is indeed the truth.
You are seeing the movements
created by your abilities,
but you will never arrive at the
truth that's going to happen.
None who stand before me
shall ever get there,
regardless of their abilities.
This is the power of Golden Wind Requiem.
This is unknown even to Giorno
Giovanna, who controls me.
Giorno Giovanna!
I won't even give you the
chance to regret your death!
What am I saying?
I-I...
haven't moved at all from the start!
Th-This premonition that I had...
It's the truth that's going to happen!
My invincible Emperor Crimson should
be heading toward victory!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Episodio 38
Golden Wind Requiem