JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 13  We Picked Up Something Crazy!
Next on Morioh Radio, we have a
letter from "Troubled Lonesome Boy."
"Kai, listen to this.
I can't get a hold of my girlfriend
at all and it's making me blue."
I wonder if she's mad because
I proposed suddenly.
And I spent all my pay on an engagement
ring with a ruby, her birthstone...
So you were able to successfully
retrieve the bow and arrow.
Yeah, from Akira Otoishi's place.
He'd been committing burglaries with his Stand.
Roughly 500 million yen worth.
The police are still looking into it.
Try doing something with your Stand again.
I'll send you to the ends of
the Earth and kill you there.
I'll be safest in prison!
Chili Pepper's in pieces.
Even if he gets out of jail,
I'm sure he won't try anything again.
Jotaro, what are you going
to do with the bow and arrow?
The Speedwagon Foundation is going
to hold on to it and research it.
It's a crucial piece of evidence we can use
to unravel the mystery behind Stands.
That's great.
Thank goodness!
That means this incident's been resolved!
It didn't end up being that big
a deal, but yay! Hooray!
I'm still questioning Otoishi about the Stand
users that were created here.
Stay on your guard, just in case.
Yeah.
Right.
Sure.
Coffee in Japan is still the best.
Waitress, can I get a refill?
Whoa! Jeez.
Be more careful. I look away for a second and...
Josuke, don't you have to go?
The bus will be here soon.
R-Right...
Yeah. Come on, let's go. Stand up.
I wonder if those two will be okay.
I'm worried.
Whoa, this cake is so good!
Can I get another slice, waitress?
Hello, this is the Higashikata resid—
Hey, Mom. It's me.
Josuke? It's unusual for you to call me.
Do you need something?
Well, uh... Hey, y-you're going
to be home all day today, right?
Yeah? What about it?
N-Nothing! As long as you're
there, it's fine. Bye!
Hey!
What was that all about?
He'd better not be planning
something weird again.
Crap. I hope Mom didn't
think that was weird.
Oh, for crying out loud...
I told him to wait until I was
done with the phone call!
Hey, wait!
Hello? Can you hear me? Hey!
Did you just call for me?
Yeah. We can't get a taxi at this hour,
so we're going to take the bus to my house.
And... I know I'm being pushy, but I'm
going to confirm one more time.
You can only look from a distance.
Make sure you don't talk to my mom!
Promise me that.
My mom won't be happy just
because you came to visit.
She's gonna be a wreck.
I know that. I promise.
Also, one more thing.
I'm gonna be calling you Mr. Joestar.
Huh?
W-Well, you know... I might
as well lay it on the line now.
I mean, it might seem cold,
but calling someone I just met "Dad"
or "Pops" is just not happening.
So after you see my mom, I want
you to go right back to America.
Right...
You're absolutely right. I understand.
Man, this is awkward.
I know it's best to be honest, but still,
there are some things between
people that just aren't possible.
Hey, Mr. Joestar...
Excuse me, did you see where the burly
old man who was just here went?
He got onto that long-distance bus.
Bright Deer
Long Distance Bus
To Sapporo
Y-You can't be serious! Damn it!
I'm sorry about that.
You said we were getting on a bus, so...
But I'm surprised you caught
up to the bus by running.
We were just about to get onto the freeway.
Right now, I'm thinking it might have
been better to just let you go...
To Hokkaido!
Ugh, my stomach hurts.
Sorry about that.
Josuke...
Something seems to be
pulling on my trousers.
Oh, really? Don't let them
drag you off somewhere again.
Wha...
J-Josuke! There's a Stand user nearby!
Yup, there sure is.
Two, in fact... Me and you.
Anyway, is there a vending
machine nearby? I need a drink.
Wh-What is this? They're not footsteps.
Hands? Hand prints?
Oh my God! Josuke, the Stand just laughed!
See? Right here! On top of the sand!
There's no way I'm letting him see my mom.
Now he's seeing and hearing things.
This is concrete!
Where did it go? Where is it? It's gone!
Where did you go? It's gone!
Great. This old man is seriously bad news.
Hermit Purple!
Get out of here, you mutt! Shoo! Shoo!
Do you hear something crying?
It's right here, Josuke.
A baby! There's a naked baby right here.
I can tell when I'm touching it. It's invisible!
What?!
I-It's there!
It's really there!
It's all squishy.
Well, I'll be damned.
It's an invisible baby!
It feels like it's only about
six months old or so.
But how did a baby turn invisible out here?
I'm assuming it's a Stand ability, but...
There are a lot of questions,
like, "Why did the enemy
Stand user make it invisible,"
and "Where is its mom?"
Josuke, I think the baby
is actually the Stand user.
It's a Stand user without realizing it.
Because it's been separated from its
mother, it instinctively went invisible.
Huh?
Even adults can develop ulcers,
spot baldness, and gray hair
before they realize it for
psychological reasons, right?
I believe that finding its mother
will be the way to solve this.
H-Hey, just hurry up and make it stop crying.
I-I'm not really sure what to do, either.
I did something similar to this,
but that was a very long time ago.
There, there...
Th-This is...
Did you figure something out?
Yes, when I just touched it now.
It's a little girl.
Right, the way to tell if it's a boy
or a girl is between the legs!
Did you find out something else?
Josuke,
do you have any tissues?
Th-That smell...
I-Is there one on your hand? A huge one?
I-It's invisible, so I couldn't tell
for sure until I could smell it.
And I just scratched my beard with this hand!
Shi
Shini
Shinin
Shining
Shining D
Shining Di
Shining Dia
Shining Diamo
Shining Diamon
Shining Diamond
Jo
Josuke
Josuke Higashi
Josuke Higashikata
I'm returning your manuscript to you.
I'll be looking forward to those
fixes for the volumes, Sensei.
For the time being, we're gonna
have to get milk and diapers.
And since she's naked,
we need to get her some clothes.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Joestar.
What? I-I'm buying them?
Of course. Look at me.
It'd be too embarrassing
for me to buy baby goods.
There'd be rumors that
a 16-year-old delinquent like
me got some girl pregnant.
But I only have American traveler's checks.
Oh, fine...
You can use my credit card.
Sorry about that.
Don't buy anything too expensive.
I've worked hard to build up my
savings, and I don't have much!
I got it, I got it.
Welcome.
Can I help you find something?
Um... Do you carry disposable diapers?
Of course! Is this your first time here?
Yes, it is, but...
These diapers are easy to change,
even if you're living on your own.
Silky Smooth Underwear
For Adults
You won't have to worry overnight, either.
Um... I'm looking for a baby, not myself.
P-Pardon me! So you're
looking for baby diapers.
Were you looking for cloth diapers,
or disposable pull-ups?
Uh... What was that?
As you can see, this one
will need a diaper cover,
but the disposable pull-up
is simple and economical.
I-I don't really know, so could you just...
What size do you need?
Size?
How old is the baby?
Depending on the baby's size,
we have newborn, S-size, M-size,
L-size, XL-size, boys' and girls'.
Th-There are that many options nowadays?
W-Well, she's a girl, and when
I held her, she was about this big.
What do you mean by "when I held her," sir?
It'd be inconvenient for us
if you bought diapers
that were too big, and then
tried to return them after
they've been pooped in.
Oh, all right. Give me all of the sizes.
I also need baby wipes,
powdered milk, and baby bottles...
For baby bottles, we have glass or plastic.
Huh?
Glass ones don't scratch or
start to smell as easily,
but they are a bit heavy for a baby to hold.
The plastic ones are light,
but may have a noticeable smell.
Which one would you like?
U-U-Uh... Um...
We also have various shapes and designs.
We have ones shaped like
rocket ships and racing cars.
This one, the baby can hold by itself.
And this one, if you turn it
upside-down, the doll inside moves.
I-I have no idea, so if you
could just throw in a few...
And which bottle nipples
would you like, sir?
Rubber ones are soft,
but don't last very long.
Silicon ones last, but are a bit hard.
This one is called a "Chupatoreni."
There's a diaphragm where
the nipple goes in the mouth,
and the flow of milk is adjusted
by how hard the baby sucks on it.
This is a NUK from Germany.
The shape is slightly flattened, and is said to
more closely resemble
a mother's natural shape.
And just like when drinking breast
milk, it will not come out
unless they use their jaws.
O-Oh, all right. Whatever is fine.
Just give me all of them.
As for the nipple holes, we have round,
Y-shaped, and cross-shaped varieties.
J-Just give me all of them.
And some baby clothes and socks, too.
I'll be paying by card.
Thank you very much, sir.
130,000... I don't really
understand yen that well.
I wonder how much that is in dollars.
If 100 yen is about 80 cents...
Well, whatever.
I didn't waste any money,
and it's just baby stuff.
I'm sure it can't be that expensive.
Damn it...
What's he doing? He's taking forever.
By the way...
The girl who got the ring.
I wonder what happened with that.
Since he didn't get an answer,
I wonder if that was a no.
They could be super conflicted about it.
I can't stay here...
If people from school find me here...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Josuke.
Here's your card back.
You're done? A-All right, let's go.
Now we won't have to worry
about losing sight of her, but...
If strangers see that she doesn't
have a face, they'll be creeped out.
I thought about that and...
bought some makeup, too.
Let's try some foundation first. There we go!
Hey, I think she might actually be cute.
My, what a beauty!
This face will help us find her mom.
We've finally got some hope. We can do this!
That was a good idea!
Good, good! All right,
now let's try some lipstick.
And let's draw on some eyebrows
and eyelashes... Like that.
I knew he'd do that...
So this geezer's the type to get carried
away when you compliment him.
Now we can finally take you around
without having to worry too much.
We can't put makeup on your eyes,
so we'll just have to use sunglasses.
That looks great!
Here's some milk.
Maybe I went too light on the foundation.
It looks like it's starting to come off...
Th-That's not it!
What is this?! Sh-She's...
Sh-She disappeared! And so did my hands!
This baby's not just making herself invisible!
She's making everything
around her invisible, too!
Mr. Joestar! Let go of the baby!
I'm telling you to hurry up
and let go of the baby!
Th-They're still invisible,
even though I let go of her.
She's powering up!
This isn't good.
It looks like everything within
about thirty centimeters
of that baby is becoming invisible.
But this doesn't make sense.
If she keeps trying to protect
herself with her Stand,
who could even feed her or take care of her?
So it must be due to feelings of anxiety.
It's stress.
She doesn't want to be touched
by someone she doesn't know.
If she powers up any more,
no one will be able to get near her.
We'll end up invisible, too.
That's some weird junk.
I wonder who's gonna clean it up.
Well, I guess someone will do it.
Not me, though.
Look out!
What happened?
This lit cigarette butt was...
Oh, you can't see it.
What the hell are you doing, Mr. Joestar?!
Don't space out at a time like this!
I, uh...
The stroller completely disappeared!
And the ground, too!
So it is stress!
The more scared she gets,
the wider her range gets!
That's the sound of the stroller flipping over!
The invisible baby... fell into the water?!
Wh-Where is she? Make some noise!
I can't even see any bubbles! Where is she?!
J-Josuke...
Shut up!
This all happened because he
couldn't keep it together.
That stupid old geezer!
This irresponsible guy is my father?
He's so irresponsible, he was okay with
abandoning my mom for sixteen years.
There's no way in hell I can
respect someone like him.
There's no way we can get along.
You stay out of this.
Where is she? She should
be right around here.
I don't care if I turn invisible, too.
Just hurry up and touch me!
Come on!
She's not here... Hurry!
Damn it! How the hell am I supposed to find
an invisible baby in clear water?!
Josuke, I...
might die in just a moment,
so when that happens,
please give my regards to your mother.
I mean...
I am quite old now.
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm adding color to the water...
It's the center...
The color of the blood is turning
more and more invisible.
The child is in the center.
Mr. Joestar...
No one else would think to do this.
Not for someone else's child,
who they've never seen before...
They wouldn't go this far.
I wanted to look cool
in front of you.
H
Her
Herm
Hermi
Hermit
Hermit P
Hermit Pur
Hermit Purp
Hermit Purple
J
Jo
Jose
Joseph
Joseph J
Joseph Jo
Joseph Joe
Joseph Joes
Joseph Joest
Joseph Joestar
Well, a lot happened...
But it looks like everything
worked out for now.
O-One hundred and thirty thousand yen?!
The savings I worked so hard for...
That stupid geezer!
There, there.
Episode 14
Let's Go to the Manga Artist's House, Part 1