So there you are... Boss...
That's where... you were...
And that's... whose body you're using.
The moment I got tired and could
feel my soul being sucked out,
you said you had to go because
things were going south...
It's true...
If you're there, Boss...
We're going to win for sure...
But...
I'm so lonely...
Could you... call me again...
like you always have?
Boss...
No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Eternal greatness exists only within myself.
Sing a song of sorrow in a world where time has vanished.
Episodio 36 Diavolo Surfaces
Mista! Hurry up and pierce
your Stand with this arrow!
What's going on?
Requiem's suddenly heading toward us.
Giorno! Stop Requiem!
I can't! It's too far away!
Crack
Wha—
My gun...
What are you doing, Mista?!
It's because you're touching the arrow!
No way! Why is this...
Let go of it, Mr. Polnareff!
Let go of the arrow!
Glad I took that cop's Beretta just in case.
But what the hell, Bullets?
Why'd my revolver break all of a sudden?
M-Maybe the boss got close?
You dumbass! Think before
you talk, Number Five!
Are you saying you saw someone coming
close to us in this big, open space?
We didn't see anyone at the
moment the revolver broke.
It's metal fatigue.
It's because he's been overusing the gun.
The axis of the cylinder broke.
We haven't had a chance to do
any maintenance or inspections!
H-Hey!
What the hell is this thing's problem?
It's heading toward m-me!
No, Mista. It's heading towards me.
Even though it has the arrow back...
Golden Wind!
Batoom
Requiem intends to finish me
because I touched the arrow.
Mista, run!
Reload, Bullets! Reload the gun!
This isn't a revolver!
We need another cartridge!
It'll take time to reload it!
I-It's no use...
I'm finished...
I'm throwing it! Catch it, Giorno!
I'm gonna throw the turtle to you!
Mr. Polnareff!
You okay, Mr. Polnareff?
He's okay. B-But... how?
Mista, do you remember what
I said back at the Colosseum?
There's still more to Requiem's
ability that I'm not aware of.
But I'm starting to understand.
Requiem stopped because
the starting time has come.
The starting time?
Yes.
It's because
my body has started to change!
That's why it stopped trying to kill me!
This is Requiem's true motive,
now that it's gone berserk.
The ability to make beings swap souls,
meaning the ability that makes them
start to change into something else.
The prelude is over, and the actual
piece is now starting to play,
so it gave up on killing me.
The 4.5-billion-year history of this
world's creatures is starting to change
into something else within a matter of hours.
All of it!
I see...
So that's what makes Requiem
so truly frightening.
However...
Thanks to them, I was able to see it.
I'm starting to understand the answer.
I'm close to figuring out how to
get that arrow from Requiem!
I'm realizing the method!
Wh-What the hell is going on?
What's up with this ability?
How far has this damn thing spread?
It doesn't look like they're
dying or in pain...
Everyone just has these vacant stares.
But there is this fear of
becoming something else.
The fear that, slowly but surely, both my
body and my soul are going to disappear.
Trish!
I-I'm fine. But...
The starting time is imminent.
It will happen differently for
each of us, but it'll start soon,
for all of us.
We don't have much time left...
That's what you're saying?
Polnareff! This is happening
because you brought the arrow!
You said it had the power to defeat the boss,
but instead, you basically ended us!
Stop! This is far beyond
anyone's expectations.
It's more important that we
find a way to defeat Requiem.
That's right. Good. Get closer.
Get closer to Requiem!
If we get closer, I'll be able to fully see
Requiem's secrets, because I'm right here.
The arrow's power will become mine,
and the world will grovel at my feet!
After it!
Good!
Don't move, Mista!
Trish, Bucciarati! Both of
you stay where you are!
Stay right there!
Wha—
I just told you not to move, Mista!
We can catch up to Requiem in a second!
What the hell? Shut up, you dumbass!
My body's disappearing already!
I picked up your revolver.
The one that you said broke a moment ago.
This broken part doesn't match up
correctly with the rest of it.
If it just broke due to metal fatigue,
they should still fit together.
What are you getting at, Giorno?
Bucciarati, I need you to
stay right there, too!
We need to keep a distance from each other!
You dumbass! Requiem is getting away!
The Bullets said it was metal
fatigue, so it's metal fatigue!
I have a new Beretta, too!
The parts aren't matching up
because a piece flew off!
That could be...
But it could be something more.
We'll be able to tell as soon
as we see this lost piece.
Golden Wind.
I gave a part of the gun
life and let it loose.
Moles are basically blind, but their
sense of smell is unparalleled.
Looks like it's returned,
and it found its lost piece.
Fit
H-Hey, wait a sec!
Are you saying someone just used
immense force to tear the gun apart?
Listen up! The Bullets and
I are very clear on this!
There's no one who got close
to me in this square—
You're exactly right. No one did.
That's why we need to stay
apart from each other,
because his range is only a few meters!
Giorno, you...
No one got close to Narancia
when he was attacked, either.
No one... other than us.
Mr. Polnareff, if your guess is correct
and the boss had two personalities,
then he should be able to get in
and out of another's mind freely.
Diavolo has inhabited one of us.
Wha—
If he stays hidden,
Trish can't detect his existence.
The reason he's staying hidden now
is because he's waiting for us
to obtain the arrow for good.
That's why he also appeared for a
brief moment to destroy the gun.
W-Wait a second!
I know I keep saying this,
but stay away from me, Mista!
Stay out of his range!
My gun was destroyed!
You're the one closest to the gun.
I-It's...
It's not me!
O-Oh, yeah. When Narancia was attacked...
The one closest to him was...
Shit. I must do something.
Requiem keeps moving farther away.
This rookie, Giorno Giovanna...
He's hiding in one of us.
But despite that, we have one advantage.
Diavolo can make Emperor Crimson appear,
but he doesn't have complete control
of the body he's inhabiting right now.
If he had total control
of the body he's currently inhabiting,
he wouldn't just stay quietly hidden.
It's because he can't manifest
and move around freely
that we all still live and
haven't been eliminated.
In a sense, we have him cornered.
It's the turtle!
It was the closest one to my revolver!
Polnareff is the one who's possessed!
That's not possible.
Mr. Polnareff was almost
killed by Requiem earlier,
because the boss destroyed the revolver.
The boss won't let the body he's
inhabiting be put in danger.
Plus...
I only sense one being's life force.
This turtle only has one soul in it.
You can tell that, Giorno?
Only if I can get closer
and touch their body.
How can you be so certain?
Life force is a mass.
If I actually touch someone,
I can tell how many there are.
There's no other way.
I have to touch each one of you and find out.
But how are you going to get closer
within Emperor Crimson's range?
I learned how to detect
Emperor Crimson from Mr. Polnareff.
The moment the droplets suddenly
increase is when time has skipped!
Correct.
But whether you can avoid his attack
or not will be a matter of luck,
as is whether you'll be able
to just barely dodge it.
It's definitely not me.
When Narancia was killed,
I was the farthest away.
Then I'll check you first
so we can be at ease.
Hey!
Stop right there! Stay away from me!
D-Don't come any closer!
If Diavolo is actually in you,
what's going to happen to me?
When Narancia died, his body was empty.
My soul was able to travel from
Narancia's body into my own,
but it was empty.
There's no chance that he's possessing me.
Oh, really?
That's just what you're saying.
I have no way of confirming your ability.
Not to mention, Giorno,
do you have a way to definitively
confirm that you only have one soul?
You can't check yourself with
your own ability, can you?
Mista, we can't go after the
arrow unless we find out!
Come any closer and I'll blow your limbs off!
Stop!
Check me first, Giorno.
Hurry up and do it!
We're losing more and more time.
Just as you said,
depending on how we look at the
situation, we have the boss cornered.
There's no other way.
Yes...
We have to do this right now.
Someone's going to be attacked...
If we get closer to one another...
Slice
Giorno!
It's Mista!
He was the one possessed!
Spicy Lady—
No, Trish!
It's you!
He got closer instantly by
moving your body closer to him!
I've been waiting for this
moment, my daughter...
The moment you unleashed your Stand!
Diagram of swapped souls
Bucciarati
His body has died
(which means Doppio
has also died)
Trish            Mista
Diavolo
(Emperor Crimson
had possessed him)
Giorno
Turtle   Polnareff
My daughter...
If you hadn't revealed your Stand,
I might've actually been cornered...
Zipper Man!
If I can grab the Stand,
I can also move the body.
Now I can at least make this body run.
We're going to be attacked!
Brace yourselves!
He's going to make time leap—
Wha—
D-Don't tell me...
Why's he running without attacking us?
Through observation, he's already found
a way to get the arrow away from Requiem!
There's no time! That takes priority!
Shoot, Mista!
Don't let him get there
first, no matter what!
Stop wasting time!
This isn't the time to hesitate
because that's your own body!
That's not it...
I've already fired, Bucciarati.
It seems that... I've already fired six shots.
He's running as he makes time leap!
He predicted the course of the bullets!
After him! If he gets the
arrow, we're finished!
That shadow...
The reason no one can touch the arrow...
If I'm correct...
When I move, Requiem's shadow moves
in the opposite direction from me,
despite the location of the sun.
Which means...
To that man, it should look like the
shadow is stretching toward me.
In Bucciarati's eyes, the shadow is
stretching in front of Requiem.
Which means...
This shadow is in different
places depending on the viewer!
This is the mystery of Requiem!
This is why it can control everyone's souls!
This thing is the shadow of one's soul.
Requiem itself is the shadow of my soul!
That's why attacking it will
mean attacking yourself!
If we can get rid of this shadow,
I can get the arrow!
And...
If it has a shadow, then my own
light should be somewhere, as well!
He still doesn't have the arrow!
We're rushing in, Mista!
The light is behind my own mind!
He just destroyed something behind his head!
What in the world did he do?
Now I've got it...
I, Diavolo, now have the arrow!
If Diavolo found a way to grasp the
arrow, we should take advantage of it.
Because the arm he tore off of me and these
droplets of blood are all just particles.
Golden Wind shall now
appear!
These ants!
What just happened?
This is good, so far.
Let's go...
We have to hurry.
Blast the arrow away from him!
Don't let him grab it, Mista!
I'm already shooting!
They made it through!
Despite him predicting their
movements, we're still far apart.
He can only knock the ones coming
at him out of their trajectory!
The rest of you knock that arrow
back and bring it to me, Bullets!
H-He'd already thrown...
...a civilian into the air!
He figured out the bullets would land
and returned the arrow to its place!
The trash ability of an underling...
There's no way your weak mind can
surpass Emperor Crimson's predictions.
You will not be able to get through.
You're still just trash.
I will admit though, Bucciarati,
your team has made me sweat.
I never dreamed you would be foolish
enough to betray the organization,
nor did I ever think you'd
find out my true identity.
But the fact that I've been able to figure
out this arrow's true power is a blessing!
It's a gift granted to me by fate
because I was able to defeat my past!
I need ammo, Bullets!
We told you, Mista!
It takes time to reload that cartridge!
We're finished!
Wh-What in the world?
Spicy... Lady...
You didn't deflect Mista's bullets.
I just made them softer.
The bullets stretched out like
chewing gum and stuck to your hand,
and I had them use their elastic force
to return and blow through it.
Trish... You're still conscious!
I'm going to overcome this.
I'm not going to live in fear
and run away from the fate
that you've passed on to me.
If it's in my way, I'll just climb over it!
The arrow's flying toward me!
I'm the closest!
He can't get past me!
Even if he predicts where
it'll fall and erases time,
I'm still closer to it!
If only... My daughter,
if only you hadn't been born...
Fear truly does come from the past.
You have genuinely angered me!
What?
Booooom
You said you'd overcome this, did you not?
You were right, Trish. Now you
can surpass not only the past...
but their heads.
Trish!
Episodio 37
King of Kings