...is nothing compared to the heart
of justice that's here right now!
It's definitely here!
It's right here for sure!
Compared to that heart, you're nothing!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Th-This is a dream...
This... is a dream.
The idea that I'm being cornered like this...
This has to be a dream.
You don't have...
...anywhere left to run.
You're finished.
J-Josuke's badly hurt...
The battle had already begun
while we were waiting.
Which means...
That's Yoshikage Kira.
Someone's hurt over there!
Get back! There's a chance of
an explosion from a gas leak!
Bring the ambulance over here!
Bring the stretcher!
It's dangerous, so please get back!
Are you all right?
Just get back!
Can you hear me?
An ambulance is on its way.
You're going to be all right.
Don't let that lady near Kira!
We'll get you treated at
the hospital right away.
Please, hang in there.
It'll be okay. Hang in there.
O-Oh, no!
That lady's been turned into a bomb!
Can you see how many fingers I'm holding up?
Jotaro, we need your Star Platinum.
I know.
But it's no use unless I can get closer.
Even if I stop time, we're too far away,
and I can't do anything to him.
I have to get at least five meters closer.
You turned someone into a
bomb and took them hostage?
Just try it! I'll fix her right up in a heartbeat!
No! It's not as simple as taking a hostage!
He's got a hidden ability!
It's an ability called Bites the Dust,
and it can blow away time!
Episode 39    Goodbye, Morioh – The Heart of Gold
It must only work on people who aren't
Stand users, like me or that lady,
and occurs coincidentally
whenever Kira is in trouble.
Which means, when he's in despair
like this, this ability activates
and becomes a bomb that can
turn back time one hour!
What the hell?
The knuckles and skin on
your hand are so soft...
You have such cute, white fingers...
Will you rub my cheek?
Huh?
Rubbing my cheek calms me down so much...
When I was a child...
You've heard of Leonardo da
Vinci's Mona Lisa, right?
When I saw that painting in an art book...
When I first saw that,
I don't know how to put it...
Um, this is a bit dirty, but...
Everything About
Leonardo da Vinci's
World
I got an erection.
I just cut out the part with her hands
and hung it in my room for a while.
I want to cut off yours, too.
What are you doing?!
My name is Yoshikage Kira!
I've killed 48 women with
beautiful hands up to now.
You're the only one!
You're the only one who
will know my identity!
O-Oh, no! Bites the Dust is about to start!
If we don't defeat him now,
everyone here but that
lady will be blown away!
Jotaro!
Are you coming for me, Jotaro?
Bites the Dust was created because
I didn't want to run into you!
Come closer! Just try and stop time!
How long will you be able to stop it?
Just try to corner me more!
Pushing me to the limit again will
make Bites the Dust appear!
Jotaro, stop time!
Don't let him push Killer Queen's switch!
Wh-What?
No, this is the limit! I'm pushing it...
Now!
I-I did it! It activated!
I was able to return!
It went into effect.
I was able to have Bites
the Dust take effect again!
I beat them!
Now I can be free!
What was that just now?
The birds came from behind me and...
What just happened?
Come to think of it, this isn't
the way I usually take to work...
But if Bites the Dust did
turn back time one hour,
I should be on my way to work now...
What time is it right now?
That's right. I had put my
watch in my chest pocket.
This is...
Why is it broken?!
It's 8:29! Bites the Dust
did go into effect again!
The watch that Hayato broke with Stray Cat
should have returned to normal, too!
Haven't you realized it?
So the Kosaku Kawajiri that Rohan took
a picture of was Yoshikage Kira...
And it's finally over, isn't it?
They finally cornered you, Yoshikage Kira.
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
Well, I guess that's no surprise.
It happened fifteen years ago.
Something very traumatic must have happened.
Something so traumatic that you don't
even realize what happened to you.
Are you a new Stand user?!
I'll make you realize
that you're already dead!
What?
This isn't any Stand ability!
This is proof that all that's here is the
completely black soul of a dead killer!
Well? Do you remember how you died now?
Even if I stop time right now,
I'm too far away from him.
Don't let him push the switch!
No, this is the limit! I'm pushing it...
Now!
Act Three! 3 Freeze!
He's now within five meters!
S-h-i-t!
You rotten pieces of shit!
Star Platinum! The World!
Koichi, you truly are a reliable guy.
I'm truly thankful that I came
to this town and met you.
And...
Good grief.
I made it in time.
Time has begun to move again.
Crush
H-He did it!
He made it in time!
I'll push it... I'm gonna push it...
Bites the Dust will go into effect again...
H-How? He just suddenly went flying back!
I'm gonna push it... I-I'm gonna push it...
I'm gonna push the switch right now...
I know he's our enemy,
but he really is something.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Morioh Fire Department
Someone's on the ground back here!
What?!
O-Oh, no! A guy's been
run over by an ambulance!
I didn't realize he was there!
Drive back forward! Forward!
You there! Get outside of the tape!
Get back! Please hurry and get back!
Are you one of the injured, too?
It's no use. He's dead. He died instantly.
He's dead?
It was like he dove under there himself.
This is my responsibility.
I'm not trying to make excuses, but I
didn't have a chance to restrain him.
This is unbelievable.
His head was caught between
the tire and the road...
The skin on his face has been ripped off.
Pardon me.
Do you happen to know the
identity of the deceased?
He said that his name was Yoshikage Kira.
Kira...
There's a family by the name of Kira
in Kotodai that goes back generations.
I heard its only current member lives alone,
so he might not have any family...
An accident... His demise was
due to an accidental death.
But this is how it should be.
There would be no way to punish him in court.
This was the best outcome.
I... didn't actually get along
with my dad that well...
But my dad was murdered by him.
I wanted him punished.
I wanted someone to punish him.
It looks like you remember, Yoshikage Kira...
The exact way you died.
It looks like you remember now!
Just what are you?! Who the hell are you?!
Fifteen years ago, you didn't
have a Stand ability,
so you couldn't make corpses disappear.
That's why, when I died,
it was in all the papers.
Do you remember this wound on my back?
Or, since it was your first murder,
you forgot to take my hand,
so perhaps I wasn't as memorable?!
It's you...
I believe your name was Reimi Sugimoto...
What the hell have you been
doing here for fifteen years?!
Wait...
Why would you go to the
trouble of showing me
the wound on your back and
telling me who you are?
This wouldn't be the place where you're
not supposed to turn around, is it?
My father told me that there was a road in
this town where spirits of the dead walk,
and if you were to find yourself there,
you must not turn around.
If you were to turn around,
an uncontrollable power
would drag you off somewhere.
You weren't showing me
the wound on your back so
I'd end up in front of you,
forcing me to turn around, were you?
You weren't trying to trick me, were you?
Let's have you turn around.
I'd like to see what would happen.
Come on! Turn around!
You will turn around!
Did you really think
that I didn't expect you to try to do this to me?
We've been waiting fifteen
years for you to come here...
"We"?
Arnold!
What?!
Now, let's have you punished, Yoshikage Kira.
What? What are these things?!
Deadly Queen!
Make these things explode!
I-I...
Wh-Where are they going to take me?
Who knows?
But...
I'm sure it's somewhere you
won't be able to rest in peace.
Now,
we can finally...
We can finally go...
Help Wanted
Reimi! Are you really leaving?
It wouldn't hurt if you stayed
a little longer, would it?
It feels like this town's
losing its guardian angel...
It makes me uneasy,
knowing that you're leaving.
Thanks... But there's nothing
left for us to do in this town.
The time has come for us to leave this town.
We have to go.
Or what? Are you going to cry when I leave
because you'll miss me, Rohan?
Don't be stupid.
Kisara
Drugs
Why would I miss you?
You already died fifteen years ago.
I said this before, but I still
believe that ghosts should give up
whatever attachments they have left
here, and just hurry up and pass on.
Oh, fine! Since this is the
last time, I'll be honest!
I will miss you!
Of course I don't want you to go!
Hey.
Josuke! Everyone!
So it's finally over, Reimi.
Yukako! Hazamada, and everyone else!
We came to see you off.
Everyone...
I know it's strange to say this
to a dead person, but take care.
I'm going to miss you, too.
You're a wonderful young lady.
Reimi! Thank you for everything!
Because of you, this town was saved!
Thanks, Koichi.
But I believe we all saved Morioh together.
I'm sure that no one here
will ever forget you.
Thank you, everyone.
Goodbye, everyone.
Goodbye, Reimi.
Goodbye...
He's awfully late tonight...
I wonder if he had to work overtime.
He could call, at least...
Oh, Hayato.
You go on and eat before it gets cold.
I'll eat when your father gets home.
Hayato?
I'll wait, too...
I'll eat with you
when Dad gets home, too...
You sure?
By the way, have you gotten
a little taller lately?
Our town, Morioh, was deeply hurt.
The town was hurt by the
monster named Yoshikage Kira
that this town itself had created.
I'm sure that Hayato's mom
will forever be waiting
for her husband to return.
Shigechi's parents will forever
be waiting for him to return.
The families of the daughters and
sisters killed by Yoshikage Kira
will forever be waiting for their return.
The pain of their wounds
will now only get deeper.
How can we try to ease this pain?
Will it be life-threatening for this town's
future, or will it eventually disappear?
I have no idea.
Are you worried, Jotaro?
About leaving this town?
Yeah, a little.
After watching Josuke and the others
get involved in this incident in Morioh,
there's one thing that I can say...
That the young people in
this town have hearts of gold.
The same hearts of gold shining with justice
that we saw when we headed to Egypt.
I saw that within Josuke and the others...
As long as they have that, they'll be fine.
We won't have to worry
about this town any longer.
Hey, Old Man!
Can't you hear me, Old Man?
Now, then... I guess I should say
goodbye to the son I'm so proud of.
The picture of my mom
that I just gave you...
You still got it?
Yes. I put it in my wallet,
just as you asked.
I'm leaving without seeing your mother,
but I wish her nothing but happiness.
Ah... So you put it in your wallet...
This is the edge of that picture.
Shining Diamond!
I'll be taking this!
A dad should give his son an allowance, right?
Not to mention, if you take
that picture back home,
your old lady's gonna get mad at you again!
Y-You little brat...
You gonna take back what you said about
him having a heart of gold, old man?
Take care!
The invisible baby's
mother was never found,
and the baby ended up being
adopted by Joseph Joestar.
Jotaro Kujo got his doctorate
from a thesis he wrote
while he was here about a
starfish he saw on the beach.
Josuke, that jerk!
He ate the snack I was
saving for myself again!
Ugh!
I'm gonna drink his juice.
Koichi!
Sorry!
I was late because I was making us lunch.
Huh? You made us lunch? Thanks!
I can't wait to eat it.
So good!
Whew
Oh, here it comes! Yeah! That intensity!
You might be able to turn
back to normal, Dad!
Well, whatever.
My skin is so soft!
My eyes feel so refreshed!
The food here was amazing!
Right? Even I look so much more
beautiful that I don't know what
I'm going to do with myself.
You're shining, Yu.
So shiny!
You think so?
I'm shiny, eh?
Grazie!
I look forward to your next visit.
I just saw Ko holding hands
with a really pretty girl!
Huh? What does that mean?
He hasn't told me anything!
Did you hear about
Mr. Kira who went missing?
I did! You mean how he turned
up as a faceless corpse, right?
That's so scary...
What are you gonna do about it?
Wha?
I'm telling you that juice
sprayed out from the can
you kicked and got all over my manga!
That's not my problem!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
All right. Warm-up exercises done.
Shonen Jump
Thanks for waiting!
Serialization Returns!
Is it really so interesting to
look at the town all the time?
Nothing ever changes.
It is.
This town is very interesting.
And so, for most people, the summer
of 1999 passed like any other summer.
Hey, did you hear?
Apparently, Rohan was caught
shoplifting at Kame Yu.
What?!
That's insane if it's true.
Yeah, but I'm not really sure.
You aren't even sure?
Jeez... Well, let's go.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
End