This arrow is very precious.
It's the only one there is.
It's my precious objective.
I just have to retrieve it.
Don't you dare pull out that arrow!
It'll make him bleed even more!
Because my little brother's an idiot,
I have to kill you now.
Which means it won't be good
if something happens to this arrow.
If the lady next door happens to see it,
or if it snaps in half, that'd be bad news.
I'm a very methodical type, you see,
so I want to make sure I put
the arrow away properly.
When you're listening to CDs, you properly
put the first one away in its case
before listening to the second one, right?
Everyone's like that.
I'm like that, too.
Oh? You're gonna come into this house?
Think before you speak!
If I don't come in, I can't kick
your ass and treat Koichi's wounds!
Bro! I haven't lost yet!
Hold off on attacking him!
Attack?
We ain't finished yet!
Something's coming from...
the darkness of the ceiling!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 4  The Nijimura Brothers, Part 2
Okuyasu...
How stupid you are never ceases to amaze me.
If you hadn't come staggering in here,
my Worse Company would have
attacked Josuke for sure.
And you actually walked into
its attack trajectory.
Bro...
Your Stand, The Hand, is terrifying,
but you're completely incompetent.
I told you over and over,
ever since we were kids,
that incompetent people drag down
everyone around them, didn't I?
I told you over and over that people
only have the right to live
if they keep growing, didn't I?
What's with his injuries?
What kind of attack makes you
end up with wounds like that?
Anyway, it seems that something's up there.
Little brother,
I think it's only natural that
morons like you should die!
It left a ton of holes again!
What kind of attack is that?
Shining Diamond!
Are you trying to attack your brother, too?!
Josuke Higashikata...
I'm sure he won't abandon
this brat he called Koichi.
He'll most likely come in here again.
I'll kill him, no matter what...
I'll kill anyone who gets in the way
of this bow and arrow's objective,
no matter who they may be!
Now, then... How about you tell me
about your brother's Stand?
Tell me what his Stand really is!
If you tell me, I'll treat your wounds.
Like hell... I'm gonna tell you...
Dumbass...
As I thought.
Well, then... I guess I have no choice!
I'm gonna go in there again,
so just don't get in my way, Okuyasu.
Koichi doesn't have much time!
His Stand attacks from somewhere
within this darkness.
Going in here is pretty dangerous.
I've got no choice but to
use all of my senses fully...
Hey, wait a minute!
Huh?
Why, Josuke? Why did you treat my wounds?
Shut up. I'll tell you later.
I might attack you! I'm your enemy!
You want a piece of me?
After I hear your answer!
Why did you treat my wounds?
I'm not very smart,
so you're gonna have to tell me!
And that wound on your hand!
You got that when you were
pulling me outside, didn't you?
I wanna know why you went
through all that to save me.
There's no deep reason.
"There's no reason he has to die."
That's what I thought back there.
Koichi...
The trail leads upstairs.
I still have more questions, Josuke!
What's your problem?!
I'm begging you, just let me save Koichi!
Why?!
Why don't you use your Stand's
powers to fix your own hand?
You should just fix it up
like you did with my face.
My Shining Diamond can't
repair my own wounds.
It just means life isn't that easy.
And, more than anything,
I have no way of saving people
who've already died.
Let me just say one thing, Okuyasu.
If Koichi dies, I don't know what
I'm gonna do to your brother.
So don't hold it against me. It was your
brother who caused all this trouble.
You got that? If you do, stay outside.
Koichi!
Damn it... This is definitely a trap.
He plans to attack me from somewhere
as soon as I get close to Koichi.
But...
Even if I know it's a trap,
I have no choice but to go!
Koichi doesn't even have seconds left!
What?!
Okuyasu, you bastard!
Josuke!
Gyaon
Koichi just...
Because I'm stupid, I just
act on what's in my heart.
Just once, just this once,
I'll repay my debt to you.
I won't do anything else.
I won't help out my Bro,
or do anything to you, either.
This is it.
That's just great, Okuyasu.
Hey, you were in great danger, Koichi.
I'm glad you came to.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Five...
I-I got my head trapped between the gates,
and then, uh... um...
Wh-Where are we?
That dangerous situation we were
in earlier isn't over yet, Koichi.
I want to go down those
stairs and go outside,
but I wonder if Okuyasu's brother
will let us do that safely...
There's definitely something up there.
Something's lurking in the
shadows of the ceiling.
What's that?
Something really fast just went by.
Josuke, what's going on?
Koichi, I'm sure you have no
idea what's going on right now.
For now, don't ask any questions,
and get closer to me.
Earlier, it was creepy
because I couldn't see it,
but I feel a bit more at ease
now that I've seen it.
It just looks like a shrimp
with very little power.
This battle's gonna end with
me sending Shining Diamond
after that shrimp the next time it pops up.
There you are!
What the heck? There's a ton of them!
And that uniform...
Burn
Wh-What's...
A bunch of guys that look like
toy soldiers are falling...
Are these Okuyasu's brother's Stand?
Ow!
You bastard!
I guess attacking two or three
won't do enough damage.
And the wounds are small, but their
destructive power is the real thing.
We're sure to get seriously
hurt if we fight these things.
Since Okuyasu decided to meddle
and save that brat,
my plan's been derailed.
But they won't be leaving this house...
Nor will they leave my Stand,
Worse Company's, battlefield.
Wo
Wor
Worse
Worse Co
Worse Com
Worse Compa
Worse Company
Kei
Keicho
Keicho Niji
Keicho Nijimura
Worse Company?
Josuke, wh-what's...
Don't ask questions.
I'm sure you don't get it,
but just shut up and stay back!
We're in real trouble right now!
All units, halt!
Ready, aim...
Fire!
Left face!
As I thought, that's enough
destructive power to blow off
our limbs if they hit us head-on!
Lucky! There are some windows.
Koichi, this is the second floor,
but we're gonna bust out
those windows and dive out.
I guess I was a bit naïve...
Just great... They have helicopters, too?
Those look like the American
army's Apache helicopters.
Look out! There's a tank!
You're right. They have tanks, too.
Koichi, be caref—
What?
Wh-What did you just say,
Koichi? Can you see them?
These soldiers, tanks, and helicopters...
You can see them clearly?
Yeah. I'm not sure what's
going on, but I can see them.
Could it be that since you were shot by
that arrow, you became a Stand user?
Oh? So the little shrimp
has the power to use a Stand now?
There you are, Okuyasu's big bro.
You've got some guts,
showing yourself like that!
My Stand, Worse Company,
has unbreakable defense.
It's an army that won't let
any invader leave alive.
I'm sure you want to beat me...
But I can tell you right now that
your Shining Diamond's attacks
will never reach me.
Look! Do you see my army's
beautiful formation?
All units, maintain battle
formation! At ease!
It feels so good when they're
so beautifully together.
Though I'm a bit pissed off
that their formation is
a little off, since you
killed two or three of them.
You sure are methodical.
You came out here just to explain that?
No, the reason I came out here
is to watch you, brat.
M-Me?
That's right.
Koichi, was it?
It seems, despite my expectations,
you had the aptitude to be a Stand user.
Make your Stand appear right now,
and show me what it can do.
You might have the ability
that I've been looking for.
If you have that ability, I'll let you live.
B-But...
The ability you're looking for?
What the hell are you after?
You're in no position to be
asking questions, Josuke!
My decision to kill you hasn't changed!
Be thankful that you get to live a bit longer.
That's just great.
Hey, what're you doing?
Make your Stand appear, brat!
S-Stand? I have no idea what's going on...
Oh? It's your first time? I see!
Fine! Josuke, show him how
to make a Stand appear!
Huh?
Your Shining Diamond's range
is less than one meter.
If that shrimp's Stand's ability
is able to compensate for yours,
you might be able to escape my Company.
True... It'd be great if it's a
Stand that can kick your ass.
Okay, getting your Stand to
come out is easy, Koichi.
You just need to feel like
you want to protect yourself,
or you want to kick his ass.
Huh?
The rest is just instinct.
A Stand that's unique to your
mentality should come out.
W-Wait! I can't understand
all this out of nowhere!
You don't understand?
Then I guess we'll just have to put
you in a situation that makes you!
Do it, Green Beret!
Boom
What?!
That's...
Hey, Koichi, try moving it.
M-Move what?
That Stand!
Stand?
I-I made this appear?!
What happens after this?
What kind of abilities does
this egg-shaped thing have?
Abilities? I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but this is all I can do!
This is it!
What? That's it?!
This Stand...
That's enough! That's all I need to know!
All units, battle positions!
Koichi, withdraw your Stand.
If they attack that thing, you'll die, too!
Withdraw? How do I make it withdraw?!
Commence attack!
Kablow
J-Josuke!
Good. Now Koichi and Josuke
have been separated.
The crack in that egg...
The brat hasn't realized it yet,
but it might be something worthwhile.
The only one who's going
to die right now is Josuke.
Ow...
Hey, Okuyasu's big bro,
if you're going to use an attack
flashy enough to destroy this house,
I'm gonna do the same.
Let's make this just great.
Josuke Higashikata...
Is it true that you hate it when anyone
says anything insulting about your hair?
Why don't you try insulting it?
Just to test that out.
No, there's no need.
Because I'm going to declare that I'll
blow off the head that your hair sits on.
First, my Worse Company is
going to shoot your legs.
You won't be able to run away then.
Next, we'll damage your arm.
Then you won't be able to guard yourself.
And then, I declare that I'm gonna blow
your brains out, along with your hair.
I see. That's a flawless plan...
If you ignore the fact that it's impossible!
I'm very methodical, you see.
If I say I'll do something
in a certain order, I will.
That's what a declaration is.
He's wide open...
I just need to make that
Stand thing appear again.
It's only an egg-looking thing,
but if I can make it ram into him,
I might be able to beat him!
I-I'm going to do it! Be confident!
I'm going to beat him!
I'm very interested in your Stand,
so I won't kill you just yet.
You bastard!
All units, charge!
Just like Moses, who parted the
Red Sea and walked across its floor,
I'm gonna make my way through
this army and beat you down!
You fool! My plan is going
exactly as I have declared,
Josuke Higashikata!
A l-landmine?!
First, damage to your legs!
And now, Apaches, fire your missiles!
My arm...
First your legs, then your arm.
It feels so good when
things go as I've declared.
Let's see if you can stay in
one piece as my Worse Company
fires all its missiles, shells, and rounds
into that damaged arm of yours!
You've lost, Josuke Higashikata!
All units!
Get ready to fire at once!
What do you think you're
doing, Josuke Higashikata?
Are you surrendering?
Are you asking me to let you go?
That's not happening.
All units, fire!
My plan is already finished.
What?!
My missiles that just attacked Josuke's arm...
Did you forget?
My Shining Diamond can repair
what's been destroyed.
If you forgot, then write it down.
You know, methodically.
Episode 5
The Nijimura Brothers, Part 3