"Head to the Pompeii Archaeological Park.
I've hidden a key near the dog mosaic."
"That key is for a vehicle that'll
bring my daughter safely to me."
Fugo! Abbacchio! Giorno!
You three head to Pompeii and get that key!
Episodio 12  The Second Mission from the Boss
The city of Pompeii was known to the Romans
as a peaceful, prosperous health resort.
It was then abruptly destroyed
by the lapilli and lava
that came from the eruption of Mt. Vesuvius
on August 24th, 79 AD.
Later, archaeologists discovered
that all the houses, streets,
wine bottles, and even
carriage tracks left behind
were preserved as they were when
the volcano erupted 1,800 years ago.
The dog mosaic we're looking for
is located near the entrance of the
House of the Tragic Poet in Pompeii.
Oh, Fugo,
you were supposed to turn right
at that corner, not left.
You should've told me sooner, Giorno.
What point is there if you
tell me that after I turn?
You're exactly right.
I apologize. I'll be more careful next time.
That's not the point here, damn it!
Hey, Fugo.
We're in a hurry, so don't lose it now.
I know that!
Damn it...
Well, Fugo's always like this.
I'm more concerned about
this newbie, Giorno Giovanna.
If Bucciarati insists that I treat him
as one of us, I'll follow his orders,
but there's just something
I don't like about him.
This guy's going to do something...
Something that might get us killed.
Pompeii, huh?
I haven't been here since
I visited on a field trip as a kid.
Abbacchio, Giorno, let's hurry.
The place we're looking for
is about 100 meters ahead.
It should take us about thirty
minutes to get what we need
and get back to the others.
Abbacchio, Giorno, be on your guard.
To think we'd be found so soon...
How many are there?
One... for now.
He's peeking around that
stone pillar behind us.
Pillar? Which one would that be?
Wake up, Giorno.
There's only one pillar.
Can't you see it?
Fugo, there is definitely a single pillar,
but I don't see anyone, either.
Quit messing around!
He's heading right toward us!
Fugo?
There! The guy walking over here!
H-He was right there...
A guy came out from behind that pillar!
I saw him in this mirror!
Wh-What?!
There! He's right there! He's coming out!
H-He's inside the mirror?
He's revealed his Stand!
Who's going to fight him?!
Hold on, Fugo. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Is something wrong with the mirror?
This isn't good! He's going to attack!
Get away from the mirror!
What?
Giorno! Abbacchio!
Wh-Where are you, Giorno? Abbacchio?
Where did you go?!
The guy who was in the mirror is gone, too.
What did he do?
It was bizarre to have a mirror hanging
in a place like this to begin with!
What in the world is this ability?
I don't...
I don't know what it is...
But there's something
off about this scenery.
I'm right here.
What?!
Pannacotta Fugo...
Highly intelligent, with an IQ of 152, and
entered university at the age of thirteen.
But he went berserk on a professor there
and beat him senseless with
a four-kilogram encyclopedia.
From then on, he spiraled
down to where he is now.
The ones who accompanied him are the
former cop Leone Abbacchio and...
No documents on the
other guy. He must be new.
I think I heard you call him Giorno.
What did you do to them?
Y-You bastard...
Where did you hide them?!
My watch is backwards?
Also, I was wearing it on my left
wrist, but now it's on my right?
D-Don't tell me this place is...
Your ability is—
I guess you're pretty quick on the uptake.
One at a time, Fugo...
It didn't really matter who was first,
but we'll start with you, since you
were the first to look at the mirror.
I-It wasn't Abbacchio and
Giorno that disappeared...
W-We're inside the mirror!
It was me!
I'm the one who was dragged in!
Fugo!
Where did you go, Fugo?!
Hey, Giorno!
Didn't you see anything?!
I'm not sure.
It looked as though he suddenly
disappeared to me, as well.
Fugo! Where did you go?!
Before he disappeared, Fugo yelled
at us to get away from the mirror.
And he asked whether we could see the
man walking from behind the the pillar.
This mirror...
Is there something... about this mirror?
The question is...
Where did you hide the boss's daughter?
That's the most important question...
But I'm pretty sure I also need to know why
you three came to Pompeii, the city of death.
I figure you're here to look for something...
And if that's the case, you came here to get
something that'll help you protect the girl,
isn't that right?
If you turn just up the way, it'll lead
you to the famous dog mosaic.
Is there something there?
Well?
I'll be taking it!
Tell me what you came here for, Fugo!
I refuse!
Then die!
No...
You'll be the one dying when
you witness my ability!
Purple Smoke!
My Stand won't appear?
I see... So your Stand
is named Purple Smoke.
Something's wrong. My Stand did come out.
I can feel it... So why?
Hey, Giorno...
Slowly walk toward me.
Slowly what?
Just come over here, you dumbass!
Forget the "slowly" part! Just get over here!
What?! Th-That's—
Giorno! Forget about that!
That's not our enemy! That's Fugo's Stand!
Just hurry up and get away from it!
Don't get any closer!
Fugo's—
Get away from Purple Smoke!
Hurry up!
Your current location is inside the mirror.
I'm sure you can figure out exactly
why I dragged you in here alone.
If I'd brought you in here
along with the others,
who can fight, it'd put me in danger!
I control the inside of the
mirror... That's my ability.
All the things in here are
objects that have no life.
You and I are the only living beings here.
That's because I didn't allow anyone else.
I only allowed you, and you alone, to come in.
Which means... your Stand
ability was left outside!
This is my Mirror Man!
Purple Smoke has appeared
outside the mirror.
Then there should be some way to fight!
Mirror Man
Illuso
Pannacotta Fugo was born
into a wealthy family
that owned a huge home
in the suburbs of Naples.
On top of being born into a life of luxury,
he was born with high intellect,
having an IQ of 152.
It appeared as though he
lived the perfect life.
But the weight of the expectations
that his parents and others
put on Fugo were slowly
crushing his young heart.
At times, Fugo would experience fits of
rage that even he didn't understand,
but he would do everything he
could to control them and get by.
Then, when he entered university
just after turning thirteen,
that rage went out of control
in the worst possible way.
Fugo.
Professor.
What are you doing here so late?
I'm working on the assignment due next week.
I couldn't find the right judicial precedent...
Oh, come on.
I told you that if there's anything you didn't
understand, you could come to me anytime.
No, I shouldn't keep bothering you...
My job is to teach and lead young people
like you in the right direction.
How about it?
Why don't you come by my house
again for dinner, and...
Please excuse me.
Now, wait just a moment.
I wouldn't mind telling you what's
going to be on the next test...
It'll be fine. Just relax, now.
Stop... Stop...
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop!
I'll be gentle.
I told you to stop, damn it!
I looked up to you!
You piece of shit!
Did you hear?
Apparently Fugo's really close
with one of the professors.
Are you sure he wasn't
the one to lead him on?
That's probably how he got
into this school, too.
Fugo's parents used their money
to ensure he was found not guilty,
but they then treated him
like filth and disowned him.
All alone, Fugo started shoplifting
and picking pockets to survive.
Ironically, this lifestyle actually let him
use his intellect to its full potential.
You little bastard!
How dare you try to dine and dash?!
I'm gonna make sure they throw you in jail!
No, that won't be possible.
Are you familiar with the De Sica
vs. Argento case from 1982?
Going by that judicial precedent,
there's a very good chance that the court
will see this as me acting out of necessity.
Mr. Bucciarati!
Please say something to this brat!
Well, that sounds interesting.
That was right around the time Bucciarati
was thinking about creating his own team.
That basically sums up my life story.
Please don't pity me.
I don't think of myself as unfortunate.
I see. But, well...
I think our meeting is fate.
Would you like to join my
team, Pannacotta Fugo?
I want your intellect and knowledge.
Mr. Bucciarati, was it?
Joining a gang doesn't sound so bad,
but I've already made up my mind.
I'm going to live on my own,
not bothering with anyone else.
Oh? And why is that?
I told you.
When I lose my temper,
I do horrifying things.
If I were to join your team,
I might even end up killing you.
In that case, let's see if
that'll actually happen.
Come with me, Fugo.
I'll bring out the best in you,
including that fierce,
impulsive rage of yours.
Those words moved Fugo's heart.
After that, Fugo underwent Polpo's
test and gained Purple Smoke.
So this is Fugo's Stand...
Fugo's not here, but his Stand
appeared for some reason.
Since that thing appeared, Fugo must
be okay for the time being, but...
Damn it! Where the hell is Fugo?
How's he protecting himself?
Get back, Giorno!
Get back even further!
Fugo rarely lets this guy out.
He only does when he's in serious trouble.
Which means that Fugo's
trying to fight somewhere!
Get further back, Giorno!
He seems to be more worried about
that Stand than about where Fugo is.
He acts like he feels threatened.
What the? It just started
attacking out of nowhere!
This isn't good. We really shouldn't stay here.
We're getting out of here! Come on!
I don't know what you're talking about!
There's something in that mirror!
We need to find where Fugo is!
That's far more important right no—
Stop talking back to me, you little shit!
I don't care what happens to you,
but I'm trying to be nice and warn you,
since you don't know what's going on!
It punched it! Run, Giorno!
I see.
So you activated your Stand
outside the mirror.
But... that doesn't mean a thing!
It doesn't matter what your Stand
tries to do with its ability.
It will never be able to hit me.
But I can hit you as many times
as I like and finish you off!
A crow?
Why did a crow fall?
A crow just suddenly...
Stay back.
When Purple Smoke uses its
fists, no one can stay nearby.
What the hell is with these corpses?
It's a killer virus.
That's Fugo's Stand, Purple Smoke's ability.
A virus?
Look at its hand.
When it hits something with its
fist, that capsule breaks open,
and the virus comes spilling out!
The virus disperses into the
air and enters your body
through inhalation or skin contact.
It then multiplies rapidly.
It infects its host within thirty
seconds, then kills them instantly.
And once the virus spreads, it doesn't
matter who's nearby, be they friend or foe.
Just like those crows, all of your
metabolic functions will shut down,
and you'll die as you
rot from the inside out.
That includes your Stand, too.
What's its range?
Five meters.
Right now, Fugo should be
controlling his Stand
somewhere within five
meters of his opponent.
That's definitely important,
but what's the range on the virus?
How close do you have to be
to be infected by the virus?
At this distance, we should be safe.
The virus that comes from that capsule dies
within a few dozen seconds of exposure
to an average indoor level of light.
So those crow corpses will soon
be disinfected by the sunlight.
Savage!
It attacks like an explosion,
and then disappears like a storm.
It's a Stand that personifies
Fugo's violent nature.
What's it doing?
I think it's trying to wipe off the
drool that dripped on its leg.
It always looks pissed off,
but it's apparently
really high-strung, and really
cares about being clean.
I guess you could say that's
the Stand's idiosyncrasy.
It doesn't look like the Stand
itself is very intelligent...
It's just a reflection of his violent side.
That would also mean Fugo's
isn't able to see Purple Smoke.
He's not controlling it properly at all.
If he was, he wouldn't let it do that.
This corpse...
This crow...
Is it sick?
Was it infected by some virus or bacteria?
I knew it... Fugo's unable to control it.
It just attacked some random spot again.
Wait, is it actually random?
There must be something in that mirror!
Now the mirror got attacked
from the outside...
But it's no use, Fugo.
That's just a normal mirror,
the kind you can find anywhere.
No matter what your Stand
is doing out there...
No matter what ability it may use...
Not even viruses can enter
Mirror Man's world!
Abbacchio, Giorno, please get my message...
Please make sure you don't
get dragged into the mirror!
We need to hurry, Giorno!
Hey, Giorno!
Don't just stand there! Let's go!
Let me ask you this... Where are we going?
To get the key?
You're willing to abandon Fugo,
who's in danger right now?
Watch your mouth, you bastard.
Listen up. Our mission is to get the key
and safely get that girl to the boss!
I want to save Fugo as much as you do,
but getting that key is paramount right now!
Even if I was the one currently
being attacked instead of Fugo,
I would want you guys to abandon me.
I beg your pardon...
but I don't believe that's true!
Fugo is indeed in danger,
but he hasn't lost!
We should risk our lives and save him!
And making any movements when
we don't know the enemy's ability
is dangerous to us, as well.
No! All three of us being taken out
is the worst possible outcome!
I'll say it again! We're moving on! Come on!
And I humbly decline!
We're going to solve this mystery,
save Fugo, and defeat the enemy!
That's the best way to ensure we're all safe!
I have seniority here, so in this
situation, what I say goes!
Are you still going to decline?
You'd better be prepared!
That is, if you manage to survive!
I'll ask you one more time, Fugo.
What are you looking for here?
I have no intention of telling you.
I see.
Very well. There are still two others.
I just need the last one
standing to tell me.
You're finished. Take this!
Episodio 13
Mirror Man and Purple Smoke