It's hard to imagine
that another assassin
from the organization is
in Venice right now.
It should be wide open.
Let's head toward the airport!
We'll get a plane!
We're going to get a plane and head
to Sardinia, no matter what.
We must find out about the boss's
past as quickly as possible...
or we lose.
Marco Polo International Airport
I don't feel any life energy.
There are no living creatures on
this plane, not even a cockroach.
All right, let's take this plane.
Don't let any living creature
or machine near this airplane.
After taking off, an airplane glides at
a few thousand to ten thousand meters
at a speed of around 800 kilometers per hour.
Once in the air, there's no
Stand user who can control
that kind of speed or power from the ground.
Our destination is Sardinia.
The flight should be around two hours.
Episodio 24 Notorious Chase
You're gonna fly this thing
with Moody Jazz's replay?
B-But there's no guarantee that
this thing flew to Sardinia.
I'm pretty sure there's this
thing called INS that lets you
put in a destination, and it'll
get you there automatically.
I saw it in a movie once.
If I find the INS and input our destination,
there shouldn't be an issue.
Really? You're going by what was in a movie?
Abbacchio, how long until takeoff?
No idea. I can't exactly fast forward this.
It'll probably take around ten minutes.
Bucciarati's leg... Was it injured
in the restaurant battle?
Still, despite how deep that
cut looks, he's barely bleeding.
Up front, to the left! Something's coming!
Something's heading our way, Mista!
Stop right there!
Just so you know,
anyone who gets near this plane will
be shot dead, even if they're a saint!
And it's not like a saint would even come here.
If you care about your well-being at all,
you'll turn your back to this plane
and get the hell off this runway!
Apparently your ears are plugged up
with wax, but do your best to listen.
I'll warn you one last time.
I'll let you go, so get
the hell off this runway.
He's a Stand user!
Six Bullets!
Giorno! Narancia! Be careful of the enemy!
His signal disappeared.
He's the only enemy in the area.
No one else is trying
to get near this plane.
Giorno! As you can see, he died instantly.
There's no need to check up on him.
Yes, I know, but we need to be cautious.
He went down surprisingly easily.
It's like he showed up only to be defeated.
Hey, are you mocking me and my Bullets?
It just means that he was no match for me!
He's obviously way weaker!
Yeah! Yeah!
He's completely dead.
Not only is he not breathing, but his
heartbeat and life energy are gone, too.
Mista! Giorno! We're taking off!
Hurry up and get on!
Come on, Giorno. Let's go.
I wonder if my father...
No, your boss
might have guessed that I'd go to
Sardinia to find out about the past.
Former.
Our former boss.
I'm sure the thought crossed his mind.
That's why we need to find out about
the boss's past as soon as possible.
I figure that when he met
your mother in Sardinia,
he wasn't a gangster who
needed to hide his identity yet.
He was just an ordinary young man.
He became a gangster after that.
He must have some kind of identity.
The true identity of the boss from
fifteen years ago surely exists.
As his daughter, you should
be able to track it down.
Something, anything...
Do you remember anything more detailed
from your mother's stories of the past?
Cala di Volpe.
Cala di Volpe... The fox's tail?
It's a resort located in a beautiful,
emerald green coastal area.
My mother mentioned that she met
my father there while on vacation.
She also mentioned that my
father grew up in Sardinia.
Apparently, he spoke with
a Sardinian dialect.
But then he disappeared, and my mother
never found out more than that...
Not even his name.
I'm not even sure what I should look for.
Besides, this is all just from
my mother's reminiscing.
You're the boss's only living relative.
That's why he's trying to eliminate you.
Cala di Volpe...
That means we have our destination.
Mista.
Get your gun out and take aim.
Listen to this sound...
Sound? You mean the sound of the engine?
What are you talking about?
Just please, get your gun out.
There's something weird about this cabinet.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
The only one being weird is you.
You're the one who said there wasn't
so much as a cockroach on this plane.
That's true... I don't feel
any life energy, even now.
But...
But what?
Are you trying to say there's a
remote-controlled Stand on the plane?
You sure you're not just freaking out?
I could very well just be freaking out.
But I know I heard something.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm going to open this.
Please have your gun ready.
A freezer...
I-I apologize. I was getting
a little too high-strung.
Giorno, what the hell kind of joke is this?
When did you put that in there?
You're trying to scare
me with chicken scraps?
What the hell's so funny about that?
Th-That's not chicken.
It's still wet. Th-The blood's still fresh.
Aren't these the fingers of the fatty
I blasted back at the airport?
Giorno, am I wrong?
Calm down, Mista.
Hey... Is there another one now?
You two. Is something wrong?
Giorno, you confirmed that there weren't
any signs of life on this plane.
But Mista is saying that it looked like
those fingers increased from three to four.
Is there any life energy in those fingers?
They are just bones. They have no life.
If these bones had any signs
of life or were a Stand,
plant life from Golden Wind's
powers wouldn't grow from them.
It freaked me out because it
looked like there was one more,
so I could've just been seeing things...
But there's still something
really off about this!
Indeed.
I'm not sure how or why, but someone
put these in here on purpose.
Let's throw these outside.
Huh?! But opening the door is super dangerous!
Apparently, the difference in air pressure
would send us flying like some rat in a toilet!
Everyone, hang on to something.
Zipper Man!
Pop
Guess you didn't need to hang on after all.
Anything else out of the ordinary?
Check every inch of this plane.
I want some pizza, too.
I want to go back to Naples and
enjoy a simple Margherita...
This jet looks like a train station bathroom.
But it must be some rich guy's jet...
What the hell is this?
The enemy Stand's name is...
Notorious Chase.
Who wrote all this, and when?
Who the hell wrote this?!
What?!
Th-These fingers...
I-It can't be! We threw
the finger bones outside!
We didn't even touch them!
Is this what made that graffiti?
A corpse?
B-But this can't be...
The Stand ability of someone who's dead?
Is this thing getting bigger
by consuming my body?
Golden Wind!
Cut off my right arm!
What?!
It's consuming my arm in the same shape.
My Stand... is being consumed!
The one who was scribbling
on the wall was me...
The one who brought the fingers
onto the plane... was me!
What's going on, Giorno?
H-Hey...
Golden Wind!
You should probably make a
new right arm fast, Giorno.
Was he trying to jump onto Golden
Wind's right arm just now?
What's going on, Giorno?
This is unthinkable!
We've never dealt with a
Stand like this before.
It goes against all we know.
A Stand... Does that mean the
user is hiding somewhere?
The user isn't here.
He's already dead. He died on the runway.
That man came here specifically to die...
so that his Stand could
automatically trace us.
Its energy is still alive.
It appears to be a Stand that only
activates when its user has died.
There's no user, so it can keep
up with this jet's speed.
But it's super slow, Giorno.
Actually, it's not moving at all. Did it die?
It's not moving?
No, Narancia...
It's eating, so it doesn't
have to move right now.
I got too close. This thing is fast.
My bullets...
It got four of them just now...
That's more than half.
Number Two! Three! Six! Seven!
This thing's seriously bad news!
Don't get too close.
Everyone, stay back.
Mista!
Shit! Don't get close to it!
For some reason, it changed
its target to Narancia.
It's using some criteria
to decide who to attack.
How dare you underestimate me?!
I just need to stay away from it, right?
But...
My L'il Bomber can blow this thing
apart without getting close at all!
That movement...
It's definitely tracking something.
I-Impossible! It's fast! It's way too fast!
This isn't good! At this rate,
it's going to attack all of us!
N-Narancia!
Trish! Hide inside the closet!
What?!
Why is it going after Trish?!
Hurry up and shut the door!
I-I won't make it in time!
Trish!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
I figured out...
what it's tracking.
It's movement!
This Stand reacts to movement and
prioritizes attacking whatever moves!
It matches the speed of the
fastest target and prioritizes it.
If we can get this thing off the
plane along with my left arm,
we'll get to Sardinia safely.
Then everything will go as planned.
Giorno, wait!
Who's going to heal your wounds
if you lose both your arms?
Swap with me! Get that Stand onto me!
We won't make it in time, Bucciarati!
It's climbing up higher!
D-Don't!
Giorno!
How can this be?
We haven't even gotten to Sardinia yet,
Mista!
and both Mista and Narancia are...
How can this be?
If we weren't in an enclosed space like this,
they might not have been so badly injured.
My idea to board a plane was naïve...
No one could've predicted this.
And it's because we're on a plane
that we were able to blow that Stand away.
Regardless, we have to tend to their wounds.
They're all gravely injured.
Let's get them inside the turtle.
Hang on a second.
Tend to their wounds... Their wounds...
Giorno's arms...
They can be healed, right?
With Golden Wind's powers...
Golden Wind and Zipper Man's powers activate
once their fists hit or touch something.
This is the most damage
we've endured so far.
Giorno Giovanna is no longer able to fight.
That probably goes for Mista
and Narancia, as well.
Giorno can't recreate the
arms that he's lost!
Trish, you should get some rest.
I'm going to go tell Abbacchio.
I'm...
heading to Sardinia for myself.
Just for my own safety...
And...
For my future, I want to
find the key to my father.
But Giorno and the others are different.
They're making decisions based on
what they think is right,
not for their future or safety.
I...
can't even begin to understand that.
Was that... a ball?
A ball was rolling around?
I-Impossible!
It didn't get blown away
by the plane's speed?
No, it's the opposite...
Giorno...
It's movement!
This Stand reacts to movement and
prioritizes attacking whatever moves!
In that case, the plane is
moving through the sky...
The faster something is,
the more it prioritizes catching it!
It attacked the knife just
now because I dropped it...
I want to run into the
closet and shut the door.
Slowly...
I have to move slowly...
I have to escape without any sudden movement.
I-It's so sensitive!
Why did it change direction?
It must've reacted to something.
That's... Giorno's brooch?
Could that brooch be...
alive?
Golden Wind... No, Giorno's arms...
H-His left hand?
C-Could it be forming his left hand?
Before Giorno cut off his arm, he used
Golden Wind to give the ladybug life
and created the hand he lost.
Giorno's not out of the game yet!
If I can protect that left hand,
Narancia and Mista's wounds can also be healed!
B-But how am I going to do that?!
Episodio 25
Spicy Lady