Deadly Queen... is what I've named it.
I'm going to eliminate you now,
so I can sleep soundly again tonight.
I warned you not to move!
Don't underestimate Harvest!
There are this many?
Not only that, but crushing three
or four did no damage, either.
If you move any more,
I'll cut that something-or-other
artery in your neck!
Oh, yeah! It's the one called the "carotid"!
I'm gonna cut it! My Harvest is invincible!
And it looks like your Stand
is the type that has power,
but can't go very far.
Looks like its range is about
one to two meters, right?
If you want to die, go ahead and try to move.
I see... So individual users have
their own unique powers?
Stand? Hmm... Stand, eh?
By the way, my Deadly Queen
also has a special power...
He has something... Grab it!
What? It's just a 100-yen coin.
What were you planning to do with this?
Well, I thought I'd show you my
Deadly Queen's special power,
seeing as how you're already
as good as done for.
Deadly Queen's special power
is that it can turn anything
it touches into a bomb.
Anything...
Even a 100-yen coin.
Throw away that 100-yen coin, Harvest!
Now I can relax and sleep well tonight.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 22     Yoshikage Kira Just Wants to Live Quietly, Part 2
Did you know there's a salon
that'll grant you love?
Huh? Seriously? That's hilarious.
It's true! I hear it worked for
someone in the high school!
Looks like one blast didn't kill him...
Wh-What happened to me? What...
What the...
What the heck happened?!
I told you.
My Deadly Queen can turn
anything it touches into a bomb.
I turned this 100-yen coin into a bomb.
I can push the switch whenever I want,
and my opponent is blown
to bits from the inside out.
Though in your case, Shigechi,
half of your face blew into your head,
and about a third of your brain got
mixed in with the flesh of your face.
Before I deal one more blow
to you, I just remembered
there's something that I
want to confirm with you.
You called this power a "Stand."
That Josuke and Okuyasu also
have Stand powers, don't they?
H-Help me...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You must die.
I can't leave witnesses alive.
No one is allowed to know the true
identity of one Yoshikage Kira.
But you see, I'd like to
know about Stand users.
I'm sure I'd be able to find out
with some research, but I'd
like to ask you personally.
Josuke, Okuyasu...
Who are the others?
How many more are in this town?
What are their powers?
I-I don't know...
I'm certain you must know.
Listen, if you don't tell me...
I will eliminate your parents, too.
Wha...
What?
M-My mama and papa?
Hurry up and tell me.
If you do, nothing will happen to them.
If you take too long,
someone might show up here.
Just names will do. Come on, hurry it up.
E-Everyone was saying they were
looking for a murderer in this town!
A murderer... They meant you!
You killed Reimi Sugimoto, too!
What? Reimi Sugimoto?!
You're still able to use your Stand?
Deadly Queen!
That brat...
He was so torn-up, too.
I-I'm... gonna go to Josuke...
Josuke's Shining Diamond...
can fix me...
I'm... going to protect Mama and Papa...
I'm gonna protect Mama and Papa from him!
That nasty, filthy guy
can't live in the same town as Mama and Papa!
High School Ahead
No middle school students beyond this point
—Middle School Principal
I have to go...
to Josuke...
Oh, sorry.
Are you okay?
I have to go...
You don't look so good.
He's from the middle school.
Th-There's something wrong with him.
We should get a teacher...
No, just leave him alone. He's creepy.
Let's go.
J-Josuke!
You said everyone was looking for me?
Do you mean there's someone in this town
who knows about Reimi Sugimoto's murder?
But no one will be able to pursue me...
No one knows the identity of Yoshikage Kira.
As long as you are out of the picture...
I'm gonna protect my Mama and Papa...
Deadly Queen has already
touched the doorknob.
Josuke!
This is Deadly Queen's power.
He's been eliminated without a trace.
Did someone call my name just now?
Yeah, I heard it, too.
H-Hey, Josuke, look!
I... found... you!
Sh-Shigechi?!
Shigechi!
S-Something's not right, Josuke!
Harvest was gushing blood
when it disappeared.
That's not a normal way
for a Stand to disappear!
Why did just one of them
show up in front of us?
Let's go to the middle school.
We have to find Shigechi!
Oh, dear. Where did that fall off?
Well, I guess I can't help it now.
I hope my usual tailor
has the same button...
How horrible...
It happened again. It's him again...
Another soul killed by him is flying away...
He must have encountered him.
Shigechi...
There's no doubt about it.
This boy is dead.
Shigekiyo encountered him,
and was killed by him.
I can tell.
Though I don't know why he encountered him,
or how he was killed.
But it was definitely him.
I can tell it was him because he killed me.
I looked for Shigechi everywhere,
but couldn't find him.
He disappeared within just five minutes
after Okuyasu and I separated from him.
Shigechi's books and school
supplies were all left behind,
and his parents have
requested a police search.
That probably means...
Y-You're saying... The culprit is a Stand user?
You guys probably don't
know much about Shigechi,
but I can't imagine there's anyone
who can beat Shigechi's Harvest.
This guy killed Shigechi within five minutes,
and managed to hide his body
somewhere within the school.
Jotaro, now that it's clear
we're dealing with a Stand user,
we'll have to help out, as well.
Josuke.
I heard you picked up a button.
Yeah... One of the Harvests brought it to me.
This is it.
This is Shigechi's final message.
It could be that Harvest ripped it off of
the murderer's clothes and brought it to you.
Let me hold on to this button.
I'll do some research.
Y-You can locate the guy with the kind
of button you could find anywhere?
It's possible.
We might be able to figure out the brand
of the clothes and where it came from.
I see...
I-If we're done talking, I'm gonna go home.
I-I'm kind of in a weird mood.
I-I'm really annoyed...
Let's go home, Dad.
There's something wrong with Okuyasu.
Yeah... Shigechi was a greedy,
irritating little punk,
but he was the type you
just couldn't leave alone.
We can't believe he's gone.
Not to mention, he must feel
annoyed because he can't tell
if he should be angry or sad right now.
We both feel that way.
I'm sure Okuyasu feels it far more.
Damn it...
It appears something awful has
happened outside my notice.
I'm going to warn all the customers
who come to my restaurant.
Phew... I don't think he'll come
to my place, but just in case...
Stand users eventually attract
other Stand users...
Though I never want to meet that guy.
So now everyone's going to take action, huh?
Oh?
That was Josuke just now...
And Okuyasu was there, too.
Hey, listen to this.
Last Friday was my birthday, right?
The guy I'm seeing gave me this
super lame ring as a present.
Look at it! Why would I want this thing?
Though I still put on an act like,
"Oh, my gosh! I'm so happy!"
I was dating him because
his dad owns some land,
but he's a total bumpkin.
This really is a kiddie ring. How much was it?
Probably around 150,000 yen.
I'm gonna go pawn it off for some money.
It doesn't compliment my
beautiful fingers at all.
That woman's heart is ugly,
but her hands and face are beautiful...
If she comes to me, she can
date me with a cleansed soul.
Oh, I have to go. See you later.
Okay, bye-bye!
I'm afraid we'll have to part ways now.
Let's keep this farewell clean.
Shigekiyo Yangu: Deceased
Stand: Harvest
De
Dead
Deadly
Deadly Qu
Deadly Que
Deadly Quee
Deadly Queen
Yoshi
Yoshikage
Yoshikage Ki
Yoshikage Kira
Good morning. This is Morioh Radio,
brought to you again today
by your neighbor, Kai Harada.
How is the beginning of the
new week treating you so far?
Already, there are only three days left in June.
Now, let's eat.
And once it's July...
That's right, it's vacation season.
Oh, yes.
I've got several errands to run today,
What plans do you all have?
so I'd like you to stay home.
I can't wait.
And now, the perfect song for this sunny day
Let's eat dinner together when I get back.
in the middle of the rainy season. Here you go.
Thank goodness they still
had the Parisian special.
Talk about lucky!
Let's hurry up and go to Yohee Lake.
Wait, Asuka's not here yet.
What? What's taking her so long?
It's been four days since Shigechi's incident...
Nothing has really happened since, but...
There's no doubt that there's a
killer somewhere in this town.
Honestly, anyone can look suspicious,
yet anyone can also look
completely innocent.
Ah... H-Hello, Jotaro.
Um, did you find anything out since last time?
Like, about the murderer's button, or...
No, not really.
There's nothing yet.
I-I see...
Um, where are you going?
Nowhere, really.
Just over there.
Ah...
Oh, man... He doesn't really talk, so it's
hard to have a conversation with him.
Rohan-sensei is scary because he's so
overbearing, but Jotaro's silence is scary, too.
Isn't there something
we can talk about? Um...
That's a very lovely coat!
Centipede Shoes
This store appears to be a shoe store.
Huh? Oh! Yes, it's a shoe store.
Is there something wrong?
We also do simple tailoring
It's a shoe store, but they also do things
on the side, like fixing waist measurements
on skirts and hemming pants.
There's also an electronics
shop that sells flowers.
Is there something wrong?
I heard about all of the
tailors around Morioh,
but I didn't think to ask about places like this.
Something wrong with this button?
No, if you haven't seen it
before, don't worry about it.
I just couldn't remember what
it was originally attached to.
Little boy, would you
like an animal cracker?
Animal Crackers
I always eat the camel last,
so you can have any of the others.
No, thank you.
Oh, okay.
But not only have I seen that button before,
but look, I just finished repairing
the suit it came off of.
A customer came in yesterday,
asking me to put on the exact same button.
See? It's the exact same button.
Jotaro!
Good grief. We found it, Koichi.
Found it?
Oh, n-nothing...
M-More importantly, what did
the customer look like?
Do you know his name?
His name?
Well, of course I do. What do you take me for?
I remember all of my customers' names.
That's how you're supposed
to treat customers,
even if you have hundreds or thousands!
Really?
Yes! That's amazing!
Could you tell us his name?
Anyway, the jacket has an order tag on it.
Of course I remember it...
Even out of hundreds.
But I figure it might be faster to look.
Let's see...
Kira
The last name is... How do you read this?
I think it's...
Wh-What is it? M-May I see it?
Um... Um...
Look over here.
Wh-What the?! My hand!
J-Jotaro! L-Look!
Watch out, Koichi! Don't go any closer!
Hey, I told you to look over here.
Is that his Stand?!
J-Jotaro!
H-He's here! He's taking the jacket!
To think someone would actually investigate
the button that fell off my jacket...
Did they see my name?
Why do things like this keep
happening to me lately?
Good grief.
Who would've thought he'd
come to get his suit now?
But I will make them disappear
with Deadly Queen's second bomb.
Just like that brat Shigechi...
It's still moving!
The jacket is evidence!
Wait!
Don't run after it without thinking.
The way that jacket is being
pulled is suspicious.
Something about that Stand...
is dangerous!
Episode 23
Heart Attack, Part 1