What are you looking for here?
I have no intention of telling you.
I see.
Very well. There are still two others.
I just need the last one
standing to tell me.
You're finished. Take this!
Footsteps... Someone outside
the mirror is running.
Does that mean your friends decided to
abandon you so that they
could go get something?!
They're heading toward the dog mosaic.
That settles it.
Fugo, you're basically done for already.
I'm going to go get whatever
that thing is first!
W-Wait, you bastard!
Abbacchio... Giorno...
Where is it? Where is this key?
There it is. That must be it.
A mirror?
Has that always been there?
What is that? A key?
What?
I see.
I guess I just have to
take that key from you.
That's... It couldn't be...
Now that you've seen me,
you're finished, too!
Episodio 13  Mirror Man and Purple Smoke
Sh-Shit!
Damn it...
I'm starting to understand
the enemy's ability.
So he's inside the mirror...
Assuming that's even possible.
Fugo must've been dragged into
the mirror and disappeared,
separating him from his Stand.
Regardless, right now,
I need to grab that key!
Shattering the mirror actually
worked in my favor, Abbacchio.
Anything reflected becomes
an entrance to this world.
Now that it's in shards, I have even
more entrances to grab you from!
And I'll give you, and only you,
permission to come into the mirror!
There! I've brought you in.
I'll be taking that key, too!
Wh-What?!
O-Only a Stand can grab the
neck of another Stand!
There's no way you could grab Mirror Man's neck
when I'm the one who dragged you in here!
Shattering the mirror didn't
actually work in your favor!
It just means the space you can look
outside from became smaller!
You couldn't see who you
dragged in here, could you?
You gave permission...
for just me to enter?!
Th-That's...
Grazie! I'll happily get dragged in!
Moody Jazz!
Shit! That's a Stand!
Inside the mirror...
So it's a world where everything's reversed.
Of course we couldn't know.
There's no way we'd comprehend this
ability until we were actually attacked.
Fugo must be in here, too.
So, how do we get out of here?
If I have to kill you to get
out of here, that's fine.
That's why I sent Moody Jazz in there!
The ability to transform into others...
Well, shit. You got me.
Looks like your Stand
itself isn't that strong.
So, what? Can it only
defeat powerless humans?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Get on your feet and come at me!
Listen up... Like I said at the start,
you're already done for.
I must say, I was a little surprised
when it was your Stand that came in,
but that doesn't change a thing!
The reason I'm not standing is
so that I can crouch down.
I'm crouching because I need to!
Well, yeah.
You're bent over to make it easier to kick you.
I was crouching so I could pick
up this shard of the mirror!
Hey, why are you so surprised?
Is it because I have this arm?
I'm sure you're very familiar with this arm!
I told you! Anything that
reflects becomes an entrance!
If I can get your reflection
with a different shard,
that becomes another entrance!
Do you get it now?
It's your arm that I dragged in here!
To make sure you can't move about,
I'll only allow half of your body to come in.
As for your Stand,
I permit half of it to get out!
Now your Stand won't be able to move!
The key's mine!
Damn it. He's going to take the key.
That doesn't just mean
we failed the mission.
It also means that Giorno
will end up being correct!
And I humbly decline!
We're going to solve this mystery,
save Fugo, and defeat the enemy!
That's the best way to
ensure we're all safe!
Damn it... My pride's not
going to stand for that!
I'm not letting him have that key!
I swear on my pride and my dignity
that I, Leone Abbacchio,
will protect this key!
It's true. Because Mirror Man uses
all its energy to drag someone in,
it doesn't have much destructive power.
That is indeed one of its traits!
But if I do this to you, we don't exactly
need strength to kill you off instantly!
If we just stab this in with the strength
of a four-year-old child, it's pretty easy.
I win! Thanks for telling
me where the key i—
Something wrong? Go on, finish me off!
What the hell are you doing, Abbacchio?!
How dare you hide it from me?!
Even if you can move with your
current body, it won't be much!
I'll be able to tell immediately! Get it?!
Hide?
What are you talking about?
What exactly did I hide, and where?
What the hell are you doing, you bastard?
Let me see that hand!
Seriously, what the hell are
you doing, you bastard?!
Did you lose something?
Did you find what you
were looking for? Well?
Why did he do that to his own hand?
Wait... If he chopped off his own hand,
his Stand's hand outside the mirror is...
It can't be...
Its hand is gone!
Don't tell me...
I-It has the key!
And it's going back!
If I remember correctly, a newbie named
Giorno is just around the corner!
He chopped off that hand
to give him the key?!
You should've sliced open my
throat when you had the chance.
If you had, my Stand's hand
would've stopped moving.
Whoops, so close. But you're a bit too late.
That was the sound of the key
falling to the ground.
The key is going to get picked up!
That's some bullshit you pulled off!
But I'm not letting that
brat named Giorno get away!
I'll drag him in here, too!
Do you understand now, Giorno, you shithead?!
All that matters is that
one of us returns safely.
If you return safely with the key...
The most important thing
is to fulfill the mission.
Hey, Abbacchio.
Can you even imagine what's
going on over here?
You sure have a loyal companion.
After you worked so hard
to deliver the key...
What do you think's going on over here?
Not a damn thing!
That brat's not running away at all!
It looks like he doesn't
have a clue what's going on.
Giorno! Get the hell out of here!
Take the key and run!
He won't hear you when you're
screaming inside this mirror!
Sh-Shit...
Now then, there are two
possible actions I could take.
First is disposing of Giorno
after I get the key.
Second is slitting Giorno's throat first,
then safely retrieving the key.
Let's see...
I guess I'll slit Giorno's throat first!
He's noticed me.
I'll allow only Giorno to enter!
I've dragged him in!
Slice open his throat, Mirror Man!
Wh-Wh-What?!
H-He's... That's impossible!
It's the virus! G-Giorno...
He's been infected by Fugo's Purple Smoke!
You're not getting the key!
And Fugo, Abbacchio, and I...
will safely return to the others!
Pannacotta Fugo
Purple Smoke
Giorno Giovanna... That brat
doesn't understand anything!
You're going to die if you infect
yourself with Purple Smoke's virus!
My heart died along with him back then.
I don't feel anything anymore.
I don't feel a damn thing,
even though I've lost my hand...
The only time I can feel at ease
is when I'm following the orders
of something great and absolute.
Because then, all I need to do is be a
soldier who doesn't have to think for himself.
Meaning...
Getting the key and protecting
the boss's daughter...
Carrying out this mission is
the most important thing.
And yet Giorno... That stupid brat...
He chose to put himself in danger to
save Fugo and me, rather than
taking the key back safely!
Damn you, you stupid brat!
How dare you come in here infected?!
Are you out of your damn mind?!
Now I'm infected, damn it!
Ah, yes. You seem to be experiencing
the same symptoms as me.
Apparently Purple Smoke's virus infects
your whole body within thirty seconds.
It's over now.
It was over as soon as you dragged me in.
Shards of the mirror that
Purple Smoke shattered...
Did Giorno put them back together?
When the enemy chased after Abbacchio,
he took some shards with him.
Giorno must've realized that!
He then figured out the
enemy's ability from that,
then infected himself with the virus and
allowed himself to be
dragged into the mirror!
Because there's no other
way to defeat this enemy!
Damn it! Of all the underhanded...
But don't underestimate me.
It's not too late yet.
I need more resolve,
but it's not too late yet!
Mirror Man! Allow only me
to leave this mirror!
But don't allow the virus!
The part of me that's infected
is not allowed to leave!
That's not good!
If he gets outside, the virus
will be separated from him!
Abbacchio lopped off his
own hand to get the key.
So, I, Illuso, c-can do the same thing!
This is nothing!
Giorno! Grab him!
He got away...
Giorno... After you...
risked your own life to come in here...
So... he stepped outside the mirror.
Th-That was really close, but, ha!
My resolve... My resolve wins in the end!
This is nothing!
I figured he'd go outside.
That's for the best, though.
He's going down, no matter what.
Now that he's stepped outside,
there's a chance I might survive!
Fugo! Now that he's outside,
Purple Smoke can follow him!
Finish him off!
I can't, Giorno.
I can't tell where he is from inside here.
I have no way to attack him!
I know where he is.
Golden Wind, who's outside,
turned that brick into a snake.
That's why it's moving.
Snakes can tell where humans are
by sensing their body temperature.
Got him!
What?!
A-After I built up the resolve to chop
off my own arm and came out here...
This... This can't...
S-Stop it! Stop! Damn it!
I'm going to be infected!
I-If that virus capsule bursts...
I-It looks like luck hasn't
completely abandoned me!
If Mirror Man can stop this thing's
punch even for a moment...
If I can just block it once...
Let him have it, Purple Smoke!
Mirror Man! Use everything you have left!
I...
I did it...
I stopped it!
Now I just need to take this arm...
into the mirror!
Huh?
What?!
B-But I blocked its punch...
After I built up the resolve...
to leave the mirror!
W-We did it! We're outside the mirror!
We defeated him, so his ability disappeared!
B-But Giorno, Purple Smoke's virus has
already spread throughout your body.
Once you've been infected,
even I can't do anything about it.
Yes, Fugo, and this is how it should be.
This...
Him leaving the mirror
worked out for the best.
Once I was infected and he
dragged me into the mirror,
his defeat was inevitable.
But I was glad when he refused to
admit defeat and left the mirror.
Since the mirror world
was undone before I died,
I was able to encounter this snake.
Th-That snake...
It's alive, even though it's
surrounded by Purple Smoke's virus!
I created this snake from the brick where
Purple Smoke's capsule was broken.
Since it was born from a place that was
covered with the virus, it won't get sick.
Do you know what that means?
That snake has immunity!
And if we take blood or cells
from something with immunity...
We can create a serum that'll
stop the virus from spreading!
Golden Wind!
Extract the serum from this
snake and inject it into me!
Giorno Giovanna...
I thought he was some newbie
that I just couldn't figure out,
but he comes up with the most insane
ideas and pulls them off...
And there's something
I can trust behind that.
It's not something that's spoken.
He has true loyalty within him!
Just like Bucciarati did back then!
Giorno! You have my utmost
respect after risking your life!
No, Fugo...
I'm not the one who risked my life here.
I just made a prediction
and followed through.
The one who truly risked his
life here... was Abbacchio.
His hand is in grave condition right now.
He's the one who risked his
life to protect the key...
And if he hadn't carried
the key all the way here,
we couldn't have defeated the enemy.
Please don't worry about me...
and go tend to his wounds...
Giorno!
Are you okay, Giorno?!
Damn it, Giorno...
I was going...
to beat the shit out of you...
But with my hand like this, I guess I can't.
I'll just have to do it later...
Thus, they got the key
they were ordered to retrieve!
Special Program
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure Golden Wind