I knew he was crazy, but not this crazy!
Straizo! What will it be?
Smashing your brain, sunlight or Hamon?
Those are the three ways to erase you.
H-He's a murderer!
Help! He'll kill us all!
JoJo, w-what have you done?!
Yeah, the repair bill
will go through the roof.
That's not it! You shot a man!
A man?
You mean Straizo?
What's going on?
The bullets I fired have
strange dents in them.
Smokey, run outside!
I hope what I shot was only a man.
If he was, time in jail
is the worst that'll happen to me.
I-I don't understand.
Calm yourselves!
I can't hear anything!
Get out now or I'll French kiss you!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 11: Master of the Game
What in the world?
So this is a vampire!
Dio's failure was overindulgence
in playing with his powers.
He wanted to experiment
with their limits.
That made an opening
for Jonathan to strike.
But my philosophy is different.
I'll find the extent of my powers
after I've destroyed you.
I'll show you no mercy!
And I'll start with the technique
that Dio used to kill Jonathan!
Out of ammo?
My eyes can fire high-pressure essence.
Face my Space Ripper
Stingy Eyes, Joseph!
JoJo!
A mere trifle.
All that is left is Erina Joestar.
And--
Now you'll say, "It will be easier than
drowning an infant."
Your next words will be, "How can
he live with a hole in his head?!"
H-How can he live
with a hole in his head?!
Too much time in a backwater
like Tibet isn't good for you.
Life in the city makes you strong.
You could've won if you were
a bit more observant.
Take a good look
at the face of that clock!
I was told my grandpa was taken down
by Dio firing something from his eyes.
A mirror?!
So you finally noticed, Straiz-oaf!
I also heard that you're as allergic
to Hamon as you are to sunlight!
I'll knock you out of the park!
Shoot!
Let's see, now. I hear
Hamon melts vampire faces.
Now we find out.
H-He's fine!
It's like nothing happened!
Was Granny wrong?
No, you would grow into a deadly foe
if left unchecked for too long.
A secret before you die.
There is an insect in Southeast Asia
called the Satiporoja beetle.
30,000 of their tiny stomachs were
dried and woven into this scarf.
It conducts Hamon far better than
the human body, dispersing it.
It's like an electrical ground.
I am the successor of 4,000 years
of history in the art of Hamon.
I know all its strengths
and weaknesses in battle.
I am not ignorant like Dio!
Wow, that's really something!
But do you think I'd rely on
gimcracks like Hamon alone?
I'm also fast!
He put a grenade in my scarf! How?!
A pitiful trick!
You should've spent time in the city!
Take a look at the grenade you
knocked away!
You son of a...!
I-I got him!
W-What the heck is he?!
Smokey, don't look!
Too late!
God, I won't do anything bad again!
I won't steal or anything else!
Just save me!
H-He's a monster.
D-Do you have a way to
beat a monster like this, JoJo?
Yeah, I do.
Really? You do?
Yeah, I have one last card up my sleeve.
One last card? W-What is it?
I saved this one for last.
Look at his legs.
They were blown to smithereens
and haven't healed yet.
That's our ticket.
A-And your last card?
I'll use my own legs.
Use your legs? How?
To hotfoot it out of here, Smokey!
Outta the way!
I can't believe this guy!
Follow me, Straizo!
Wait up, JoJo!
Even if I am immortal, it will take a
lot of energy to regenerate after that.
All right! What a scoop!
The papers will eat this up!
Here's my chance to become a reporter!
Pressure applied
by fingertips: 235 kg/cm2
Leaping ability:
Currently 4 m 22 cm
I-Is something behind me?
We should be safe now, right?
I'm afraid not, Smokey. Listen.
Listen to what?
Oh, the river?
Wrong! Look up!
H-Help!
He came after us! Run for it!
This woman is my hostage!
If you run, I'll kill her!
If you come up here, I'll let her go.
What are you thinking?
I don't even know that woman, moron!
Let's run, JoJo!
This is a test!
If you flee now, I'll know
what sort of man you are.
I need time to heal and
will not pursue you.
You would not seek revenge
for Speedwagon.
But if you come up here after the girl,
your personality will be clear to me.
You would pose a great threat
to me in the future.
I would have to eliminate you
here and now!
In five seconds, I will kill her!
Climb up or run! Decide now!
I wouldn't fight for a hag like that,
even if she was my sweetheart!
I'll kill her by pulling down
on her lower jaw.
I'll tear right through her neck
and into her chest.
Would a master of Tibetan Hamon really do
such a cruel thing to a girl?
A-A tooth! He ripped out her tooth!
That bastard! He really did it!
I'll show no mercy!
You fiend!
Straizo!
You'll pay for that!
You're inhuman to the core!
You pretend to be cool,
but you're full of fire inside.
I'll demolish you, Straizo!
Taste this!
I can beat that move now!
I won't fall for the same
tired old stunt twice!
Hamon!
Im--
"Impossible," you say?
Impossible!
I deflected your shot
with Hamon glass!
I knew you'd aim for my forehead.
It was easy to intercept.
Apologize to Speedwagon in hell!
You'll sleep soundly tonight, Granny.
Why save me from falling?
I might still have enough power
to blow your arm off.
Shut up and do it, then!
I'll just punch you with the other!
I want an answer.
Why did you throw
Speedwagon's body into the river?
Something is fishy.
Joseph, your grandfather Jonathan's
blood flows strongly in you.
Outside you are opposites,
but you're both insatiably curious.
And now I warn you that your nature has
trapped you in a fate you can't escape.
What do you mean?
Soon you'll learn of the Pillar Man.
Soon you'll meet the Pillar Man!
Don't feed me any of your nonsense!
I threw the bodies into the river
because of him.
The pillar sucked blood
from the bodies in the cave.
It was like a plant
drawing up nutrients.
It was ghastly.
So I dragged the bodies outside.
But I am sure he will awaken soon
from his 2,000-year slumber.
Joseph, you will meet him soon.
Soon you'll learn the truth of him
and meaning of evolution.
Your destiny is already written!
Hamon?!
That means you're creating Hamon
inside your own body!
I regret nothing.
I want to go to hell feeling full
and young rather than withering away.
Being young again was
a supreme joy for me!
Straizo, wait! I need to know more!
Farewell, JoJo!
JoJo...
1938, the year that the Second World War
began to engulf the planet.
The German army sought to conquer all.
Their weapons were cutting-edge.
They used astrology, sorcery,
alchemy and psychic powers.
Every tool available was employed
in their bid for world domination!
Their spy network in Mexico
Mexico
caught wind of Straizo's actions.
I-I'm terribly sorry,
Major von Stroheim!
M-My hand slipped!
Lick.
You cut me, right?
Now lick my wound clean.
Yes, sir.
Don't make it hurt. Gently, now.
Slowly, slowly.
Ahh, I think the pain
is just about gone now.
Watch out, now! Watch out!
You'll cut yourself!
Pardon me, Major von Stroheim!
The old man found on the bank
of the Rio Dada is awake.
We will question him!
Are you all right? What's your name?
Let me escort you home.
What was that for?!
How dare you call me a hag earlier?!
That punch was payback, jerk!
Did I...?
You did. Something about
not fighting for a hag.
Seriously?
Well, that's odd! But you're so pretty.
How strange!
Yowch!
You can't even remember your own words?!
You ogress...
She was too scared
to feel the pain earlier.
But I'm worried about
the Pillar Man Straizo mentioned.
Let's go to Mexico!
How are you feeling, Speedwagon?
We have a saying in Europe.
"A town where the old kill themselves
is soon to fall."
I think you hold a secret
as dangerous as that.
And it's about that man!
We obtained the pillar from the location
we extracted from you!
God, why do this to me?!
Why not let me die?!
Why did you let me live?!
You're mistaken, Speedwagon.
I am the one who made you live.
And the Wehrmacht made you talk!
Though you are old, we know that torture
would not make you talk.
You went alone and penniless into Texas.
Near dead in the desert, you found oil fields
and changed the world economy.
See?! German medicine
is the world's greatest!
It can do anything!
A truth serum?!
What more do you want from me?!
Everything! Tell us everything!
Tell us about the past!
About Straizo! About Joestar!
Tell us so we can awaken the Pillar Man!
N-No! You don't understand a thing!
He could destroy the world!
Prepare for the blood feeding experiment.
I expect perfection!
- Help us!
- I don't want to die!
I have a proposal.
Choose one from among yourselves.
We need blood for an experiment.
The lot of you must choose
who will be the one to die.
The rest of you will be released today.
I volunteer.
If I volunteer,
you'll let everyone go, right?
Excellent, young man.
Courage like yours is to be commended.
We allow only the fit to live.
Execute everyone except the boy!
Let the experiment begin!
Next episode
Don't be too proud! He's dangerous!
I've brought you some tequila.
You. Who among you disturbed my slumber?
He's in the ventilation ducts!
Chapter 12: The Pillar Man