What unbelievable luck!
If that coffee hadn't spilled this morning...
How... How is that possible? I...
You brat...
To think that you knew
about Stray Cat, as well!
I guess it's futile.
So long as I don't undo Bites the Dust,
it'll keep automatically protecting you.
I... I failed!
I-It's almost time!
The fact that you tried to kill me
using Stray Cat's air bullets...
Hayato, you wouldn't have
come up with that idea
if you hadn't repeated this morning
three, no, four times.
And the fact that you've
returned for the fourth time...
It means that Bites the Dust's fate
is to blow up not only Rohan,
but another one of his friends, as well.
That means you must have told
people other than Rohan about me.
No... Perhaps you were just asked about me.
Who did you kill?
Hm? Was there a shrimp named Koichi?
What about Jotaro Kujo?
I'd be very happy if he were to die.
E-Everything's over...
Letting you return to this
morning again is dangerous.
Because I'll be attacked again.
Once the others die, I'll undo
Bites the Dust for a short while.
Bites the Dust is invincible!
Luck is on the side of Yoshikage Kira!
That name... The name you said just now...
Oh, did I just say my real name?
Yes, my name is Yoshikage Kira.
I don't care if you tell that to anyone.
By the way, what time is it?
I...
I didn't tell anyone.
I never said a single word to anyone
about you in the first place.
I only made a phone call.
He said that he overslept and was late,
so I found his number and woke him up.
I made a call from the house
this morning. That's all!
You're the one who said it.
You're the one who said it yourself!
I was just waiting.
I was just waiting for him to hurry up
and get here without oversleeping!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 37   Shining D (Diamond) is Unbreakable, Part 1
Hey, Josuke.
We're gonna be on time
to meet up with everyone.
Hold it, Okuyasu!
I'm not sure if it's coincidence or fate,
but this guy just said a name
that I can't believe I heard.
I-I-Impossible!
You said "Yoshikage Kira"
just now, didn't you?
Huh? What?!
H-How could such a coincidence...
It's no coincidence!
It's not fate, either! This was a gamble!
I made a gamble!
And he came!
I know I heard you say it!
You definitely just said that name!
It can't be...
You bastard!
If you just coincidentally
have the same name as him,
I can fix your wounds at any time.
H-He's Yoshikage Kira?
Th-That's impossible... You brat!
H-How could this be?
I need to undo Bites the
Dust and protect myself!
Return, Deadly Queen!
Cold... The rain is going down my back.
Honestly, does no one show up on time?
Oh?
That's Koichi and Jotaro.
Yes! I made it in time! I won against fate!
I don't need any intense joy.
But I didn't want any
deep despair, either....
My goal was to live a
peaceful life, like a plant.
You've shown yourself!
Now I'll make sure your face
doesn't look so peaceful.
I guess this picture that Rohan
took was an instant jackpot.
Looks like it wasn't coincidence
that we ran into him, Okuyasu.
I don't know the details,
but since he gave his real
name to Hayato Kawajiri,
we may have gotten here
just in the nick of time.
Just so you know, I wasn't
running away from you.
If I wanted to kill you all,
I could have done so at any time.
The reason I didn't was just
because I don't like fighting.
Strife is the exact opposite
of the peaceful life that
I aim for, so I hate it.
It's easy to win one battle,
but then you accumulate
stress for your next battle.
It's a foolish thing to do.
Fighting with others is a
sad and endless process.
We were coming after you because
you killed Shigechi, you dumbass!
A pig bastard like you whose
hobby is to kill people
doesn't have the right to talk about
what he wants to do, you dipshit!
Be careful, Josuke!
Don't touch that shitbag Deadly Queen's hand.
That's the only reason I
didn't dispose of you all.
You're the only three destroying
my peace right now.
I have no choice but to fight the
ones who find out my identity.
Hey, get behind us, Hayato Kawajiri.
Shining Diamond's range is 1-2 meters,
and it has the ability to fix
anything that's been destroyed.
I won't need to use that ability against you!
I'm just gonna kick your ass!
Josuke!
Dora.
He's strong...
Yes! I can't see it, b-but that's amazing!
Kira just spit blood and went flying!
You're moving way too slow, Deadly Queen!
I guess yearning for a peaceful life
has left you lacking in motivation.
Looks like your Stand isn't cut
out for one-on-one battles.
Josuke, don't let your guard
down just because he's slow!
If it's best to fight him
without touching him,
it'd be better to use my Stand, The Hand.
Bring it!
Scraping away space to teleport, eh?
I attacked Josuke, but now the
direction of my attack has turned...
Toward you.
I-Inside my backpack...
What?!
Though I guess it worked out.
It still hit right on the dot,
despite being the first time I've used it.
I-I wasn't touched... I-I wasn't even touched...
The air... The air breathed fire!
Okuyasu!
Th-The air... breathed fire?
The air...
The reason I kept that
thing around was for this.
I can use Stray Cat's ability to control
the air for Deadly Queen's explosions.
Hayato, You brought it for me!
Invisible air and an unstoppable explosion!
Could any two things in this world
be more compatible than that?
He was keeping it just for this purpose...
And I'm the one who brought it here!
I said that it appears luck is on my side, didn't I?
In Japanese, "fate" is written with
characters meaning "luck that brings life."
How fitting.
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Oku
Okuyasu
Okuyasu Niji
Okuyasu Nijimura
Is something wrong, Jotaro?
No, it's nothing.
I just thought the rain
sounded like Josuke's voice.
I'm sure he overslept.
If he doesn't show up in
the next five minutes,
I'm going to head to Hayato
Kawajiri's school without them.
I'll fix you right now, Okuyasu!
That's not going to happen.
Because I'm going to blow you away first.
It launched air like a bullet!
And he turned that air into a bomb!
It's coming! You've got to run away!
You can't see it?
It's that area that looks distorted!
I-It's going to hit!
Fix?
He's trying to use that
ability to fix Okuyasu...
The ability to fix things...
To think it's so fast that you were able
to create a wall from the broken slate.
I-It's shooting again!
I-It's coming!
Presumptions are more
terrifying than anything else.
Especially when you're
under the impression that
your strengths or abilities are impressive.
I-It's starting to come through!
Even though it came in contact
with it, it didn't explode!
Hmph. I thought it might blow his head off,
but it appears that the
explosion was a bit shallow.
Deadly Queen's explosions aren't
limited only to things it touches.
That would be a presumption.
It can explode at any given distance.
No matter where you might hide,
or how fast you might try to guard
yourself with a wall or metal plate,
it can go right through and explode freely!
You cannot run anymore.
Die!
It's no use! There's no way to dodge it!
I can't run?
I have no intention of running away...
And I haven't from the beginning.
Then I wouldn't be able to fix Okuyasu!
He's heading toward it?!
I-It went through!
You can make it explode at any distance?
Looks like there's an exception to that.
If I happen to explode when
I'm close to you, Kira,
you're not going to be safe, are you?!
All right, Okuyasu. Now I can fix you.
Don't touch him!
I think... he might have just
used Okuyasu's body and...
Damn that Hayato...
Impossible...
I didn't see Deadly Queen touch Okuyasu.
How can you tell, Hayato Kawajiri?!
You're not a Stand user!
I can tell!
I've lived in the same house
as him until this morning!
I can tell by his expressions!
It touched him without us noticing!
There's no doubt!
Okuyasu's body's been turned into a bomb!
Yoshikage Kira!
I'm not sure...
Since you were charging toward me,
I'm not sure if I was actually
able to touch Okuyasu or not.
It all happened so fast.
Should I just try pushing the button?
D-Don't, Yoshikage Kira!
Hurry up and shoot the next air bullet!
Shoot it at me, damn it!
There's really no need to rush
into attacking you right now.
Josuke Higashikata, I lose nothing
by deciding whether to attack or not
based on your movements.
There's a chance that Okuyasu
wasn't turned into a bomb.
You might be able to fix
him with Shining Diamond.
This might be too forward of me,
but there's only one way to save
Okuyasu's life in this situation...
And that's for you to touch him and fix him.
Even if I turned him into a bomb,
if you touch him using Shining Diamond,
you might die from the
explosion, but Okuyasu won't.
If you were to sacrifice yourself,
you'd at least be able to fix your
best friend's wounds, wouldn't you?
D-Don't touch him!
I'll wait until you make your decision.
You can decide whether you're going
to touch your best friend and fix him,
or come after me.
I'll wait as long as it takes
for you to make your decision,
but I guess there's no way you'll touch him,
even if he is your precious best friend...
I have proof that you shouldn't touch him!
I'm sure he can't control
more than one bomb at a time!
Once he's used his explosive ability,
he can't create the next bomb
until the first one has gone off.
As proof, he could be
shooting off tons of bombs,
but he's only shot off one at a time!
He changed Okuyasu into a bomb,
so he can't shoot now!
What are you trying to say?
I'm telling you that there's
a way to save Okuyasu-san!
And for that...
Deadly Queen, switch on the bomb.
I just need to touch him!
What?!
H-Hayato, you...
All right! Shining Diamond!
You're insane, Hayato Kawajiri...
You've got some guts.
Are you really a grade-schooler, kid?
If I wasn't expecting you to use your
ability to f-fix things, I couldn't do it.
Besides, you can't die.
If you die, he can easily kill me,
and then he'll be free.
He'll eventually kill my mom, too...
and other people in this town again!
No, you'll die.
To think that your ability to fix things
is so powerful that it can fix what
I've blown up instantaneously...
I've just been reminded that it's the most
troublesome ability to have against me.
Deadly Queen!
Josuke, he's firing!
I'll detonate it upon impact so
you can't put your guard up.
However, since there's a chance you'll
dodge it if it detonates on impact,
I shot a small one so it'd be hard to see.
I wonder if you can dodge it while
holding Okuyasu, and with debris from
the explosion stuck in your wounds...
Hurry up and run, Josuke!
If the explosion so much as grazes
you next time, it'll be fatal!
Okuyasu! I fixed your wounds.
Wake up, Okuyasu!
Hurry and move! He's going to get you!
Eight meters until impact.
Come on, you can wake up now!
You're totally fine now, Okuyasu!
Josuke!
Just seven more meters.
Just open your eyes, Okuyasu! Hey!
Hey, Okuyasu! Hurry up
and open your damn eyes!
Hey! Let's work together like
we always do and kick his ass!
Josuke...
I'm going to place that bomb
right under his nose,
as precise as one of
Joe Montana's touchdown passes,
and then detonate it from there.
Four meters until impact.
L-Let go! If you don't run,
you'll be hit head-on!
Okuyasu is... Okuyasu is already...
Shut up!
You need to hurry up and
run away yourself, kid!
Two more meters until impact.
The explosion will cover
approximately a three-meter radius.
I see it! It's about two
meters in front of you!
Hurry up and run away!
Okuyasu... Okuyasu is already dead!
He's not dead!
Okuyasu is fixed!
He's going to open his eyes!
I'll get it one meter closer
and then push the button.
Josuke!
Splash
Th-The air bullet was split
by a knife of blood!
Did the blood flowing through Josuke
just fly out with immense
power and cut it like a knife?
That's it! Just like when I stabbed it with
the needle from the compass in the attic,
the air from the cat weed shrank!
He used the blood from his wound
like a water pressure cutter
to cut through it...
But I wonder about the air bullet.
It didn't shrink! It's heading toward you!
An air bullet that's become a bomb is
kept stable by Deadly Queen's abilities.
That's why it won't shrivel!
No matter if you try to crush it
or cut it into pieces,
the bomb ability won't go away!
It'll detonate as soon as you touch it.
All right, impact.
Huh? H-His body...
is floating?
Detonate!
No, it's not floating...
I can't fix my own wounds with
Shining Diamond's abilities,
but if it's debris from the road
that got into my wound
in the first explosion...
I can fix that!
Th-The piece of the road that was
in his wound pulled his body!
I don't have a choice.
It's someone else's house,
but we're going to run in here, Hayato.
P-Please leave Okuyasu behind.
If you're holding Okuyasu,
you'll be killed!
He'll catch up and he'll get you!
Would you just shut up, Hayato?
Okuyasu and I get along
great. He's my friend!
That's not what I'm talking about!
When you fixed Okuyasu's
wounds, he was already dea—
Stop!
Don't. Don't you dare say any more.
Think about defeating him!
I don't like it...
If he didn't have that
ability to fix things,
my bombs would be invincible.
The most terrifying thing getting in the
way of my peace of mind isn't Jotaro.
It's him!
Josuke Higashikata!
Episode 38
Shining D (Diamond) is Unbreakable, Part 2