O-Ow! Hey, right here...
Hey, Fugo... Could you
take a look right here?
Oh, dear. You've definitely got one.
It's pretty big.
Ow! That hurts!
Quit it! Don't touch it!
God damn it, you bastard!
You're gonna pay for
that, you piece of shit!
I've got a bump on my head because of you!
I hope you're prepared!
Take this! And this!
Seriously! Who do you think you are?!
You bastard!
Hey, something fell off him.
Let's see...
Mario Zucchero. His home address is in Rome.
So he's a gangster from Rome.
So is that thing on your face garbage?
Or is it a piece of seaweed?
It looks like it could be seaweed, but it
also looks like it could be a piece of plastic.
It'd break my heart if
it's actually garbage,
because it'd mean that this
beautiful ocean is polluted.
Mind if I take a closer look at it?
Hey.
I asked you if you'd mind if
I took a closer look at that.
Answer me when I ask you
a question, would you?
Capri.
When the ancient Greeks colonized
various lands in the Mediterranean Sea,
they looked for places with the
most beautiful scenery in the world.
One of those locations happened to be Capri.
Its blue sea, its sparkling sky...
But in sharp contrast,
it also had a shoreline
made up of white precipices,
making it look like a fortress.
During the age of the Roman Empire,
there was an emperor who made
this island his vacation home and
didn't return to Rome for ten years.
Bruno Bucciarati and his crew
are about to land on this island
in order to claim Polpo's secret
fortune of ten billion lire.
Episodio 07 Six Bullets Appears, Part 1
Bucciarati, let's start to
make a course toward land.
I've been looking for a while now,
but there isn't a single boat following us.
No one should know that this
boat is heading to Capri.
Yeah, there are no boats, but...
The problem is whoever that guy
heard about the secret fortune from.
I have a hard time believing
he followed us on his own.
You seem very interested in these,
but they're not mine.
They were inside the boat.
Which would you prefer me to use?
The glasses or the fishing line?
We need some answers from you.
If we don't get some, we'll be in danger.
You have a partner,
don't you, Mr. Zucchero?
And they're also a Stand user, aren't they?
That's why I'll be using these.
You don't even want to bother telling
me which one you'd like me to use?
If you won't pick one...
I'll just have to use both!
Well? Do you feel like talking now?
Ma-ri-o Zuc-che-ro. Heaven, Hell,
or the 9th Circle of Hell...
Heaven, Hell, or...
The 9th Circle of Hell!
He's headed for the 9th Circle of Hell,
according to this name divination!
If you're not going to tell us the name of
your partner who's coming after
us and their Stand ability...
You should probably start worrying
about your other eye, Mr. Zucchero!
Quit playing around, you dumbasses.
Damn it, come here and look at this.
He was using the radio on the boat.
Sounds like you found something
with Moody Jazz's replay.
Let's have a look.
This whole boat was flat,
but we'll be able to see him
in 3-D now that it's back to normal.
Giorno!
I have no intention of showing you my Stand!
Turn around.
I'll do you a favor and let
you hear its voice, at least.
When I was watching the replay of him,
he started using the boat's radio.
He's contacting someone.
I've already made four of them my hostages.
All that's left is Bucciarati and one other.
I'll have this taken care of in no time.
They were heading...
to Capri!
They haven't mentioned where
the money's hidden, though.
Hey, what do we do about this?
He told them where we're heading!
After I get rid of his five friends,
I'm gonna make Bucciarati cough it up. Over.
Was that yacht named Lagoon?
What's your current location?
We're about two hours out from Capri.
Bucciarati is wary of anyone following him,
so he's taking a very roundabout route.
Got it.
I'll take a high-speed boat
and wait for you at Capri.
Dock at Marina Grande. Over and out.
That's the end of the conversation.
The radio cut off.
How could this be?
This isn't good. With a high-speed vessel,
they can get from Naples
to Capri in thirty minutes!
That means they're definitely
already on the island!
Who is it? Who the hell was on the radio?
I'm going to make this guy tell
us who it is, no matter what!
No, he's a hardcore gangster.
It'll probably take some time
to get anything out of him.
He probably won't say anything today.
Besides, he might not know what
his partner's Stand looks like.
It's very possible his partner's
kept it secret even from him.
Then what are we supposed to do?
What if we just come ashore like this?
If they find out we're the ones on
this boat instead of Zucchero...
Also, if this boat doesn't arrive at
Marina Grande in about an hour...
They guy on the radio is sure to think
something happened to Zucchero.
If that happens, who knows if
we'll be able to get the money?
In fact...
I have my doubts we'd make it
back to Naples in one piece!
What are we going to do, Bucciarati?
There's no time to hesitate.
We should at least outfox the guy.
I'll somehow get to the island first and—
Before this boat docks,
all we need is someone to head to the
island first and get rid of the guy.
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you sure you're not stupid?
Get to the island before this boat?
What are we supposed to do? Swim there?
Yes.
Huh?!
I can change this ring buoy into a fish.
If I have it pull me, I'll be able to get
to the island faster than this boat.
Of course, since it's my Stand,
I'll be the one going.
I, Giorno Giovanna, have a dream.
I want that ten billion lire.
We have to use that money
to make Bucciarati a capo
and move our way up the ranks.
Giorno...
You're going to go? All right, fine.
You've got some good ideas, boy.
But sadly, you don't know this
guy's name or what he looks like.
Capri is filled with tourists.
How the hell are you going to find him?
I agree with Giorno's plan.
Even if we don't know who this guy is...
If he's waiting for Zucchero
to arrive in this boat,
I think there's a high possibility
that we can attack first
rather than wait for him to attack.
So how many people can
that fish pull, Giorno?
My Stand, Six Bullets, is made for killing.
It's perfect for situations like this.
I'll be going, too.
Six Bullets
Guido Mista
It took us quite a while to swim
from the yacht to the island.
We have 20 minutes before the time
Zucchero was supposed to meet
up with the man on Capri.
That's about all the time we have left.
Giorno, how does the marina look?
Not good.
Just as Abbacchio said,
there are a lot of tourists.
And they all look like they're
waiting for someone.
They're probably just waiting
for sightseeing vessels, but...
Mista, you have a plan to find the
guy among that crowd of tourists
in the next 20 minutes, right?
What... are you doing?
It's way past lunchtime.
I'd prefer to go to that
restaurant over there,
but it's probably a bad idea
to have lunch at a restaurant
right in front of the marina.
I don't know what this guy looks like,
but he probably knows what I look
like since I'm on Bucciarati's team.
That goes for you, too.
I have no idea what you're talking about,
but listen, Mista.
I know we said about 20 minutes,
but if he's the panicky type,
we might only have about ten.
Maybe even five.
He may get suspicious when the
Lagoon doesn't come into port
and figure out that something
happened to Zucchero.
If that happens, we won't
have a chance to find him.
We have to make our move imme—
And I told you, this is my lunchtime!
Lunchtime is for lunch!
Even boutiques and bookstores in
this country honor lunchtime.
No one works if they don't have their lunch.
I'm not saying I'm like that,
but these little guys pretty much expect it.
Lunchtime!
Give us food!
Here you go, guys. Lunch is served.
Tuscan salami is delicious!
Delicious!
This is the best!
Hey, gimme that!
Hey, come on now, Number 3!
Stop making Number 5 cry!
Stop fighting. There's enough for all of you.
They all believe that they do the most work,
so they have the right to
eat more than the others.
I work so hard not to play favorites.
Number 5! Quit crying already!
What are they?
How many of those things do you have?
Hey, don't call them "things."
They get pissed off when
they're treated like pets.
There are six of them,
and there isn't a Number 4
because four is bad luck.
There's one for each bullet.
For each bullet?
This guy here keeps rushing us.
Could you guys take your nap
after your work is done?
Hell no!
Hey, Number 3!
I keep telling you not to hit the others!
Mista!
I'll convince these guys to work.
So, Giorno...
You get the radio out of that plastic bag.
There'll be a feast after we do this job!
Let's do this, you guys!
Listen up. I'm going to sneak up
to the security watchhouse
and hide in its shadows
so that no one sees me.
Is there anyone waiting for
a yacht named Lagoon?
We've received a transmission from
a Mr. Zucchero on the Lagoon!
Please come to the boat watchhouse!
Is there anyone waiting for
a yacht named Lagoon?
We've received a transmission from
a Mr. Zucchero on the Lagoon!
He might decide to be cautious
and not answer the radio call...
Please come to the boat watchhouse!
Or he might get excited and run
out, thinking the hiding place
of the ten billion lire has been found.
This is a gamble,
Is there anyone waiting for the Lagoon?
but the one who comes
to the boat watchhouse
to answer that radio call is our guy.
We've received a transmission
from a Mr. Zucchero!
Giorno, if anyone comes near the
watchhouse, give me a signal.
If you're waiting for the Lagoon,
please come to the boat watchhouse!
I'm gonna shoot the guy
who takes the radio call!
But Bucciarati told me to not kill
him, so I'll miss any vital points.
Or at least, I'll try.
No one's making a move yet...
No one's heading over there.
Is there no one?
No one's waiting for the Lagoon?
There's a transmission from Mr. Zucchero!
No, there's no one. Nothing.
He's supposed to be
somewhere on this island.
Is he just being too cautious
to answer the radio call?
Did something happen, Zucchero?
Why did you request an announcement?
Is there a problem? Over.
What's going on?
No one's heading toward the watchhouse.
He's there! How?!
This isn't good. Does that
watchhouse have a back entrance?
He's already inside the watchhouse!
It's too dark to see his face.
Mista hasn't realized he's in there!
At this rate, the guy's going to
realize this is a trap and run!
I have to let Mista know!
What? The guy's coming to
answer the radio call?
Which one is it?
Who's heading toward the watchhouse?
N-No!
He's not heading there!
He's already inside!
Don't come out!
He's by the window!
That guy is...
one of Bucciarati's guys!
Didn't Zucchero take care
of him on the yacht?
Mista! Behind you!
He's on the radio! Mista!
Damn it! He can't hear me.
It's better than him not noticing!
He's already there!
Mista! He's already on the radio!
Come on! Pass, pass, pass!
Go, Six Bullets!
Menacing
Here we go!
Shoot!
Bazoo
Yay!
Heck yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
D-Did he get him?
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Wh-What was that noise?
Gunshots.
Did it bother you?
It probably wasn't as loud as in the movies.
But if it did bother you...
I'm sorta busy right now,
so I'll listen to your complaints later.
Guess Giorno just can't wait.
So there was a rear entrance...
Meaning he came through this
door and got on the radio.
Either he was being cautious
or he's just used to always
going through the back door.
Still...
Good job, Bullets!
Yay!
Leg!
Leg! Hey, hey!
We got his right leg!
We shot him right through his right leg!
Yeah, you sure did.
Now he won't get away!
There are a bunch of people outside...
And this side is basically a cliff.
There's no way he could climb up.
He must be scurrying about right now.
If he were to hide somewhere...
He must be in that truck.
If he's a Stand user, his Stand is probably
close-range and extremely powerful.
If he was a remote-control type,
he would've attacked me by now.
In that case, the guy who
just got shot in the leg
is probably hiding behind the truck,
trying to lure me as close to him
as possible so that he can attack.
Well, it's not like he's going to
get me, even if I get close to him.
He's probably just beyond there.
But so long as we don't
know what his Stand is,
going over there alone
isn't a safe plan at all.
I should wait for Giorno and—
Well, I guess that option's out.
The guy's in the driver's seat.
He must've jump-started the engine.
It'll be bad news if this
truck gets away right now.
Damn it! This isn't good!
I haven't seen his face yet!
Giorno probably hasn't, either!
I don't know what his Stand is
yet, but I don't have a choice!
This is for the ten billion and Bucciarati!
Eat lead!
Mista!
Episodio 08
Six Bullets Appears, Part 2