Look over here.
J-Jotaro! L-Look!
Watch out, Koichi! Don't go any closer!
Hey, I told you to look over here.
Is that his Stand?!
J-Jotaro!
H-He's here! He's taking the jacket!
Good grief.
Who would've thought he'd
come to get his suit now?
The jacket is evidence!
Wait!
Don't run after it without thinking.
Something about that Stand...
is dangerous!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 23    Heart Attack, Part 1
Centipede Shoes
It's a bomb... It's a bomb Stand!
So this is how it got Shigechi?
That's why we couldn't find him,
no matter where we looked.
He's... He's getting away!
Don't go after him, Koichi.
Huh? Don't go after him?
What are you saying?
If we go after him,
we'll get to see the face of the person
who killed Reimi and Shigechi!
We need to cautiously
observe and act, Koichi.
Wh-What are you talking about?
We just happened to miss the
name tag on that jacket.
But considering how big the jacket was,
we can tell that the guy's
about 175 centimeters tall.
He's an office employee, and not married.
If he had a wife,
he wouldn't have brought his
jacket here for a button repair.
He's between the ages of 25 and 35,
and he looks pretty rich.
Judging from the material and design,
that jacket was a high-end brand.
Even if we don't follow him now,
we've significantly narrowed
down who it might be.
I-I see...
W-Wait! That doesn't mean
we shouldn't go after him!
He's a murderer!
It's not that I don't want to
pursue him, but we can't.
Because that bomb Stand
is somewhere over there.
Huh?! The Stand?
Y-You saw it?
I didn't see it, but it must be there.
Slowly walk outside through the door.
It "must be"? Hang on.
How can you know it must
be there if you can't see it?
If he were the kind of guy to leave right
after getting rid of the shop owner,
then he never could've kept getting
away with killing for fifteen years.
He's someone who gets rid of all evidence.
Which means he plans to get rid of us.
Hold on a sec... Aren't you being too cautious?
If the Stand isn't here,
the murderer must be far away
with that jacket by now.
Listen up, Koichi.
Observing doesn't simply mean to look.
It means to look carefully.
Look
Carefully
It doesn't mean to just
listen, but to listen well.
Listen
Well
Otherwise,
we're going to die.
H-He's sounding high-and-mighty,
but my Reverb isn't useless.
It's matured a lot, so isn't
Jotaro underestimating me a bit?
I wonder if the bomb Stand
is really still around.
If it's not, we're gonna look really stupid!
Look over here.
I-It's really here!
I-If I keep touching it, it'll explode!
Star Platinum!
After all those hits I landed...
This thing's pretty hard.
It's going to explode!
Star Platinum! The World!
I hate doing anything that's tiring,
so I'm going to destroy you now.
Y-Yes! You must have stopped time.
Now no matter how much we
touch it, it won't explode!
I will make sure the people searching for me
die in an explosion.
My Deadly Queen's Heart Attack
always gets its prey, no matter what.
I-Impossible! It wasn't destroyed
by Star Platinum's power!
A-A Stand that's this hard... Impossible!
Stay back, Koichi.
It's still perfectly fine!
It hasn't slowed down at all!
Get back, Koichi!
Y-You've hit it so much that you're hurt,
but it hasn't sustained any damage!
Get further back, Koichi!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
What are you doing?!
It'll explode if you're touching it!
Let it go, quickly!
Look over here.
Good grief. I've never met
such a sturdy Stand.
I think my confidence is going to break first.
J-Jotaro, at this rate,
it's going to blow us up!
You need to get further away.
This time, I'm going to take it apart for sure.
I-I'd like to say something.
A Stand controlled from far away
doesn't move with that much power.
But that thing's power and explosive attacks...
The power behind those explosions wouldn't
be possible if the user wasn't nearby.
The user should be within fifteen...
no, ten meters of here!
And?
"And"?! It's ten meters!
My Reverb has a range of fifty meters!
It can find the culprit!
I told you, Koichi. Don't go after him.
You just need to think about protecting
yourself with your Reverb.
Don't do anything else.
Wh-Why?!
The culprit is no longer nearby.
This is a remotely controlled Stand.
I've had many encounters with
various Stands, so I know.
Look over here.
Its actions are too simple for it
to be controlled from nearby.
You know from experience?
That's not logical at all!
There's no way a Stand that powerful
can be controlled from far away.
The user has to be close by!
So Jotaro really is underestimating me.
I've grown, too!
I can find the culprit and defeat him, too!
Distance, ten meters.
H-He's there! That's him! He has the jacket!
But something's weird...
H-He's too far away.
He's more than fifty meters away...
And he's only getting further away.
He's outside Reverb's range!
Th-The bomb Stand is being
controlled from far away?
That's impossible!
Having that power and being
that far away is inconceivable!
Look over here!
Wh-What? It's heading toward me?!
I figured it out.
That Stand goes after things
with higher temperatures first.
That's why it's so powerful,
despite being controlled from far away.
Bring out Reverb and protect yourself!
Even if I stop time, you're too far away!
C-Crap!
Reverb is...
fifty meters away, where the culprit is!
I'm sorry!
Good grief.
Star Platinum! The World!
The reason this thing attacked
the shop owner first
was because he had a hot drink.
And it targeted Koichi because
his body temperature rose
from being so worked up.
If there's something hotter,
it should go toward that.
Time has begun to move again.
I was right.
It goes after things with the
highest temperature first.
I'm saved...
But if body temperature is
enough to make it explode,
then when it's near fire...
This power...
Huh?!
Jotaro!
H
He
Hea
Hear
Heart
Heart A
Heart Att
Heart Atta
Heart Attac
Heart Attack
Yoshi
Yoshikage
Yoshikage Ki
Yoshikage Kira
How could this happen?
This is all my fault, Jotaro!
This happened because I went after the culprit.
If he hadn't caused the fire for my
sake, it wouldn't have gotten him!
Wake up, Jotaro!
Jotaro! Jotaro!
That explosion wasn't a human!
Look over here.
It's going to deal the final blow!
It's too strong!
It's just like Jotaro said!
It'll attack something that's hotter
than body temperature first.
Look over here.
I have to take this chance to run!
I want to call Josuke.
He'll fix Jotaro!
I have to call him!
This is... the kitchen!
There's plenty of heat here!
I need to buy some time
and run out that door.
There's a phone!
W-Wait a sec! It's not a gas stove!
Why does this house have an electric stove?!
It's going to take some time to warm up!
The oven's electric, too!
Wh-What should I...
I know! There should be some hot water.
Go over there!
It's empty!
Look over here.
Wait. If I observe carefully, like Jotaro said...
This thing has a weakness!
A weakness I didn't notice earlier!
And I'm starting to get pissed off.
Why do I have to regretfully run away
in fear from a murderer, like,
"Please, God, save me"?
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
Why do I have to think that I'd rather
be looking for a public restroom while
I have diarrhea if I could only get
out of this situation safely?
Isn't something wrong?
The one who should be
running away in fear...
is you, murderer!
It always attacks based on temperature...
But that's exactly what your weakness is!
The fact that you never give up
on that is your weakness!
It's been almost three minutes.
I don't know what's going
on at that shoe store,
but there's one thing I can say with
more faith than anything in this world.
Heart Attack has no weaknesses.
It'll track down its target, no matter what.
Now, then... Since that's over with,
I have to call Josuke on the phone.
He should be home now...
Sizzle
Now that thing's lost track of us.
Keep chasing after the word "sizzle" forever...
Just like a donkey chasing after a
carrot hanging in front of its face.
That's what your weakness is.
Hello, Higashikata residence.
Josuke, this is Koichi! There's trouble!
Jotaro is hurt bad, and it's my fault.
Please hurry and get here!
What?! Don't say that so suddenly!
I don't get what you're talking about!
Just hurry up and get over here.
It finally happened!
We encountered the murderer!
I've captured his Stand here.
What did you capture?!
Say it so I can understand! Where are you?
Wh-What's happening?
Ow, hot! I turned it off, but now
it's getting hotter and hotter.
What's with this piece of crap?
How can you cook anything good with this?!
Hey! I'm asking you where you are, Koichi!
Look over here.
Crap! It's ignoring the
letters and coming this way!
Koichi, where are you?
Hurry up and tell me, you dumbass!
I'm at Centipede Shoes! Hurry!
Crap, Reverb's tail letters also...
Reverb's tail letters got destroyed!
The damage...
That explosion wasn't a human.
Look over here.
A-Again! It's coming after me again.
But I can't use the tail letters anymore.
Wh-What am I going to do?
How can I fight it?
Reverb Act 2!
What's wrong, Reverb Act 2?!
Act 2!
Where are you, Act 2?!
Why won't you come?!
Act 2 was killed in the explosion!
It's split in two!
N-No, wait...
If the explosion killed it, I'd be
dead too, because I'm the user.
N-Now I remember! It looked
like Reverb died once before, too.
A-And then...
C-Could it be...
Boooom
Reverb Act 3!
Um, is that who you are, sir?
Please give me orders.
D-Does this mean I've grown?!
You're amazing, Act 3!
Please give me orders.
Er, I don't know what your
powers are, so... F-For now...
Please protect us, Act 3!
Um, protect us, please.
You can do that, right?
Understood.
Dogyan
This air pressure!
Th-This Stand has incredible speed!
It has way more speed than Act 1 and Act 2!
Snap
Special move: Reverb Act 3 Freeze!
Kerbam Bam
Crash
H-Hey, Act 3?!
It's too strong. I can't.
You can't?!
This enemy has a seriously heavy power.
S-H-I-T.
I pushed, but I lost.
You pushed and lost? You can't be serious!
I'm telling you to protect us!
I have finished protecting us,
just like you ordered.
Look over here.
You finished?! In what way?!
You're completely useless!
We haven't grown at all!
Look over he—
Wh-What?
This is taking far too long.
Why is Heart Attack taking so long?
Wh-What's going on? My left hand just...
My left hand that released
Heart Attack just suddenly...
Sir, what's wrong? Are you all right?
Oh, it's nothing.
Allow me to pay for the cup.
I'll be leaving, so can I get my check?
Th-This is...
M-My left hand... is heavy!
S-Sir?
I-Impossible! My left hand! My left hand...
It feels like there's a 40
or 50 kilogram weight on it.
What's going on over there?
Sir, are you all right?
D-Don't mind me.
Please, allow me to give you a hand.
It's heavy!
What are you doing, sir? How could you?
It's sunken into the pavement
and having a hard time moving...
Act 3! What did you do? This power...
3 Freeze!
I've rhymed "three" and "free."
Act 3, what is this power?
Why is it moving slower? Tell me.
There's really nothing to explain about it.
It's heavy...
For whatever reason,
Heart Attack has gotten heavy.
This isn't good. I need to retrieve it.
I have to go retrieve Heart Attack myself.
Episode 24
Heart Attack, Part 2