Episodio 28: Beneath a Sky on the Verge of Falling
Which means that the only thing
Li'l Bomber can track right now...
I was winning...
I would've won...
But you had thrown the scalpels at them...
Boss...
He's down! Li'l Bomber finished him off!
All right.
I'll go find out who it was.
Hold on, Abbacchio.
We don't know how many of the boss's
men are on this beach right now.
I need you to hurry
and replay the footage of the one
who took the photo of Trish's mother
on this beach fifteen years ago.
We need to get out of here as soon
as we can, or we'll be in danger.
But there's only one of them on the cliff!
Bucciarati, I remember the
Stand from the plane.
Despite Mista turning that guy into
a corpse, we still went through hell.
I have to confirm who's up on that
cliff, or I won't be able to relax.
Narancia, is the enemy up there dead?
He's barely hanging on.
But his breathing has just about ceased.
He hasn't moved a millimeter.
All right.
Narancia and I will be the
ones to go and check.
Abbacchio.
Use your Moody Jazz to get
the replay going right away.
All right.
We can't stay here for too long.
How much time do you need?
Well, we're talking fifteen years ago.
It'll probably take eight to ten minutes.
Do it in five.
Giorno, Trish, and Mista are standing by in
the turtle, so I'll bring them out here, too.
And the moment we learn the boss's
true identity from Moody Jazz's replay,
we'll leave here.
Narancia, use Li'l Bomber to signal for
Giorno and the others to get out here.
You got it!
I finally... figured it out...
I know... your identity...
Before I die...
show me... show me your face...
I will not allow you to continue this
conversation any longer, Risotto Nero.
The last thing I wanted was for Bucciarati
and his crew to find out we were here.
You should die with pride as the leader
of the Hitman Team,
since you made it this far.
I'm sure your men who are waiting in
the afterlife will be proud of you.
You're going to die at any second.
And Bucciarati will come find
you up here at any moment.
Before that happens, give me back
all the iron you stole from my body.
If you do, I'll finish you off myself.
Wouldn't it be the worst embarrassment
of your life if you were
to die slowly and miserably
in front of Bucciarati
and his men, who took the lives of your team?
Not to mention, they already
consider you a pathetic enemy.
I... die...
What was that? I couldn't hear you.
Hurry up and give me back the iron
that was in my body, Risotto Nero.
I'm saying... that I won't die alone.
Within the chunks of flesh
that Li'l Bomber blew off...
The parts of me that scattered...
This time, I'll be the one using it...
Li'l Bomber, that is!
Die!
What the heck? Li'l Bomber is...
That bastard stuck itself to my Li'l Bomber!
Foom
Emperor Crimson.
I blew away 0.5 seconds' worth of time.
Everything that was in this world
within that span disappeared,
and all that remains is what
happened after those 0.5 seconds.
Just the results of the bullets hitting you.
Rata tat tat tat tat tat
Well done, Risotto Nero.
You died before you could lose your pride.
But that also means I'm still facing
this unfortunate predicament.
This isn't good.
I have to do something...
Are you sure, Narancia?
Yeah.
Something made its way into Li'l Bomber!
Shit!
They're coming...
I have to hide... and somehow
replenish my iron...
Stop right here.
We need to assess the situation
carefully from here.
Got it.
It's all right, Bucciarati.
His breath's completely stopped,
and his Stand has disappeared.
He's definitely dead.
Though, I shot him in the face, so it
might be hard to tell who he actually was.
That man is probably the
leader of the Hitman Team.
How can you tell?
He's here alone without a team,
which means that either
he was a very confident killer
someone sent after us,
or he had no one left on his team.
And he was just killed by whoever
this other very confident killer was
for getting in the way.
Uh, hello? Bucciarati?
It was my Li'l Bomber that
turned him into a honeycomb—
You're wrong. You were just being used.
There was someone else here.
Look at his right foot.
Li'l Bomber's attacks would
have left burn marks.
But there are no burn marks on that foot.
It was only torn off.
But... there was only one person
on Li'l Bomber's radar!
I'm still not getting any other signal!
And why would anyone
need to do that, anyway?!
Neither of them likely expected
the other to be as powerful as themselves,
so the survivor is probably very badly wounded.
Though, I don't know how they're
hiding their breathing.
Narancia, you sent out a signal for Giorno
and the others to gather, didn't you?
They should be heading to the place
the picture came from right now.
All right, let's go after them.
From now on, don't overlook even
the smallest hint of breathing,
even if it's a lizard or a mouse.
The other killer is still nearby.
He's an extremely dangerous killer
sent by the organization.
Damn it...
To think I'd have to endure this hell
back home on Sardinia,
all because of those bastards...
I know this is a rocky area, but there
are way more than I expected.
When I'm tracking the breathing of
things like frogs and field mice,
there are just too many!
And if I make the range too sensitive,
I'll even pick up the breathing of the
tourists and the exhaust from their cars.
Damn it! Should I just light
this whole place up?!
Calm down!
Frogs and field mice will try
to hide in nearby holes.
Those aren't the movements
you're looking for.
Look for the movement of someone
trying to get away from us.
Movement of someone trying
to get away from us...
I have to hurry...
Abbacchio...
I have to stop his Stand!
That must be it.
Hey, where are Narancia and Bucciarati?
I only see Abbacchio on the beach.
An enemy must've appeared.
They're probably pursuing the enemy.
And it seems that Abbacchio
hasn't started his replay yet.
Trish remembered that the photo
was taken fifteen years ago in June,
but she doesn't know the exact date.
Moody Jazz is searching with
a timer for the exact time.
When it figures that out...
It'll be able to change into the boss.
Let's go.
Hey, let's play over here.
You're the goalie today.
What? No way!
Rock-paper-scissors, then!
Well? Can you tell them apart?
I found it, Bucciarati! There's just one!
It's 80 meters to our right.
That must be it. It's not very fast,
but it's headed toward the tourists!
Narancia, don't attack just yet!
First, we have to determine
exactly who we're dealing with.
His movement stopped.
Bucciarati?
Blood?
You, there! I'm about to attack you!
If you are unable to fight anymore,
come out from behind that rock.
I promise not to take your life.
I'll wait just three seconds. Got it?
It's been three seconds!
I take it you're prepared to fight!
Zipper Man!
Rip
Hey, come on!
Where the heck are you
kicking the ball? You suck!
Oh, come on!
It's your fault for not
being able to get it!
Just shut up and go get it already!
You go get it!
It's already the 25th.
June's going to be over soon.
How long is this gonna take?
It better actually be June
fifteen years ago, damn it.
Higher! Higher, damn it!
Throw some rocks at it!
Shake the branches! Climb up there!
Hey! Pipe down, you little brats!
Go play someplace where there's more room!
Duh, we know that.
Who the heck kicked it up there?
Hey! Stop throwing rocks!
Reach out your hand a little more!
I know, damn it!
I can't reach any further!
Oh, hell. Go on, move out of the way!
What the hell is this?!
Wait.
Don't attack, Narancia!
He's just a kid! He's one of the tourists!
His mouth is sewn shut with
the laces from his sneakers!
Only a Stand user could have done this.
They must've switched places with him.
And by the look of this kid,
he seems to have lost a lot of blood.
But where did all that blood go?
What the hell?! Where's the
bastard that did this to him?!
How the hell did he disappear?!
He was super weak a second ago!
I don't know...
What in the world is going on?
Thanks!
All right!
C'mon, let's hurry!
Thanks, mister!
Thanks!
Hey, wait up!
Nothing beats coming back home.
Luck's on my side.
Let's go!
Kick it right this time!
You're the one who kicked it over there!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Leone Abbacchio
Moody Jazz
Uh... What are you doing under there, officer?
Sorry to bother you while you're eating.
I'm conducting an investigation.
I'm looking for fingerprints.
There was a robbery across
the street last night.
The victim was struck with a bottle.
It shattered, and shards went everywhere.
But all the shards weren't on the sidewalk.
Particularly the part that was being held.
We heard that the suspect
threw something away here,
so I thought I might find
something in this recycling bin.
I should be able to get some fingerprints.
That's the part I'm looking for.
You're going to look through all that?
Well, it's my job.
I see.
Yeah...
Say, uh...
Yes?
For reference... I'm just curious.
What are you going to do if
you don't find the shards?
You might not get any fingerprints.
No... Even worse, if you do find them,
and the suspect hires a crafty
lawyer and is found not guilty...
What makes you keep working so
hard despite all those problems?
Well...
I'm not just after the result.
When all you want is the result,
you start to look for shortcuts.
And if you take that shortcut,
you might lose sight of the truth.
You'll become less motivated.
I think the most important thing
is the will to find the truth.
As long as you have that,
even if the suspect gets away this time,
you'll get them eventually, right?
Because that's what you're after.
Don't you think so?
I envy you.
I used to think I wanted
to become a police officer.
Ever since I was a kid,
I wanted to become a
distinguished police officer.
At some point, I even had
that same will you have.
But I messed up.
You see, people like me
are worthless.
We never see things to the end.
We always mess up somewhere along the way.
That's not true, Abbacchio.
You're doing great.
We have the same will.
That will you had when you
first became a police officer
resides within your heart again now...
Abbacchio.
Why...
do you know my name?
Come to think of it...
I think we've met before.
Where are you going, Abbacchio?
I'm getting on that bus!
I'm starting to remember...
That's right!
I have to go!
I need to get back to my comrades!
Did you forget, Abbacchio?
You came here on that bus.
This is the last stop.
You can never return.
Y-You're...
That's right! You're...
You're the one who died
because I took that bribe...
Abbacchio, you did very well.
That's right...
So well that I can say I'm proud of you.
No way...
This can't be happening!
God damn it! You can't be serious!
Hurry up and heal him, Giorno!
I said hurry up and heal him!
Don't make me kick your face in, you bastard!
It happened in a moment...
It happened in a second at close range.
We were too late...
We were too late.
How could someone like Abbacchio
let him get that close?
Mista...
Don't let Trish out of the turtle.
The enemy will probably attack
again, to try to finish Trish off.
We have to leave here immediately.
This is my fault.
We can't gather any more
clues about the boss here.
Wh-What are you talking about, Bucciarati?
Abbacchio is gonna wake up any second!
It's just taking a bit longer than usual!
He'll wake up if we just
wait a little longer!
Right, Giorno?!
That's what happened before, right?
H-Hey!
That's enough, Narancia!
It's too dangerous here!
You need to use Li'l Bomber
to survey the area.
What are you talking about, Bucciarati?
What the hell are you talking about?!
If the enemy's gonna show up,
I'll kill him right here, right now!
If he's nearby, I'll face him head-on!
Mista! Right, Giorno?
Hey, Mista!
We have to go, Narancia.
Just as Bucciarati said!
Wh-What?
What did you just say?!
Giorno!
You're probably just not trying hard enough!
Bring him back!
Give it all you have, you bastard!
That's enough, Narancia!
Shut the hell up!
Narancia!
Abbacchio...
Are we just going to leave
him here, Bucciarati?!
Abbacchio all alone?!
I don't want to leave him behind!
This is an order, Narancia!
Abbacchio knew that this was a
possibility when he came here!
We're leaving.
Bucciarati, wait!
That's...
Bucciarati, wait. Just for a moment.
This must mean something. It has to.
He's holding something.
What is it?
It looks like a piece of rock from somewhere.
It must mean something. Golden Wind!
Go back to where you came from!
Hey, look!
Apparently, Abbacchio
had completed his replay!
This is a death mask!
A death mask from the replay!
Right before Abbacchio's
Moody Jazz disappeared...
It took the last of its Stand energy
and pressed its transformed
face into the stone pillar!
Abbacchio left us this at the very end!
This is the boss's true face!
Abbacchio, you did a great job.
And your will to get to your truth...
The ones left behind will get it.
Because that's what important.
Special Program
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure Golden Wind
destino