Something isn't right.
I've felt someone's eyes
on me since this morning.
But nobody could be out here.
I'm on a motorcycle
in the middle of the open desert.
Who could be following me unseen?
There's no way.
It has to be my imagination.
You're a sharp one.
You sensed my presence, a feat even
wild bats aren't able to accomplish.
Who the hell are you
and why are you tailing me?!
I'm not tailing you!
I'm capturing you so our army
can ask about Straizo, Joseph Joestar!
S-Straizo?!
Our army?!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 12: The Pillar Man
By your face and accent,
I'd say you're German.
What do you have to do
with Straizo and Speedwagon?!
Come on!
I'll beat some answers out of you!
You face the SS commando knife of I,
Donobang, with your bare hands?
I feel insulted.
Come then, stripling!
Here! Have your flea-ridden
magic carpet back!
A-A cactus!
Victory!
You'll need to do better than that
to challenge me, you booger!
Now, my booger, say,
"I completely agree, Herr Donobang."
I-I completely agree, Herr Donobang.
What's that? I can't hear you.
You're a very nimble fellow.
I wanted to save myself some trouble
so I'm lying down here for safety.
What? You think you're safe there?
Have you lost your mind?
Wh-What's with this cactus?
Take a real close look.
The cactus was my goal all along!
Cacti are made up of 95% water
and conduct Hamon fabulously.
Now, it's time to talk, Donobang!
Tell me everything you know.
I see.
When Speedwagon's body disappeared
I had my hopes, but...
He really was safe.
Well. That's a fine piece of news.
Granny Erina will be
pleased to hear it.
But who knows how the Germans
are treating him?
I'll rescue him.
Then I'll rush home
to see Granny Erina's smile!
D-Don't leave me!
Major von Stroheim,
the pillar is cracking!
It now holds the blood
of five prisoners.
The subject's capabilities are unknown.
Feeding it too much may be dangerous.
How was the blood extracted?
No! Don't answer that! I can imagine.
Speedwagon.
Why so scared?
Aren't you overreacting a bit?
Don't be too proud! He's dangerous!
Listen to me.
That room is a bunker.
Its iron walls are 50 cm thick!
It is equipped with flamethrowers,
machine guns and time bombs.
What child fears a grizzly
in a cage at the zoo?
None at all!
I believe he's nothing more than a
cheap caveman who's lived too long!
Something's spraying out!
It's blood!
The blood it absorbed
is pouring out!
We can't see a thing!
Use the sprinkler system!
His outer layer is taking on
a flesh-like color and luster!
He's alive! He looks human!
He needs a name.
"The Pillar Man" is awkward to use.
I, Stroheim, will be his godfather!
Let me think.
I'll name him after the
Mexican sirocco! Santviento!
He's standing!
Stand up for us!
Show us what you are made of, Santviento!
Look at that! Our Santviento
is quite the comedian, isn't he?!
The ultimate organism?!
What's ultimate?!
Behold, Speedwagon!
He's sniffing around like
a man barely out of the trees!
Do you think he has much brains?
This is a farce!
Whatever. Let's say he made the masks.
You, begin the experiment.
Open the door to the next chamber.
Yes, sir!
W-What is that?!
A prisoner.
A prisoner with a mask, that is.
A-A vampire?
A few days ago, he was a feeble,
toothless old man on death's door.
We haven't fed him today,
so he must be thirsty.
He'll attack quickly.
How will they perform?
Let's watch and see!
What's this? What a surprise!
Is he just an ordinary man?
We have no other subjects to test!
Shall we use the explosives planted in
the prisoner's head, Major von Stroheim?
Major?!
Very well. Do it!
W-Wait! Belay that order!
His jaw. L-Look at his lower jaw!
A-And his arms. Look! Look at his arms!
I thought he was losing the fight,
but Santviento is absorbing the prisoner!
He is pulling him into his body.
He's eating the prisoner!
What a fantastic creature!
The masked man is his fodder!
Santviento feeds with his whole body!
T-That means he'll take in all of
his prey's energy!
He ate him! He ate the masked man!
He ate him!
A-And he's grown!
Keep your head!
Remember he's in a sealed chamber!
He only gained some weight
after feeding.
And his intelligence?
What of his intelligence?
Is he capable of thought?
S-Stroheim.
What the...?! He spoke!
H-He said my name!
But he shouldn't be able
to hear me in there!
My cactus pal Donobang said this is where
the secret underground facility is.
Speedwagon has to be in there.
Now, how to get inside?
Vegetables, canned goods, meat, ham,
eggs. That's a basket of food.
All right. Now we have to frisk you!
Don't make that face.
Smile when I frisk you!
Raise your skirts! And smile!
Go on through!
Next!
I've brought you some tequila.
Is that all right to bring through?
Put your hands up!
You twitch and we shoot!
Why? Why are you panicking?!
That's a furtive movement!
Fire!
Hold it! I-I understand! I won't move!
Damn! Y-You Germans are too smart!
You saw right through my disguise!
You're nuts! Of course we did!
What a creep!
No girl in the world is built like
such an ox, you ox!
Look at yourself
with clearer eyes, moron!
What was that?!
Hamon!
Oh, tacos!
Shoot, that was depressing.
I suppose they won't see
through an army uniform.
W-What's going on?
I-I can't tell.
Weren't you watching?
Major von Stroheim, I was
looking away for a moment.
You were here.
Everyone was here.
But nobody saw.
This is no time for refreshments!
I-It was only a moment.
I only took my eyes off of him
for a few seconds.
My vision is perfect, but I couldn't
see what was happening inside!
This is unbelievable!
The chamber is sealed!
But the subject somehow escaped!
The walls show no damage!
Listen up! Calm down and search for him!
I am sure he's just concealed
himself somewhere!
Cut off all oxygen!
We'll wait for him to come out!
The film record is ready for viewing!
Show it to us!
Yes, sir!
Begin.
He's running for the wall!
H-He couldn't be...!
He's going into the ventilation ducts!
The entrance is only
four by twenty centimeters!
But somehow he's stuffing himself
into that tiny gap!
Incredible! He didn't just
dislocate his joints!
H-He broke up his own skeleton
to twist and alter his shape!
T-That means he's somewhere
in the base's ventilation system!
The Pillar Man Santviento spoke your name
earlier, Major von Stroheim.
He must have heard your name
through the vents!
Do the vents lead here?!
Soldier! Stand away from that vent!
You're in danger!
I-It's Santviento!
Major von Stroheim,
did something happen?
It's so dark! I can't see!
Who turned out the lights?
Santviento crawled into the soldier's body!
Where is everybody?!
Don't leave me here all alone!
I'm not sure what's going on...
...but I've never felt so full of life!
What a nightmare.
If this creature escapes,
it will be a dire foe to the Fatherland!
We must destroy it!
It has to be killed here and now!
Very well! Shoot him!
Blast that soldier's body to pieces!
That tickles!
He's still alive!
I knew it!
He's immune to bullets!
What a monster!
Why is he pointing?
What's he gonna do?!
Wait! Do you think he's
making a pistol?!
Is he imitating us?
W-When he spoke, he only said my name.
He's mimicking us!
It's just mindless aping.
That means he's not intelligent at all!
If he's only as smart as a monkey,
perhaps we can still use him!
You...
Who among you disturbed my slumber?
H-He spoke!
He is capable of thought.
A-And his intelligence is great!
He has learned our speech
in this short time!
Die!
What the...?
He took a bullet we shot at him
and fired it back at us!
Hey, old man!
Hide over here!
He's still got more bullets to fire!
No! I don't need any help
from a German soldier!
Good heavens.
You never change.
Still stubborn at a time like this.
I-I can't handle this alone!
S-Stay away!
Hey, I need some of your hair!
Just a handful or two!
Yeeowch! What are you doing?!
It'll only hurt for a bit.
You're assaulting an officer!
Who are you?
That brashness... It couldn't be...!
I call this one Hamon Hair Attack!
You're... You're...!
Joseph Joestar!
Barrier up!
I think you need to start moisturizing.
If you aren't careful, you'll go bald,
Mr. German Army Man.
W-When did you get here?
Hey, old man!
Ha...ir...
Anyhow...
...what a scene I've dropped in on.
Next episode
His intelligence is incredible!
This is horrifying!
Now together, Santviento!
You primitive.
He's crawling into the wound in my leg!
Chapter 13: JoJo vs.The Ultimate Being