All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Enyaba, there's something I'd like to ask you.
What does it mean to live?
To obtain what one desires.
To put it simply, that is all it means to live.
People want money, they want fame,
they want food, they want love,
they want a lover...
But when they attempt to obtain what they desire,
there is always a battle, is there not, Enyaba?
Indeed.
If they lose the battle and
fail to obtain what they desire,
they feel frustration and a sense of failure.
They are hurt...
And they feel fear when
faced with the next battle.
I believe that conquering
fear is what it means to live.
The one who will stand at the top of the world
is the one who feels no fear whatsoever.
Do you understand, Enyaba?
I was the one who told you about
the existence of your Stand and how to use it.
And you have an immortal body.
Is there anything that you fear?
Perhaps.
What concerns you?
The Joestar bloodline.
Joestar? Those two? They are mere trash.
They are no match for your Stand!
Yes...
But when the lives of those trash
are so deeply entangled with my own,
I cannot help but believe it is destiny.
To be more specific...
It is not the Joestars that I fear.
It is the fact that I cannot
underestimate the Joestar bloodline.
I feel that I must rid the
Joestars from my wheel of fortune.
You thought to eliminate them
yourself simply because you feel
that they cannot be underestimated?
Yes.
Foolishness!
You should never engage in such foolishness!
We already have seven Stand users—
The Empress, The Hanged Man,
Strength, The Wheel of Fortune, Temperance,
The Emperor, and The Devil— on the move.
You need not worry about
taking action yourself, Lord DIO.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 7: Strength
Whoa!
A-A freighter!
I didn't see it at all.
Jotaro, what are you concerned about?
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
Do you think there might be
another Stand user on this freighter, too?
No, I was just wondering why
no one's shown themselves,
even though the ramp is down.
They came this far to rescue us!
There has to be someone aboard!
Even if they're all Stand users,
I'm getting on this boat.
Grab on. I'll help you up.
Good grief.
Wh-What's with this boat?!
There's no captain in the pilothouse!
There's no operator in the radio room.
There's no one anywhere!
And yet, look!
All the meters and machines are working properly.
Maybe they're all in the bathroom
with a bad case of diarrhea.
Hey! Isn't anyone around?
Everyone, come over here!
A monkey!
There's a monkey inside that cage.
An orangutan.
Who the hell cares about a monkey?!
Let's split up and find whoever's been feeding it.
Well?
It doesn't appear to be broken, but...
Avdol! That sailor's in danger!
Good grief.
A welcome like this is a bit much for a girl.
B-But no one was touching it...
I saw that crane move, even though
there was no one operating it!
Th-That crane impaled him on its own!
Be careful! There's someone here.
Hey! Don't touch any of the machinery.
If it moves or runs on electricity,
don't lay a finger on it!
If you want to live, follow my orders.
Don't leave the cabin down
below until we say it's okay!
Did anyone see even a
glimpse of a Stand just now?
No...
My apologies...
I was the closest to the crane,
yet I felt nothing.
All right. I will have my
Hierophant Green look around.
I-I have no idea what's going on,
but dangerous things keep happening
when you guys are around.
Are you guys jinxes?
I've heard about people who cause
disasters that endanger everyone,
and that I should avoid them.
Is that what you are?
I have just one bit of truth for you.
We are on your side.
Make sure you stay with the others. Got it?
Okay.
You want me to open the cage?
I can't.
I don't know where the key is, and you're so big.
You're giving me an apple?
But it doesn't make sense...
This apple's been cut with a knife,
and the color hasn't changed yet...
It was just cut.
Hey, so there is someone
somewhere on this boat, right?
Do you know where the
person who feeds you is?
Scratch
Y-You're a pretty smart monkey, aren't you?
Is a monkey like you actually into looking at
pinups of human girls?
Hey, be careful!
They say an orangutan has
five times the strength of a human,
so it could easily rip off your arm.
Come on. Stay with us in the
room on the other side.
Don't go off by yourself.
O-Okay...
It's inconceivable.
I've had Hierophant Green search everywhere,
but I can't find any signs of life.
We've searched every
pipe and crevice, but nothing!
Well?
I-It's no use. I can't get a connection.
Well, try one more time!
I'm all sticky from the salt water...
Hey!
Jojo!
Here's your lock!
This ape... is no ordinary ape.
Could it be that he's...
Slice
I-Is he the one that removed the fan?
So this ape's a Stand user.
But where's the Stand?
Why can't I see it?
What?
The steel propeller bent on its own?
Jojo!
Wh-What is this?
Once again, I can't see the Stand,
and yet the window broke.
Star Platinum!
What's with this thing?
The ape sank into the wall and disappeared!
Hey. You saw that, didn't you?
Stay close to me.
Something bad is going down.
The ape vanished into the wall...
But that orangutan has to be the Stand user...
When I touched it with my hand,
I felt a Stand's energy coming from it.
But why can't I see the Stand?
But... if I can see it, that would mean...
Wh-What?
Wh-What is this?!
C-Crap!
Th-This is...
Is this freighter...
C-Could it be that the ship itself is...
So the Stand is the freighter!
C-Crap!
All of it! Everything!
This ship itself is a gigantic Stand!
The ship?!
There are Stands that people,
like that girl and the crew members
who aren't Stand users, can see?
We would have to assume
that it's because the
energy of its presence is so
enormous and powerful.
But it must demand tremendous
power to operate such a gigantic Stand.
Kakyoin! Use Hierophant
Green and contact Jotaro!
I-I can't!
It's got a firm hold on my Stand.
So this is what it means to face certain doom.
We were already hopelessly ensnared.
The pressure is getting greater...
At this rate, our bodies will be torn apart.
E-Everyone will be...
W-We were careless...
The word that the orangutan
was pointing to was "strength."
It means force, energy, power, or aid.
And... it is the eighth card of the Tarot!
The eighth card of the Tarot. It suggests challenge,
powerful will, and hidden instinct.
It suggests challenge, powerful will,
and hidden instinct!
Ba-Bang
This ape thinks it's already won.
"This ship, the entire thing, is my Stand!"
"You've completely lost!"
"You can't do anything!"
That's what it's saying.
That's what this ape is saying!
That button's not part of your Stand.
You mad?
I guess it wounded your pride,
since you thought you'd already won.
No, it's not hurt...
Because apes don't have any pride!
Graaaa
That's exactly what makes you an ape.
What's going to hurt...
is your head!
Good grief.
I've heard that, when frightened,
animals show their stomachs
to signal that they're giving up.
So you're asking me to forgive you?
But you've already broken
the rules of being an animal.
So I don't think so.
Wham! Wham! Wham!
It's distorting...
The whole ship is twisting up!
Hey. Be surprised later.
This ship's about to sink.
We're gonna get out of here,
by the boats we came in on.
I-I can't believe it.
The ship's shape is changing.
It's turning into such a shoddy little boat...
Unbelievable...
So that monkey used its own
Stand to get this far into the ocean.
What terrifying power.
That was the first time I've
encountered such energy.
We were completely overwhelmed.
If Jotaro hadn't figured it out,
we would have been done for.
But are we going to encounter
even more Stands with
unknown powers from now on?
Want some gum?
So we're going to be drifting again.
Good grief. My cigarettes are soaked.
There'll be plenty of sun and
time for them to get dry, Jojo.
We'll just have to pray that we get
rescued and reach Singapore safely.
Tokyo
It's been four days since we left Japan...
Crash
Hong Kong
Cruiser Sinks
Ghost Ship
Singapore
There are 46 days until the time limit.
Cairo
Strength
Forever
It seems Strength has been defeated.
But have no fear.
The remaining six Stand
users are all very powerful.
And one of them is also my son!
My son's right arm shall take care of them all.
You are a strange old woman.
What is it that you desire?
I have already told you many times...
My wish is to stay by your side.
Your guardian spirit has an
unbelievable amount of power.
Your ability to escape trouble,
and your strange life,
are also the result of that.
I would like to see your life!
That is all...
Once upon a time,
a prince from the land of Sumatra
went out to sea, seeking new lands.
He then found an island where
there were white-maned
lions called Singas,
and so he named the island Singapura.
A country of straits that ships and tankers from
around the world pass through!
A country whose people share
both Western and Eastern heritage
thanks to free trade: Singapore!
Good grief. We're finally here.
We'll stay at a hotel tonight and
figure out our route to Egypt.
All right, let's stay at that hotel.
Next Episode Preview
I guess you guys won't even give us a chance to rest.
She'll be in danger if she stays with us.
And Polnareff fell into that trap?
There...
...is...
...a...
...traitor.
Joestar, you bastard.
Episode 8
The Devil