Poco, where in blazes
were you at this hour?!
D-Dad...
I'm glad you're safe,
b-but where's Sis?
She went out to look for you.
She... She went out?!
Poco, what's the matter?
You're acting strange.
Sis!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 8: Blood Feud - JoJo & Dio
Think about this.
Take this lovely flower.
Your youth is blooming
just like this flower is.
Consider this carefully, mademoiselle.
If this flower blooms fully,
it will only wither away.
A shame, don't you think?
She's sweet sixteen!
So pure and innocent!
Look at how full of delicious
life energy she is, Lord Dio!
Those without manners
aren't fit to live.
So, mademoiselle...
I offer you a choice.
Wouldn't you like to enjoy
your youth for all eternity?
However, I will not force my friendship
upon you, unlike some.
You are free to choose your own destiny.
Devil.
What's that you said?
You're just a damned d-devil!
Alas. Though you will soon part,
allow me to introduce my companion.
This is the dreaded Doobie.
Since I am not to your taste,
you might enjoy his company.
Bye, mademoiselle.
W-Who's there?!
Who indeed?
There's no need
for introductions to a zombie!
Sis!
Poco!
Bit you! Bit you!
What's lurking under his mask?
L-Look at that!
That zombie is full of snakes!
Venomous cobras and flesh-eating vipers!
Surprised, are you?
Those snakes bit his face,
and not just once!
How troublesome.
I don't have time for Dio's games!
Impressive.
He squeezed out the poison.
He's learned a lot about blood flow
in a very short time.
It's because Baron Zeppeli gave
him his life energy before he died.
I'll use a bit of Hamon to
boil the blood of those snakes!
Sis!
Poco!
I'm back from hell, Dio.
Still alive, JoJo?
I suppose that means
you've defeated my two knights.
Lord Dio, we await your order
to eliminate him!
I'll let my fangs
make an impression on him!
Dio!
No. This one...
This one I will handle personally.
Allow me to be frank, JoJo.
I didn't want to have
to do this personally.
We were raised in the same house.
Making you undead does not please me.
That's why I left this business
to my knights.
But in the end, I underestimated you.
Seeing you alive makes me realize
I was too soft of an emperor.
Now I will slaughter you
without a hint of hesitation!
Same here.
I'll feel no guilt for killing you!
By the way, what happened
to that dapper mustachioed
gentleman you were with?
Did he run off?
Dio, I must express my feelings.
This shames me as a gentleman, but...
...truth be told, I, Jonathan Joestar,
will kill you to satisfy my anger!
Come, JoJo!
Dire!
JoJo, stand aside.
I have the right to satisfy
my anger first.
Zeppeli was a companion through
two decades of harsh training.
Dio, I will send you
straight to the bowels of hell!
Wait! He has hidden abilities
you don't know about!
What an interesting walk.
With enough training, humans are able
to make themselves float on the air.
But in just one night, I have gained
power beyond any human guru!
You think you can beat me
with such sleepy movements?!
You fell for it, fool!
Thunder Cross Split Attack!
Incredible! By crossing his arms
he can attack while keeping his guard up!
It's a perfect stratagem!
No fighter has escaped it.
He's...!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
I-I can't move!
He's been flash frozen!
Dio vaporized the moisture in his body,
turning him to ice in an instant!
Dire can't send Hamon into Dio
unless his blood is flowing!
That Dio is truly fearsome!
He froze Dire's whole body at once!
Y-You...
So feeble!
You thought you would ever
be able to touch me, fool?!
You came here just to die like a dog!
I'll give them all a good show!
- D-Dire!
- Stop!
JoJo, it's time.
You're the next one
to be sent to oblivion!
Dire!
A Hamon-filled rose's thorns do sting.
How...
How dare you scar my face?!
Dire...
Speedwagon!
Here!
Dio, I've just seen the way
to beat your flash freezing.
I know how to send Hamon into you.
Dire spent his life to teach me.
I'll fill Blueford's sword of luck and
pluck with Hamon and slice you!
You dare touch me...
You dare touch me with your
Hamon filthier than frog urine?!
You've pushed your luck too far!
Now you'll be a feast for my zombies!
They'll gnaw the faces off your skulls!
Now he shows his true colors
as the worst man in the world!
His cool sophistication is
nothing but a cheap mask!
Now that he's had a humiliating taste
of Hamon, we see his real face!
I will show you no mercy!
I am Pajyu!
Jones!
Pluton!
Barnum!
Needle Vein Strike!
Roses are living things, so Hamon
will remain inside of them.
But steel is different.
I have to maintain contact.
There is a great horde of them.
I'll handle them for you.
As far as I can tell, Dio
is as swift as a leopard.
Thanks to Baron Zeppeli,
Jonathan just might keep up.
But Dio is strong enough to
pulverize flesh and bone with ease!
The battle will be decided as they meet
in the opening moment!
I'll squeeze the life out of you!
I'll cleanse the world of your evil!
H-He grabbed some roses
when I wasn't looking!
Now!
W-Wow!
He circled to Dio's right
because that eye can't see!
D-Damn! JoJo is a veteran fighter!
Y-Yes!
He finally defeated Dio!
Wrong,
you fools!
I-I...
I'm frozen!
So feeble!
Now you will become
one of my children of the night!
I've got your rubbery
carotid between my fingers!
So warm and springy.
What a pleasant feeling.
A kick!
My legs are frozen, too!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
Enjoy this anguish, JoJo!
Move and this delicate
blood vessel will snap!
I'll open your carotid and exchange
your blood for my vampiric essence.
W-We have to help!
Zombies!
Keep those peasants back
for a moment.
They just won't stop coming.
We won't be able to help.
Now, JoJo, I'll fill you with vampiric
essence and make you my slave!
Don't think you've won, Dio!
You've made a fatal mistake!
And how so?
You haven't frozen me completely
because you are still feeding.
If you freeze me, my Hamon will stop,
but you can't drain my life, either!
Your tactics are flawed!
He put the sword in the flame!
That blade is conducting the heat
faster than I can freeze it!
Hamon is coming up the blade!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
Take this!
He got him!
Look again! You can tell that
the Hamon didn't go through.
My arm...
My arm is frozen again!
I only touched his face!
You underestimated me, JoJo!
I will admit it.
I admire your explosive tenacity.
I must say that your use of fire
was marvelous.
But JoJo, nothing can escape
my icy grasp.
Just a touch on the arm is enough.
I can freeze your whole body in
two seconds.
He squeezed out
the vampiric essence!
Jonathan hasn't given up yet!
Why are you puffed up like that?
Still looking for a fight?
No matter how you struggle,
human ability is limited.
Your Hamon training is useless!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
A monkey cannot stand
against a human!
And compared to me,
you are a mere monkey, JoJo!
Wrong! With enough conviction,
humans can do anything!
Humans will grow!
Let me demonstrate!
You won't, because
you'll be a zombie!
His hand, it's burning!
His glove is on fire!
It just might get through Dio's ice!
Which one of us will fall in the end?!
We find out now, Dio!
H-He was blocked!
No!
He's breaking through!
I'm disintegrating!
The pain! The burning!
My reign...was supposed...
to last...for centuries!
You had to be destroyed, Dio.
I won't...
He shot his essence from his eye!
He was centimeters
from incinerating my brain!
T-That was close!
The last throes of a demon
clinging to life in this world.
Dio's falling down the cliff!
Dio...
He's fainted!
He's worn out. He should be.
He's seen too many fatal fights tonight.
But why would he cry
after killing a bad guy like that?
He spent his youth together with Dio.
But me? I can smile happily!
Are you watching, Baron Zeppeli?
He did it!
Jonathan finally did it!
Dio is dead.
It may sound like an exaggeration,
but the world is saved!
Next episode
What a joyous occasion!
These are tears of joy.
R-Run...
I want to stay like this forever.
Is my new body here?
Chapter 9: The Last Hamon