I should be able to meet up
with Melone in about an hour.
Ghiaccio, I'll leave the
situation to you and Melone.
You can never be too careful.
I'll stay here and try to figure
out where they're headed.
Got it, Risotto.
How much longer are you going
to make me wait? Hurry up.
You should have no problem restoring this.
Risotto.
Do you really think you can get
away with betraying Passione?
We're a bit short on time.
Next will be your left eye.
As long as you have your right hand
and right eye, you can still work.
You should know better than anyone!
Anyone who betrays the boss will be erased...
Episodio 18  Head to Venice!
What?!
The hand that I cut off has already
become another living creature
and invaded your body.
As you can see, it turned into a piranha!
There's a huge hole that goes
all the way to its head...
and it can still move?
Wh-What's wrong, Babyhead?
Answer me! Hey!
This is turtle shit...
This is literally shit that
the turtle left behind!
Why the hell do I have to go through this?
Damn it!
This pain in my heart...
You're going to make up for this
by dying in disgrace! I'll see to that!
If Bucciarati and Trish won't turn back
to normal unless I destroy you...
then I'll do it!
You're not getting away.
Next, I'll go for your head!
Go ahead and try it...
you dickhead!
Dickhead
I'll kill you...
Go ahead and try it...
Damn it...
The only problem with auto-tracking is
that it won't listen to me 100 percent.
You bastard!
You got me three times already.
I know the range of your attacks!
That bastard's range...
just grew!
It's gotten taller?
It must've grown even more
because it got pissed off!
Di molto!
I knew choosing that woman as the
mother was the right choice!
Simple is best.
I'm going to kill this bastard
exactly how I want to kill him!
Bring it back, Golden Wind!
Die!
Useless!
A direct hit.
You should get your eyes checked.
You didn't hit my head!
I've won! This is the end!
I told you, it's useless.
Wh-What the hell?!
Look again.
The hand that Golden Wind
brought back wasn't its own.
It's the bike.
I gave the bike life and had
it return to us as a hand.
Crush
You just took that bike into your body,
as a part of you.
This is nothing...
I'll just split apart and get away aga—
Think about it.
There's gasoline in bikes.
I'm pretty sure I can cause a big enough
explosion to keep you from splitting apart
in time to escape.
What?!
Kabooom
Sizzling... Burning...
Looks like doing what you
wanted was useless...
in the end.
Burn burn burn burn burn burn burn...ing...!
I-It disappeared?
My contact with it disappeared?!
Damn it! This is unbelievable!
Curse you, newbie!
He did it.
It should be somewhere around here...
My car is gone!
Where's my car? Was it stolen?!
That's Melone's bike...
I was told to leave no stone unturned and
take a leaf out of someone's book if
I have to, in order to find them...
I get the "leave no stone unturned" part.
I totally get it.
I mean, you have to turn
stones over to find stuff.
But what the hell does it mean to
take a leaf out of someone's book?!
What's a leaf doing inside a book?!
Damn it!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Why the hell is there a leaf in a book?!
You think I'm stupid?! Damn it!
Hey, Melone! Bucciarati and his
crew are nowhere to be found!
Are you listening?! Hello?!
I hear you...
But I haven't completely failed just yet!
I still have Bucciarati's blood!
I can create an infinite number of Juniors!
I'll have them track Bucciarati
down immediately!
You'd better, Melone.
We need to be extra careful with the newbie.
We should get rid of him first.
I'll find an even better mother
and create an even more
powerful and invincible
Junior to go track them down.
What the hell was that?
It looked like a snake...
What? What's wrong?
What's a snake doing at a station in Rome?
I-It's burning!
This is... that newbie's ability...
He must've used Junior's corpse to—
Hello?
Hey, Melone! What's wrong? Hey!
The venomous snake I left
at Roma Termini Station
reverted to being one of
the enemy's components.
We disposed of the user.
That makes five.
If the information we have is correct,
there are only two members
of the Hitman Team left.
Still, we can't let our guard down.
Let's haul ass to Venice!
Now Melone, too?
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit!
Hello?!
It's me. I've managed to
get that thing analyzed.
Huh?!
I'm sending the data right now.
We've received a new order from the boss.
Abbacchio, could you come
over here by this chair?
Me?
Here's the order.
"Have Abbacchio use his Moody Jazz
near the chair and rewind 14 hours."
Someone was inside this turtle
before we got here.
I think that's what this suggests.
Got it.
Then I'll search from around 15 hours back.
It transformed.
Hey, I've seen that geezer before!
That's the capo, Mr. Pericolo.
So he was the one who placed the turtle
next to the water fountain at Naples Station.
And approximately 14 hours
ago, he entered this turtle.
I'm continuing the replay.
Bucciarati and team, I will now
give you your final order.
Final order?
The reason we're using this method to give
you information is to prevent leaks.
I'm about to tell you something of utmost
importance that no one else must learn:
how you're going to hand
Trish over to the boss.
How we're going to...
...hand Trish over?
Well, here it is.
Once you safely get to Venice,
go to this sculpture and retrieve
the OA-DISC that's inside.
It contains the data on how
you're going to hand her over.
Hey! He set it on fire!
Abbacchio, pause it!
Right.
I'm pretty sure this is the
entrance to Venice...
Right in front of Santa Lucia Station.
The lion statue is from there.
That is all.
Make sure that you obtain the OA-DISC.
They've already found out about me.
The most important thing is to
deliver Trish safely to her father.
We mustn't leave any kind of evidence.
Thanks to the boss, I was able to live a
very wealthy, blessed, and fulfilling life.
My mission is now over.
I pray from the bottom of
my heart that you stay safe.
What the hell?!
Mr. Pericolo...
They should've received the order by now.
Obtain the disc, or getting to me
is going to prove rather difficult.
The most important thing is
what awaits at the end...
Bring my daughter Trish here...
to Venice.
The marine fortress city on the water,
visible in the morning haze: Venice.
There is only one road by which one can
travel there from the mainland by car:
the Ponte della Libertà, which stretches for a
length of 3.5 kilometers over a shallow ocean.
The station lies just beyond the bridge.
The lion statue where the disc is
hidden can be found in a square there.
Giorno, there's no one tailing us so far.
Yes. There's no one coming
from the front, either.
The city is still asleep.
We're the only car on this road.
Why do the windows keep
fogging up so quickly?
Ow!
What the hell?!
I apologize.
The tires just slipped a bit.
On a straight bridge like this?
Be more careful, damn it!
Do you even have a license?
No. I'm only fifteen.
What's that thing stuck on the window?
It's on the inside.
I didn't notice it when
I was looking outside...
No, wait...
That shape...
It's a finger!
Let's open the windows a bit.
It's morning, so the different temperatures
inside and outside the car are fogging them up.
Wh-What?! What's with this wind?
At first, we were scared frozen... But...
With the help of a computer,
it wasn't too hard to recreate
the ashes that were lying next
to Pericolo in the photo.
You guys are naïve!
There's no way you can get
away from the Hitman Team!
An enemy?! They somehow got
onto the roof of the car!
Mista, what are you doing?! Shoot the roof!
This car is being frozen
at an insane speed.
It's so cold that my finger
got stuck to the window
and broke off before I even felt the cold.
If I don't peel my face off of it,
my brain's gonna freeze up.
But I'm not sure if I want to
sacrifice my face, either...
Where's the turtle?
I don't see the turtle inside the car.
You two aren't with Trish and Bucciarati?
If you're actually bothering to split up...
I got it!
That means you must be on a mission
to get something extremely important.
The location in the picture...
There must be something
at the station in Venice!
Blood finally spurted from my hand!
Yeehaw!
Bonk
I-Ice!
The guy's encased himself in ice and
froze himself to the roof of the car!
The bullets can't get through to him!
What's wrong?
C-Crap! We're starting to freeze, too!
Save me!
Number Two!
Don't go!
Number Two! Number Three!
Fwooooo
What?!
A-All I did was blink... and now
my eyelashes are stuck together!
He must've waited for this to happen
before getting on the roof...
This car is currently going
80 kilometers per hour.
Which means...
It's the same as being stuck in wind
blowing at 20 meters per second.
The effective temperature drops by 1° Celsius
for every meter of wind velocity,
so we're currently freezing at -20° Celsius.
Then stop the damn car!
Why the hell are you still flooring it?!
Yes. I've been trying to stop it.
But the brake pedal is
frozen and won't go down!
I'm losing the steering wheel, too.
The engine's running and doesn't
seem like it's going to stop.
The surface of the car has
reached -100° Celsius for sure!
And at incredible speed!
So this is... the enemy's ability!
Th-The blood that was spurting
out of my hand froze...
The moisture from my breathing caused
my nostrils to freeze together...
And now, my lips...
Shit! I can't breathe!
S-Stop the car, Giorno!
You can turn the car into a
frog or something, can't you?!
Do something with your ability!
I've already tried that, as well.
But there are no organisms that
can be born at -100° Celsius!
You know Paris, France?
In English, they pronounce it "Paris,"
but everyone else pronounces it
without the "s" sound, like the French do.
But with Venezia, everyone pronounces
it the English way, "Venice."
Like The Merchant of Venice
and Death in Venice...
Why, though?!
Why isn't the title Death in Venezia?!
Smack Smack Smack
Are you friggin' mocking me?!
It takes place in Italy, so use
the Italian word, damn it!
That shit pisses me off!
Bunch of dumbasses!
Looks like it's finally becoming
a bit difficult to drive.
Mista...
My Golden Wind needs heat.
So sadly, all I'm really
useful for right now...
is picking up bullets.
You won't be able to fill
the car with any more holes.
I'll just freeze you to an even lower tem—
When you fire bullets,
they heat up, don't they?
So when I fire the bullets that
Giorno picked up for me...
It creates heat!
I guess I'll go ahead and shout
this for Giorno, while I'm at it...
Golden Wind!
We did it!
Plant roots have the energy to prop up
asphalt in roads and even shatter rocks!
Keep hold of the steering wheel, Giorno!
We're gonna get the hell outta here!
Shink
Tch.
So that must be the ability of the
newbie Melone was talking about.
But you're not getting away!
Seriously? That bastard!
He's still coming after us!
I'm gonna be the one who gets his hands on
whatever's at the station, no matter what.
You're wasting your bullets.
My ability, White Ice, freezes the moisture
in the air to an extremely low temperature,
which I then wear like armor.
This also allows me to skate,
but I'm also wrapped in something so
strong that even bullets can't pierce it!
Go faster, Giorno!
I can't go any faster!
The tires are still slipping.
Even worse, they found
out about the station!
They haven't found out about
the turtle where Trish is,
so depending on how you look at it,
that's kind of a bright side.
You're always so optimistic, aren't you?
You're very unusual.
He's coming! Floor it! Faster!
I told you, I can't!
If we slip, we're going
to lose even more spee—
Just do it, damn it!
I said floor it, so floor it!
I told you! This is useless!
Number Three and Number Two
up on the roof, come back!
I hope you get to share a hot,
passionate kiss with the road.
Your face will be well-acquainted
with it at the speed you're going.
Yeah!
Good. We managed to lose him.
Now get us into the city and
head straight for the station!
Before he can catch up to us, we're going
to get our hands on the thing and hide!
Giorno!
You're not getting away!
There's no way you guys are
going to make it to the station!
He's freezing the moisture
from the car's exhaust!
What kind of temperature do you
have to freeze it at to do this shit?
You bastard! Eat lead again!
He opened the trunk! Which means...
Sh-Shit! He got into the trunk!
Stop the car, Giorno!
He's gonna freeze the brake pedal
so it'll be useless again!
There's no need for that...
Gunslinger Mista.
Seeing as Trish isn't here, this is what
I was planning to do in the first place.
Shatter—
G-Giorno!
It only cracked?
Is he invincible?
How can I destroy this armor?
Giorno! Get away from him!
No! Not yet!
We made it to Venice!
I'm diving into the canal!
Episodio 19
White Ice