This old man is familiar to us.
Well, at least his bearing
and scar should be.
Nice to see you again, Speedwagon.
I hear you're an oil tycoon
in America now.
That's an exaggeration.
You look as young as ever, Straizo.
I can't believe we're the same age.
Hamon energy is life energy.
I must say I envy you.
49 years after Jonathan's death,
a new age has arrived.
Straizo has succeeded Master Tonpetty,
and Speedwagon has made a fortune.
They set off for Mexico
to see something.
That something was discovered by
a digging team founded by Speedwagon.
That something was a secret known
only to those select few.
When you witness this, I think,
no, I am sure you'll feel a chill.
It's frightful enough to make
your hair stand on end.
It's even worse than the terror we faced
50 years ago when we fought Dio.
This place is tremendous.
This is why I summoned you.
I-It's...
...the mask!
There are so many of them!
New York, 1938
It was the fall of 1938.
I was out looking for a mark as usual.
You must be kidding!
You've never heard of this beverage?
By your accent, I'd say
you're from England. Tourist?
Oh? You just moved here, eh?
Anyhow, if you want a drink, pay me.
Money is the rule here.
Hey, friend!
He took your wallet! After him!
What a sucker!
Piece of cake!
Hey, Smokey. Looks like
I finally caught you red-handed!
You worthless street scum!
I'll make sure
they lock you up for 20 years!
Take it easy!
I only pinched a wallet!
I hate all of your bottom-feeding kind!
But I'm a nice guy.
Bring me twenty dollars
every week.
Plus half of what you steal.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's the stooge who got robbed.
I'm keeping your wallet
as evidence.
Well, how should I put this?
Let's see...
That wallet was actually a gift
to him, officer.
The 195 cm giant of an Englishman
was covering up for me!
So I need you to let go
of the wallet and the boy.
What's that?
Like I said, it was a gift.
He's a close friend of mine.
Please let him go.
A close friend?
Tell me your close friend's name.
Don't lie to me!
You want to spend some time in the pen?
You bonehead!
I'm curious.
I don't understand why you did that.
What was the purpose behind it?
There's no purpose!
I do what I feel like, dimwit!
If someone wipes a booger
on your right cheek, then--
You picked the wrong man
to mess with, pig!
Y-You're resisting arrest!
Shoot me!
But I'm warning you!
When you pull the trigger,
I'll break your finger like a match!
Not from over there!
I'll blow your brains out!
Suddenly, it seemed to me
like his body was glowing.
It was like magic.
The cap flew off with enough
force to snap the cop's finger!
I lost my temper again!
N-Now I'm in trouble.
G-Granny Erina will be furious!
W-What is this guy?
He beats up cops and then worries
about what his granny will say?!
So, Mr. Pickpocket,
shall we high-tail it?
He didn't know how he launched
the bottle cap with such force.
He said he could always do it.
His grandpa died young,
but he could do the same thing.
His dad died in the War,
but had no such talents.
He didn't have a mom, either.
I owe you big time.
My name's Smokey.
What's yours?
Joestar.
Joseph Joestar.
Battle Tendency
Chapter 10: JoJo in New York
You can call me JoJo.
What is this?
Who is the man in that pillar?
It's not a carving.
He has amino acids. He has cells.
And though faint,
he has body heat and a pulse.
This man is alive!
Straizo, what is he exactly?
How long has he been here?
What are the masks for?
Why is he here?
None of that matters!
We have one purpose here!
I called you so that you
could destroy him utterly
with Hamon while he sleeps!
What of Joseph Joestar?
How is the young man doing?
I hear he used Hamon
to save your life once.
Why bring JoJo up now?
I believe it was back
when he was 13 years old.
Yes, some men hijacked your plane
so that they could ransom you.
Hey, kid! You can't stay back here.
Get up front!
You're hijacking Speedwagon, right?
I'm just a bystander.
I'm just going to read my comic.
You go do your business.
Don't give me any lip, punk!
JoJo!
T-This is bad.
That suit were a gift from Erina.
That'll set him off for sure!
Take it easy, JoJo!
You guys knew the plane might crash
if you hijacked it, right?
Was that Hamon?
T-The kid is crazy!
We're gonna crash!
Grab the yoke!
I can't fly!
Wrap the pilot in this!
We're jumping!
You never think things through!
I do think.
At least enough to keep
you and Granny Erina safe.
You're my only family, after all.
He looks just like his grandfather,
but he's far from a gentleman.
That was when I discovered
that Joseph could use Hamon.
So he inherited Hamon breathing
from his grandfather Jonathan.
That's right.
But why bring that up now?
W-What the devil?
I just killed these men.
And when you die...
...Jonathan's grandson will feel
grief and anger.
He will grow to hate me.
S-Straizo!
Straizo...
A-Are you mad?!
Quite the opposite.
My thinking is very clear.
I chose the path of Hamon
in order to forge my body.
But as I trained, the aging of my body
became painfully clear to me.
Hamon gives only the slightest edge
over ordinary people.
Its practice cannot prevent
the aging process.
In the battle all those years ago,
I secretly admired Dio.
He was powerful, beautiful
and immortal.
I coveted the power of the mask.
I didn't care who got in the way!
Y-You've become twisted, Straizo.
Your blood will now
grant me immortality.
With you gone, only Erina and
Joseph Joestar will know of the mask.
Once I am rid of them, I'll take my time
and learn more of the mask than Dio did!
Y-You mustn't!
T-There are terrible things
we don't yet know!
Eri...na...
Jo...Jo...
Why don't you look
where you're going, dolt?!
Go find a dog
to lick your butt clean!
Now get out of the way, you...
Hello! What was that? Slow down!
Say that again so that I can
understand your gibberish!
I might have to smack you!
JoJo.
What are you doing?
G-Granny Erina!
What are you doing to that man?
Well, uh, you see...
Taxi!
I was just grabbing a taxi.
Oh, JoJo, you're so thoughtful.
Climb in, Smokey.
The Joestar family,
just a grandmother and grandson.
Over time, I heard bits of their past.
Granny, Speedwagon called us
all the way to New York, right?
And now he's off on a trip?
He's unbelievable.
I'm sure his oil business
has him tied up.
Hey, Granny...
Was Speedwagon really
Grandpa's best friend?
That's all? Really?
What are you implying?
Well, he's single, right?
And you're a widow.
I just wondered if that was
the extent of your relationship.
You scoundrel!
Sorry! Ow!
I was wrong! Forgive me!
I know Speedwagon is just loyal!
The Joestars were short-lived.
Erina lost her husband
in an accident at sea.
The son she was pregnant with and
a girl who survived the wreck married.
They became JoJo's parents,
but were claimed by war and disease.
Granny Erina was extraordinarily gentle,
to punks like me and anyone else.
Maybe it was because she was lonely.
JoJo was the same.
Their kindness got him into trouble.
It was for my sake.
Hey, waiter! Waiter!
Yes?
You let that stinking animal in here?
His odor is ruining my appetite!
You shouldn't let that kind in!
Sir, as long as the bill is paid,
we are happy to serve anyone.
What? You mean you'll let
beasts like that eat beasts in here?
I'll just be on my way.
JoJo!
Granny, you aren't going
to stop me, are you?
No. People can have
their own opinions...
...but he insulted a friend in public.
Take him down,
but mind the other customers!
I was hoping you'd say that.
Looking for a scrap, boy?
If you're looking
for your brass knuckles...
...they're not in your coat pocket!
Check your back pocket!
No way!
Now you'll say,
"How did you know that, bastard?!"
How did you know that, bastard?!
By the abrasions on your right hand,
I know you fight using brass knuckles.
Plus, the blood
on your shirt isn't yours.
You just came from a fight.
Since the blood is on your shirt,
I know you took your coat off to fight.
So when you removed your brass knuckles,
you had to put them in your back pocket.
Now you'll say,
"So what, you little punk?!"
So what, you little punk?!
Gotcha!
You like that?!
Don't get uppity with me!
I'm afraid you missed.
What are you punching?
It wasn't me you were pummeling
so happily.
I can predict anything your simple brain
can come up with.
Don't you get that, moron?
Please forgive my underling, madam.
You're Erina Joestar, aren't you?
I do a lot of business
with Mr. Speedwagon.
He told me all about you
in London a while back.
I'm glad to meet you.
I heard something through the grapevine
that hasn't appeared in the papers yet.
Mr. Speedwagon was killed.
Are you serious?
Rumor has it his killer
was a Tibetan monk.
A monk?
Straizo?
The bodies of Speedwagon and his team
washed up along a river in Mexico.
No one knows why they were killed
or where the monk went.
I think I might know.
It has to do with something
Speedwagon said long ago.
It must involve the stone mask and Dio.
JoJo, that guy's a mafioso!
Don't trust him! It must be a scheme!
Believe what you want.
Try your breast pocket
if you want your lighter.
Smokey, I appreciate the warning,
but I believe what he says.
These guys are only after money.
Information like that is valuable
to the Mob, so I believe it.
But!
Even if it's true, you can't just say
something like that to Granny Erina.
Do you see how you've upset her?!
You're thoughtless!
Events from 50 years ago
are coming back to haunt us.
Don't be scared, Granny.
I'm here for you.
No, Joseph. I'm scared for you!
I don't want you to get
wrapped up in this.
I'll be fine.
If it's my fate, I accept it.
I don't understand
what is going on, but...
...these two must
have an unimaginable history.
Hey, Smokey.
Chilly today, isn't it?
Take a look at this magazine.
What is it?
Do you think it can really
make them bigger?
What's this?
"Go from an AA cup to a C cup."
It's a bunch of snake oil.
Don't buy into it.
What's that?
I think $1.25 a pair is too...
Let's see...
I say.
You look kind of familiar,
yet different.
Tell me, have we met before?
Why isn't your breath steaming
when it's so cold out?
And I think I caught a glimpse
of fangs in your mouth just now.
Was I just seeing things?
Don't try to fool me.
Even out here in the streets,
JoJo, I'm taking your life!
Before your abilities grow!
You think so?
I knew he was crazy, but not this crazy!
He's right in public!
Where did he even get that
Tommy gun he's blasting away with?!
I was waiting for you, Straizo!
I don't think you'll go down so easily.
That was for Speedwagon.
This is war!
Next episode
So this is a vampire!
I'll demolish you, Straizo!
German medicine is the world's greatest!
You don't understand a thing!
Apologize in hell!
Chapter 11: Master of the Game