All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
My son has just died...
I can sense the misfortune that
has befallen my son, Centerfold,
through the connection we share as a family.
My precious son...
So you died covered with wounds like this...
I sense it through this pain,
the same pain you felt.
You were magnificent as you
fought for Lord DIO, Centerfold!
But...
To kill someone like you, with a soul so pure...
I'm sure they did something underhanded.
Damn them!
The bastards!
I will make sure they pay a terrifying price
with the Empress card!
Crush
Move!
Now is the time to take action...
With the Stand that kills slowly!
I'm so sad!
I shall kill them all!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Varanasi
Calcutta
India
Jojo and company are heading to
the sacred city, Varanasi, by bus.
Episode 12: The Empress
Listen up.
I don't usually lecture.
Stupid people are stupid because
they don't understand something
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
even when you keep repeating it.
You know guys like that, right?
Idiots that just don't understand.
But you know, uh...
I never got your name...
Nena.
Nena! That's a great name.
You're the daughter of
a wealthy family in the sacred city Varanasi
that we're passing through, right?
You're good-looking, and I can
see that you're a smart girl.
I have an eye for people,
so I'm going to lecture you.
Hol Horse is a horrible, lying bastard.
You're being tricked!
Your parents would cry.
Listen up.
You can't end up like this.
It's easy to do that when you're in love...
But you can't look at things this way.
It's important to look broadly, and be rational.
Hey. It's coming into view.
The city of Varanasi.
The holy river, the Ganges.
Saints, the old, the sickly, children,
cows, dogs, monkeys, food,
excrement, burning corpses...
This river gently embraces
all these things as it flows.
Everything from birth to
death is laid bare in this river.
It is said that people can spend months
here in the sacred city of Varanasi
without getting bored.
That is probably because
the scenery one sees in this city
reflects the scenery of one's soul.
Chomp
Man... it's getting worse.
What's wrong, old man?
You don't look well.
Looks like the spot that I thought
was a bug bite got infected.
It's definitely swollen.
It would be best to have a doctor
look at it before it gets worse.
Hey, doesn't that sort of
look like a person's face?
Stop kidding around, Polnareff.
Sorry 'bout that.
Want me to go to the hospital with you?
No! Stop treating me like an old man.
Let's cut this off.
Huh? What'd you say?!
It's definitely infected.
If we don't cut it off and get
the poison out, it'll get worse.
Hey, hey, hey.
Can't we just put some
medicine and a bandage on it?
Don't worry. We'll numb
the area, so it won't hurt.
No problem. No problem at all.
Come now, lie down.
I studied medicine in England.
I can do appendectomies, too.
Uh-oh. It's a little rusty.
Well, that's no problem.
All right.
Let's chop that off.
What the hell?
I don't want to watch it being cut off.
No problem.
Hey, are you done?
Is it over yet?
Shriek
What?!
Hey, Doctor!
Trying to cut me?
You're pretty stupid, you moron!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
I'm the Empress, as in the
Empress card, Old Man Joseph!
And now, I'm gonna bloody you up good!
When did you get on me, damn it?!
Clang
It has teeth! It stopped the scalpel!
It's so strong!
It grabbed the scalpel!
Slice
Oh, no!
Th-Thank goodness it was my artificial hand.
You bastard! You're gonna cut yourself?
I'm part of your body, Old Man Joseph.
You can't get away from me now, honey.
Now, why don't I guess what you're thinking?
This is what you're thinking...
Stands can only be beaten by other Stands.
Your Stand, Hermit Purple,
uses the power of remote viewing,
the ability to see things far away.
Is that enough to fight?
Can that defeat the thing
that's fused with your arm?
Nope! Not possible!
Where's the user?
Where was I when you stuck to me?
You fool! Like I'd tell you!
Damn you!
Are you going to your friends?
I wonder if it'll go that smoothly.
Doctor, your next patient is waiting...
Th-The doctor...!
H-Hey! Don't get the wrong idea!
I didn't—
I am the culprit!
I am Joseph Joestar! An American!
I'm staying at Hotel Clarks!
What?!
By the way, girlie.
I have a thing for hot
young nurses like yourself.
What?!
Murderer!
Wait! It's not true!
Oh, no...
Now you can't go back to the hotel.
Now I can kill you without
anyone getting in the way!
Y-You little bitch!
I'll crush you to bits!
What?
Hey, this is your arm.
Take care of it, you shitty old man.
It grew arms. I-Is it continuing to grow?
H-Hey! Let go!
What are you holding on to? Let go!
Nope!
Officer! The culprit's over here!
He's right here!
It's been a while since it came to this...
Hey! What are you doing?
Overdrive!
You moron!
This is your arm!
You think your Hamon would
work against your own body?
You, right there! Don't move!
In that case, Hermit Purple!
I-It's squeezing me...
I can use Hermit Purple this way, too!
I told you not to move!
You! Stop right there!
Damn it!
What are you doing? It's dark in here!
What is happening?
Hermit Purple
Joseph Joestar
So really, Nena...
Real men don't talk big.
That's how you figure out who's a liar.
Since I was avoiding the police,
I ended up going in the
opposite direction of the hotel.
If I'd known this would happen,
I would have taken Polnareff with me.
Instead of a petty guy like Hol Horse,
how about me? Am I not your type?
I don't dwell on the past.
I don't care who you were dating in the past.
What's important is the future.
If our feelings understand each other.
Oh, look over there.
That place is a hotel run by a
Japanese woman named Kumiko.
She manages it with her Indian husband.
Out of the way.
You'll get run into.
We can probably get a room very cheap.
Oh, really?
Now, what about this hotel?
Crunch
Wha...
What are you doing?
I'm eating, Joestar.
To get bigger.
You stole those at the market!
You quick little bastard.
Plop
Why, you...
Wham
Now I'm this big!
You might say I'm mooching off my parent...
Well, I guess in this case
it'd be my parent's arm, Papa.
You ugly bitch!
I'll show you that I, Joseph Joestar,
have many years more
fighting experience than you!
I said that, but what the hell am I going to do?
Damn it...
Anyway, Hermit Purple!
Father, thank you for raising me.
But you shouldn't tie your children down like this.
You need to raise your children to be free.
Chomp
Oh, no!
I-It's no use.
I want to use Hermit Purple's
remote viewing to find the user,
but I don't have a camera!
Wh-What should I do?
At this rate... is not just my arm,
but my whole body going
to become part of her?
I've now grown enough that I can kill you.
See? My hand can reach your neck.
If I bust the carotid artery
in your neck, you're done for.
Oh, no!
What's that guy doing?
You bastard!
What the hell is that?
Look!
That guy's got a nasty-looking growth on his arm.
Damn it! Where's the Stand user?
Polnareff, sir...
I'm a woman who can't survive
without a reliable man.
I love you... Because you're
very reliable and kind.
H-Hey, where did all that come from?
I-Is this for real?
I'm totally going to fall for her!
Lucky!
Hey, Joseph Joestar.
You idiot.
You keep getting further and
further from Jotaro and the others.
Do you think I'm running around
randomly just to wear myself out?
I'm running so I can kill you!
It was so...
I could dunk you in this!
Blop
Stick
You senile old man!
A nail?!
I picked it up earlier.
I picked it up when we were
rolling around on the ground earlier.
So I can cut open your carotid artery!
Did you think I'd suffocate
if you stuck me in here?
Die!
I have a physical form,
but I'm not a living organism.
Did you already forget that?
Only Stands can defeat Stands.
Hey, didn't you say you were going to show
the difference in our fighting experience earlier?
Where's that "experience" you were talking about?
You're just a helpless geezer who's gotten too old!
M-My artificial fingers...
They were on the verge of breaking
from her attack earlier,
and now I can't get any strength in them...
Just one more push, now.
Your life as an invalid is
about to come to an end.
There's not a single way you can defeat m—
Huh?
Not a single way...
What?
Not a single what?
Sorry, my hearing isn't what it used to be.
Run that by me one more time.
Coal tar!
You stuck me into coal tar!
It wasn't to suffocate me,
but to solidify me!
B-But...
How did you know there was coal tar in there?
With the power of my Stand, Hermit Purple.
H-Hey, everyone look...
What is this?
The ashes that foreigner spilled everywhere...
They've formed into a map of the city.
Y-You used spirit photography!
That's how you found the coal tar.
You used the ashes to make a spirit photo!
Now I think you should be able to see
the difference in our fighting experience.
Once your opponent starts to boast
his victory, he has already lost.
This is how Joseph Joestar does things.
I guess I just get better with age.
And...
A Stand can tear away another Stand.
You're going to say,
"Stop, anything but that."
Stop! Stop, anything but that!
Bam
This isn't good. It pains me, too.
Children can't depend on their parents forever.
You've got to go out on your
own once you've grown big!
Now then... where's this Stand user?
W-Well, then, Nena...
Let's swear our love with a kiss.
What? What? What the hell?!
Wh-What's wrong, Nena?!
Burst
Gyaah
So that's The Empress's Stand user...
Huh?
Huh?!
This ugly woman...
She attached her Stand to me
as a tumor with a human face,
and camouflaged herself as a beautiful woman.
That was pretty careless...
She totally played you, Polnareff.
U-Ugh...
Empress
Nena
And here I thought we'd
finally be able to sleep in a bed.
Maybe if the old man hadn't screwed up
and gotten cops chasing him down.
I took care of things.
We can take this car.
Polnareff, you can do the driving.
Hey, are you still in shock?
I was the one attacked by the Stand.
I'd rather have gone through that...
Next Episode Preview
So, we're finally leaving India.
Well, I am a girl.
Did you see the driver's face?
More trouble would be especially bad now.
A truck? Impossible...
By the way... do you like sumo?
Episode 13
Wheel of Fortune