Good morning! Greetings, all.
This is Morioh Radio,
and your host, once again, is me,
your neighbor, Kai Harada.
What a refreshing morning.
And I have the perfect song
here to start off the day.
Here's our first song of the morning.
Oh, there we go.
We usually get good reception
when we pass that tower.
Is this your first time in Morioh, sir?
Yeah.
What kind of place is it?
Morioh? Hmm...
Oh! The beef tongue cooked in miso is good.
Anything strange about it? Any incidents?
No idea.
Sorry, I actually don't know that much about it.
Oh, where was I supposed to drop you off again?
In front of the station is fine.
Understood.
Good grief...
I just hope nothing annoying happens.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
In April of 1999, on my very first day
of high school, I met two bizarre men.
Episode 1  Jotaro Kujo! Meets Josuke Higashikata
I finally start high school today...
I wonder what the people will be like.
My name's Koichi Hirose.
Though you don't really have to remember that.
I was so nervous on my first
walk to my new school that I...
Bam
Eh? H-Huh? That's strange.
We just ran into each other,
and the things in my bag flew out...
Sorry I wasn't watching where I was going.
H-He's huge! He's over 190 centimeters!
I have a question.
Do you know of a Higashikata
household around here?
Higashikata? No...
Then how about this address?
It's Johzenji 1-6.
Jotaro
Kujo
Jotaro Kujo...
If you take the #3 bus,
it'll get you to Johzenji.
If you wait a little while, it'll get here soon.
Thanks.
The first guy was this man, Jotaro Kujo.
I found this out later, but he's 28,
and he's a marine explorer.
He's famous in the scientific world
for his ecological research.
He seems really wild, but
intelligent... or cool, I guess.
Hey! Are you a new kid?
You better introduce yourself.
Y-Yes, sir! My name is Koichi Hirose,
and I'm a new student.
Good morning, Senpai!
All right. Well said.
S-So scary...
Oh, it's okay. They're getting on a different bus.
The hell are you doing, you bastard?!
Who do you think you are?
What am I doing? Well...
The turtle that lives in this pond woke up
from hibernation, so I was watching it.
I don't handle turtles really well.
I'm scared to even touch them.
So I was thinking it's about
time I got over my fear...
That's not what I asked!
Stand up, dumbass!
You're pretty tall for a first-year.
But before you have the
nerve to dress like that...
You dumb shit! Who said you could wear that?
You need to talk to us first!
W-Wait... I'm not a fan of reptiles.
They scare me...
Slap
What the hell are you smiling at?
I'm sorry. I had no idea, Senpai.
There are a lot of guys
I last saw in a hospital after they
said they didn't know and were sorry.
You wanna end up
like this turtle?! Huh?!
Th-They're awful...
I'll let you off the hook this time.
Take off that jacket and the pants,
and leave them here.
With your cash!
Yes, sir! I'm very sorry!
That just means if you don't want them
after you, don't dress like that.
What pisses me off more is that
he isn't even mad after what
they did to that turtle.
Hey, wimp. Why don't you tell me your name?
Yes, sir.
Josuke Higashikata, from Class 1-B.
What? Josuke Higashikata?
Student ID
Name: Josuke Higashikata
"Jo" and "Jo," eh?
Josuke, we're gonna call
you "Jojo" from now on!
Okay... Thank you very much.
Hurry up and take off that uniform.
The damn bus is here.
If you don't hurry it up, I'm gonna
shave off that Astro Boy hair, too.
Well, what are you waiting for? Hurry it up!
Hey, Senpai...
What did you just say about my hair?
What? A Stand?!
My nose... My nose!
I won't let anyone get away with making
fun of my hair, no matter who it is!
Did you say my hair looked like Sazae-san?
Huh?! No one said that...
I heard you, damn it!
What the heck? That punk just went flying.
Some kind of Stand just
appeared from behind him.
Huh? That turtle's wounds are...
What the heck?
Where you got punched
is going back to normal!
Hey, he's all better!
But does it look like it healed all weird?
His face looks kinda different.
Huh?
No way! What does it look like? Hey!
I had to touch that turtle,
even though I didn't want to, thanks to you.
What are you gonna do about that, huh?!
Wait! My nose! What's it look like? Huh?
Good grief. So he's...
Gah! That scared me!
Oh, it's just the turtle again.
I was right. That turtle's all better.
Josuke Higashikata...
Born in 1983.
Your mother's name is Tomoko.
She was 21 at the time,
and was going to college in Tokyo.
You've lived here ever since you were born.
In 1987, when you were four, you came down
with a fever due to an unknown cause,
and for the next 50 days,
no one knew if you'd survive or not.
Your father's name is...
Good grief. This is such a rotten role to play.
Your father's name is Joseph Joestar.
He's currently 78.
He's the founder of Joestar Realty.
I've heard of him before.
Apparently he's a huge
real estate mogul in the US.
He's still doing all right,
but when I was looking into how
to split up his inheritance,
I found out that he had a son
in Japan, which would be you.
He didn't even know about it himself.
That old piece of shit...
Going on about how he'd
only ever love his wife,
yet I just found his son who was
born when he was 62 years old
as a result of an affair.
Whoops. I guess I shouldn't have said that.
My name's Jotaro Kujo.
I guess, technically, I'm your nephew.
How bizarre.
Nephew? Oh, uh... Nice to meet you.
Let's talk while we walk.
And so, eventually, you're gonna get
a third of the old man's inheritance.
I came here to tell you that.
The whole Joestar household is in chaos
since the old man's affair came to light.
It's in chaos?
Yeah... My grandma, Suzie Q,
is the angriest she's ever been
in their 61 years of marriage.
I-I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry
I've caused such a fuss!
Hey, now. Hold up.
Why are you suddenly apologizing?
Well, I mean, causing trouble
in a family is no good.
My mother has told me that she was
in love when she gave birth to me.
I accept that, too.
Could you tell, uh, my dad, um...
Mr. Joestar, I mean,
that he doesn't have to worry about us?
That's all.
What's with this kid?
I came here prepared to take
a punch intended for the old man,
and instead, he's actually apologizing?
Hey, it's Josuke!
Oh, it is!
Josuke!
How are you?
Talk about a coincidence!
Let's go to school together.
Your hair looks as cool as ever.
You're looking sharp.
You're so different from the other guys.
Um... I'm actually in the middle of
something important right now...
Huh? What the heck?
If you don't hurry, we're going to be late.
You can talk later.
Hey, Josuke.
I'm not done talking to you yet.
Run these girls off.
What's his problem?
Hey, have your stupid talk about hair later.
H-He actually said it.
He talked shit about his hair!
You bastard...
What were you saying about my hair, huh?!
This isn't good.
Don't blame me!
Josuke hates people insulting
his hair more than anything else.
It's just like what happened earlier!
Hold it, Josuke.
I wasn't insulting you...
Shit! Here it comes!
Bash
Josuke!
There's blood!
Did you see it, Josuke?
This is called a Stand.
It's the physical manifestation
of your psychological energy.
Joseph Joestar has one, too.
Stands can only be seen by other Stand users.
It pisses me off when someone
talks bad about my awesome hair.
I can't even help it!
So this is Josuke's Stand!
Th-This power...
You're wide open from your chin down!
Bastard!
What?!
Huh?
When did that happen?
What's going on?
When did y—
Josuke!
No!
Shut up!
It pisses me off when girls freak out!
Get out of here!
Fine...
It seems like they know each other.
Besides, he's scary.
But he's kind of hot...
I don't get it...
I have no idea what's going on!
But something is definitely happening!
It's been a while...
Actually, it's been ten years.
But I was able to stop time for half a second.
If I hadn't stopped time...
I doubt we would've been killed,
but one of us would've been badly injured.
Here, Josuke.
Ah, uh... No. It's okay.
I see.
There's actually another
reason I came to see you.
The other reason is this picture.
Something is hiding in this town.
Something very dangerous is approaching.
When Old Man Joseph tried to
get a spirit photo of you,
this is what he got instead.
We're not sure why...
But he's probably a Stand user.
This doesn't concern you, but I wanted
to at least show you the picture.
You've been warned.
Koichi-kun...
If you happen to see him,
don't go anywhere near him.
Calling the police won't help.
Just run.
Josuke...
Don't lose your temper
and go after him, either.
You'll get hurt, just like a moment ago.
Oh! The entrance ceremony!
Ack! Look at the time!
Aw, shit...
Who knows what my mom'll do to
me if I'm late on the first day?!
Hey, I'll listen to everything
you've got to say after school.
Hey, Koichi, was it? Let's go!
Huh?
Hurry!
Right!
The other bizarre guy I happened
to meet is Josuke Higashikata.
He's unpredictable and can go
right from goofy to pissed off.
I guess his family situation is complicated.
And we only just met...
Josuke Higashikata... What a weird guy.
And his Stand...
This hat... It's back together?
So his Stand reforms things into a
different shape after they're broken?
If it had been my face or head...
Talk about creepy.
But if I think about him as a
potential ally, he should be reliable.
If you overlook his ridiculous
personality, anyway.
I just hope this has nothing to do with Josuke.
Shi
Shini
Shinin
Shining
Shining D
Shining Di
Shining Dia
Shining Diamo
Shining Diamon
Shining Diamond
Jo
Josuke
Josuke Higashi
Josuke Higashikata
Hey, girl!
Where are you headed? I'll give you a ride.
Hey, don't be so cold!
C'mon! C'mon!
Ooh, v-very pretty!
You'll go wherever I want?
Hell yeah! I'd go anywhere with you.
Then you can go straight to Hell!
Huh?
Crush
Hey, you okay?
Officer!
G-Go get that crazy bitch!
She injured me! That's a crime!
Nah, I can't do that.
What?!
That's my daughter.
Huh?
Well, you know. You caused trouble for others,
then you called my daughter a crazy bitch.
I'll let it go this time,
but be more careful in the future.
You okay, Old Lady Murakami?
Come on. Grab your bag.
Hey, Tomoko!
Dad.
You headed home?
Yeah.
Let's go home together. I'm done for the day.
How's Josuke?
Today was his entrance ceremony, right?
He'd better not be up to any trouble.
Hmph. Who knows?
That idiot can seem calm,
then get pissed off outta nowhere.
I wonder who he took after.
Hey, now...
But...
Deep down, in the bottom of his heart, he's kind.
No need to worry about him.
Oh, yeah.
Why don't we celebrate him
starting high school tonight?
Yeah, I'm planning to.
But I wonder if he'll come home early.
He'll probably stop somewhere again.
No doubt.
Hey, I want to stop by Kame Yu.
Huh? I just bought you an
expensive bag the other day.
I want to look at, like, clothes today.
Watch it, dumbass!
Pay attention to where you're walking, moron.
He's super creepy.
He's not even gonna apologize
after running into someone?
Forget him. Come on.
I know. You just wanna go to Kame Yu, right?
Huh?
Anjuro Katagiri, a.k.a. Angelo.
Born in Morioh in 1964.
His IQ is 160.
He was sent to juvie for robbery
and rape when he was just 12.
Since he committed that first crime,
he's become the most awful
and disgusting criminal in Japan's history.
He spent most of his youth in jail for his crimes,
a total of 20 years by the time he'd turned 34.
His last crime was so vile, it'd make
even a rat in the bathroom puke.
He was eventually arrested,
and the sentence they gave him
was death.
But, somehow, the execution failed to kill him.
Shortly after, Angelo escaped.
He most likely became a Stand
user right before his execution.
I'm not sure why,
but he's hiding out in this quiet town...
Somewhere.
Koichi, you heading home?
Oh... Yeah.
We're in the same class.
Yeah... Talk about coincidences.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Ah... Hey! J-Josuke!
Huh?
Oh, you want to hear what
that Jotaro guy has to say?
It's been bugging me,
and it has to do with this town.
You're amazing. I'm gonna pass.
Why?
I'm sort of curious,
but when I thought it through,
I don't think getting involved with being
some guy's lovechild is a good idea.
Why?
Well, I mean...
Things are just fine as they are right now.
I see...
I wonder what that is.
Maybe an accident or something?
Wanna go after it?
Yeah.
What? Are they shooting a drama?
It's dangerous, so step back. Step back!
Talk about a huge commotion.
A man robbing that convenience store
took a female employee hostage inside.
Huh?
Look! There he is!
Don't move! Drop the knife!
Let the girl go!
Shut up! Get back!
Th-That lady has rung me up before!
His eyes are messed up.
He'll totally kill her if he loses it.
All of you, get outta the way!
I'm getting into the car!
This isn't good, Josuke! Get back! Back!
R-Right.
Hey, you with the stupid hair!
Sorry, let us step back—
I told you to get away from the car!
I'll kill you!
I have...
a bad feeling about this.
I knew it!
Loom
C-Crap! Here it comes!
At a time like this? In this situation?
After Mr. Jotaro warned him!
Who's that?
H-Hey! Stop!
What did you just say?
Wh-Who the hell are you? Get away from me.
You don't care what happens to her?
Get back, you fool!
What are you going to do if he loses it?
I told you guys to stay back, too!
D-Damn it! You're pissing me off!
I've made up my mind! I'm gonna stab this girl!
Oh, really?
Th-There's a hole in his body!
I pissed you off?
That's my line!
Huh? I-I'm fine?!
She's back to normal. It's happening again.
M-My army knife! It's inside my stomach!
H-How?!
You'd better get a surgeon to take
that out... in the prison hospital.
S-Seize him!
What's going on?
Josuke!
Hey, Koichi.
Are you okay?! That was...
What the...
What are you doing, opening your mouth?
Who would have thought
I'd find another Stand user here?
I possessed this man and was having
a blast with that robbery, and then...
How dare you get in my way?!
He's the guy from the picture!
I'll be watching you from now on.
I'll be watching you all the time.
What'd you say, you bastard?!
Josuke!
You idiot! Get him!
What were you thinking?!
M-Mr. Officer! W-Wait a sec...
What Mr. Jotaro said was true.
Let me go! I didn't do anything!
There's something in this town...
I can feel the presence of
something completely unknown.
Something bad is here in Morioh.
Hey, Josuke! Answer the phone!
Josuke! Answer the damn phone!
Yeah, yeah. One sec.
Hello?
It's Jotaro.
Oh, hi.
We didn't have a chance to
actually talk yesterday.
We need to talk about the
guy hiding in this town.
Oh, I actually wanted to
talk to you about that.
Mr. Jotaro, where are you right now?
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
What happened?
Well...
Damn it, this pisses me off.
Where the hell did I put the shovel?
That little brat...
Looks like he's got a cozy little family.
Not to mention he's got himself
a hot, young mother...
I'm jealous.
Josuke Higashikata, don't get cocky, now.
I'm going to destroy your livelihood,
your soul, and your life.
Episode 2
Josuke Higashikata! Meets Angelo