Budogaoka
Bank
Great Year-End
Lottery
Congratulations on your entry.
You've come just before the expiration date,
but you've indeed won the
third place prize, five million yen.
Now, then... Here you go.
This is the promissory note
for five million yen.
Morioh Station Branch
As it states on the paperwork,
you'll be able to cash it in three days.
Promissory Note
Budogaoka Bank   Morioh Station Branch
Total
Please pay the amount stated above
in exchange for this promissory note.
One, ten, hundred, thousand...
Th-There are six zeros...
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 19    Shigechi's Harvest, Part 2
Now, I do have one question...
Reception Office
From which vendor did you
gentlemen purchase this ticket?
Sniff, sniff.
Wh-Which?
Wh-Why do you want to know that?
Oh, it's just a formality.
You stupid little brats.
You won five million yen? That's too fishy.
I'm a very capable bank associate,
and I smell something rotten here.
Or perhaps
there's a reason you'd rather
not answer that question?
W-Well, of course we bought it in Morioh.
Oh? Well, that's bizarre...
There isn't a single lottery vendor in Morioh.
O-Oh, right...
It must have been when we went to S City.
We bought all kinds of things,
so I don't remember that well...
I-I-I-I-I-It was a while back, too...
I just realized something bizarre...
On the other side of the lottery ticket,
there's a place to write your name
and telephone number, and...
Ichiro Morishita
Ichiro Morishita...
The name written here doesn't
match any of your names.
N-Name?!
Phone number?!
That was written on the back?!
E-Er...
Well, well, well, well, this is truly bizarre.
This is your lottery ticket, isn't it?
Oh, yeah! Now I remember!
I wrote down my friend's number
on that instead of a memo pad!
Oh! Is that so?
Then how about we give
Mr. Ichiro Morishita a call?
We can also tell where
lottery tickets are purchased
with the serial number here.
If Mr. Ichiro Morishita was the
one who purchased this ticket
and remembers exactly where he bought it,
we'll then have to check this signature, too...
To see who this ticket belongs to.
Depending on the situation, we may
have to turn it over to the police.
The police?!
Hello? This is Morishita.
Hello, I'm calling on behalf of Budogaoka Bank.
I wanted to inquire if Mr. Ichiro Morishita
had purchased the Great
Year-End Lottery ticket.
Oh, I'm Ichiro Morishita,
and yes, I bought one.
Yeah, I'm sure I bought one.
Yes! You stupid little brats!
My sense of smell was correct!
There's no way God would grant
brats like you the winning ticket!
Morishita
So you did! You bought a lottery ticket.
Yeah, I did.
Morishita Ichiro
But I bought like, ten, and
none of them were winners.
I'm going to change just part of the signature...
Kinoshita Ichiro
You see, Mr. Kinoshita, your lottery ticket...
Kinoshita? My name's Morishita.
Huh? But it said "Mori"!
What? How strange...
Your phone number is 1771-1281,
correct, Mr. Kinoshita?
I told you my name's not
Kinoshita, you dumbass!
It's Morishita!
Why are you wasting my time with this?
I threw them all away.
Why don't you sell some
winning tickets sometime?
P-Pardon me...
J-Just wait, you!
The number you are trying to
reach is currently not in use.
Please confirm the number and try again...
A-Are you satisfied?
I-I-I'm terribly sorry for my rudeness.
Yay! It's my money!
I won this five million yen!
Hey, you promised that half
of it would be ours, Shigechi!
Did I say that?
You're doing that again?!
Hey, Josuke! Why are you stopping me?!
You're not gonna let him get
away with it again, are you?
No... This time, I'm not backing down, either!
There's no way you're getting away with this!
Well said, Josuke!
Of course you wouldn't back down!
It's only logical!
So now you don't want to
split the money, Shigechi?
You realize this amount is way too
much for that to fly, don't you?
Here.
This should be enough for you guys.
You didn't really do anything, after all.
I'll take pity on you
because you're my friends.
Crush
Why, you—
Hey, Okuyasu!
Give us the money, you dumbass!
You promised us half,
so you're going to give us half!
Stop being greedy, you idiot!
You're always so quick to hit. Don't be rash.
When dumbasses don't get what you're saying,
this is how you make them understand!
Are you hurt?
I'm sorry Okuyasu suddenly hit you.
But, Shigechi, let's not cause any trouble.
We're gonna hold onto the promissory
note for the five million.
In three days, when it becomes cash,
let's split it evenly in half, like we discussed.
But, man, he's ridiculous.
I'm done hanging out with him.
But you know,
I think we should reflect on the fact
that we thought about using him
to get some pocket money, too.
You dummy.
Huh?
I'm not gonna think of it like that.
The only reason he was able to get
the five million was because of us.
If it was him alone, he could only
get maybe tens of thousands.
But he's getting 2.5 million on his own.
2.5 million!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes!
Like I'll give it to you.
Like I'll give it to you!
I heard everything, damn it!
I won't give you guys even one yen!
We got that five million
because of my Harvest!
You're no match for my Harvest!
You wanna see proof?
You want to see some solid proof?
I'll show you!
Ow!
Bastard!
No! The promissory note for the five million!
You're underestimating us, you little punk!
If you keep chasing me,
I'll kill you.
Shigechi...
You're gonna kill us, you backstabbing bastard?
You'd better be prepared to die if you're
gonna bring out your Stand against us!
W-Wait, Josuke...
What's wrong?
What's this sensation?
M-My legs...
are itching really bad.
Itching? At a time like this?
They itch really bad!
My whole body itches!
Wh-What is this?!
Lift up your pants, Okuyasu! Hurry!
What?!
They're inside my pants!
I-It's no use!
Knocking off two or three of
them won't damage him at all!
Damn it!
He's running away!
I-I'm starting to get really pissed off.
I've already been super pissed off!
We're not letting you get away, five million!
Now he's totally made enemies
of the Okuyasu-Josuke duo!
Shi
Shin
Shinin
Shining
Shining D
Shining Di
Shining Dia
Shining Diamo
Shining Diamon
Shining Diamond
Jo
Josuke
Josuke Higashi
Josuke Higashikata
Damn it! How dare he make a
fool of the great Okuyasu?!
I'm gonna beat him to death!
He must be really dumb to be greedy enough
to take the whole five million.
You stupid fatty!
You think you can run with a body like that?!
See? That's what you get, moron!
H-He keeps summoning Harvests under
him like a caterpillar track,
or like a bucket relay!
What the hell? He's ridiculously fast!
He may be a simpleton, but he's pretty clever.
Are they like his natural instincts?
Crap! We're gonna lose him!
Calm down.
We just need to
have our Stands lift our bodies in
the same way he is, and climb up!
I get it!
My five million...
You actually think you can
get away from us, Shigechi?
Bring it on!
I'll carefully pop your Harvests, one by one!
My Harvest is amazing.
It'll gather anything!
Even screws holding pipes together.
Even bolts!
If you want to talk about amazing,
there's also my Shining Diamond!
Heya.
I'm still super pissed off, but right now,
I'm still willing to forgive you.
I'll just hit you two or three times!
Come on, give us the promissory note
for the five million, Shigechi.
I told you...
If you came after me,
I'd kill you.
Wh-What?
My hands...
That hurt...
I can't stand! Okuyasu, be careful!
He did something to me!
O-Okuyasu, you too?
You still haven't figured it out?
You guys are drunk!
A-Alcohol?!
Liquor
My harvest gathers anything!
It brought some alcohol
from the liquor store earlier,
then injected it into your bodies!
Right into your veins!
Wh-What?!
You bastard!
When you inject alcohol into your veins,
even a tiny amount will get you really drunk!
C-Come to think of it,
I've heard that alcohol is in the
same group as anesthetics...
Th-That bastard... m-might be pretty smart...
Or it might be his natural instincts.
I-I'm gonna murder him!
There's no way we're gonna lose
just because we're drunk!
M-My eye!
Josuke, hurry and fix it!
W-Wait, Okuyasu!
You guys had the nerve to
call me unreasonable and other
things earlier, didn't you?
I'll show you what happens
when you underestimate me!
D-Damn it!
You have the nerve to get cocky after
you're the one who broke your promise?
I'm seriously going to get pissed off!
There's no telling what I'll do then!
Shut your stupid mouth, Josuke!
Your Stands' powers are nothing!
You guys are useless!
Make demands once you have
even half of Harvest's power!
Josuke, close your eyes!
Josuke!
Damn, so close!
But it's no use closing your eyes.
Harvest can get anything!
It can rip off your eyelids
and pry out your eyeballs!
All right, Shigechi, stop!
Forgive us already! It was all our fault.
Oh? You're apologizing?
Damn it, you little punk!
Oh? Okuyasu, it doesn't seem
like Josuke feels that way.
I-I'll give him a talking-to!
Just let us off the hook with this!
This is the 10,000 yen you gave
me and the rest of my money.
Let us off the hook with this.
Who's going to fix my eye if Josuke gets killed?
O-Okuyasu...
Oh, yeah! I just remembered!
I felt really bad for you guys,
and gave you more than 10,000 yen!
Here, take this, and please forgive us.
I get it, Okuyasu!
Just like baiting a tanuki
with food and catching it,
you're trying to lure him
over with cash to defeat him!
I totally got what you're thinking!
Okuyasu, being honest like that
is very favorable with me.
There, there.
Hey, wait a sec.
Okuyasu, you aren't trying
to trick me by luring me
closer with money so you can attack
me with your Stand, are you?
Ah! So you are!
Did you really think I'd fall for that?
You really thought I was that stupid?
I won't forgive you anymore!
That's fine, if you don't forgive us.
But it's too late.
Don't you realize that you're
already in The Hand's range?
I'm going to scrape away space
and make it
teleport!
We got it back.
Got it back?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'll just easily take it back...
You don't seem to realize, Shigechi,
that you have no chance of winning now.
The five million!
What are you doing?!
Inconceivable! Inconceivable!
Stop!
Why would you do that?!
Inconceivable! Inconceivable!
That's five million yen!
Basically, just try and injure or kill us.
The only one that can fix this
note is my Shining Diamond...
So there's no way you can win.
Oh... I-I see! Conceivable!
And what happens next certifies your loss.
H-Huh? Again, inconceivable! Inconceivable!
Inconceivable! Inconceivable!
What are you doing?!
Pick them all up, Harvest!
Looks like you don't realize that
the fact that you're having
Harvest go pick them up
means that you've lost.
So now who's going to protect you
from these two drunks right here?
Oh, conceivable...
Smash
We did it.
Now, Shigechi...
Why don't we review something very simple?
The one that collects all
the pieces is your Harvest,
and whose Stand is the one that
will put them back together?
Hm?
Who is it?
Who's going to fix it with
their Shining Diamond?
J-Josuke...
Whack
Josuke? Did you just address me so casually?
M-Mr. Josuke!
That's right, it's Mr. Josuke.
But who was the one who just took
back the promissory note from you?
Say his name.
O-Okuyasu...
Mr. Okuyasu!
Well done. That's a good boy.
All right, next, let's do a little calculation.
How should we split the five million?
How would we split it so
that no one feels slighted?
H-Half is fine...
In half?
You realize now that there are
three of us here, don't you?
So isn't half a bit off?
That doesn't really add up at all.
Hello?
I-It'd be a third...
Th-That's right...
If it was just me, I'd only be able to gather.
I-I was wrong.
We all found this lottery ticket.
We wouldn't have gotten it
without the three of us.
I...
I realize that now. I was blinded by greed.
Let's split it up evenly,
so no one is slighted.
Bam
Yes!
B-Bills!
I-It's five million yen!
Please consider depositing it into our
Budogaoka Bank for peace of mind.
Of course!
We finally did it! It's like a dream!
Wait... Splitting it up evenly
so no one is slighted, huh?
Huh? This is weird.
If we're going to split it up evenly,
isn't it unfair if we don't include
the number of Stands we have?
If we consider that my Stand,
Harvest, is about 500,
then we should split it 500 to 1 and 1.
Don't you think so?
You little bastard!
You're seriously going to
argue about this again?
It's never going to end, you dumbass!
O-One third is fine!
Josuke Higashikata – Money Currently in Possession – 1,666,666 yen
It's a bit unforgivable for first-years
in high school to have this much, but...
To be continued!
Episode 20
Yukako Yamagishi Dreams of Cinderella