This building was originally
a 14th-century castle.
It was converted into a hotel
in the early 1900s.
But it closed 10 years ago
when its owner died.
Now Kars has turned it into a shelter
from the sun.
The enemy lurks within.
But JoJo and Lisa Lisa
know nothing of the hotel's layout.
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 21: A Hundred Against Two
Damn it!
What's with the creepy cobwebs?
Clean the place!
We're depressed enough
without these decorations!
But look at this trail of blood.
Wamuu took a heavy beating from Hamon.
Caesar didn't go down without a fight.
We can't let Wamuu recover!
We're going in, Coach Lisa Lisa!
What is it?
W-Well...
T-This doorknob really grossed me out.
It feels like
I'm grabbing some guy's hand.
I'm not a door!
Huh?!
What are you looking for?
I said I'm not a door.
A vampire!
Look out, JoJo!
JoJo!
If it weren't for that weapon,
I'd have peeled your face clean off!
I'm Wired Beck.
I killed my lover,
but escaped from prison.
But then Lord Kars made me
part of his gang with a mask.
He has my loyalty.
I'm not going to let you go in
and disturb Lord Kars's rest.
Those fiends! So they're already
unleashing their hounds upon humans?!
How troublesome.
You're just a pawn
that's bound for hell.
Here, let me give you a little push
into the abyss!
Lisa Lisa?
Beautiful! Magnificent!
Such lovely skin you have!
Hold me! Let me drink your life
through that skin!
I'm in a bad mood.
I don't want to hear from
or look at a worm like you.
But if you want to hold me, just try.
It'll be the last thing you do.
Spikes!
So that's what they are!
They're spikes, not fingers!
He's covered in wire-like body hair!
I don't like it when women
make jokes about me.
Girls who laugh at me get punished!
I'll give you a squeeze!
I'll hug you to death!
Yikes! He's faster than I thought!
Her scarf!
I see. Her scarf
becomes a Hamon-filled weapon.
A scarf?
You want to catch me?
Don't make me laugh!
And now I'm free!
Uh... Wha...?
Where are you going?
Come, JoJo. Let's move.
O-Okay.
Lisa Lisa's movements flow like silk.
She doesn't waste any effort!
Hey, don't ignore me!
Hey, you!
A woman like that
has to be punished, right?
Oh, no, friend. Your time is up.
You're the one who got punished.
You got a dose of Hamon.
Don't be ridiculous!
She's got what it takes!
I thought she'd be weak in a fight,
but she's better than me!
I'm impressed!
She's my coach, after all!
By the way, JoJo...
...you still haven't taken the antidote
Caesar stole for you, eh?
This?
Why?
I'll drink it after I beat Wamuu.
This ring isn't a promise between
Wamuu and me anymore.
It's now a promise to Caesar
to fight and keep living.
Lisa Lisa, will you hold it for me
until I need it?
No.
You should keep it.
Who knows what may happen to me?
As they went deeper,
the trail of blood grew ever thinner.
JoJo and Lisa Lisa were fully aware
what that meant.
Wamuu's wounds were healing.
Are they here?
I've been waiting.
You've grown quite a lot.
Bastard, you killed Caesar!
Calm down, JoJo. Look at the floor.
Don't worry, my head is cool.
I noticed, too. The footprints, right?
There are two sets.
That means Kars is here! Where is he?!
Show yourself!
Yes. Two sets of footprints.
But I feel dozens of lungs breathing.
It's her. I see...
You're quite composed and
perceptive for a woman.
I can see how JoJo and Caesar
learned so much so quickly.
And you can feel even slight breathing.
You're among the finest Hamon warriors.
Wha-What the...?!
You, you're all vampires, aren't you?
Damn it!
No response? That's creepy.
Kars!
Lord Kars gave us, his chosen,
eternal life!
It's 100 against two!
When our master gives the order,
we'll tear you both to shreds, JoJo!
T-This is bad. It's 100 on two.
Lisa Lisa, we can't win this one!
Wait, Lord Kars.
Back in Rome, we promised
to fight each other.
I want revenge for Master Esidisi.
Please allow me to fight.
I shall not.
Our goal is to obtain
the Red Stone of Aja.
Don't forget that, Wamuu.
Yes, lord.
That's right. We can't.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
I know I could beat you.
But even if I did,
all these vampires are still here.
Win or lose, I'd still die, right?
With odds like that,
giving up is only natural.
I'm throwing in the towel.
Blast it! You all saw, didn't you?
And I thought I could
zap them all at once, too.
Now, kill them!
If you kill us,
you'll never have the Stone.
Hold!
What's this, woman?
I'm not stupid enough
to be carrying the Stone here.
If one of us isn't
in a certain place at a certain time...
...the Stone will be destroyed!
Don't try to fool me, woman.
Do you think
you'll be able to find it in time?
The bomb is a small thing,
but is enough to damage the Stone.
Is all this true? She never told me.
I'll just run with it!
Yeah, it's all true!
If we die, boom! Kaboom!
Even so, we can't let you
leave here alive.
I have a suggestion.
JoJo and Wamuu can fight one-on-one.
And Kars,
you and I will fight one-on-one.
And to the winner...goes the Stone!
What?!
The victor will win the Stone
and the future.
It will all be clear.
Who will hold the stone, us or you?
Who will survive?
The Pillar Men or humankind?
Why you...!
Wamuu?
It's laughable, Lord Kars.
S-She's good!
She's a better gambler
than I could even dream of being.
You've got pluck, woman.
Very well. We fight for the Stone.
But don't get cocky!
You have no tomorrow!
She just turned a dire situation
into more-or-less even odds.
All right, then. Let's do it!
We need a proper time and place
for our battle.
Wamuu, your thoughts?
We fight tonight, under the full moon!
The place will be at the foot of
Piz Berlina, 15 km southeast of here.
We meet at the Skeleton's Heel
stone circle.
Many warriors found death
or glory in that place.
A stone circle?
Hey, you can't just pick a place
that suits your fancy!
Wamuu, I think that's a fine choice.
Now, about the Stone...
JoJo!
Bring the Stone to the Skeleton's Heel
at midnight tonight.
And be sure to remove the bomb.
The woman stays here as insurance!
Lisa Lisa!
They don't want us to run.
It's a reasonable request.
Go and fetch the Stone.
Don't worry about me.
Right. I'll see you at the arena.
Trust me.
I do.
Caesar...
Until yesterday,
I lived only thinking of myself.
But a new feeling burns inside me now.
Is this compassion?
Curse it!
I just want to wreck those bastards!
And I'll do it for Caesar, Meshina,
Lisa Lisa and the rest!
I'll fight for you all!
As I thought, there's no bomb at all.
Lisa Lisa, you're deceptive,
even under pressure!
Now, maybe I should bring you
a change of panties, hmm?
What're these photos?
It's Granny Erina!
Why would Lisa Lisa have this?
Who are these people?
May 1889?
It's 50 years old!
This young man is Speedwagon!
Granny Erina!
And Straizo is holding a baby!
Lisa Lisa... I know nothing about
her life or her past.
Why does she have these photos?
It's the real thing.
We accept your bargain.
We'll fight you one-on-one!
You saw the photos.
That means you want to talk, right?
Actually, I had planned to talk to you.
Just who are you?
Fifty years ago...
Erina lost her husband, Jonathan Joestar
on a ship on the Atlantic.
He was your grandfather.
That day, your grandmother
saved a baby girl's life.
That was me.
The baby in that picture is me.
H-Hang on now.
That was 50 years ago!
If you were a baby 50 years ago...
H-Hey! How old are you, anyway?!
Y-You're 50?!
I-If you're 50, that means...
...y-you're old!
Right? Normally...
Y-You look like you're in your late 20s.
They say Hamon energy is life energy
and keeps you young.
But I guess you don't behave
like a young woman should at all.
I think I see a wrinkle
behind those shades!
Just kidding.
Now, prepare the arena!
Light the fires!
There's no time to talk now.
But we do need to.
My roots are connected to yours.
Our roots?
The mask killed my parents.
Since Erina was pregnant
when she rescued me...
...I was raised by Straizo.
A-Are you serious? By Straizo?
Straizo taught me about Hamon.
Straizo gave me the Red Stone.
So S-Straizo is your foster father!
It is tragic that the fear of aging
drove him to such madness.
My feelings about you defeating him
are complicated.
But I feel it was destiny.
What can I say?
I-It is very complicated.
What a bizarre relationship.
Lisa Lisa carries
a past full of sadness.
JoJo, we're out of time.
W-What's the rumbling?
They're here. Now the battle can begin.
T-They're...!
Out of the way!
I don't care if you get crushed!
I-Is that a d-dinosaur?!
N-No, it's a horse!
Lord Kars, Lord Wamuu, please move!
They've gone berserk!
Lord Wamuu, please!
What fine steeds.
We used masks
to turn these horses into vampires.
V-Vampire horses?!
In this arena, JoJo will face Wamuu
in an ancient-style chariot duel!
A chariot duel?!
An ancient Roman death match!
You'll ride through the arena
while you fight!
Lord Wamuu or JoJo? Who will fall
or be beaten down while riding?
Defeat means death!
Those are the rules, JoJo!
The beasts have 150 horsepower!
Even Lord Wamuu can barely control them.
Now wait a minute!
I'll fight you on any field!
But vampire horses
are your minions, right?!
Worry not. The reins conduct Hamon.
Wamuu will use his strength.
You can use Hamon to control them.
I-Is that right? They look vicious!
Don't bite, now!
I see. A little Hamon does it.
Wamuu! Wamuu! Wamuu!
Wamuu chose an ancient form
for this battle.
That means he's serious.
He's not doing this for fun,
or making sport of it.
Beat him, JoJo. We have to win this.
There are no draws!
Wamuu!
I haven't taken this antidote yet!
I promised Caesar I'd drink it
after I kill you!
That promise will give me
power I've never seen before!
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
I ride to battle!
Next episode
Wamuu! Wamuu!
Start!
Chapter 22: A True Warrior