All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 20: Death 13, Part 2
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
Saudi Arabia,
approximately 8,800 kilometers from Japan.
It's been around four weeks since we left.
If we don't hurry, there'll be serious trouble.
Kakyoin...
Hey, Jotaro.
What do you think is up with Kakyoin?
He was flailing around in his sleep on
the plane, and now he looks like this.
He even went after the baby.
Something's wrong with him.
I think he's at his wit's end.
I don't know if he can continue this journey.
I panicked back there, thinking
Kakyoin had figured out who I am...
But now, Kakyoin's half-doubting himself.
And we're in the middle of the desert.
Now, I just have to wait
until they're all asleep.
If there's no one to wake them up...
That smells great. What are you making?
Baby food.
This is milk, egg yolks, bananas,
and bread all stewed together.
Here. Want a taste?
It's good!
I could totally go for this!
Give me more! More!
Hey, now. There won't
be any left for the baby.
You bastard! Don't eat my food!
I'm hungry! Hurry up and feed me!
A—
A scorpion!
Th-This isn't good!
That was close...
C-Crap!
Kakyoin was watching.
He killed the scorpion.
Th-That baby really is...
Sh-Shit!
That's all you get.
Mr. Joestar, Polnareff, did you see that?!
Huh?
That baby isn't normal after all!
He just killed a scorpion!
In the blink of an eye!
He stabbed it with a safety pin!
Kakyoin, hold on.
What are you talking about?
That is not a normal baby!
He's not even a year old,
but knew what a scorpion was...
And he killed it with those tiny hands!
A scorpion?
Where?!
In here!
The dead scorpion on the pin should be in here.
I-It's not here...
B-But it's true!
Where'd you hide it?!
Is it in your clothes?!
We got it, Kakyoin! That's enough! Stop!
Mr. Joestar!
I said this earlier, but you're tired.
Let's talk again tomorrow morning,
after you've calmed down.
Okay, open wiiide! It's dewicious!
Oh? That's strange. I'm sure you're
hungry, but you don't want any?
Say "ah."
S-Stop it!
There's a reason I can't eat right now!
Mr. Joestar! I'm sure of it now!
I don't know where he hid the scorpion,
but he's a Stand user!
And I have the very thing to prove that!
Look at the wound on my arm!
At what it says!
This is a warning.
This must be a wound I got in my sleep.
Oh, my God!
Kakyoin, did you do that to yourself?
Eh?
K-Kakyoin, you've finally...
Oh, my God!
That big idiot!
Didn't you realize that if you showed
them that, they'd think you were a fool?!
D-Did they misunderstand me even more?
A-At this rate... I have no other choice.
I'll have to use force!
Hierophant Green!
Bam
It's no use. He's totally lost his mind.
I-Impossible. I-I'm certain, Jotaro...
His Stand was the one in our dreams, Polnareff.
We can't fall asleep, Mr. Joestar.
Please, believe me. Everyone...
If we fall asleep, we'll be killed.
Please, believe me. Believe in me...
Yes! I got away without being found out!
You guys lose!
You lost to your own disbelief in your friend!
It's my victory, you fools!
I can't believe it...
So Kakyoin can't fight or travel with us anymore?
We'll figure out what to
do with him in the morning.
Let's go to bed.
Polnareff, help me move Kakyoin.
Sure thing.
Jotaro, bring the sleeping bags.
Yeah.
Did you say something?
Not really. He's just heavy.
Now I can slice you all up and scatter
your remains all over the desert!
I see.
Why are we in sleeping bags at an
amusement park, like a bunch of idiots?
That's right!
Th-This is...
Jotaro! Mr. Joestar! Be careful!
I-I remember now.
W-We're inside a dream.
It's terrifying!
This is a world of nightmares!
Oh, so it's just a dream.
Then I'm just gonna relax.
Don't have the same reaction I did!
Listen! What Kakyoin was saying is true!
Baby. Stand.
We're in enemy territory.
I know it's hard to believe,
but the Stand user is that baby!
There's no one to wake you up now.
So there's absolutely no way
for you to escape Death 13's world.
Now I'll finally finish you all.
Since I made Kakyoin pass out,
he should already be somewhere in this world.
We have to find him!
Where are you, Kakyoin?
I have to apologize to him.
P-Polnareff, what's with your hairstyle?
Did you mess up styling it?
Eh?
Polnareff!
Curl
What?
M-My...
My artificial hand!
Pop!
Holy shit!
How are we supposed to fight this?
How?!
A-Anything can happen here.
There are no rules or logic.
It's a world where we're at his mercy!
Wait. There was just one rule.
The thing that'll
slice us into little pieces
is his Stand,
and his Stand alone!
Lali-ho!
Death 13
Manishu Booi
Lali-ho!
Star...
It's no use, Jotaro!
We can't bring our Stands into the dream world!
...Platinum!
Rumble
Th-That's odd... His Stand appeared.
Clank
Lali-ho! I'm a fake!
Loom...
This overwhelming power! This absolute fear!
It's so much fun!
A Stand is spiritual energy.
And dreams are the spirit unguarded!
Death 13 has surrounded that unguarded spirit,
and that's why you can't summon your Stands!
Although...
Whoosh
If you had
summoned your Stands before you fell asleep,
you could have brought them with you,
like the clothes you're wearing,
the sleeping bags, and the artificial hand.
Death 13 will never have to face another Stand!
And the only thing that can
defeat a Stand is another Stand,
so I'll always win!
Now...
How about you give me a scream?
One that symbolizes how happy and
refreshed I feel at my easy victory!
Lali-...ho?
Lali-ho!
Oh, it's just the fake one I made.
Wh-What?!
Impossible!
This one's not a fake!
Crush
This is the real Hierophant!
It's back!
It's Kakyoin!
Kakyoin's right there!
Bam!
When I lost consciousness earlier,
did you forget that I had Hierophant out?
I had Hierophant hide underground
before I fell asleep.
Squish
Help me!
Now, it's time for your punishment, baby.
D-Damn it!
Let go!
Stop, Death 13!
He's completely in your blind spot.
If you keep resisting...
Even if you're just a baby,
your neck will be broken.
Kakyoin!
Kakyoin. We owe you an apology.
I thought you might have become weak-minded.
I couldn't believe in you.
You were fighting this battle alone...
I'm sorry.
No, Polnareff. It couldn't be helped.
I only figured out a way to bring my Stand
with me into the dream after you hit me.
So in a way, this is all thanks to you.
R-Really?
I-I can't help but feel a bit conflicted.
I'm kind of ashamed...
He's holding back because I'm a baby...
Kakyoin, your naiveté will cost your life!
You're still inside my nightmare world!
Hey, what's with the clouds?
The clouds... are moving strangely,
and coming closer!
Don't try anything funny,
Death 13!
Kakyoin! Get Hierophant away from his back!
What?
I'll chop you in half!
I-Impossible!
He chopped himself...
in h-half.
Kakyoin!
Lali-ho!
Didn't you realize it?
Death 13's body is actually hollow!
Death 13 is just the head,
arms, and the giant scythe.
You enormous fools!
Let's see.
Kakyoin's body should also be
split in two inside the sleeping bag.
Just kidding!
Kakyoin!
Y-You're all right?
Please look closer.
My Hierophant isn't so careless
as to stay on his back forever.
He's not chopped in half!
He's taken on a string-like form...
And he's crawling into my ear!
M-My arm is moving on its own...
It's coming in...
Bam
I told you!
He was in your blind spot,
so your scythe couldn't touch him.
Now, if you don't wish to
be destroyed from within...
How about you heal this wound on my arm?
Anything can happen in dreams,
so I'm sure you can heal a cut, right?
R-Right...
All right, everyone. Wake up!
Polnareff, wake up! Breakfast is ready!
I feel like I had a terrible dream...
Same here.
I can't remember it,
but I still feel like it was terrifying.
Kakyoin!
A-Are you all right?
What do you mean?
Wh-What do I...
You were totally deranged last night!
You even carved letters into your arm...
H-Huh?
The wound is gone?
Now, I'll just go change the baby's diaper.
Huh?
Come on, it's morning.
He seems to be getting along with the baby,
so maybe I was just dreaming...
So... Did you sleep well?
Oh, well!
Everyone has forgotten.
A Stand whose existence is completely forgotten...
What a unique Stand.
But I remember.
I'm the only one who brought
a Stand into the dream.
Listen. Because you're a baby,
I won't mortally wound you,
or injure you at all.
We'll take you to a nearby town.
You need to go back to your mother.
But don't ever come near us again.
If you do, I'll punish you.
Just like this...
My poop?
Oh, Kakyoin.
You even made some baby food?
I did.
Let's see. I'm sure you must be hungry by now.
Hey, no... You wouldn't...
Come on, it's dewicious! Open wiiide!
Oh, this again? I wonder what
he's got against this stuff....
At this rate, I'll have to force-feed him.
Stop!
Hey, Mr. Joestar.
If you force him, he'll just hate it more.
In cases like this...
Coochie-coochie-coo... Coochie-coochie-coo...
Coochie-coochie-coochie-coochie-coo...
See? Isn't it delicious?
Ba-dum-tss.
Hierophant Green
Noriaki Kakyoin
Saudi Arabia
Red Sea                                                   Arabian Sea
Egypt
Cairo
Joestar and the others have now
crossed the Arabian Peninsula,
and are currently crossing the
Red Sea, about to enter Egypt.
But!
Hey, old man. Something's not right.
You're going the wrong way.
Shouldn't you be heading directly west, to Egypt?
You seem to be heading toward that island.
Yeah, that's right. I have my
reasons for not telling you before,
but before we enter Egypt, we need to
make a slight detour and meet someone.
He's a man who's extremely
important to this journey.
An important man...?
Next Episode Preview
I'm the one who let Avdol die.
There's no way I can make up for that.
To thank you for freeing me from the lamp...
It's an actual treasure!
...I'll grant you three wishes!
Can you bring someone back to life?
Episode 21
Judgment, Part 1