Jonathan won his battle.
But he lost everything to do so.
I brought him here three days ago.
He's totally alone.
I hope I can give him the will to live!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 4: Overdrive
Spirit! What Jonathan
needs now is spirit!
It's the middle of the night,
but his room is lit.
What's going on?
That woman!
Has she been
attending to JoJo all this time?
Her hands are cracked from
being wet so long.
She must have cooled his burns
thousands of times!
I'm glad.
He's conscious!
You're through the worst of it.
You'll be fine.
You've been treating me?
You...
How could you be here?
You look like...
No, never mind.
It couldn't be.
You really look like her.
Who do I look like?
Erina Pendleton?
It's nice to see you,
Jonathan Joestar.
JoJo...
Erina, you've really grown!
Me? You've grown a lot more!
But...
It really is nice to see you again.
Yeah.
I wasn't cut out for that
sort of work, anyway.
I'll come back later.
Time for Speedwagon to play it cool.
I-I must have fainted.
Oh, dear!
But your arm is broken!
I'll always hold you.
Some people are just fated
to meet each other.
-Whitechapel, London-
You're out playing too late, you harlot!
Most humans are bound
by the laws of good.
They fear the power of evil.
But a rare few are born
unfettered by good...
...the evil elite.
I can use you, Jack the Ripper.
Submit your will to me.
I'll give you wondrous power
and unprecedented pleasure.
You need worry no more.
Only Speedwagon and I know
about the tragedy here.
The police think it was an accident.
But where is the mask?
I didn't find it in the rubble.
I hope it was smashed.
I think it was.
I want to forget all this.
JoJo!
Erina...
Who is he?
He's been following us.
Is something wrong?
No, everything's fi--
Mister Jonathan Joestar.
And the lady is Miss Erina Pendleton.
W-Who are you?!
You did well to survive
against the mask's power!
JoJo!
That's right. Squeeze every bit of air
out of your lungs.
JoJo!
He's injured! How could you?!
He's out of breath,
but there's no need to worry.
W-What on Earth?!
What's happening?
I feel so...
M-My arm!
I am Baron Zeppeli.
Courage alone won't
defeat the mask.
But my arm was shattered!
The pain is mostly gone.
I can even lift this rock!
That's incredible!
W-What did you do to me?!
Who are you?!
One question at a time, please, JoJo.
I did nothing.
Your breathing killed the pain.
Why did you do that to me?
How do you know my na--
H-He's gone.
I said one question at a time, JoJo.
I'll show you the answer.
Follow me.
What you will see
will change your destiny.
I struck your diaphragm with a finger
and altered your breathing.
How did you alter it?
Allow me to demonstrate its energy.
What does he plan to do?
What's happening?
L-Look at the water!
Those ripples are unnatural!
This is the same energy
that removed your pain.
Don't!
T-The frog wasn't hurt!
That was Sendo.
S-Sendo?
Hamon, or ripple energy, creates Sendo.
My Hamon energy went through
the frog's body and split the rock.
JoJo, I know for a fact the mask
is still intact.
Dio, the mask's master, holds it!
What?!
Did you just say Dio?!
I did!
I have sought the mask for decades!
I intend to destroy the mask
and vanquish its owner!
You are destined to fight
against the mask.
You must master Sendo
or face certain death!
And humanity will fall with you!
T-This is...
JoJo, what's going on?
What does he want?
Erina...
I can't let her get involved in this.
Anyone but her...
A-Astounding!
The blossoms!
U-Unbelievable!
The Hamon energy left from healing
his arm revived the blossoms!
This JoJo may be an untapped
wellspring of strength and talent.
This youth may be the one
who can save the world!
My power is slowly returning.
The food chain...
Pigs feed on grass.
Humans feed on pigs.
And we feed on humans.
Humans are our food,
so we are the true masters.
Bon appetit, Jack.
I'll start with a few wicked servants.
Next, the world!
It will all belong to me.
Humanity will kneel at my feet!
-One week later-
I studied Hamon under the tutelage
of the unfathomable Zeppeli.
I knew I had to defeat Dio.
And this is why.
JoJo, let me tell you why
I am hunting the mask.
It started when I was a young
Will A. Zeppeli.
At the time I had a limitless thirst
for the unknown.
I traveled the world as part of
my father's archaeological team.
One day, we were excavating
an Aztec site...
You mean...
That's right. It was my misfortune
to unearth that cursed mask.
On the voyage home, one of our team
donned the mask and chaos ensued.
He tore off the heads of his companions
in a bloodthirsty rampage.
The entire crew of 58 was killed.
I dove into the sea to escape,
but he followed me!
Suddenly, dawn broke!
In the light of the rising sun,
I saw his face.
It was the expedition leader...
...my father.
The ship drifted away
with the mask still aboard.
I was filled with dread
that the power of the mask
might be unleashed again.
I knew I had to find a way to stop it.
That path led me to the ways of Hamon.
Hamon energy comes from the flow
of one's own blood.
The mask drains energy
from the blood of others.
They are two sides of the same coin,
the same energy!
I see!
It's like using fire to fight fire!
Correct. Strike them with enough
Hamon energy, and they will explode.
And the waves created by Hamon...
...are the same as waves of sunlight!
Baron Zeppeli, please teach me
how to use Hamon.
I'll do anything to learn it!
I'll teach you, like it or not.
You will be Dio's first target
in his conquest of the world, JoJo.
Listen, JoJo.
Breathing affects your blood.
Your blood carries oxygen you inhale.
The oxygen in your blood
affects your body's cells.
Your cells are your body.
Like ripples in the water, breathing
properly creates Hamon in your body.
And that creates energy!
His arm suddenly extended!
How did he do that?!
It's called a Zoom Punch.
I dislocated my shoulder and extended my arm!
Hamon energy dulls the pain.
JoJo, do not break the rhythm
of your breathing.
Hamon energy is sensitive
to emotional disturbances.
Yes, sir!
Hey!
Jonathan!
Speedwagon!
We're headed for Wind Knights Lot?
That's right. I confirmed
that someone like Dio is there.
Many have gone missing there recently.
We have no time.
JoJo, your final test will be combat.
Yes, sir. I'm ready to do battle.
Same here!
Here's the entrance to
Wind Knights Lot!
We'll attack while the sun is still up.
I left without saying goodbye to Erina.
I will return to her!
What the...?
Driver, why have we stopped?!
Careful, there's no sun in here!
Hey, driver!
Is it Dio?
Where did he go?
Both of you, step away from the horses.
What in blazes?!
He was hiding inside the horse!
Jonathan, this guy...
This guy is bad news!
He's crueler and crazier than Dio!
So Dio's already gathered evil minions!
Stand aside, you two.
I'll do the fighting.
He's a zombie.
They feed on the living to gain
eternal life.
But they are mere puppets
that must obey their masters.
I'll let you enjoy the most
exquisite terror!
Once the blood has drained
from your faces, I'll drink every drop!
Wriggle in despair, little worms!
Now, what's his next move?
If I were him...
JoJo, this method of thinking is key.
First you must consider the situation
from the enemy's viewpoint.
If I were him, I'd cut off the route
to the sun by blocking the entrance!
He's collapsed the tunnel's mouth!
Jump, Speedwagon!
Here he comes!
H-He's covered in knives!
S-So that's how he
shish-kebabbed the driver.
Hamon Cutter!
My Hamon Cutter is far sharper
than your knives.
JoJo, here's your next lesson.
Think of a flea.
A miniscule insect, right?
Despite their size, they
see fit to challenge towering humans.
Should that be called courage?
I don't believe so.
So what is courage?
Courage must know fear
and make fear its own!
Fear upsets breathing!
Conquer fear and your breath
will never fail you!
Hamon breathing comes from courage!
A good human is a brave human!
Courage is a marvel of humanity!
Though powerful,
zombies do not know courage!
They are just like fleas!
Sendo Wave Kick!
My Hamon energy has disrupted
the zombie's body.
He didn't even spill his wine!
JoJo, you will finish him off.
Destroy his entire brain.
That's the only way to kill the undead.
Time for the slaughter,
you naughty little pigs!
I'll dice you to bits and eat you!
You're really going after him?!
It has to be done.
But JoJo will do it alone.
JoJo.
You must destroy him
without spilling a single drop.
One last lesson, JoJo.
In the land of Norway, they say
the north wind created the Vikings.
Spill a drop and
even if you destroy that zombie...
...I will abandon you.
Listen to yourself!
Have you gone insane?!
You stay out of this!
I'll do it.
The north wind created the Vikings.
It's a labyrinth.
It was made to create confusing
shadows even when lit.
O-Oh, no! The fire!
The light will only make me a target!
But now I have no clue
where he'll come from.
How fragrant!
The smell of fresh blood.
First I have to think like the enemy.
He must be close.
Next, I have to make fear my own.
I will control my breath.
Come! I'll chomp down on your carotid
and pull it out with my teeth!
The harsh wind from the Arctic Ocean
gave birth to the mighty Vikings.
In other words,
challenges can create opportunities.
Will that wine create a Viking?
If not, then Dio has already won.
These ripples! It's Hamon!
So my north wind is this wine!
The wine senses Hamon.
It goes through the glass, my arm,
my body, the ground...
I can feel his vibrations!
The wine is a Hamon detector!
My spirit trembles!
I'm burning up!
I've found you, zombie!
Pierce this wall!
Sendo Hamon Overdrive!
Come here so I can suck your blood!
Sounds like JoJo figured it out.
The north wind has made a new Viking!
Next episode
We meet at last.
I lay my curse upon you!
Can he overcome this delusion?
A duel between heroes!
Dio, I'm ending your madness!
Chapter 5: Knights of Darkness