Man, I'm hungry.
After we visit Big Bro's grave,
let's get something to eat, Josuke.
I'm not hungry.
Italian Cuisine
Trendy
100 Meters to the Left
There's a new Italian restaurant.
Apparently it's just ahead.
Just ahead is the cemetery.
No one would come to eat at a
restaurant in a place like this.
Josuke, I think that might actually
be what brings people in.
The flavor must be like,
"Oh, man! I can't stop drooling!"
Let's go! Let's go!
Is this it?
Trendy
I thought this was an empty building...
Maybe they remodeled it. It looks nice.
What? "Depends on the customer"?
Today's Course
Depends on the Customer
With Coffee & Dessert
From 3,500 yen
The inside looks nice, too!
Welcome.
Episode 10  Let's Go Eat Some Italian Food
Two of you?
Come, have a seat.
Uh... Thanks...
Please.
R-Right...
Um, are you a foreigner?
Si, Signore. I'm Italian.
My name is Tonio Trendy.
Please call me Tonio.
Well, this is great! We get
to eat authentic Italian food!
I have traveled the world.
I've studied various cuisines to
better the cuisine of my motherland.
Then I came to Japan hoping to get my chance.
Morioh is a wonderful place.
There are plenty of farms where
you can get fresh produce,
and the seafood is wonderful, as well.
I love it very much.
Using the ingredients
that Morioh has to offer,
I will bring you food that
will make you feel your best.
Nice! I wonder what I should get.
Could we hurry up and get the menu?
Menu?
We don't have a menu here.
What do you mean you don't have a menu?
Because what I serve depends on the customer.
So show me the menu.
No, no! It means that I will determine
the dishes by looking at the customers.
What the hell?
You mean you're not going to let the
customer eat what they want? Huh?
You had diarrhea last night, didn't you?
Your intestinal walls are inflamed.
And you didn't sleep enough. You only
slept about four hours, didn't you?
No wonder your eyes are so puffy.
Let me see your left hand, too.
Yes, yes... You have athlete's
foot on your right foot.
You have two cavities and your
left shoulder is stiff, right?
H-How do you know all that?!
That's all correct!
By looking at both of your hands,
I know everything about your health.
Oh, I'm sorry!
What about you, signore?
Yeah, I'm not really hungry,
so just coffee is fine.
I'll have a cappuccino.
Ho capito.
Healthy food that concentrates
too much on being healthy
usually doesn't taste good.
If it tastes even a little bad,
we don't have to pay.
We can complain and leave.
Right.
J-Josuke...
This water... No, is this mineral water?
What's up?
I-I've never had water this delicious before!
It's like... water filled with elegance...
It's like the water a princess in the Alps
playing a harp would drink, perhaps.
It's so soothing.
Like the first water you drink after
wandering in the desert for three days.
Y-You're right! This is great!
So good!
Whew
You're right. This is delicious.
What brand of water is this?
Th-This water is so delicious
that I'm about to cry.
Hey, you don't have to cry just
from drinking some water.
Maybe it's because it's so pure.
Do you have a handkerchief?
The tears won't stop.
The tears just keep flowing! It won't stop!
O-Okuyasu! Hey, there's
something wrong with you.
Are you okay?
Gush
O-Okuyasu!
Wh-What the hell's with these tears?!
They just keep flowing!
Okuyasu, y-your eyes, your
eyeballs, the white part...
It's all shriveled up and squishy!
Momento! Please do not panic.
Y-You bastard! What did
you make Okuyasu drink?
Please, calm down! His eyeballs will
only be shriveled up momentarily.
That mineral water is from
snow on Kilimanjaro in Africa
that melted 50,000 years ago.
It's water that flushes out
the inside of the eyeball,
along with any dirt,
and helps relieve insomnia.
The reason you didn't start
crying when you drank it
is because you got plenty of sleep last night.
Josuke!
I'm not sleepy at all now!
I feel refreshed! Like I slept a full ten hours!
Seriously? O-Okuyasu, are you sure
there's nothing wrong with your eyes?
Josuke, when you drink water
this good for the first time,
trust me, you're bound to cry.
I cried even more when I watched
the movie Champ on video.
Really?
Yeah!
Here's your cappuccino.
R-Right...
Now, shall we continue with the meal?
Hey, that looks really good.
Ingredients
• Mozzarella cheese (4 thin slices)
• Tomatoes (5 thin slices)
Tonio's Special Dressing
• 1 Anchovy • Seaweed • Olive oil
• White wine vinegar • Lemon juice • Salt • Pepper • Etc.
• Balsamic vinegar (just a splash) • Toast • Lettuce (for garnish)
(Best eaten within 15 minutes of preparation)
For the antipasto, we have a salad
with mozzarella cheese and tomatoes.
M-M-Mozzaza?
Mozzarella cheese is a soft, fresh cheese
whose fat has been taken out.
Everyone in Italy loves to eat it.
The first people to use tomatoes
in cooking were the Italians.
Nothing can compare to the way
an Italian prepares tomatoes.
This is not bragging. It's merely pride.
Please, help yourselves.
Heck, yeah!
Yeah, that's pretty good.
It's good. Pretty good.
But... I'm not sure what it is, but this
cheese doesn't have much flavor.
No! No!
You need to put it in your
mouth with the tomato.
What? With the tomato?
Well, most foreign dishes don't
suit Japanese tastes.
So good!
Huh?!
The juicy part of the tomatoes
wraps around the mild cheese!
The cheese brings out the tomato,
and the tomato brings out the cheese!
It's like harmony, or like a harmony of tastes!
It's kind of like a Simon and Garfunkel duet!
Ucchan with Nanchan!
The Ashita no Joe that
Tetsuya Chiba drew
with Asao Takamori's original story.
Grazie! I couldn't be
happier that you enjoyed it.
H-Hey, Okuyasu. Let me try a little.
No way.
You should just order some yourself!
There's no way you're getting mine.
I wouldn't give you any even if
you were about to die of hunger.
It's so good! I'm so glad I was born, Mom!
Damn it! I knew you were cheap,
but I didn't know it was this bad!
Fine. I'll order a plate myself.
Ho capito.
However, the only one who will have
his stiff shoulder cured is the
customer right there,
who has the stiff shoulder.
Huh? Stiff shoulder?
C-Come to think of it, my neck feels a bit hot.
It's oddly sweaty.
Sir, I recommend that you take off your jacket.
S-Suddenly...
I-I-I'm getting really itchy!
S-Something slimy is stuck to my fingers!
That would be dead skin.
Dead skin?!
It's proof that your metabolism has
improved and blood is circulating well.
The calcium, vitamins, and minerals
in the antipasto that you just ate
have stimulated the thyroid gland in
your throat that controls your metabolism.
All of your bad cells are
coming out as dead skin.
Keep scratching, and get
all of the dead skin off!
Okuyasu, stop scratching!
It's as big as a softball now!
You're starting to dig at
the muscle in your shoulder!
N-No! You're wrong, Josuke!
It's light!
My shoulder feels so stupidly light!
I feel like there's a balloon on
my shoulder now, it's so light!
Look! My shoulder's so much more flexible!
I've never been able to do this before!
My shoulder isn't stiff anymore!
Now, if you'll excuse me for a bit.
I have to make sure the pasta boils properly.
Holy crap! That Chef Tonio guy is a genius!
N-No...
Something's definitely wrong here!
There's definitely something
strange about his cooking!
Morioh Landmark 3
"Italian Restaurant Trendy"
How to get there: 1 minute on foot
after getting off the bus headed
towardMorioh's Kunimi Mountain
Pass Cemetery
An unusual restaurant with no
set menu. The chef will decide
the menu based on how the
customer is feeling that day.
Because seating is limited, it is
recommended that you
make a reservation.
Now, let's continue with the meal, shall we?
Next is the primo piatto.
This will be your pasta course.
I call it... harlot spaghetti!
Ingredients
• Spaghetti • Pitted black olives
• Olive oil • Anchovies
• Garlic • Red peppers
• Cherry tomatoes
•Misc: Parsley, salt, pepper, etc
•Parmesan cheese
(Best eaten while still hot)
Apparently the name of this dish came from
hard-working ladies of the night
making something random
that happened to be good.
Usually, you don't put cheese
on pasta with garlic,
but this pasta is an exception.
Are there red peppers in this spaghetti?
Yes, there are.
Rome
Naples
The harlot's spaghetti uses a pasta sauce
that is one of the oldest in Italian cuisine.
Spaghetti
Tagliatelle
Linguine
Fusilli
Penne
Farfalle
It was born in my hometown of Naples.
Lasagna
Conchiglie
Tubetti
That is why I recommend this dish.
Oh, well... I can't eat spicy things.
I can't even eat curry rice unless it's
Vermont Curry's mild flavor
with the apples and honey.
I can't eat sushi with wasabi in it, either.
I can't! It's super spicy!
This is way too spicy!
If you can't eat spicy food, Okuyasu,
then don't eat it.
If you can't eat it, don't worry.
I'm perfectly fine with not
charging for that pasta.
I will go make the secondo
piatto, the main dish.
However, my spaghetti is made
such that even people who
do not like spicy things can eat it.
Even if I don't like spicy things?
Hot!
I totally admit that you're
a talented chef, Tonio!
That guy's definitely a genius!
But this was a miss.
No, maybe you were lucky
that you couldn't eat it.
Don't you think this food and
that water are way too weird?
It's too suspicious!
Suspicious? What is?
So hot!
You lost a softball's worth of dead skin,
and you cried your eyes out!
You think so?
When I went to Shirabu
Hot Springs in Yamagata,
I lost even more dead skin,
and my back pain went away!
That much is totally normal.
Hot!
Listen! I just remembered what
that Toshikazu Hazamada said.
Stand users, for some reason,
seem to be unknowingly...
Stand users are drawn to each other!
Josuke!
Are you saying that Tonio
is a Stand user, too?
Shh! We don't know yet!
That's why I'm saying he's suspicious!
Suspicious, eh?
Hot! I can't eat this!
If you can't eat spicy food, stop licking it!
Th-That's right. I can't eat
spicy food, but you know...
I just want to keep licking
this spaghetti sauce.
Why are you eating it?!
I-I know! I shouldn't be able
to eat something this spicy...
But...
I can't help myself. Once I tasted it,
I was sucked in by the spiciness.
It's like when you eat your age
in beans at the Setsubun Festival,
and you don't even really like them,
but before you know it,
you've eaten a whole bag!
Hey, I told you to stop eating that!
M-My stomach's opening up!
The more I eat, the more I want to eat!
It's so good!
Okuyasu, you idiot!
Your tooth! Your tooth just flew out!
That's my cavity! My rotten tooth fell out!
C-Come to think of it, I had a
cavity on my lower jaw, too...
That's a cavity, too!
Your tooth! A molar is
growing in at that speed?!
This settles it. I don't know
what he's plotting, but...
Shining Diamond!
But I wanted to eat more...
I'm going to revert that spaghetti
back to its original ingredients!
What were those little things just now?
A Stand!
Tonio Trendy was a Stand user after all!
Are you all right, Okuyasu?
My sleepiness is gone.
My shoulder stiffness disappeared, and
new teeth replaced my cavities, but...
M-My stomach hurts!
My stomach's hurting so bad!
Wait there!
Tonio! Just what are you plotting?!
Where is he?
So the main course is finished...
Good, good... You're eating that right up.
Looks like the main dish,
lamb in apple sauce, is a success.
What?!
What are you doing there?
You saw, didn't you?!
So you came in here to spy on me?!
You will pay for this! Prepare yourself!
Why do I have to listen to you
threatening to make me pay?
That's my line!
What the hell are you trying
to do with your cooking?!
Okuyasu!
Why are you eating?!
I can't help it! My stomach hurts,
but I can't help eating it!
Every time the tanginess of the apple sauce
and the juice from the lamb goes
down my throat, I feel happiness!
To think a flavor like this
existed in this world!
Don't eat that meat, Okuyasu!
I'm so happy! It's like happiness over and over!
It's so good!
M-My innards...
My stomach!
Okuyasu!
You'll pay for this!
You bastard!
Wash your hands with soap right now!
Medicinal
Huh?!
It's unforgivable!
Entering the kitchen without
permission is unforgivable!
You! The kitchen must stay clean!
S-Soap? Are you telling me to wash my hands?
Hey, Josuke!
My guts suddenly feel way better!
I feel really full, too.
I feel totally satisfied.
Huh?!
My diarrhea tummy's all better!
What?!
Good for you.
Nothing brings me more joy and
happiness than a customer who
enjoys my cooking and becomes healthy.
The puppy...
This dish was a little iffy,
so I was having him taste it first.
His tummy was a little upset, too.
Y-You... seriously only wanted
to feed Okuyasu good food?
What else could a chef ask for?
That is what I live for. That is all I hope for.
You're a Stand user, aren't you?
We are, too.
Oh, I cannot believe it!
When... When I went around the world
looking for what my ideal cooking would be,
that's when I realized my powers.
This is the first time I've met
anyone else with similar powers.
But you! You lack common sense!
Huh?
You touched things without
washing your hands, didn't you?!
The number one enemy in a kitchen is germs!
That's why I got angry!
H-Huh? I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean it!
You'd better prepare yourself!
Now, let us continue with the cooking.
Dessert is... flan?
But I'm a street punk!
Hmph! Me eating flan is laughable.
So good!
You really are a genius!
I'm so proud to live in Morioh,
where a chef like you lives!
Damn you, Okuyasu!
It appears that he's pleased.
You! Your hands aren't moving!
This is so pathetic...
Hey, my athlete's foot is all better!
Please come again. Grazie!
Trendy
P
Po
Pole
Pole J
Pole Ja
Pole Jam
To
Toni
Tonio
Tonio T
Tonio Tr
Tonio Tre
Tonio Tren
Tonio Trend
Tonio Trendy
You're Jotaro Kujo, right?
I'm with the Speedwagon Foundation.
Apparently, anywhere near
electrical wires is dangerous,
including phone lines and power lines,
so I came to deliver this message myself.
"I should be arriving at
Morioh's port tomorrow at noon.
From Joseph Joestar."
Episode 11
Chili Pepper, Part 1