Leone Abbacchio became a police officer
after graduating from high school.
This was due to his strong sense of justice.
But soon after he became a
police officer, his lifelong dream,
Abbacchio realized there were many
contradictions that came with this job.
The police were supposed to
risk their lives to save others,
while those very people they
were risking their lives to protect
were the ones who were stealing,
injuring others in hit-and-runs,
Hey, you two!
and throwing rocks at police cars,
breaking their windshields.
Honey!
Are you all right?
Hey, you!
You're a cop, aren't you?!
The masses were unappreciative,
demanding, and irresponsibly
discredited and insulted the police,
asking, "What are the police even doing?!"
Even if the police risked their lives to
arrest criminals who were lower than scum,
"Serial Burglar Isacco Finally Arrested!"
"A Whole Group Wiped Out"
the law for the masses was rather
lenient as long as they had money,
"Isacco Released
on 70 Million Lire"
"Victims Furious"
and they would be released.
Quit causing us so much trouble.
My bad.
It doesn't matter now.
We just have to find more people to rip off.
Eventually, Abbacchio started to
learn from these contradictions.
Come on, Officer.
Cut us some slack.
That girl's father is swimming
in debt, so she needs the cash.
It's not like we're hurting anyone.
Hey, are you done yet?
I've got a client waiting.
I know, I know.
Even if I were to arrest them,
they'd just post bail and be released.
The only difference is they pay either
me or the court and their lawyers.
You're a very passionate man,
and a very passionate police officer.
One night, they received a report
that a shop was being robbed.
Abbacchio! Go around the back.
Freeze! You're under arrest!
H-Hey, it's you.
Looks like I messed up.
You're...
He's been shot in the head.
Hey, couldn't you just pretend
that you didn't see me?
Come on, let me go.
I won't cause you any more trouble.
No! You're under arrest!
Come on, think this through...
If I get arrested, the fact that you took
a bribe from me will get out, too.
That gun's really dangerous...
Could you point it somewhere else?
Abbacchio! He has a gun!
Ow! It hurts, God damn it!
I'm gonna die...
I'm really gonna die...
That moment was the end of Abbacchio's future.
Not only was he charged
for being a dirty cop,
but he allowed his partner to
die because of his actions,
and that was a cross he'd have
to bear for the rest of his life.
It was then that his body and
soul plunged into darkness.
No matter who died, or even
if he lost a limb or two,
his heart would probably
never be moved again.
Abbacchio, wasn't it?
Episodio 06  Moody Jazz's Counterattack
You can solve the mystery, right?
I'm counting on you!
Giorno!
What the hell are you doing?!
Roar
G-Giorno!
Giorno's in trouble!
Giorno Giovanna...
You're one crazy bastard.
All this to prove yourself...
What the hell is wrong with you?
Y-You bastard...
Th-This Stand...
Use your Golden Wind to defend yourself!
I-Impossible!
Giorno... Where are you?!
Don't go down there, Bucciarati.
Actually, stay back.
It's not that I trust Giorno
Giovanna as one of us,
but Giorno seems to believe
that you won't abandon him.
He does some pretty crazy shit.
Giorno Giovanna...
What if that had actually killed you?
So, again, Bucciarati, don't go down there.
Th-That fly...
Narancia's shoe...
Giorno's powers haven't disappeared yet.
Does that mean Giorno's alive?
They're here, Bucciarati!
Narancia and the enemy are below deck!
Zipper Man!
Narancia, Fugo, Mista, and Giorno aren't here!
Maybe they're right under where the fly is.
It's just like Giorno said.
The enemy's not just hiding in some
locker or behind something to attack...
Hey. The fly's coming around now.
That's strange...
Where is the enemy going?
How and where is the enemy hiding?
Regarding this enemy's abilities...
I hate to admit it, but it looks like I'll
have to accept what Giorno was saying.
I'll use my Stand to solve this mystery!
But... This spot's bad news, Bucciarati!
Moody Jazz!
Does Narancia from five minutes ago work?
Yeah. That should be fine.
Is the fly all right?
It's heading toward the bow.
Now's our chance. Do it quickly.
Yeah.
What's that noise?
His headphones.
Five minutes ago, Narancia was
listening to his boombox.
Huh? What's wrong with this thing?
It just stopped working!
Why'd it stop?
This isn't it.
I just bought it!
Narancia was attacked a little after this.
Damn it! How dare he sell
me something like this?!
I'll try fast forwarding and searching.
That stupid old guy from the electronics
store is gonna regret this!
That ten billion now belongs to us!
With that money, we can
claim the rank of capo!
A-Awesome!
Where is it?
That was my voice.
Where'd you hide that kind of
fortune on Capri, Bucciarati?
It was right after this conversation
that Narancia was attacked!
I can't tell you that yet.
We'd better be able to see just how
he was attacked, Abbacchio.
My Stand replays everything.
We'll be able to see everything,
from Narancia's sweat to his pulse.
And it'll follow him everywhere.
It's about time.
Let's get behind Narancia.
He's about to be attacked!
L-Look! It's the same wound Giorno had!
Roar!
It's coming!
Th-This is...
He's deflating like a balloon losing air!
Mario Zucchero
Tender Machine
Air is leaking from his wound, deflating him.
Looks like we know what
the enemy's abilities are now.
He's being pulled in!
Pause it, Abbacchio!
I see... So he's inside the pipe.
This is the answer to our mystery.
His nails, flesh, and bones are
all floppy like a condom,
even his shoe and his belt buckle,
but he still has a pulse.
Just like Giorno said, he's alive.
So that's what's going on...
The enemy is also doing this to his own body,
hiding in pipes or between the planks or walls,
and he's dragged in Mista,
Fugo, and Giorno, as well.
That explains why Giorno's fly
can trace the general area,
but can't pinpoint exactly where they are.
We figured out the enemy's ability.
Now all we have to do is chase the enemy,
find out where Narancia and the
others are and save them,
and then beat the shit out of the guy.
I'm resuming Moody Jazz's replay.
Chase? Wait a second, Abbacchio!
While you're replaying, you can't attack or
defend yourself. You're totally defenseless!
It's dangerous to go into the pipe.
I know exactly where Moody Jazz is going.
When that bastard is near, use your
zippers to open the floor and get him!
We can't defeat the enemy if we
don't chase him, Bucciarati!
It went left.
That's where he got Mista.
Moody Jazz is going right
underneath that ring buoy.
It's going around toward the cabin
where it got Fugo and Giorno.
So the enemy is moving them around
while keeping them captured.
It's moving much slower...
That's where the bastard
was hiding earlier.
On the inside of that rope fastener!
The enemy's right below the deck there!
The enemy's coming for us.
I'm not sure if he knows that
we know his ability, but...
Bring it on!
The pipes! Cut through them
and get them outta there!
Zipper Man!
Th-They're not there!
Where's the enemy, Abbacchio?
Where's your Moody Jazz? Where are they?
Right there.
It's my Stand. I know where it is.
It's right around there.
Right around where?
I'm telling you, right where you opened up!
My Moody Jazz is definitely right there!
Where are they?
Impossible... It's definitely right here.
Does this mean there's a mystery
we haven't solved yet?
This isn't good!
Undo the replay and call your Stand back!
I already did.
Something's wrong...
What wall is this?
Where the hell are you?
Did you hear that, Bucciarati?
That's the sound of the inside of a pipe.
We can't see it, but Moody Jazz
is definitely right there...
inside the pipe.
What are you doing?
The enemy's right there!
The pipe's wide open, but it's in the pipe...
It's coming closer...
So it's right here...
We need to run!
Run?
That Giorno Giovanna, whom I hate,
told me to solve this mystery.
He's an annoying little brat,
but I'm going to solve it!
Abbacchio...
It's coming!
There's one more mystery
surrounding this enemy.
I'm finally starting to see it.
I'll solve this and kill that bastard!
That awkward feeling I got
when I saw the mast...
Back then...
Bzzzzzz
It's right there! Call back your Stand!
I've figured out the other mystery!
Abbacchio...
Kill him... Bucciarati!
This mystery...
The place the enemy's hiding...
You're being dragged in! Grab on to me!
Damn it!
He's not there...
Where did he go?
What?
You bastard...
Where did you take Abbacchio?!
He's not in the cabin or
the drainage pipe...
Where are you hiding
Abbacchio and the others?!
The fact that there are
seagulls flying around...
must mean we're getting close to shore.
Looks like you're finally
all alone, Bucciarati.
You bas—
Oh, hang on one sec.
Ah, ah, ah!
I'm the one who's gonna
do the talking here.
Shut your trap until I tell you
to answer my questions, damn it!
Very good.
I can finish you off at any time,
and your crew is still alive,
but in suspended animation.
You should be grateful.
I could've killed them and
thrown them into the sea,
all chopped up nicely so the
fishies could eat them easier.
Depending on your actions, I may even
consider turning your crew back to normal.
All you have to do is tell me
where Polpo's secret fortune is!
Are you from Passione?
You really...
don't get it at all.
I'll murder you, you little shit!
Listen up! All you're allowed
to say is where the money is!
Just try and utter any other word
from that asshole of a mouth!
For every word you say,
I'll kill one of your friends!
Say, "What?" and I'll kill them!
Stay silent, and I'll kill them!
If I find out you're lying later,
I'll kill them again!
Got it?
Speak cautiously and very carefully.
Now, then, let me ask you...
Where's the money hidden?
Black-tailed gulls.
Sorry, where?
Those aren't seagulls.
They're black-tailed gulls.
How do you tell them apart?
The ones that sound like they're
meowing are black-tailed gulls.
You called them seagulls, but you were wrong.
They're black-tailed gulls.
I'm gonna kill one now!
Just try it! Better hope you
don't get dragged down!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
I didn't punch the deck earlier
to find where Abbacchio was.
It was to put a hole in
the bottom of the boat.
A h-hole?!
Abbacchio figured out where you were,
and he was kind enough to show me...
where you are and how to know for sure.
It was Abbacchio's blood.
Abbacchio intentionally hurt his hand
and showed me the blood trail.
The blood trail didn't
go down below the deck!
It was cut off right on the deck!
So what does that mean,
and where was he dragged to?
I rented the yacht that was on the left.
Abbacchio realized that when
he looked up at the sky.
I know where you are,
so if you don't wanna drown,
you'd best come out.
There were two boats!
Bwaaaaa
You bastard...
You were hiding by thinly covering
this yacht with another one.
You were traveling through the thin gap
between them and attacking us from there.
No wonder we couldn't figure it
out. You get points for that.
Stay back, Bucciarati!
I'll kill your friends!
You should know better than anyone that
you couldn't survive in a gang if a measly
little threat like that scared you.
Give up, and I'll forgive you.
But the moment you stab Abbacchio...
I will end your life.
Fwip
It's just as Giorno said.
The fact that you had to hide
to attack is your weakness.
You're way too slow.
Pop
Abbacchio!
Well done...
Abbacchio,
what's important isn't the end result.
It's how you get there.
Join my team.
Don't die bound by your past.
Episodio 07
Six Bullets Appears, Part 1