July 15th (Thurs)  8:30 PM
This isn't good... This isn't good at all!
I need to let Yoshikage know!
Reimi!
You took this picture, Rohan?
Yes, why?
This one is marked. Is there
something wrong with it?
The one you have circled looks a little boy.
Hayato Kawajiri
Oh, him...
It's nothing, really.
He seemed to be snooping around,
so he caught my attention.
But this boy, Hayato Kawajiri, has the
same last name as this man here.
Huh? Really?
Look!
Kosaku Kawajiri
It's the same.
You're the one who
researched this, aren't you?
They do have the same last name.
At this rate, Rohan Kishibe will
find his way to Yoshikage!
July 15th (Thurs)  8:48 PM
Hayato? Hayato!
Ugh...
Hayato, I've been calling you!
You can at least answer me!
D-Darling...
I thought it was Hayato in the bath.
I mean, look at this!
Hayato left his clothes in the hallway
as if they exploded off of him.
Unlike you, no matter how many
times I warn him, he's such a slob.
And he's not answering me again.
I'm sure he's probably got his
headphones on, reading manga again.
Oh! Darling, your fingers are bleeding.
What happened?
We need to put a bandage on it.
I-I'll do it myself.
I can apply a bandage myself.
Okay...
I just got my fingers caught
in the door, that's all.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
July 15th (Thurs)  8:50 PM
Hayato Kawajiri?
Are you saying this grade-schooler has
something to do with Yoshikage Kira?
Episode 35    Bites the Dust, Part 1
We're not 100% sure yet,
but Rohan-sensei said
something bugs him about it.
True, there's something wrong if he's
secretly taking videos of his dad.
So, tomorrow morning,
we're thinking of meeting up
and going to visit Hayato Kawajiri's house.
Apparently, Rohan-sensei's
already found the address.
That bastard Rohan sure works fast.
All right. I just have
to invite Okuyasu, right?
And of course, there's Jotaro, too.
I'll talk to Jotaro.
All right. See you tomorrow at 8:30 AM
at the intersection with the Pepsi sign.
Got it.
8:30, huh? I'm gonna be late for school.
But if we talk to this kid,
we might find something out.
Are you okay?
You're acting a bit strange, darling...
And you look pale.
I told you, it's nothing.
I caught my fingers in the door.
Can you blame me for being pale?
More importantly, can you make me some tea?
I'll be down soon.
Of course.
This just came to me out of the blue,
but lately, I can't help but
think that you're immortal.
I'll go make you that tea now.
If something happens to me,
your secret's going to be found out!
Don't you lay a finger on me or my mom!
This isn't a deal!
You have to listen to me! Got it?!
You're too naïve!
Do you really think I would allow that?
I can't believe you actually
got rid of Hayato.
What a stupid thing to do.
I'm trying to think of what to do right now.
It's no use thinking about it.
I see you made it look like
he fell and hit his head,
but the timing was unfortunate.
That Rohan Kishibe has started
investigating Hayato Kawajiri.
They're still not positive
that Kosaku Kawajiri is you,
but they're coming to
check this house tomorrow.
It's a bad idea to stay in this house any longer.
Shut up. I'm thinking right now.
Ever since you were a child,
when things didn't go your way
and there was nothing you could do,
you would always bite your nails.
You poor thing.
You must be in so much despair right now.
There's no other way around it.
You're going to have to
leave this town, Yoshikage.
If you go now, you can escape to someplace
they can't follow you, before they find out.
Are you telling me to flee Morioh?
You know very well that I'm done
with living my life in fear,
having to worry about
someone coming after me!
I will never leave this town.
What?!
The arrow acted on its own!
I didn't do anything!
I didn't even touch the arrow!
Th-The arrow...
Y-Yoshikage!
Hayato! Hayato?!
July 16th (Fri)  7:30 AM
Are you planning to sleep all day, Hayato?
Hurry up and wake—
What, you're already
awake? That's a surprise.
Hayato, breakfast is ready.
Honestly, why don't you ever answer me?
I couldn't sleep very well last night.
He... He found out that
I saw him kill someone.
Anyway, I made sure that he
wouldn't be able to lay a finger
on me or Mom, but...
What should I do now?
I-I don't understand...
What happened, Yoshikage?
You've been acting strange since last night.
Listen to me, Yoshikage!
That Rohan Kishibe has started investigating
Hayato Kawajiri for some reason!
They're going to come
check this house tomorrow.
There's no need to worry.
B-But, Yoshikage!
Deadly Queen has gained a third ability.
I... I don't understand.
What could have happened
to make you so carefree?
-Morioh's Very Own-
Miso-stewed Cow Tongue
Miso-stewed cow tongue.
What? No way! We're on the air already?
Er, um... It's now 7:55, so here's
the weather today for the prefecture.
Today should be sunny.
Hayato! Hey, Hayato! Answer the phone.
After that bath last night, he changed.
Wh-What could have happened?
Hayato! I asked you to answer the phone!
Crash
My precious tea set!
This is all your fault!
Why do you always ignore me?!
Fine! You think your mother's
just a bother, right?!
Do whatever you want, then!
Now, now. Let's not fight
first thing in the morning.
If it broke, I'll just buy you another one.
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
No, it's not.
They had the wrong number.
Hayato's just at an age where
he doesn't want to talk much.
We're family, so we all need to get along.
You know, get along.
Well, I'll head off to work now.
Do you mind if I give you a goodbye kiss?
Huh?
I'll be off now.
H-He left...
No, I'm right here.
Why don't we walk together part of the way?
Going from feeling refreshed
to falling into despair...
So much has happened lately.
I've been on an emotional roller coaster.
But now I'll be able to feel at ease.
Since you cornered me last
night, I was able to mature.
Really, your will last night was so strong.
To think that you would actually turn
around and threaten me, Yoshikage Kira...
Y-Yoshikage Kira?
Did I just say my real name?
A-Are you planning to kill me after all?
Kill you?
Because you found out my secret?
There's no need for that.
Because I've matured.
No matter where you go and
what you do with anyone,
it doesn't matter, because
now, none can rival me.
I have no interest in you anymore.
If I wanted to kill you...
I would have gotten rid of you last night.
From now on, we're all going to get
along and live happily together.
So just relax... Like we're family.
Well, I have to head to the station.
Make sure you study hard, Hayato.
Rival... He just said none can rival him...
Which means there must be others
that have the same kind of abilities as him.
But what's with that creepy confidence?
If he's unrivaled now, does that mean
he's gained some other abilities?
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
You're...
Hayato Kawajiri-kun,
aren't you?
De
Dead
Deadly
Deadly Qu
Deadly Que
Deadly Quee
Deadly Queen
Ko
Kosaku
Kosaku Kawa
Kosaku Kawajiri
July 16th (Fri)  8:24 AM
I've been waiting for you.
My name is Rohan Kishibe.
There's something that I wanted
to ask you out of curiosity.
It's about this picture.
This is you, right?
Were you taking video of your
dad in the corner there?
Wait.
What... is this?
Well, I know that was sudden...
But it's much faster to just read
about Hayato Kawajiri than
to ask bothersome questions,
and I can get honest answers this way, too.
[Warning]
You mustn't
read any further.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
What Heaven's Door turns into a book
should just be the memories of this boy's
life experiences, without any falsehoods.
And yet... a warning?
[Warning]
You mustn't read any further.
What in the world is this?
Is this "warning" what he experienced?
I thought I'd just casually
look into this child,
but now this has definitely
caught my interest.
[Warning]
You mustn't read any further.
"You mustn't read any further"?
Who in the world could this warning be for?
An old guy walked by with his fly down.
He sneezed and said, "Damn it."
Some women laughed at him.
Wh-What is this?
This is getting even more confusing.
What does it mean?
Damn it.
J-Just who is this boy?
It rained.
Ugh, the forecast didn't
say it was going to rain!
At 8:27 AM, lightning struck
above the Pepsi sign.
8:27...
Wh-Who in the world is this Hayato Kawajiri?
Why is he experiencing things in the future?
Could he be a Stand user?
No... This is too odd to be a Stand ability.
All I can read with Heaven's Door
is what he has personally seen or heard.
The answer to this should
be written somewhere...
My dad isn't my dad
He made a man and a woman disappear at an apartment in Jozenji by making them explode.
He's a murderer. I found out who
he was. He has inhuman abilities.
My dad's name is Yoshikage Kira
Yoshikage Kira
Kira...
I-I did it!
This kid was the jackpot!
I finally found him!
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri!
He's disguised himself as this kid's father!
Ro
ha
n
Kishi
be
was
also
ki
ll
ed
"Rohan Kishibe was also killed"?
"He was killed by Kira,
He was killed by Kira,
who had matured.
who had matured..."
Deadly Queen's third bomb, Bites the Dust.
Heaven's Door!
Rohan Kishibe, Deadly Queen
is already inside your eye!
That is what you are seeing!
The switch for Deadly Queen's third bomb
has already been activated!
Deadly Queen's third ability...
It is a bomb to blow away anyone
who tries to come after me!
It will activate in anyone who tries to get
close to Hayato in order to learn about me.
He was killed by Kira,
who had matured.
Rohan Kishibe was also killed.
It'll also activate if Hayato happens
to verbally reveal my identity,
and if he writes it down,
it'll activate immediately.
Which means it's a bomb
I implanted in Hayato!
C-Come to think of it,
I was supposed to meet Koichi
and the others here at 8:30...
I finally... found out Yoshikage Kira's identity...
Koichi is coming. I have to tell him...
I... I finally... found him...
Yoshikage Kira is Kosaku Kawajiri.
I found him with my Heaven's Door.
I have to tell...
Koichi...
And now,
this is the real third
ability of Deadly Queen!
K-Koichi!
I-It was a dream?
I couldn't sleep very well last night.
I kept having these weird dreams...
Hayato!
Are you planning to sleep all day, Hayato?
Hurry up and wake—
What, you're already awake?
That's a surprise.
Hayato, breakfast is ready.
Honestly, why don't you ever answer me?
D-Didn't this...
What? No way! We're on the air already?
Th-This morning TV program...
Hayato! Hey, Hayato! Answer the phone.
Th-This isn't a dream...
What I just saw wasn't a dream.
Th-This is the same morning.
It's repeating...
Today's morning is repeating again!
Yoshikage Kira... His name is Yoshikage Kira!
He's doing this!
This is the unrivaled ability
he was talking about,
and he planted that inside me!
Hayato! I asked you to answer the phone!
Oh, yeah!
Look out—
Ow...
That was a nice catch. It was almost
as if you knew it was going to fall.
But if you can hear me,
you could at least answer!
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
Huh? No, it's not.
It appears I'm the only one
in the world who's aware
that this morning is repeating.
It's almost as if you knew, huh?
Apparently you blew someone
up and came back, Hayato.
No, really. I don't know
exactly what you've done.
This is called Deadly Queen Bites the Dust,
and it automatically protects me...
from inside you, Hayato.
Did you know that I already
killed you once last night?
As though as it was trying to remedy
the despair I was feeling
from the situation I was in,
I gained a brand new ability.
By using that ability on you,
time went back an hour,
and the fact that I killed you disappeared.
At the same time,
you became a bomb to protect me.
You told someone about me and the
bomb activated, and then you came back.
Who did you blow away, hm? Come on, tell me.
Who did you kill?
I-I didn't tell anyone...
I see! Then someone must have
been asking you questions.
It must be that Rohan Kishibe.
Even if you have no intention
of telling anyone,
as soon as someone asks you about me,
Bites the Dust will activate.
And then you will blow him up and come back.
The very fact that Rohan Kishibe
encountered you has disappeared!
That is Deadly Queen Bites the Dust.
You won't be able to tell anyone.
There will be no one who
can ask you anything!
Episode 36
Bites the Dust, Part 2