Let me see the key we obtained again,
Narancia.
Huh?
Here.
Wait! Don't throw it!
You little shit!
Dang, talk about overreacting.
Isn't the fact that you're
feeling pain a good sign?
I just had it reattached thirty minutes ago...
It still hurts, damn it!
"I thank you for protecting
my daughter, Bucciarati.
Go to the drinking fountain with a turtle
on the sixth platform at Naples Station,
and use this key.
Then, take my daughter to Venice by train.
P.S. My missions for you will
end once you get to Venice."
What's supposed to be by the
drinking fountain at the station?
The boss mentioned a way for us to travel
without being found by the enemy.
The station is dangerous, but we'll
just have to trust him and go.
D-Do you think the boss
is actually in Venice?
Since it's mentioned in that note...
We don't need to think about that.
We're just going to do as we're ordered.
There's a super express leaving for
Florence in ten minutes. We'll take that.
Mista, is anyone following us?
So far, we're good.
I can't say the same for the station, though.
There'll be plenty of paid guys
who'll report information about us.
The boss's daughter, Trish.
Her life is being targeted because
of a father she's never met.
I wonder how that feels...
Yeah, I get it, Fugo...
I can't help but stare at her
you-know-whats, either.
Huh?
Th-That's...
Please forgive Fugo!
He didn't mean any harm!
He wasn't trying to take
advantage of the sudden braking
to see your breasts or stroke
your thighs under your skirt!
He just couldn't help himself!
Hey, stop that!
I actually lost my balance,
but you're making it sound worse!
Please don't tell the boss!
Episodio 14  Express Train to Florence
Florence bound leaving at 16:35 from platform 6
He's really here. That's Bucciarati.
I can't believe he actually showed up at
a station where we could easily find him.
I'm gonna kill him!
Maybe he was pushed to his
limits and lost his mind,
or he's somehow confident that
he'll be able to give us the slip.
Either way, I'm gonna kill him!
He killed Formaggio and Illuso!
I'm gonna kill him!
Hey, dumbass.
Drop the "I'm gonna kill him" crap already.
That phrase doesn't exist in our world.
Only weaklings use that phrase.
Because when I or my other team
members so much as think those words,
our target is already dead,
and the job is over!
So I've never uttered
those words in my life.
You're gonna be that way too, right, Pesci?
If you're truly one of us.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yeah... I got it, Bro!
You can say, "I killed them!"
Prosciutto...
I'm going to head straight
over there via the platform.
Pesci, you board the train
and head to the lead car.
Got it!
We'll flank him.
We need the boss's daughter alive, after all.
Bucciarati, the train's about to leave.
Is something wrong?
There's no other drinking fountain
on this platform, is there?
This key won't fit into this keyhole.
Not to mention...
you don't even need a key to open it.
It's just a stopcock.
Bucciarati, how about the
lock on that fire hydrant?
The shape's completely different.
There aren't any locks or
doors that this key will fit.
They just aren't here!
Should we pass on this train?
The next one departs in fifteen
minutes and is bound for Rome.
No!
I'm sure some of our enemies know we're
here and are heading to the station now.
We have to leave here immediately!
The sixth platform...
The drinking fountain with the turtle...
This has to be the spot!
Damn it! What's—
The turtle...
Hey, Pesci, why the hell am
I running into you here?
I-I could ask you the same thing!
Where did Bucciarati go?
Bucciarati hopped onto the
train right in front of me.
It makes no sense that he didn't
bump into you in the hallway.
Well? I'm right, aren't I?
I didn't run into anyone!
Bucciarati, his crew, the newbie, and the
boss's daughter definitely aren't here!
Something's strange...
Bro, the train's about to leave.
They must be hiding somewhere
inside this station.
They're gonna keep an eye on us tracking
them and hop on another train to get away.
Let's use some homeless guy or
something to search the station!
There was something placed
at the drinking fountain.
He must've picked it up.
He picked up something that looked black!
Get on, Pesci!
But why?!
I just have a hunch.
I don't know how,
but I think Bucciarati and the
others are somewhere on this train.
You think?
You think?!
I'm sure the boss is helping them out somehow.
I have a feeling that if we don't board
this train, we'll lose them forever!
A feeling?
Just shut up and get on, Pesci!
It takes takes three and a half hours to
get from Naples to Florence by train.
It's an hour and a half non-stop
to the next stop, Rome.
Aw, we ended up getting on...
Shut up!
Hey, the gap between the door and floor...
What's on the other side of this door?
Isn't that the driver's cab?
But there's no way seven guys are in there.
You never know.
Use your Fisher Man to attack that room.
Do it.
Fisher Man!
There aren't seven guys in here...
There are two!
Got 'em!
Damn it. It really is small in there.
I guess there's only the driver.
But they're definitely
somewhere on this train.
Huh? Hey, wait a second.
There's only one?
I know I sensed two living things in there.
I could've sworn there was one more...
Hey, Pesci!
We're going to search this
train from end to end!
We'll drag Bucciarati and his crew out!
But you stay here.
Huh?
If they realize we're here,
they might come to stop the train.
You got it, Bro!
They have the girl with them,
so they shouldn't be able to just move
around or jump off this train easily.
That's going to give us our advantage.
We'll slaughter them all before
we get to Rome and take the girl!
The key wasn't made to fit in a keyhole.
It actually fit right into this turtle's shell.
That, in turn, somehow
activated the turtle's ability,
creating this space and making the key itself
the entrance so that we could hide inside.
Th-The turtle is a Stand user?
O-Ow!
Wh-Where the hell am I?
I'm under the seat?
Ow!
B-But man, this is awesome!
This turtle is like some kind of spaceship!
But this room isn't some kind of illusion.
This is a real room.
Even the sofa and other furniture is real.
There are some chilled drinks in here.
I guess the boss left them in there for us.
Turtles like being in the shade, they aren't
loud, and they don't scuttle about.
This way, we should be able to get
to Venice by train without worry.
I guess there's no way someone
would be in the locker...
I just don't have my bro's intuition.
B-Bro!
D-Don't tell me he...
The Thankful Death!
A-Are you really going to do it?
You're going to do in all of the passengers?!
We don't even know if they're on this train!
I already told you
that I would be thorough about this!
They're definitely here.
What's the big deal, anyway?
Every year, there are lots of
train crashes all over the world.
This won't be as brutal as those.
Mr. President
Coco Large
It's probably because we're
in a room inside a turtle,
but it's sorta muggy in here.
You want a drink, too, Narancia?
There are only cold drinks,
but there's cola, mineral water,
carbonated, non-carbonated, apple juice,
orange juice, and pineapple juice.
Hey, are you even listening?
Huh? What was that?!
I'm asking if you want something to drink!
Why don't you get some rest while you're at it?
You look pretty tired.
I'll keep an eye on the ceiling.
Oh, okay!
My shoulders suddenly feel stiff,
and my back hurts. There we go...
I'd really like something warm...
Something that won't upset my stomach.
I told you, there are
only cold drinks in here!
You never listen, do you?!
I'll just eat this banana, then.
Man, gardens like these make me sigh.
They're so calming...
They're so beautiful...
I'd love to drown in nostalgia and
think back on when I was a kid
while I just lay out in the
sun in a garden like this.
Hey, stop that!
Licking your finger before
you turn the page is gross!
Huh? Did I do that?
Me? No way!
Hey, there's something
hanging from your mouth.
Talk about gross. What the hell is that?
Hey!
A tooth?
I can't eat this banana for some reason...
It's all hard and dry...
Hey... Are you messing with us?
Man, you startled me...
That sort of looks like a tooth.
I'm still pretty grossed out,
so I can't really laugh...
What is that hanging from your mouth?
Huh? Did you say something again... Mista?
You're speaking too softly...
I couldn't hear you very well...
I'm telling you, this banana is crumbling...
I-I can't eat it...
Th-They're all dry...
A-All the fruits are dry...
Wh-What the hell is wrong with you?!
Didn't you hear me? Okay, then...
There's something wrong with your face!
N-Narancia, you...
I'll say it even louder this time!
Are you paying attention?!
I can't eat this banana!
Look. It's just crumbling...
It's old, damn it...
Bucciarati!
I know! It's a Stand attack!
Th-There must be an enemy on this train!
Huh? What? What's this white stuff?
It came from my head...
What the hell is this?!
What's the matter?
Did something... happen?
Th-They've all aged!
Mama... Wake up... Wake up...
Mama... Mama...
Wake up...
Wh-Who the hell is th-this?
What? No way... This can't be!
This is me?!
What the hell's going on?
A-A Stand that makes people age?
Did they figure out we're in this turtle?!
Calm down, Mista.
If they knew we were inside this turtle,
they would've used a more direct attack.
And since they haven't,
that means we haven't been found yet.
The enemy probably only knows that
we're somewhere on this train
and, in order to find her,
they're attacking everyone
on the train indiscriminately!
D-Does that mean this train is running
with everyone on board affected?
Probably.
They're desperate.
I'm sure they'll do anything...
And without a second thought.
This leaves us two choices.
One, take Trish and somehow
get off this train.
Two, we find this enemy, even though we
don't know their range, and dispose of them.
Obviously, we'll go with the second choice.
If we want to take her and run,
we'll have to stop the train.
It's too dangerous.
Assassinating them is more definitive,
with my Six Bullets!
Yes, you're right.
But we don't have any time.
We're aging at an alarming rate...
B-Bucciarati...
M-My hands...
Th-They're crumbling!
They're falling apart!
You're right, Bucciarati.
We really don't have any time!
Wait a minute, Mista...
It's too early... to go...
What the hell are you talking about, Giorno?
I'm telling you... it's too early to go...
We don't have any time to waste!
Wait.
Hear him out.
What are you trying to say, Giorno?
Why are we all aging at a
different rate than Bucciarati?
Mista's and my symptoms are light...
Trish's are even less!
But why?
Apparently, we're just aging at
different rates! I'm going!
No... If they're attacking everyone
indiscriminately with age...
They might end up killing her as well,
despite her being the target.
There's some kind of prerequisite
to how fast we're aging.
I'll tell you what I think...
I think the enemy is differentiating between
men and women by the difference
in their body temperature.
I read somewhere that women have more
fat in their bodies, which makes them
less susceptible to temperature fluctuations.
Apparently women also age better
and live longer than men.
Don't you think it's been a little hot?
The enemy is differentiating
the aging speed based on
slight differences in body temperature.
All that matters is that the men
age faster and she ages slower.
Yeah, that sounds about right,
but then why are you and I
aging at different rates?
Are you insinuating that I'm a girl?!
Change in body temperature...
Come to think of it,
our bodies were slightly cooler...
Because we had something cold to drink.
Narancia didn't have anything to drink.
Th-That's...
Giorno, it's exactly like you said!
We're aging slower because our
bodies were slightly cooler!
Cool everyone down!
Cool everyone down with ice!
Hold it, Mista!
You're going to have to
take that ice with you!
Th-This is all that's left?
It doesn't change the fact that
we have to dispose of this enemy.
Mista, you're going to take
that ice and defeat the enemy...
Before the ice melts and
you lose your Stand power!
Just the driver... It doesn't look
like anyone else is in here.
It's so muggy...
This Stand really is
attacking indiscriminately.
I wonder if this turtle is aging, too...
But they say that turtles
live for 10,000 years.
Guess they live longer than us.
Damn it...
What's Bro thinking? This is so dangerous.
What's he gonna do if I
get old, too? Damn it...
The air conditioner?
If I turn it on inside the driver's cab,
everyone in the turtle will cool down,
and that might slow down their aging!
There it is!
Something took the bait!
Wh-What the hell is this needle-like thing?!
A d-different Stand than
the one that's aging us?
There's another one? There are two of them?
There are two enemies?!
Episodio 15
The Thankful Death Part 1