I think it might be worth it to shoot
the shit out of that fatty there!
Yes!
Th-That was close...
If I hadn't returned to my normal
size, I would've been done for!
If time hadn't passed to the
point of you becoming so small
that your Stand power
was rendered useless...
I would've been a goner!
I-I didn't get him!
D-Damn it.
If I'm getting smaller and smaller,
does that mean Li'l Bomber's
power got smaller, too?
That bastard's on the move!
Come back, Li'l Bomber!
Th-This really pisses me off,
but I need to hide somewhere.
The dude's desperate.
If he finds me, he'll do everything
he can to get me to tell him
where the boss's daughter is.
I-It's so far!
The sidewalk's so damn wide!
Move! You're in my way, damn it!
Damn it...
Now I've got you.
Well, shit...
You've caused me so much trouble.
Once you've been hit with Tiny Feet's
ability, you can never get away.
Now, you're going to tell me
where Bucciarati and his guys
are hiding the boss's daughter.
K-Kill me!
Damn it, just kill me already!
Do you really think I want to live so badly
that I'd tell you where
my friends are? Huh?!
Narancia Ghirga was born
in 1984 and is a Leo.
When he was ten...
N-Narancia...
I'm right here, Mom.
Mom...
Hey, Dad...
Mom's eye disease...
You shithead...
That was the beginning of the path
that led Narancia to where he is now.
Episodio 11  Narancia's Li'l Bomber
Hey, I need to ask for directions.
How many minutes would it
take to walk to this place?
Narancia rebelled against his father.
Minutes? That'd take you hours.
He'd sleep over at his
delinquent friends' houses,
and get by daily by eating the
food he had stolen that day.
It all went as planned!
It's all because you told
us about that shop, Bro.
You sure you don't need to go to school?
You actually come from a decent home.
Like I give a shit about that home.
The most important thing in
this world is friendship!
Yeah.
You should dye your hair blonde like mine.
Then the chicks would be all over you.
Yeah!
What? Seriously?
What do you think?
You look so dumb!
Hey, where's Bro?
Who knows? I haven't seen him in a few days.
Huh...
But the next day...
You bastards!
Put both hands on the wall!
You little shit!
You're going to juvenile hall!
What the hell are you talking
about?! Me, a robber?!
Of course I'm no—
Quit lyin'! We have a witness!
Wha—
That's him! That blonde brat is the suspect!
N-No, I'm not!
I'm sure of it! He beat me
up and took my money!
Quit lyin', you old hag!
I didn't do anything!
Just admit to your crimes, you little shit!
Hey! That's going too far!
You saw him, Counselor.
He was about to hit her again!
A robber...
A blonde brat...
Don't tell me...
No, that's not possible!
Stop thinking up shit like that, damn it!
A year later, when Narancia left
juvenile hall, his eye was afflicted.
After the officer hit his eye,
the eye wound up infected
and never got better.
When he returned to town,
strange rumors were going around.
Look at that.
I heard his mom died from
an eye disease, too.
How do they know that?
I only ever told Bro that...
Wow, they already let you out?
I don't want to get infected.
Stay the hell away from me.
It couldn't be... But Bro is...
He felt trapped, so he used me as a scapegoat...
The one most afraid of these rumors
concerning the eye disease
was Narancia himself.
This is fate...
Soon... just like Mom...
I'm going to die from this eye disease!
That's what he believed.
He had nowhere to go.
He was all alone.
Narancia had given up on
life at the age of fifteen.
How awful. He's just a child.
It's a pity, but we shouldn't get involved.
The boy brought Narancia into a restaurant,
then told his friend at the
table and the shop's host...
I'd like to feed him some spaghetti!
You don't mind, do you?
His friend at the table
didn't ask any questions,
nor did he give him a look of disgust.
He just set the plate of spaghetti
he'd ordered for himself
in front of the filthy child.
He then had the kid receive
the treatment he needed.
Three weeks later...
Why are you doing all this for me?
There's no reason.
If you want, you can stay at my house.
But kids like you should go
back home to their parents.
Also, go to school. Got it?
U-Um, are you in a gang?
I don't want to go back home.
Please let me work for you!
Don't be so naïve, you little shit!
If you say that again, I'll punch you!
As instructed, Narancia went back home
and even started going back to school.
But he could never trust his father again.
Why did he get so serious about scolding me?
There's nothing special about me.
But...
That rage didn't come from hate or disgust,
and it didn't feel like it
was meant to insult me.
It was totally different from when
my dad or those cops got mad at me.
When I think about how he
acted, I feel confident.
Real men...
should work for guys like him!
Six months later, Narancia went to see
one of the capos of the organization,
Polpo, without Bucciarati knowing...
and he passed the test.
Narancia, if you're going to
tell me where that girl is,
now is probably the best time to do it.
The girl you're trying to kidnap doesn't
belong to a gang or anything like that!
She's just an ordinary girl!
Bucciarati hates shit like that,
even if it's an order!
No decent person would like that!
We said we were going to protect her,
so we're going to protect
her, no matter what!
Would you quit with your worthless drivel?
Well, shit...
All this crap about your friends
and protecting this chick...
That's not what we're talking about here.
I'm talking about the fact
that if we defeat the boss,
we'll have a drug route
worth hundreds of billions.
Y-You bastard!
Hundreds of billions!
That's an amount worth a
few people dying over!
It's going to be ours!
There's no turning back now!
Since she's the boss's daughter,
she's bound to have a Stand ability!
The boss doesn't want
people finding that out!
We'll definitely be able to figure out who
the boss is through his daughter's ability!
His daughter is a hint for defeating the boss,
whose identity we don't even know!
What? That girl's a Stand user?
Did you know...
In South America, there's a spider
called the southern black widow.
Apparently its venom can even kill humans.
This spider isn't deadly.
I actually caught it in the sewers
earlier. It's completely harmless.
But...
Even a normal spider's bite is venomous.
Y-You aren't gonna...
More than venomous enough to paralyze
tiny little insects and eat them!
Li'l Bomber!
Whoa, there!
I told you, your Stand is powerless now!
This bottle is gonna be the ring, Narancia!
Y-You bastard! Hey!
It's looking at you!
It's looking right at you!
It's watching you carefully
with all eight of its eyes!
Open up! Open the bottle!
Damn it!
Listen carefully. Even if it bites
you, you won't die instantly.
First, its venom will paralyze your body,
so you'll no longer be able to move.
But once you can't move and it
traps you, you're in real danger.
Then it'll start injecting you with even
more venom and digestive juices.
Those digestive juices will slowly melt your
insides to the consistency of a milkshake
so it can suck you right up.
And you're going to be
conscious the whole time.
If you finally feel like talking, you can
still talk while you're being eaten.
But you're probably better
off telling me right now
where the boss's daughter is.
I really don't want to see a person
end up melted and eaten by a spider.
I-It's fast!
You bastard!
A shard of glass?!
He somehow got it and kept it on him?!
W-Webbing?
When did...
It bit him!
You can't move anymore because
your muscles are spasming.
Just hurry up and tell me.
This is your last chance
if you don't wanna die.
Damn it... Like hell I'm gonna tell you!
Damn it!
Looks like it's injecting its
digestive juices into you now.
It's gonna melt you...
Huh?
What's that?
You dropped this when you took that shard
of glass out of your pocket,
so I picked it up...
Maybe... I don't need
you to tell me anymore.
This is a map of this city.
It's a driving map. Not only that...
There are things marked on here with pencil,
so you wouldn't get lost!
How stupid are you?!
If I follow these directions in reverse,
I can see where you came from!
A vineyard!
You came from a vineyard that's
about twenty kilometers southeast!
Grazie, Narancia!
Now you can get eaten or have that
thing lay eggs in you or whatever,
you moron!
Tiny Feet
Formaggio
Twenty kilometers southeast!
The boss's daughter Trish
is somewhere in that area!
I did it! You don't have to talk anymore!
My Li'l Bomber has the ability to
detect and pursue carbon dioxide.
But carbon dioxide doesn't just
come from living creatures.
It's also produced by burning things.
I just remembered...
When I was chasing you with Li'l Bomber,
I also shot at the car.
I'm pretty sure I shot the gasoline tank...
But I can't really tell
where the hole is from here.
Still,
I was thinking that since the bullet
hole is technically burning, it'll have
carbon dioxide coming from it,
so I can find it using Li'l Bomber.
So I shot at it.
See, it wasn't the spider
I was shooting at earlier.
But it's a small hole,
so it took a while for the fire to actually
start, and I was getting nervous!
What?!
Damn it!
All the shopping bags got burned to a crisp!
Narancia's Height: 5.5cm -> 170.5cm (His normal height)
But it feels great to be back at a
size where a spider bite won't matter.
How dare you?!
I'm gonna murder all of your friends!
Hideout... Blergh!
Vineyard... Blah!
Just you wait, Narancia!
Tiny Feet!
Wh-What?!
He put out the fire with the blood
that squirted out of his wrist?!
Damn it! This isn't good!
Letting him get away now is not good at all!
I have to find him using Li'l Bomber's ability!
Sh-Shit!
Th-The radar...
These flames...
Y-You bastard! Where are you?!
Is this lucky or unlucky?
Narancia, because you set the car on fire,
you can't track me because of all the
carbon dioxide coming from the flames!
I guess if this comes down
to winning or losing, I've won!
You're not getting away!
I know where the boss's daughter is.
Now I just need to get out of
here and let my buddies know.
We'll murder you all!
Assassinations are our specialty!
Assassinations?
I'll make sure I pay you back for this soon!
You won't be able to find me anymore!
I win!
Boooooom
If I can't track your breathing...
If the flames are too big...
I'll just make them bigger!
If I set the whole damn street on fire,
you'll burn up and die because you're so tiny!
You're not getting away, Formaggio!
Are you mad, you bastard?
You actually set the whole street on fire!
Are you sane? You bastard!
Huh?!
I guess I don't need to set
the whole city on fire now.
When I asked if you were sane,
what you basically did was tell me that you
want me to kill you as soon as possible.
Thanks to the flames, I was
able to get this close to you.
Did you forget?
At this distance,
my Stand is faster than yours!
It might be.
Bring it, Narancia...
Tiny Feet!
Well, shit...
I guess your little shopping trip wasn't
as easy as you thought it'd be,
was it, Narancia?
Now things are going to get more difficult...
for you bastards!
"Go shopping," they tell me...
Mission... incomplete.
Both the money and the stuff I bought...
went up in flames...
Narancia, repeat it one more time.
I told you, the shopping—
Not that!
You just said the enemy
found out where we're hiding.
But I took care of him right after—
That's not the issue here!
Bucciarati, we should get
the hell out of here.
After I warned you so many times...
You fool!
I think Narancia did a great
job stopping the enemy.
I think he did everything he should've done.
And now that the Hitman Team knows
about us, if he's a reasonable boss,
he should give us a method of escape.
I don't think we should leave
until we hear from the boss.
Well, aren't you clever?
Do you think you're an advisor now?
And how do you know that the
boss will contact us soon?
No one cares about your damn hunches!
Bucciarati!
I think we got a message from the boss!
Message for Bucciarati
This is how the boss always
sends his orders to the capos.
This is the first time
Bucciarati's received one!
I'll check out the message.
"Head to the Pompeii Archaeological Park.
I've hidden a key near the dog mosaic."
Look into that immediately!
"That key is for a vehicle that'll
bring my daughter safely to me."
Vehicle? What does he mean by a safe vehicle?
A helicopter!
That must be a key to a helicopter!
We can go anywhere in a helicopter
without anyone following us!
It's a bit less than fifteen kilometers
from here to Pompeii.
An hour should be plenty of time
to get over there and get the key.
Fugo! Abbacchio! Giorno!
You three head to Pompeii and get that key!
Mista, Narancia, and I will remain here
and protect Trish from the Hitman Team.
Retrieve the key, and if
it seems safe, contact us.
Then we'll take Trish and
head to over to that vehicle.
I'm counting on you.
Episodio 12
The Second Mission from the Boss