None of his friends realize
that there's another Stand.
Yes, they don't realize that my Stand,
Talking Mouth, is attached to
your tongue and making you say
the exact opposite of what you mean.
Narancia,
there must be some reason
you can't tell us the truth.
Giorno!
Giorno's getting pulled under!
Even though the water's so shallow!
Li'l Bomber!
The bastard is teleporting
from liquid to liquid
while still holding on to Giorno's body,
despite there being so little water!
Yes! I got him.
If we first take care of Giorno Giovanna,
who controls life and can heal his friends,
it'll be a piece of cake to eliminate
the rest of his friends one by one.
Yeah, it's all going according to plan.
But we should finish off
Giorno immediately, Squalo.
Huh?
According to my information,
Narancia's Li'l Bomber can track carbon dioxide.
Even though Giorno's
unconscious right now,
if he's breathing, your Crush,
which bit into him, will be tracked down.
Even if you jump from liquid to liquid.
It won't be good if Li'l Bomber tracks
down your location and gets ahead.
It'll track us down.
All right, Tiziano.
I'll stop Giorno's breathing.
Right now.
Episodio 23 Crush and Talking Mouth
This isn't good.
I can't let them take Giorno away!
This enemy...
So there were already two Stands here?
Shit! The more I miss,
the more I'm spreading the water around
and giving them the upper hand!
I have to get ahead of them!
Where are they? Where'd they go?!
There!
They may be able to teleport,
but if I can get ahead of them,
I can fill them full of holes!
He's got his radar out.
As I figured, he's going to try
to track us down and shoot us.
We should stop Giorno's
breathing immediately.
Quit being so pushy. I know, Tiz.
But it sure is hard to attack
Giorno while teleporting!
I got the timing down! Now!
Wha— Into his neck?!
Giorno! I-I didn't mean to shoot you!
Wh-What? His breathing...
The symbol indicating Giorno's breathing...
It disappeared from the radar!
Shit! They got away!
Excellent. Crush went into the sewers.
I'm just going to continue down into the
canal and dispose of Giorno's body.
Hold it. What was that, Squalo?
I said I'd take his body to the canal and...
No, I'm talking about Narancia.
I almost didn't hear it,
but he definitely said it!
He said, "They got away!" With his voice!
As long as my Talking Mouth is on his tongue,
he should only be able to say
the opposite of his intent.
But he said, "They got away!"
He even said the radar symbol disappeared.
Squalo! Move from there immediately!
What are you talking about, Tiziano?
Giorno's not breathing at all!
There's no one else who
can track down my Crush!
He said, "They got away!" on purpose!
It was to put you at ease!
It was to stop Crush's
teleportation for even a moment!
I don't know how, but he's
definitely tracking you!
Back then, Giorno moved on
purpose so I'd shoot him.
That way, there'd be residue from the
gunshots, and I could actually track him!
I can see him.
I can see him clear as day!
Here we go! I'm gonna fill them with holes!
Here I come, you bastard!
This means Giorno's not dead yet!
If we can resuscitate him within
a few minutes, he'll be saved!
This isn't good, Squalo!
Now that he's fired at you twice,
he's going to go after the
residue from your bullet wounds!
I did it! I got him out of the sewers!
It's no use, Bucciarati.
I can't replay this enemy any further.
I know for sure that they were
in this cup on top of this table.
But they were only there for a moment.
From there, Moody Jazz can't
transform, nor go forward.
What do you mean, Abbacchio?
I don't know. Maybe they can teleport.
But I don't have the answer.
The replay for this enemy...
It won't go any further,
like a video tape that's been torn.
I can't believe Narancia would go this far...
No, it's Giorno.
This all happened because
Giorno intentionally got shot
by Li'l Bomber's guns.
Shit! I can't get rid of the residue!
Even in the water!
Because the bullets were from a Stand.
I have to disappear somehow.
Somewhere he can't detect me!
I've been watching...
and this shark bastard is pretty damn
fast for a remote-controlled Stand,
but it looks like it can't get
very far in a single leap.
Looks to be about two to three meters!
Shit!
H-His attacks are becoming more precise!
It could be due to injuries,
but their speed's getting slower!
Squalo!
Yes! Now I just need to end
this with a finishing blow!
Take this, you fishy bastard!
Th-This smell...
There's a gas leak!
This is all according to plan, Narancia.
Because you shot,
hot water spilled from the pot
and extinguished the burner.
Now Li'l Bomber won't be
able to shoot its guns!
Now you can't track me!
If one of the sparks from your
gun happens to ignite the gas,
you may survive, but everything
around there will burn,
filling the room with carbon dioxide,
and you won't be able to find me anymore!
Narancia, just go ahead and try to shoot
those guns!
We've won!
You know, if I can't shoot...
I have other ways of killing you!
Yes! I got the enemy!
Bucciarati! Mista! The enemy's here!
Abbacchio, the enemy's able to
move from liquid to liquid!
Giorno's breathing again!
Huh?
Wait. What did I just say?
Why was I able to speak the truth?
Squalo, I've released Talking
Mouth from Narancia's tongue,
just like you planned.
You're pretty badly injured, but I'm
sure the boss will be satisfied.
Did you just yell something, Narancia?!
Did you say the enemy's over here?
But the release of Talking
Mouth is only temporary.
Giorno's... That must be the enemy!
Wh-What?!
W-Wai—
We win, Squalo.
Yes... This is all according to plan!
Here we go, Six Bullets!
Shoot, Mista!
Wh-What?!
Sh-Shit! My radar!
I can't track them! They're going to attack!
Giorno's going to be taken
because of my lie!
N-Narancia!
L-Look for it!
G-Giorno!
Don't go after the Stand...
Go after the user!
Giorno!
Hey, Narancia!
You bastard! Why'd you tell me to shoot?!
This room was filled with gas!
Look out! It's the enemy!
The enemy's above!
No! Below! The enemy's below!
What?!
Guys!
It's no use! I can't stop
myself from talking!
I have to stop talking!
It disappeared!
They're planning to eliminate
Giorno before anyone else!
Don't go after the Stand...
Go after the user!
Giorno!
Giorno told me to find the user.
Right... They're hurt.
Because they're hurt,
their breathing is probably labored.
So that's what he means.
He wants me to use my radar to find them.
I'm alone in this. I have to do this alone.
Someone who's breathing hard...
They have a remote-controlled Stand,
but they have to be somewhere around here.
There's no time! I have to
be quick and find them!
Talking Mouth
Tiziano
Okay, this is all according to plan.
With Giorno gone, there's no
one to fix their injuries.
Now, finish off Giorno.
For good.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I've been injured,
but I have plenty of strength
left to attack him.
Hey, look. It's Narancia.
What's he doing out here?
Where is Crush right now?
Over there.
It exited the restaurant's sewer pipe
and is heading down the canal.
He shouldn't be able to track it anymore...
Don't tell me he's trying
to find me instead!
My breathing...
Calm down, Squalo.
That's impossible.
He's just struggling because
he's run out of options.
How many people do you think there
are within hundred meters of here?
Fifty? A hundred?
There's no way he could tell
you apart from the others.
But I'm injured.
If he's trying to find someone
with labored breathing...
Don't panic, Squalo.
Look at the bottom of the stairs.
There are many with even more labored
breathing than you in that square.
Calm yourself and your breathing.
If we hide your injuries and head into the
square like nothing's wrong, we'll be safe.
We still win!
Yeah, you're right... You're exactly right.
There's no way he'd find us.
I found you!
You're right there!
Wh-What?!
Shit! I have to retrieve Crush!
Calm down, Squalo! Think this through!
He can only say the opposite of
what he's thinking right now.
He said he found us,
meaning he hasn't found us!
Don't forget that!
Then why did he bother saying that?!
He wants you to panic and make your
breathing even more labored!
Please calm down. If you panic,
it's exactly what he wants.
There's no way Narancia can single you out.
This is just his futile, last-ditch attempt.
Calm your breathing.
I found you...
There you are.
I finally... found you.
He said it again!
Please, calm down.
He hasn't found us. That's fact.
He's definitely lying!
My Talking Mouth is still
definitely on his tongue...
H-Hey, look!
Wh-What?!
He cut out his own tongue!
With his own knife!
That's impossible!
No one can survive after
cutting out their own tongue,
let alone speak!
I found... you!
H-He has another tongue!
The ladybug became a tongue!
It can't be!
It's Giorno!
Giorno Giovanna!
Just as the boss had said,
he's the biggest problem!
That bastard Giorno must've created a tongue
for Narancia in the kitchen
and given it to him!
He's coming! He's heading this way!
So he was tracking my breathing!
It's the opposite!
If he was actually tracking you,
he would've attacked already!
Considering the number of people out
here, there's all kinds of breathing.
Labored breathing, slow breathing...
There's so much that I
can't single anyone out.
But I've been waiting...
I've been waiting for this...
For the moment when someone's breathing
drastically changes suddenly!
For someone to change their
breathing drastically
after seeing me cut my
tongue out with a knife!
For someone to see their Stand
hanging out along with my tongue
and panic bigtime!
That's what I've been waiting for!
Just when I thought I'd lost you
guys and was about to give up!
You, over there!
Your breathing just fluctuated, didn't it?!
Yeah, you! I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you, long hair!
This can't be!
He actually cut out his tongue to track me!
Which must mean the shark user
is the dude next to you!
He seems pretty damn pale.
Squalo, retrieve Crush!
I'm already on it!
It's traveling through the sewers
and heading toward that well.
But... there's no water here!
There's no liquid that Crush
can jump at Narancia from!
You must be him!
The guy who dragged Giorno away!
Tiziano!
Now you have some liquid... Squalo.
This didn't... go exactly
according to plan...
But this doesn't change our victory.
We're still going to... win...
I don't give a damn about the
boss's orders anymore.
I'm not going to kill you because I was
ordered to as one of the elite guard.
Tiziano... I'm going to
eliminate him for you!
I'll kill all of Narancia's friends, too!
I'll rip them to pieces and make them pay!
I'll make them all pay!
Crush! Rip out his throat!
Do you think... I'm going to falter?
Because of... Because of something like this?
We're...
going to get the hell out of Venice,
completely safe and sound.
See ya...
Volare via.
"Go flying"
You're a damn traitor...
You're supposed to be
eliminated by the boss...
You're supposed to have no choice
but to fear your future...
What in the world is driving them forward?
Why does it seem like they have hope?
Wh-What could it...
Someone just collapsed!
Giorno!
Y-Yes! He's breathing again, faintly!
Giorno, wake up! Giorno! Giorno!
Narancia...
Abbacchio doesn't think too highly of you,
but we all end up moving
under your direction,
as though you're leading us...
We might actually have some hope
for this journey... with you around.
Giorno, let's get back to everyone else.
How long has it been
since the attack began?
Four to five minutes?
Anyway, it's hard to imagine
that another assassin
from the organization is
in Venice right now.
It should be wide open.
Let's head toward the airport!
We'll get a plane!
We're going to get a plane and head
to Sardinia, no matter what.
We must find out about the boss's
past as quickly as possible...
or we lose.
Episodio 24
Notorious Chase