Could it be that while we were sleeping,
Giorno and I, and Mista and Trish...
Each pair's minds have been swapped?!
Don't attack just yet!
That Stand!
It's Zipper Man!
It's Bucciarati's...
soul!
No one can escape the fate that was chosen for them.
All that remains is the end, where you will all perish.
Eternal greatness exists only within myself.
Sing a song of sorrow in a world where time has vanished.
Episodio 35 The Requiem Quietly Plays, Part 2
Yes! Bucciarati's okay!
And he was going after the
arrow before the boss was!
The way you're talking...
Sounds like it's Narancia who's inside you.
Am I correct?
Yeah!
And you two...
I'm Giorno.
I-It's me, Trish.
Well done, Bucciarati.
You've already figured out
this bizarre situation.
That voice... Are you the man we
were supposed to meet earlier?
Indeed. My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff.
Stab
I was killed by Diavolo.
But I swapped souls with this turtle,
so I'm just barely clinging to
this world, basically as a ghost.
And that is my Stand.
The arrow's power caused it to go berserk,
and it is now Chariot Requiem.
That's the reason your souls
have all been swapped.
Wait. If our souls have been swapped,
then the one in my body is—
He hasn't woken up yet.
He's still out cold.
Are you... Mista?
Yeah. Glad you're safe, Bucciarati.
The boss, Diavolo,
who swapped minds with you,
is being watched by
Number Seven of the Bullets.
He hasn't moved an inch.
He's completely out.
Bucciarati!
Requiem's getting up!
We already know how to use the arrow.
If we take control of that arrow,
everything will be over!
Rumble
Gwooooar
Zipper Man... What in the world...
Pick up the arrow!
Requiem's charging at you!
Boom
Stop
I'm gonna knock the arrow away!
Hurry and pick it up!
Something's wrong!
Don't tell me that was...
Take this!
I'll put a hole in your brain!
The pillar next to you!
Mista, duck!
Boom
Spicy Lady!
Smack
Blam
I'll splatter your brains on the ground!
On the ground!
Let the ants swarm around you!
The flies swarm around you!
What the... Number One? Where the
hell did you come from? Hey, stop!
Cut it out!
Huh?
What's wrong, guys?
What...
It can't be...
H-Hey!
It's going to pick up the arrow!
It's going to pick it up!
What the hell?
What the hell just happened?!
I think this is
Requiem's Stand ability
when it's in berserk mode.
This is the first time I'm
witnessing it, as well!
Now that Requiem has gone berserk,
it has carried on my wish
and has become a defensive Stand.
All to make sure it doesn't let
anyone else have the arrow!
Anyone who tries to touch the arrow
gets stopped by their own Stand!
The arrow has the ability
to control your mind...
Are you saying this is a part of that?
So then, what the heck are we supposed to do?
Our Stands have powered up.
B-But, I mean...
If we try to get the arrow with that power...
S-Stop that,
Benedict!
There, there... It'll be okay.
Mista! Number Seven, the one
keeping watch, is freaking out!
Bucciarati's body...
is awake!
Diavolo? No way!
We'll have to go after the arrow later!
Position yourselves where
you can see his body!
Mista! Shoot him now!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and shoot him!
B-But that body is yours, Bucciarati!
Bullet wounds...
are wounds my Golden Wind can fully heal.
We need to make sure he can no longer move.
That's what you're saying...
Right, Bucciarati?
He stood up! He's starting to walk!
Boom
He's convulsing!
He won't be able to come at us anymore!
No one else is showing up on my radar.
No one's coming to save him!
We did it.
Now, once we get the arrow
back... it'll all be over.
Once we get back to Naples,
I'm gonna go to school!
I wanna eat some piping-hot pizza, too!
Authentic margherita from back home,
where it's baked over an oak wood fire!
I'll get some porcini mushrooms on it, too!
And then...
If I ever see Fugo again...
Maybe I wouldn't mind him calling me dumb.
Too bad Abbacchio's gone now, though...
Trish!
I'm going to protect you until the end!
We all will!
Narancia...
Mista.
Just in case, shoot both of his legs, too.
R-Right!
Trish, you have my bullets.
Give them all to me.
They're inside my boot.
S-Sure...
Hurry up, would you?
Come on, hand over the bullets!
M-Mista...
Time just skipped ahead a few seconds!
Yeah! There are bullets on the ground,
but I don't remember hearing them fall!
But that's impossible!
I didn't see it at all!
Not him bringing out Emperor Crimson
or making it disappear, either!
And why?
He hasn't moved an inch from that spot!
Trish, drop one more bullet from my hand.
Hurry it up!
The number of bullets on the ground is four!
I can't deal with the number four!
Four is the number I just
can't have around me!
If it fell when you handed them to me,
then you have to drop another one!
Is he actually Diavolo?
Trish, when we woke up, you mentioned that
you couldn't sense the boss's presence
from that body at all, right?
What about now?
Do you sense the boss nearby?
But that's not possible!
You swapped with Narancia,
and Mista swapped with Trish.
That means Bucciarati
switched with Diavolo!
That's Requiem's ability,
once it's gone berserk!
I don't really get what's going on,
but if time just skipped ahead,
then it's a fact that that body isn't
the one controlling Emperor Crimson!
Narancia, what's going on in the area?
Is there anyone else trying
to come near here?
Narancia?
Trish, please...
You need to drop... drop one more
bullet from my hand... please...
I don't know...
I don't know why I can't sense the boss.
I have no idea why!
Move. Move!
I can't sense him anywhere...
Let me through! Please!
Please! Move out of my way!
Impossible! There's no way
this should've happened!
Keep an eye on our surroundings, Mista!
Watch our backs!
Narancia!
Cut the iron bars, Bucciarati!
We need to hurry up and get Narancia down!
Leave it to me, Mista! Leave this to me!
You need to load your gun, Mista!
He'll do it again!
His attack had already begun!
Zipper Man!
Now heal him!
Hurry up and get the iron bars out of him!
The civilians outside the Colosseum
are starting to wake up.
Where is he? I didn't sense
any trace of the boss at all!
I don't get why his presence seems to
disappear and then reappear anymore...
Emperor Crimson's range is
two to three meters, at most.
So then how did he... from over there?
H-Hey! You did it!
Narancia's awake now!
Yes!
Th-That was a close one...
No... Mista.
This is... an empty... shell.
It's an empty shell.
The wounds he received...
have already been healed by my Golden Wind.
But... he's already gone.
Narancia...
isn't...
It's... completely empty.
His soul...
It's gone.
He's gone now.
There's nothing I can do...
I didn't make it in time...
It's so empty that I could slip right
back in... I could coexist in both bodies...
That's just how...
empty this body is.
Narancia!
This is too sudden...
Jean Pierre Polnareff
Silver Chariot
Where is he?
Where could he be?
This is inconceivable!
This can't be possible unless
there are two Diavolos!
Two of them...
That kid and Diavolo...
Don't tell me there are
actually two of them...
Rumble
There's only one body, but two minds!
Bucciarati! I figured it out!
Diavolo has two personalities!
That's the only possible way!
The one in that body right now
is the kid that I encountered.
The kid and Diavolo have the same body,
but their minds are separate!
At times, people's minds
can be scarred and split due to a
traumatic experience during childhood.
As they grow older, that split can
develop into a separate personality.
That split personality starts to appear much
more distinctly as they reach adulthood,
and one personality will
be dominant over the other.
That's the multiple
personality disorder theory!
Listen carefully. What I just
said isn't a hypothesis.
I've even heard of reports
from Germany and England
where the individual's physical features
change depending on the personality.
Requiem's ability tore his
soul away from his body.
One of them, the kid,
ended up in Bucciarati's body,
but the other one...
And it could be coincidental,
but they ended up in someone else's body.
That's who Diavolo is!
Emperor Crimson attacked from their body!
What are you talking about?
Two personalities?
That's who the boss really is?
Slowly but surely,
people are waking up outside.
So I don't know where he's hiding.
But he will come again!
He'll attack again, and soon!
That's possible...
But he could've already left the area.
Diavolo is also after the arrow.
That's why he attacked Narancia first.
He got rid of our radar first.
So we wouldn't be able to tell
that he was going after the arrow.
That's why he took down Li'l Bomber.
This just means you'll have to
obtain the arrow's power after all.
Either way, if you're going
to destroy Emperor Crimson,
you need to find the arrow before he does,
and get it away from Chariot somehow.
Which way did Requiem go?
To the left.
It looks like people are starting to
wake up in the direction he's headed.
Find it? But your body is...
What about your body, Bucciarati?
I missed all his vital points.
But he won't be able to stand up and move.
I made sure of that.
We're going to have to leave you behind here.
So that no one
can hurt you anymore...
Ever again.
But I promise
that I will take you back home.
Rumble
Watch out for anyone coming near us!
Let's go!
Trish! What are you doing? Stay close!
R-Right.
Hey, the woman running over there!
You're under arrest!
You're going to accompany me to the station!
Kablam
I-Is something wrong, Mista?
Nope! Everything's fine!
They got close, so I thought
it might've been the boss,
but it was just some cop.
It does indeed seem that Requiem
doesn't have a destination
in mind, nor any emotions.
It hasn't even looked at me
or the direction its heading.
It does look like a living creature,
but it also looks like something
resembling black plastic.
It hasn't even recognized me as an enemy.
It seems to be slow and even weak.
And it's a fully physically formed Stand.
Civilians can see and touch it.
Rip
Drag...
Drag
It's no use... It's not letting us get close.
It's not just our Stands.
If we try to touch it with something,
it'll come flying back at us.
This arrow might truly be invincible.
The more difficult this becomes,
the more I'm convinced that it has
some kind of isolation power
that repels everyone.
It's getting up again.
How can we pick up the arrow?
It's right in front of us!
Hey.
Requiem won't allow Stand
users to pick up the arrow.
But what if someone who's not a Stand
user tried to pick up the arrow?
Well, what do you think will happen?
Why are you asking me that?
How the hell would I—
Rumble
H-Hey, guys!
My soul is holding on for
dear life within this turtle.
I'm no longer a Stand user...
so I was able to touch it!
Mista! Hurry up and pierce
your Stand with this arrow!
Episodio 36
Diavolo Surfaces