All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
Get out. We're going home.
Get lost.
I didn't ask you to come here.
Help me?
This is my Egyptian friend
I met three years ago,
Avdol.
Red Bind!
This is...
I shall reveal its identity!
It may seem like an evil spirit, but it is not.
Jotaro! What you believed to be an evil spirit
is a powerful vision,
created from your own life energy.
Because it appears next to you,
that vision is called...
A Stand!
Bam!
That's a hundred-year-old coffin
pulled up from the Atlantic Ocean,
off the African coast four years ago.
Coffin?
After I obtained and researched it,
I found out that it was on the
boat where my grandfather,
the man four generations before you,
Jonathan Joestar, died.
It was apparently empty
when they discovered it.
But I know exactly what was inside!
Avdol and I are trying to
locate him as we speak.
He is evil incarnate!
His name is Dio!
He has awakened from his hundred-year sleep.
We are fated to fight him!
And on the back of his neck...
From this bastard's neck down,
is the body of my grandfather,
Jonathan Joestar,
Rumble
which that bastard has taken over!
Kujo
Jotaro! Wait!
You forgot something!
Goodness...
Here, a goodbye kiss.
Smooch.
You bitch...
Stop clinging to your child already.
Okay! Have a good day!
Good grief...
Hey, it's Jojo.
What? Jojo?
You're right! It's Jojo!
Jojo!
Good morning, Jojo.
Jojo, what were you doing while you
were absent from school for four days?
Hey!
Why are you clinging to Jojo's arm like that?
You're being too chummy! Stay away from him!
What the hell, ugly?
Shut it, no-boobs.
Ugly.
No-boobs.
Ugly, ugly, ugly...
No-boobs, no-boobs, no-boobs...
Shut up! You're damn annoying!
He totally said that to me!
No, that was for me!
Jojo, wait!
Wait for us!
Jojo!
Menacing
Slash
What?!
Tumble
Jojo!
The tree branches...
Zoom
Jojo!
Oh, no!
Jojo fell down the stairs!
Oh, but he's moving.
The tree branches must have broken his fall!
Did the tree branches cut my leg?
No...
It was already cut before I fell!
That's why I fell down the stairs.
There's no doubt about it.
But...
Jojo!
Are you all right?
Oh?
He's able to summon a pretty strong Stand.
I see...
No wonder he wants me to get rid of him.
But...
He is no match for my Stand.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 2: Who Will Be the Judge!?
You really scared me.
Are you okay, Jojo?
You're really lucky.
If you were even fifteen centimeters off,
you would have hit the flagstone.
Accidents happen all the time on these steps.
Starting tomorrow, you should
hold my hand when you go down, Jojo.
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
You
seem to have cut your left leg.
You should use this handkerchief
as an emergency binding.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It's just a scratch.
Hold it.
Thanks.
I haven't seen you around before.
Do you go to our school?
I'm Noriaki Kakyoin.
I just transferred here yesterday.
Nice to meet you.
Huh...
He said his name was Kakyoin.
He's not bad.
Really?
I still like Jojo better.
Me, too.
What?
What are you talking about?
Give it up.
I'm the best for Jojo.
At the time, I was weakened...
Because I was only a head.
If I hadn't stolen Jonathan Joestar's body...
If I didn't have his energy,
I would have had very little.
I never could have survived at the bottom
of the ocean for a hundred years.
But this body itself is like a
bond between parent and child,
and it seems to connect with his descendants.
They are aware of my existence.
The new power that I have acquired
by obtaining Jonathan's body...
The Stand!
This Stand also affects the
bodies of his descendants.
Advantages and disadvantages
come hand in hand. That is inevitable.
I must eliminate them...
I must eradicate Jonathan's family.
What's the deal with this cramped room?
This is why I hate Japan.
Avdol, how can you stand this?
It is quite fascinating...
This thing they call "the tea ceremony."
Tea ceremony, nothing.
Instant coffee is plenty good!
By the way, about DIO...
Mr. Joestar, now that we know of his existence,
wouldn't it be safe to assume
that he knows about us, as well?
Indeed. But if we don't
know what he's going to do,
or even know what his powers are...
Japanese coffee tastes terrible!
That's American coffee.
Jojo, how did you get that cut?
Nurse's Office
You didn't get into another fight, did you?
And take off your hat!
It's poor manners!
For pity's sake...
Sensei, has Jojo ever gotten hurt in a fight?
There's no way that would happen.
Yeah!
Well, you've got a point.
Then I guess I'll believe that
you just fell, you scatterbrain.
Hey, hold on.
What are you trying to do?
I'm cutting your pants.
Like hell you are.
Well, I can't treat you through them.
I'll take them off.
Cutting them is a waste.
You're surprisingly stingy.
Now then, while Jojo is taking off his pants,
I'll take your temperatures and
prove that you're faking ill.
We really have colds.
Yeah. Let us go home early.
Nope!
Whoops.
What is this?
Jotaro Kujo, I will kill you today
with my Stand! —Noriaki Kakyoin
K-Kakyoin?
Hey... S-Sensei!
What are you doing?!
What does it look like?
Swish
I'm waving around the
thermometer to reset it.
Swish
Th-Thermometer? Sensei...
Sensei, that's a pen!
A pen? Did you say a pen?!
Does this look like a pen to you?!
How... How stupid can you be?
This thermometer actually
looks like a pen to you?!
Then have a...
better...
look!
Stab
She's...
Noriaki Kakyoin
My eye! My eye!
Jojo...
You're not going to say
that this looks like a pen, are you?!
How is she so strong?
This isn't a woman's strength.
I saw something unknown
crawling up from the floor earlier.
Was it a Stand?
Noriaki Kakyoin...
Was he the one who cut my leg on the stairs?
Precisely.
Y-You're...
Hey. Short time no see.
My Stand's possessed that
nurse and is controlling her.
Attacking my Stand will
mean hurting that nurse, Jojo.
You bastard... Just who the hell are you?!
I told you. I'm Noriaki Kakyoin.
The name of my Stand is Hierophant Green.
I am human, but my loyalty is to him...
Therefore...
I shall kill you!
Bang
I won't hurt her.
Now that I've dragged it out... I see...
It's just a sleazy Stand that can't
do anything but possess people.
Kakyoin, this is your Stand?
All green and striped...
It looks like a shiny melon.
You're going to regret
dragging that out of her, Jojo.
Squish
Don't try to act tough.
I can see my finger marks on your forehead.
If I go ahead and crush your
Stand's head like a melon,
it looks like your head will be crushed, too.
I'm gonna keep a grip on you for a while.
I'll take you to the old man.
I'm sure he'd love to meet you...
And I'd like to know more about DIO myself.
What?
Green fluid is coming out of his Stand's hands?
I already told you, Jojo...
That you would regret this.
Feel the attack of my Stand, Hierophant Green!
Don't make any weird moves!
Emerald Splash!
What do you think?
Emerald Splash...
What looked like the bodily fluids
of my Stand, Hierophant Green,
was a vision of destructive energy!
It's pierced through your Stand's chest.
Therefore, your insides
have been torn to shreds.
And that nurse...
Wh-What?
I'm certain that I removed the Stand from her...
I already told you...
Attacking my Hierophant Green
would mean hurting her.
My Stand can reach further than yours,
but it doesn't like open spaces.
It prefers to hide within something.
If you drag it out, it gets angry.
That's why, when it came out
from her throat, it hurt her.
It's your fault, Jojo!
This is your responsibility!
This is your fault, Jojo!
You did this!
If you had let me kill you in the first place,
this nurse wouldn't have been hurt.
You're trying to stand up?
But how sad...
If I were to compare you to something,
it'd be a sandbag in front of of a boxer.
You stood back up only to be hit again.
Menacing
I, Jotaro Kujo,
am labeled a punk.
Ramen
I tend to overdo it with my opponents in fights,
so much that some are still in the hospital.
There was one idiot teacher who was all talk,
so I taught him a lesson,
and he hasn't come back to school.
At restaurants that served me lousy food,
I leave without paying the bill all the time.
But...
Even I
know nauseating evil when I see it.
Evil is when you use the
weak for your own gain,
and crush them under your foot.
Especially a woman!
That is exactly what you've done!
Your Stand isn't visible to the
victim or the law. Therefore...
I shall judge you!
Evil?
There, you are wrong.
Evil refers to the loser.
Justice refers to the victor.
The last man standing!
The method doesn't matter!
Grab
The loser is the evil one.
And now, the final blow!
What? The loser is evil?
Emerald Splash!
Well, in that case...
What?!
Impossible! He shrugged off the Emerald Splash?
...you're the evil one after all!
The one who'll be the judge is...
my Stand!
Smash!
What a powerful Stand...
You just caught it by surprise
and hurt its chest a little.
Lucky for me it's not a weak Stand,
but I have a feeling it'll become more violent.
That was close.
She should be fine once her wounds are treated.
What was that? A gas explosion?
It came from the nurse's office!
None of you leave the classroom!
I'll leave the rest to them.
I'm ditching school today.
I've got to have him explain
some things about DIO.
Hierophant Green
Noriaki Kakyoin
Ping
Jotaro's totally thinking
about me at school right now!
I felt like I had a connection
with my son just now.
I'm not thinking about you.
Jotaro!
Wh-What about school? And who is that?
H-He's covered in blood!
D-Don't tell me... you did that?
It's got nothing to do with you.
I'm looking for the Old Man.
Sucks having to find him in such a huge house.
I think your grandfather's in the tea room,
with Mister Avdol.
Oh, Jotaro...
You won't tell me anything.
Even though I... I...
worry about you so much.
But I know that, deep down,
you're a sweet boy.
Hey.
Yes?
You look a little pale this morning.
Are you all right?
Yay! Fine, thank you!
I knew it.
Well, this is no good. It's too late for him.
He's not going to make it.
He'll die in the next few days.
Jotaro, it's not your fault.
Look. The reason that this
man swore loyalty to DIO
and came to kill you...
is right here!
What the hell is that?!
Next Episode Preview
This isn't good at all... At this rate...
Sometimes having a cold isn't so bad.
I don't really understand, either.
This is the one thing I feared most!
Tell me how we should deal with this!
Episode 3:
The Curse of DIO