Hey, rifle heads!
Do I have to wait forever for food?
Kars!
What?
Von Stroheim!
Double shock!
This is spookier than meeting a ghost!
Kars!
And von Stroheim, who I thought
was blown to bits in Mexico.
They're both right here!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 19: A Race Toward the Brink
Kars!
And von Stroheim, too!
His hand is metal!
And his face is wrapped
in strange machinery!
The Germans are hiding
incredible medical technology.
Is it for military use?
Is that what saved you, von Stroheim?
JoJo, I've come back from hell.
S-Should I be happy?
He's not exactly a bad guy,
but he's a German soldier.
And I don't like how he struts around.
Still, I'm a bit happy.
Sit down on that sofa and watch me work.
H-He's glaring at me.
He knows I killed Esidisi!
And he hates me for it!
Even so!
Y-You think I'm gonna let you
psyche me out, Kars?!
JoJo...
Once I take the Stone...
...I'm going to end you.
Too bad Wamuu is in Greece.
I can't allow a Hamon-user
who could beat Esidisi to live.
Are you speaking as a warrior?
Or do you just want revenge, Kars?!
Over here, Kars!
I will be your final opponent!
No machine can stop me!
You think so?
Arms don't bend like that!
Both of his are mechanical?!
Now for the fun!
He's...!
His fingers squeeze at 1950 kg/cm2,
almost twice Santviento's strength!
You utter fool!
German science is the world's finest!
My arms were built based on
Santviento's abilities!
And so, Kars...
...we've calculated how much we should
reduce you to eliminate your power.
I'll pluck you like a chicken,
one square centimeter at a time!
Hey, JoJo!
Ouch!
Don't you dare feel sorry for me!
My proud new form...
...is the embodiment of the peak
of German engineering!
In other words, I am something
more than human!
Take this, Kars!
This machine gun can fire 600 rounds
per minute through 30 mm armor plating!
It'll whittle you down to size
in no time at all!
His torso is mechanical, too?!
What is that?!
Downstairs!
The Stone will be mine!
Getting it cost Esidisi his life!
I will not let his sacrifice be in vain!
That light!
The blade in his arm is glowing!
I control light!
Brilliant Bone Blade!
I-Impossible!
That blade is made of
hardened bone and skin!
It shouldn't be able to deflect bullets,
let alone slice them in half!
Why does his blade glow like that?!
Here he comes! Here he comes!
Here he comes!
T-That sound!
Up close, von Stroheim saw
and understood the blade's secret!
The edge wasn't a simple wedge!
It was moving at high speed!
Tiny, sharp claws like shark's teeth
slid along the outer edge of the blade!
Each claw refracted light, making the
blade look as though it were glowing!
We can't win!
Not with my weapons or
any modern technology.
We can't beat him!
And what was Santviento?
Nothing but a child!
He was a guard dog!
He couldn't compare to us.
Now I'll take the Stone.
K-Kars!
That ice-cold sheen!
An edge that can cut bullets!
I can't block that thing
with my bare hands!
Even with concentrated Hamon,
it would slice right through me!
To be honest, I want to run away!
He's too dangerous!
I can't think of a way around that blade!
But I can't just let him take the Stone!
If he obtained the Stone's power,
I'd never be able to beat him!
Damn it all!
I have to get Wamuu's antidote!
Kars wants to kill me!
Was this in my horoscope?!
The Stone is in this pocket.
The Red Stone of Aja!
I have waited for 4 --
No, 5,000 years for this!
And at last it is mine.
It was destined to fall into my hands.
Kars!
Wait there!
I'll kill you soon.
T-That bastard...
H-He really does hate me.
Letting him have the Stone
would mean the end!
Kars, you fool...
Don't think you've beaten me yet.
German science is the world's greatest!
Von Stroheim, you idiot!
How can you boast at a time like this?!
UV laser, activate!
The Stone!
H-Hey, it's sliding down the slope!
Damn it!
The Stone is sliding toward the cliff!
If it falls off...
W-What the...?
W-What's going on?
Kars!
JoJo, go after the Stone!
You can still grab it!
D-Dang...
He's moving so fast!
He plans to grab the Stone
and fall off the cliff!
He won't stop for the edge!
D-Damn it!
That cliff is hundreds of meters high!
Kars could survive the fall.
But it's as high as a skyscraper!
It'd be certain death for me!
He's caught up!
JoJo plans to slow down at the edge!
But not Kars!
JoJo can't win!
I won't let this slime have the Stone!
Run hard, JoJo!
JoJo, when I reach down to grab
the Stone, I'll be vulnerable.
You'll kick me then, won't you?
You'll attack me with Hamon,
even if the Stone falls.
Will that work, JoJo?
JoJo... He's...
Right on the nose!
Here's the kick you ordered!
Ah! He used his legs to pick up
the Stone by its chain!
What's with that arrogant grin?
I'm the one who should smile.
I expected as much.
A trick like that is really
not good enough.
My kick was aimed at the snow!
And it worked as a brake!
Looks like I'm the one
who made the nice catch!
Enjoy your trip!
N-No way!
A blade from the foot?!
JoJo!
He's falling!
T-That blade!
Kars's blade is melding with my body!
S-Son of a...!
It's 175 meters to the bottom!
Five seconds until impact!
Falling with this guy?
No thanks!
Clinging Hamon!
S-So heavy!
Hamon goes through fluids easily,
but ice and snow are solid!
However, water is slowly sliding down
the ice, so Hamon works perfectly!
That Stone will be mine!
T-That's it exactly.
That tenacity is what scares me most!
I'm best at exploiting negligence.
So a tenacious foe is the worst.
It's the opposite of negligence!
It will be mine!
More icicles!
I have to get this blade out first!
Wait, I can just send Hamon
through the blade!
Take this!
Just as I thought.
I knew you'd try using my blade.
In that case...
...into the cliff with you!
And then...
N-No!
H-He's gonna cut me!
Kars is waiting for JoJo
to rebound!
JoJo can't dodge!
I'll slice you in half
and pick up the Stone at the bottom!
You--!
Y-You won't cut this, right?
You won't chop the Stone in half
along with me!
I can use your tenacity
as a defensive measure!
Hamon kick!
Eat this, Kars!
He's using the falling icicles
as a rope!
But they're falling!
He can't reach!
In that case, I'll lend a hand!
Caesar!
Nice timing, eh, JoJo?
Since when do you two
work so well together?!
Using falling icicles as a rope?
Only JoJo would try something
that stupid.
It was predictable, that's all.
And at last you're able to think up
a stupid trick, Caesar!
W-What?!
Nice! Nice!
Very nice, Caesarino!
If Lisa Lisa is up there,
give her a message!
The Stone is safe!
I kept it from him!
That was close!
Pull him on up, Caesar.
Now, my German friend...
...your body is more durable
than even theirs are.
If you stop with the snobbery,
we can work together.
JoJo, you're a lucky one.
I'll let you hold the Stone for me
for another day.
Five days until the remaining ring dissolves.
So this is Switzerland's
famous Saint Moritz.
A winter sports hub often called
Sun Valley.
Chic, relaxed and sophisticated.
A resort the wealthy visit on holidays.
Even the cats look
they're owned by actresses.
Aren't we fussy?
Not even a glance for shrimp.
This little princess doesn't know
a thing about the world.
Well, then...
...would this smoked salmon
suit your palate?
Now, now!
I've found your preference.
Reach! Reach!
Just a bit more...
Stretch up a bit more...
Gotcha!
Oh? Did I upset you?
Enjoy, you pompous puffball!
No, no.
That was mean of me.
It's just because I'm on edge.
Five days till the ring dissolves.
Kars is serious about killing me.
I can feel the threats closing in.
I have to relax.
I'm the one always saying
that you can't mope about stuff.
JoJo, what are you doing?!
Come here and look!
Yes, ma'am!
Be right there!
That building is the address
Esidisi put on the package.
Looks like an old, closed-down hotel.
A perfect hideout for Kars
during the day.
The windows are boarded up.
No sunlight in there.
I'm sure Kars hides
there during the day.
I bet he's waiting for Wamuu.
So, what is the plan?
That's easy.
We should attack now!
I agree. Kars can't go out
during daylight.
We have the advantage.
JoJo?
I...
I disagree.
I think it's more dangerous
with the sun up.
Kars has lived for thousands of years
like this.
He won't have left himself defenseless!
Huh?!
Walking into his lair would be suicidal!
I won't go!
It'd be like a bug walking into a web!
Come on.
JoJo, this isn't like you.
Are you scared?
I'll take Sun Tzu's advice here.
Only fight when victory is assured.
I said I won't go!
Are you chickening out?!
Chickening out?
My head is cool. I'm thinking straight.
We have to wait for his move!
You want a sure victory?
Kars is alone. We are four!
We have the numbers!
We have to strike now,
before Wamuu arrives!
Caesar, you're going off half-cocked!
Keep your head. Calm down and think.
If we walk in there,
he's the one in control!
I'm not half-cocked.
I'm gonna end this!
I'll finish the fight that killed
both of our grandfathers!
I'll destroy Kars!
You'll finish it?
What about our dead grandfathers?
Who cares?
Don't drag the dead into this,
you idiot!
What did you say, JoJo?!
Family you've never met
doesn't mean crap!
Only a complete moron
would die for that!
Caesar?
Watch your mouth, JoJo!
What was that for, you--?
A sucker punch, eh?!
Oh, it's on!
What the hell, Caesar?!
Shut the hell up, JoJo!
Caesar, stop it!
You too, JoJo!
Caesar!
Y-You bastard...
Have you lost it?
You're acting like a madman!
JoJo, I thought you'd understand
inheriting a battle like this.
I was wrong!
I'm going.
Caesar, JoJo is right.
It's too dangerous.
We don't know what might be in there.
We will wait for Kars.
That's an order, Caesar.
Protecting the Stone
is our first objective.
Coach, I'm sorry.
I can't obey.
You know this is a blood issue.
It's a Zeppeli problem!
I can't leave it unsettled
while I know where Kars is!
I can't sit back
and wait for him to come!
Well?
Follow him and stop him from entering,
even if it means force.
C-Caesar...why?
Why are you so grim all of a sudden?
Why can't you wait a while?
JoJo, you've touched on
a piece of his hidden past.
You didn't mean it, but your words
hit him where he's most sensitive.
His hidden past?
W-What could it be?
Next episode
I feel like I did when I was poor!
I'll use my viciousness to destroy you!
Very well. You are worthy
of death at my hands!
Chapter 20: Young Caesar