By that time,
my life...
had already ended.
What?!
Above us! It's a helicopter!
Now they're cornered.
And whoever Bucciarati and
his men were meeting in Rome
will be dealt with by Green Tea.
We have to take care of him before the
mold's killing spree reaches the Colosseum!
Bucciarati,
we can leave the guy beneath
the ground to you, right?
Go, Giorno!
Run, Mista!
All right! Let's go, Giorno!
Either way...
I'm taking care of you first...
Buccia... rati...
Episodio 31 Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 2
Bucciarati...
How dare you ambush
me back at that village...
I'm never falling for that again.
How dare you do something so cleaver?!
No, wait...
Something so lever... no wait.
Something so beaver...
wait, or was it sever? Griever?
You mean "clever"?
I knew that, damn it!
What are you, a language teacher?!
Y-Y-You jerk!
Oh, yeah. I need to record a video.
It shouldn't take me too
long to take care of you.
Let's see...
Zipper Man!
H-He's... His power and speed...
I-If we're doing this one-on-one...
I don't even need to dive into the ground.
Th-This ability...
It surpasses my Zipper Man...
both in speed and in power!
It's recoil. He's hitting
the ground with his elbows.
He's using the ground to give him elasticity
and increasing his power with that recoil.
That's why he's fast!
Just like a boxer using the ring ropes
to increase the power of his punches!
Sanctuary!
Take this! I'm out of time!
As I thought... There's
no mold growing on you,
even though you fell.
Cioccolata's Green Tea will
kill any living creature.
What the hell's going on with your body?
I mean, I guess I'll just have to pulverize
every last inch of your body
until you can't move anymore...
w-w-with my Sanctuary!
Giorno Giovanna!
I heard that he's a newbie.
He has the ability to give objects life.
The bullets that missed...
The plant that has a hold on this
helicopter must be his plant!
They're coming.
How dare they underestimate me?
Your life force energy is
no match for my Green Tea!
I'll rot all of these vines!
We're making this helicopter
take off, Green Tea!
Spread your mold!
We're breaking free of these vines!
Wh-What?!
I can't take off!
It's not moving at all!
Th-That's not good!
Okay, looks like it's grown to its full size.
It's turned into a tree!
Now that helicopter is secured.
Mista! We're gonna climb up the
tree to get to the helicopter!
There's no need, Giorno.
It's well within range of my bullets.
Yee-haw!
Go, Bullets!
Your target is his head!
What?!
Mista! The others are saying they can't
find him anywhere in the helicopter!
Where is he?! What the hell?!
There's no way he can hide!
He can't get out, either!
Everyone, look for him! Find hi—
Number Two! Number Three!
N-Not good! Mista, hurry and
call everyone back! Hurry—
Mista!
Number Two! Number Three!
What happened to you guys?!
Th-That's impossible!
Why isn't he here?
Each Stand should only have one ability!
His ability is to attack you
with mold if you drop down to
a lower position than
where you currently stand.
That should be the only one!
Run, Number One...
Number Six! Seven!
We can't... defeat him...
Hurry up and get out of this helicopter!
He's—
...too dangerous!
Mista! Hurry up and call the Bullets back!
Undo your Stand ability!
I can't... I can't call them back...
He got the Bullets...
I-I underestimated him...
Mista!
Mista! Send me over there!
I'll go bring everyone back!
No, it's no use, Number Five.
He's captured the Bullets
that he's destroyed,
because he knows Mista won't be able
to heal unless he gets his Stand back.
I can't heal him.
N-No...
And he's probably waiting for you to come.
If he manages to destroy you,
the final Bullet, Mista will die.
He's someone we should've faced head-on!
Mista! I'm leaving Trish and Narancia here.
Right...
Watch over them!
Mista! Mista...
Follow him... Number Five.
Back Giorno up...
Take this bullet.
Okay...
I feel a life force...
Why couldn't the Bullets find him?
I don't know his exact location,
but he didn't leave the helicopter.
In that case...
Golden Wind!
There's no effect?
What is he doing?
How is he hiding in there?
Medical supplies?
He's a doctor?
The aftermath of the mold...
It's spreading to the Colosseum!
There's no more time! I have to defeat
him immediately or all will be lost!
Th-The enemy's true identity is...
Come over here, Number One!
Don't go any closer, Giorno! It's a trap!
Useless!
What?!
Wh-What the hell is that thing?
Giorno, be caref—
Giorno!
Curiosity...
is the most important
factor for mental growth.
I've never been so grateful
as I am right now for all the experimentation
that was conducted on me as a child.
I made very close observations
on what parts of the human body
I could sever and still keep that body alive...
Of course, I'm quite aware of which veins
need to be closed off to
prevent bleeding out, too.
And if I cover the parts that
I sever with Green Tea's mold,
I can continue moving around,
despite being in pieces,
and hide wherever I need to.
You can't fall, Giorno!
If you fall any further,
the mold's going to attack you!
G-Giorno!
Secco
Sanctuary
Hurry and climb up!
There are times when you truly feel
blessed, aren't there, Giorno Giovanna?
I believe there are two situations
in which you feel blessed.
The first is when despair changes
to hope... You feel blessed.
When your plant grabbed on to this helicopter,
I actually panicked because
I thought I was in danger.
I was in utter despair.
But I got through it.
I was able to turn that despair around
with my experience and mental strength.
And that makes me feel
truly blessed right now.
Golden Wi—
Don't you dare climb up here!
Giorno!
Did you forget that both of
my legs were still hiding?!
And the second situation that
makes one feel blessed...
is when you look down upon
someone who's in utter despair!
I've won!
By the time you hit the ground,
the mold will tear your body to shreds!
Giorno, take this!
Jump in there, Giorno!
Hurry and return to the helicopter!
Grazie, Number Five!
Pound him!
How pitiful.
Nothing's changed, Giorno Giovanna.
I, Cioccolata, am still going to win!
The branch you just grew is also living.
Meaning if it drops even a few centimeters,
mold will attack that branch!
Jump onto the helicopter, Giorno!
Hurry!
Giorno!
I did it! Now, show me that expression!
Show me despair!
Show me, as clear as can be,
the moment you lose all hope and die!
Show me your despair as
you fall to your death!
Bene.
The angle I calculated toward the
helicopter's propellers was perfect.
Because it was alive, the branch
was destroyed by the mold.
However,
the part of the branch that fell
from its root no longer holds life.
It's just a piece of wood.
Because you destroyed it,
the branch returned to being a bullet.
By the way, all that bullshit about being
blessed that you were yapping about...
I can't say I feel blessed at all,
even though I'm looking at you.
Because I've been winning
against you from the start.
You did it! I can't believe it, Giorno!
That was close!
You defeated him before the
mold got to the Colosseum!
Please take care of Mista's
wounds, too, Giorno!
That was close! Now the rest of
the Bullets will be back, too.
Could you move just a little
to the right, Number Five?
Huh?
I might just be worrying too much,
but... What was his name? Cioccolata?
He might actually be...
You're just pretending
to be dead, aren't you?!
And you're thinking.
Giorno?
If you can move your body just a few
centimeters before I climb up there,
you can slip beneath the trench and escape.
You'll be able to activate the mold again,
and you'll win. That's what you're thinking.
To be honest, I have a hole
in my right lung right now.
My subclavian vein has been
severed, and four of my ribs,
my right humerus, and my right
hand bones have been shattered.
I'm honestly not sure how
fast I can get up there.
But my Stand is Golden Wind.
It's a power type with a range of two meters.
If I just take a moment,
I'll be able to end you.
H-He's dead! You shot him through the head!
Good point.
If you continue to stay still,
I'll incapacitate you,
but I promise you I won't do anything else.
I'm giving you a choice.
So, what are you going to do?
I'm going to start climbing now.
Stay away from me!
Look behind you, you moron!
I've taken Mista and the turtle hostage!
You dumbass! While you were busy talking,
you apparently didn't notice
that I snuck my right arm
up from under the tree's shadow!
I'm going to chop off Mista's neck now!
If you come after me,
you won't be able to treat Mista!
Mista!
I'm the winner, after all!
Take this!
It's true.
I kept talking because I
wanted to buy some time.
The time I needed to make
the bullet that went through
your head earlier evolve
and return to your wound.
The piece that remained in your head lured
the bullet and returned to being a stag beetle.
When I aimed for the propellers,
I imbued it with Golden Wind's life force...
so that I could finish you for good,
whether you were dead or alive.
B-But you said... th-that if I stayed
still.... y-you wouldn't do anything...
Oh, please.
Did you really think you'd be that lucky?
A piece of shit like you?
Y... You're so mean!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
WRYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY!
Useless!
Burnable Trash Pickup
Mon, Wed, Fri
Giorno!
Mista's waking up!
Mista! Mista!
What's that doing there?
Is that Cioccolata's... Don't tell me...
Was he actually on the
phone during the battle?
But with who? What was he telling them?
Why, though? Cioccolata...
Why aren't you answering your phone?
But I'm calling you...
Um, it's flashing...
What's this mean again? Um...
O-Oh, right!
It does this when I have voicemails, I think!
How many do I have? Two!
When did he call?
Was it when I was chasing Bucciarati?
It's me, Secco.
I-It's Cioccolata!
I finished off the gunslinger Mista.
Yes!
Now it looks like the newbie, Giorno Giovanna,
is trying to climb up to the helicopter.
But it doesn't matter. I win.
You concentrate on Bucciarati.
I'll scratch your back when you get back.
I'm sure you want some sugar
cubes, too, don't you?
I'll throw you some.
You deserve a treat.
How many would you like?
Um... Um...
Two?
No! I want more! More! Mooooooore!
I'm only kidding. I'll throw you five.
I'll throw five at once.
Think you can catch them all with
your mouth? No using your hands.
Listen well, Secco.
We are invincible.
The strong have the right
to rule over the weak.
No, I should say that the strong
have a duty to rule over others.
Even if that includes the boss.
I plan to surpass the boss
during this battle, as well.
You're going to do this, too, Secco.
You are strong.
Giorno's here. I need to hang up.
But that's why...
I love you.
Let's go.
This should be far enough.
I should've lost that underground guy...
Episodio 32
Green Tea and Sanctuary, Part 3