Good morning. This is Morioh Radio,
brought to you again today
by your neighbor, Kai Harada.
Our first song of the morning is this...
All right, let's eat.
Oh, yes. I have a present for you.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 21     Yoshikage Kira Just Wants to Live Quietly, Part 1
Mr. Kira... Um, Mr. Kira?
Mr. Kira, if you're not busy,
would you like to have lunch with us?
Sorry, but I'll have to pass.
I need to go deliver these documents.
Goodbye.
Give it up!
He never wants to hang out.
Whenever we invite him out somewhere,
I can't tell if he's really having fun or not.
Yoshikage Kira, age 33, single.
He's serious about his work
and gets it done efficiently,
but the guy lacks any passion.
He's not a bad guy, but he just
doesn't stand out very much.
Hey, what are you so grumpy about?
The new girls at work just
invited me to lunch, that's all.
I promised that I'd have lunch with you,
so there's no way I'd go with them.
You heard me decline immediately, didn't you?
Have I ever left you alone? Hm?
Now, stop worrying about it,
and let's pick out some sandwiches together.
Katsu Sandwich
Come on, which one do you want?
Isn't the bread wonderfully soft?
The sandwiches at this shop
use bread that's freshly baked at
11 AM, so they're really popular.
They're usually sold out by 1 PM.
You can feel how warm they are,
even through the wrapper.
The katsu in the katsu sandwiches
are freshly fried, too, and so crispy.
Oh, no.
You broke though the wrapper,
and now the sauce is spilling out.
You naughty girl.
But now this sandwich has a hole in it,
so let's buy the one below it.
Thank you very much.
Morioh is such a beautiful town...
Could there possibly be
another town this wonderful?
It almost feels like we're on a picnic.
She's getting a bit ripe.
I guess it's about time to break up with her...
Time to sever ties.
"Sever ties"...
Maybe I'll go find a new girl,
one who's on vacation or something.
Oh, it's just a dog.
Shigechi!
Oyo?
Josuke, Okuyasu!
Hey, perfect timing, Shigechi.
Sorry this is out of the blue,
but please lend us some lunch money.
We forgot to bring money.
Huh? What are you talking about?
You guys should have your
share from the lottery.
That money's in the bank.
It's a pain to have to get money
from the bank just for some lunch.
A thousand yen will cover both of us.
Yeah.
Come on, please?
We'll go to the bank right after school.
Hey, that bag... You've got a
sandwich from St. Gentlemen!
They actually weren't sold out?
You can't have this! This is my lunch.
Oh, fine. I'll lend you a thousand yen...
That's the spirit!
Thanks!
I'm gonna keep an IOU for this in my planner,
so don't skip out on me.
You're the one who skips out all the time!
Let's see... "June 24th."
Well, anyway, thanks again, Shigechi.
"Lent 1,000 yen"... Lent?
Later!
Um, how do you write the
kanji for "lent" again?
Lent...
Lent
Well, whatever.
I'll just write it in hiragana.
I don't know how to write "Josuke"
or "Okuyasu" in kanji, anyway.
Huh?
M-My sandwich...
Wh-Where is it?
Oh, it's right there.
I feel like it's further away than
it was before, but whatever.
Th-That's...
Hey, Josuke, Okuyasu, wait!
You need to put your
thumbprints on this IOU!
Your thumbprints!
What? That little brat!
He mistook my bag for his and took it?
Jeez, what a pain.
How do we even put our thumbprints on it?
You know, you cut your thumb with a knife...
Y-You don't need to be so dramatic.
Fine, I'll just take your signatures.
Hey, let's hurry up and go to St. Gentlemen.
They're gonna sell out.
This isn't good. If he opens that bag...
She's wearing the ring I bought her.
And my fingerprints are on her...
With the police's investigative skills,
it'll just be a matter of time before
they trace the ring back to me.
I, Yoshikage Kira, have never left a
single clue in the last fifteen years.
And I'm not going to let
that kid do that for me!
Josuke, let's hurry.
Yeah.
I'll be waiting outside.
What should I do?
I'll just have to take it from him.
The best thing to do is to
swipe it without him noticing.
Shigechi!
You're super lucky, damn it.
The St. Gentlemen sandwiches
are already sold out! Damn it!
Oh, I see. So they sold out.
Well, that's too bad.
In that case, I guess I wouldn't mind
selling you mine for 10,000 yen.
You're such a damn cheapskate.
I guess we don't have a choice.
Let's go to Hokaben, Josuke.
Hokaben, huh?
The stuff we could get for
500 yen each with a drink
wouldn't really fill us up.
If we get school lunch as usual,
it'll be plenty, though.
Koichi said he was getting school lunch, too.
No way! He's with Yukako Yamagishi, isn't he?
Why do I have to eat lunch
with a happy couple?
Not to mention, with the lunches there,
the meat's only about a millimeter thick,
and who knows what that stuff
in the miso soup really is?
Hey, there are a lot of drinks in
the prep room in my school's gym.
The gym teacher always sneaks
coffee and tea from there.
All of the teachers are in the
faculty room during lunch,
so I sneak in through the window
sometimes and take some.
Wanna just go buy lunch and come with me?
What the heck? Are you
stealing from the school?
That's pretty cheap.
We can at least buy our drinks.
I'm not that greedy.
See ya!
And I was trying to be nice...
See ya. Oh, and pay me back
my thousand yen tomorrow!
Oh, pardon me!
I wasn't watching where I was going.
Sorry about that.
Crap... It's good that he
parted ways with his friends,
but he's heading back to school.
He's planning to eat it at school...
What should I do?
They were calling him "Shigechi," right?
There's no doubt he'll open
that bag in a matter of minutes...
This is extremely bad.
Now, then... I should be able
to eat my lunch in peace here.
Whoops! I almost forgot!
Before I eat my sandwiches,
I need to brew my coffee.
Since I'm here, I'm gonna have
some coffee before I leave.
You're a lucky boy, Shigechi.
If you had seen what was inside,
I would've had to get rid of you.
Hey, Josuke! This is it!
It's smaller than I thought...
Wh-What?
They just said they wouldn't come here!
Shigechi, you here?
Shigechi!
Oh, hey. It's Okuyasu and Josuke.
We decided we'd have some coffee after all.
Because we got the 500-yen Makunouchi bentos!
Hmph. After calling me greedy and a thief...
You've got some nerve!
Now, now, don't be so stubborn.
People tend to change the
way they think over time.
What should I do?
Eliminating one of them would
be easy, but not so with three.
Damn it! And she's only a few
dozen centimeters away...
Hey, Shigechi, get me a drink, too.
I'd actually like Japanese tea instead of coffee.
Is there any black tea? Like milk tea?
Blech. Makunouchi with milk tea? That's gross.
Damn it! He's planning to
eat his lunch up there.
At this rate, he's going to
open the bag in front of them!
Aw, it's soy sauce again.
The katsu here always come with soy sauce.
Huh? You're supposed to
eat katsu with soy sauce.
What?! You idiot!
You're supposed to eat
it with tonkatsu sauce!
If you used soy sauce, the tonkatsu
sauce would lose its namesake!
Who cares about that?
Yes!
Wh-What?
Crap!
What?
Morioh Landmark #7
Bakery "St. Gentlemen"
How to get there: Get off of the bus
bound for Morioh Budogaoka High
School and walk two minutes. It's a
bakery on the Green Road leading
from the station. It's popular
because of the varieties of bread
made there using a stone oven.
Customers include students,
housewives, and office ladies.
Their most popular items are their
sandwiches, which always sell out.
Crap!
What?
Hey! What are you doing, Josuke?
Hey! You weren't trying to
steal my sandwich, were you?
No! Don't be stupid.
There was a weird sound
that got my attention,
so I was just taking a look.
Don't you dare touch it!
There's no way you would just look at it!
I know you're going to say,
"Their teriyaki chicken sandwich is my
favorite, Shigechi. Give me a bite!"
You sure are a greedy little guy.
You got my tea yet? Where's my tea?
Don't forget, I want milk tea.
I'm just about to make them.
Now!
I did it.
Here you go.
I brought your Japanese tea and milk tea.
Sweet.
Thanks!
What's with you?
Wh-Where did you put m-my sandwich?
Huh? Oh...
Looks like it's gone.
But we don't know what
happened to it, right, Okuyasu?
Yeah.
Stop messing around!
How could you not know?
You're the only ones here!
No, we seriously have no idea!
Seriously, we're not messing around.
No joke, we really have no idea.
Y-You jerks... I-I'm really gonna get mad!
We're telling the truth!
You really need to stop.
Why would we take your sandwich—
We'll find out the truth soon enough!
I just need my Harvest to check the room!
You're such a pest! Yeah, go ahead!
Do it! Look as much as you want.
We wouldn't steal your stupid sandwich.
What? I can't see what
they're doing from in here.
What is that brat trying to do?
Hey!
I know someone's in the prep room!
That's the gym teacher!
Let's get the hell out of here, Shigechi!
B-But my sandwich!
Now's not the time for that!
Hey, come back here!
Damn you, little brats.
I thought it was strange
that my tea and coffee
kept disappearing so fast. No wonder.
I need to be more careful about locking the door.
That was rather messy,
but I got through this hard situation,
and was able to get her back.
I always have to wonder if
I'm protected by luck...
And if I do things with careful
consideration and in a bold manner,
I have a feeling that I can
live a pretty happy life.
That was close.
I'm so glad you came back to me.
Found it!
Why does someone I don't
know have my sandwich?
Why is an adult that I don't know
sneaking around my middle school?
Could it be that you're
talking to me, little boy?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
This is my sandwich.
I just bought it at St. Gentlemen.
No, that bag is mine!
There are reasons why I know!
They're reasons you
wouldn't understand, though.
Take it back, Harvest!
Wh-What? What's going on?
The bag is being pulled...
Wh-Wha?! Wh-What... My sandwich...
Is this... a r-r-real human hand?
Oh, dear. It seems you've seen it.
It also appears, little boy,
that you have the same power I do.
You can see my Harvest?
H-Hey, what's this hand?
Why are you walking around
with just a hand in a bag?
Are you by yourself? Your two friends...
I believe you called them Josuke and Okuyasu?
Do they have a power similar to yours?
Hey! Don't move!
If you move even a bit, I'm gonna attack!
You're a really creepy guy!
Don't come any closer to me!
I get a really creepy,
unfamiliar feeling from you!
Don't move! Don't move from there!
My name is Yoshikage Kira. I'm 33 years old.
My house is in the northeast section
of Morioh, where all the villas are,
and I am not married.
I work as an employee for the
Kame Yu department stores,
and I get home every day
by 8 PM at the latest.
I don't smoke, but I occasionally drink.
I'm in bed by 11 PM,
and make sure I get eight hours
of sleep, no matter what.
After having a glass of warm milk
and doing about twenty minutes of
stretches before going to bed,
I usually have no problems
sleeping until morning.
Just like a baby, I wake up without
any fatigue or stress in the morning.
I was told there were no
issues at my last checkup.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
I'm trying to explain that I'm a person
who wishes to live a very quiet life.
I take care not to trouble myself
with any enemies, like winning and losing,
that would cause me to lose sleep at night.
That is how I deal with society,
and I know that is what brings me happiness.
Although, if I were to fight,
I wouldn't lose to anyone.
Basically, Shigechi,
you are a troublesome thing
that would hinder my sleep,
therefore my enemy.
Th-That's...
Deadly Queen... is what I've named it.
I'm going to eliminate you now
before you have a chance to speak,
so I can sleep soundly again tonight.
Episode 22
Yoshikage Kira Just Wants to Live Quietly, Part 2