I have proof of your devilish plot, Dio!
He's caught me.
But I won't run.
I came back here to fight JoJo!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 3: Time With Dio
ADJUSTMENT	I found the antidote.
Dad just took it.
Dio, I'm heartbroken.
We were raised as brothers and now
I have to turn you in.
I'm sorry.
You might not believe that,
but I mean it.
That compassion is very like you.
JoJo, this is selfish,
but I have a final favor to ask.
Please, give me time.
Time to turn myself in.
What's this?
I expected him to fight
like a cornered animal!
JoJo, how did you make it
out of that slum alive?!
I'll have to distract him,
then with one quick stab...
I regret my life until now!
Being poor when I was a child
made me greedy!
What I did was wrong.
I tried to poison and rob
the man who raised me!
I came back to turn myself in.
If I wanted to run,
I could have gone anywhere!
T-That's true.
I want to make amends.
Dio --
Careful, Jonathan.
Don't trust a word that snake says.
Who am I, you ask?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Robert E. O. Speedwagon,
the meddler.
I was worried about Jonathan,
so I came back with him.
Since I like you, Jonathan,
let me tell you something.
I was raised in squalor,
and I've seen a lot of lowlifes.
My nose knows the difference
between good and bad.
And this guy stinks worse
than a pile of puke!
I've never met a man
as wicked as him!
Wicked because of circumstance? No!
This man was born bad!
This face is familiar to you, isn't it?
This man has testified
that he sold you the poison.
I've heard enough.
This is truly a shame.
I put the same love and hope into you
as I did my own son.
Dad, you need to rest.
Right, I'll go to bed now.
I don't want to see my son arrested.
JoJo, do what you must.
Yes, Dad.
So this is the end?
They won't catch him.
That face and three moles on his ear...
He was born with the devil's own luck.
JoJo, I want you to be the one
to handcuff me.
For our years together.
All right.
Be careful, Jonathan!
JoJo, being human means having limits.
I've learned something.
The more carefully you scheme,
the more unexpected events come along.
As long as you are human...
What? What do you mean?!
I'm throwing away my humanity, JoJo!
I'm moving beyond humanity!
Where did you get that?
Watch out!
Shoot him now!
I'll use your blood, JoJo!
He...
Dad!
Fire!
JoJo...
D-Dad...
I should have dodged that knife.
I let the mask distract me.
You sacrificed yourself.
Keep this.
It was your mother's.
Dad!
That wound is fatal.
How could I let that happen?!
Sir Joestar... I told you...
It's my fault. If only I
had banished Dio's father.
Dio's father?
When I first joined the force,
there was a man who tried to pawn that ring.
It was Dio's father, Dario Brando.
Yes, it's definitely my ring.
We had a pair made when
we were engaged.
A burglar named Dario Brando
was trying to pawn it.
Brando!
Sir Joestar thought he owed
a life debt to Dario Brando.
But Brando was just a thief rooting
around for gold at the accident site!
Oh, no!
Did he happen to tell you that
I gave him the ring?
He did. What a flimsy lie!
It wasn't a lie.
I did give it to him.
I-Is that true?
He is innocent.
Let him go.
Why would you let him go?!
If I were born in his circumstances,
I may have done the same.
Sell this and buy something
for your family.
Then forsake criminality
and walk an honest path.
Sir Joestar knew the whole truth
before he adopted Dio.
Hang in there, Dad.
The doctors will save you.
JoJo, please don't hate Dio.
I am responsible.
I was hard on you because
you are my real son.
But in Dio's eyes, that may have been
unfair to him.
That could have driven him
to do what he did.
Please bury him next to his father.
Dad...
JoJo, it's not so bad...
...to die in the arms
of your own son.
Sir Joestar!
What a tragedy!
Now his kindness is gone from the world!
No!
Sir Joestar passed his noble spirit
along to Jonathan!
It has become his iron will, his pride
and it will create his future!
Normally I hate spoiled crybabies.
But they are different.
They live life with no regrets.
They're giants!
T-The body!
Dio Brando's body is gone!
You, cop! Get away from the window!
H-His head...
H-He's still alive!
How?! We filled him with bullets!
Watch out! I'm sure he has a weapon!
I-It can't be!
He's coming this way!
What are you waiting for?! Shoot!
Dio, stop right there!
Dio!
Hurry up and
pull the trigger, Jonathan!
He's not dead, even after that.
I don't get it.
I can't understand what's happening.
How could this be?!
JoJo...
This marvelous power comes from
the mask, and your father's blood!
He's sucking out that man's life!
Dio, just what have you become?!
I-I'm so confused...
The knife... Dad's death...
Blood... Dio... The mask...
My notes... The brain...
Unknown abilities... Unknown strength...
Dio, you aren't human anymore!
Dad...
Stop! You don't stand a chance!
I've never seen the like!
Anything that powerful is a monster!
You're right.
Honestly, I'm scared.
But Dio, I can't let you live like this.
It's my fault. I'll finish it!
Jonathan, stop! You'll just be killed!
The brain! The mask unlocks
the brain's hidden potential!
So in order to beat Dio...
The bodies!
Warm blood...
I want to lick it all up!
You don't mind if
I suck your blood, do you?
This is hard. He was my brother.
Dad, please lend me your strength.
I have to be strong.
Dio is no longer human.
He's a monster!
Watch out!
I can't let Dio kill another person!
H-He caught it!
Even after it went through his hand!
Wait, the hole in his head
has already healed!
He's completely immortal!
You're weak! So weak!
JoJo!
I have to play with you a bit more
to test out my new powers.
Even I don't know how far they go yet.
Hiding?
Didn't I just tell you?
Human schemes have their limits.
Cease your useless struggle.
Cowering behind the curtains, are we?
Come on out!
It's not a scheme. It's courage!
He's regenerating while he burns!
Is that the source of his immortality?!
This fire isn't enough!
What are you doing?!
Get out of here, Speedwagon!
This doesn't concern you!
You can't go up!
The fire is spreading!
Jonathan, what are you planning?
Come on up, Dio!
Dio, I won't let you go
beyond these walls!
Jonathan, don't!
Is he using himself as bait
to protect his friend?
It doesn't matter.
I'll just use your blood
to heal these burns.
Fleeing up here is useless!
Falling from this high won't hurt me!
Instead, now the fire has cornered you!
Dad...
Dad, I'll miss you.
Please go to heaven
along with those flames.
And then, help me accomplish my goal.
Give your strength to the fire.
What is Jonathan doing?
No! He couldn't be!
Stop! You mustn't do it!
H-Here he comes.
Utterly pathetic!
Suddenly, JoJo's youth
flashed through his mind!
My youth...
My time with Dio...
Now I'm going to settle the score
for all that time!
He's trying to make the fire
burn as hot as possible!
If the fire burns Dio faster than
he can regenerate, he'll die!
So Jonathan waited for the flames
to spread before going to the roof!
Don't do it!
H-How dare you!
The mansion my ancestors lived in
is burning.
Dad is dead, I have nothing left.
Nothing but my life.
I'll let myself burn!
I'll end your ambition
in exchange for my life!
Goodbye, JoJo!
For a second there I admired your guts.
Now cry tears of joy
since you can die with your dad, fool!
I'm beyond human! Invincible! Immortal!
I will rule this world!
JoJo, you gave me this power!
I can't reach!
Dio, I'm back!
What?! How?!
I won't let you go!
Your fate is sealed!
Here! This is the knife
you killed my father with!
I've crushed his arms to dust and he's
on fire, but he just won't let go!
Very well!
Let's go into the inferno together!
But you'll die alone!
I'll find a way to escape,
no matter how hot it is!
Dad! Lend me your aid!
A scream! A desperate cry!
Whether at an urge from beyond or
an instinct to use his burning home...
JoJo kicked!
And across from that spot...
What the --
...was a statue of the Joestar
family's guardian angel.
How could a worm like you...
I completely forgot!
The more you beat him, the tougher he gets!
JoJo!
This wasn't what my life
was supposed to be.
Jonathan!
Dad...
You're alive.
You're alive!
He...
He won!
There it is.
Next episode
Courage is knowing fear!
This guy's worse than Dio!
Wriggle in despair!
Who do I look like?
Please, teach me how to use Hamon.
Chapter 4: Overdrive