Ow...
Yeah, you're going to have
to go to the hospital.
I know that! I'm asking you to
do something in the meantime!
Very well.
H-Hey, Fugo, you aren't—
Hey!
What the hell is this?!
Staples!
But wow, it actually closed up,
just like closing a comic book!
Narancia, could you wrap up his
stomach with masking tape now?
Sure thing.
You sure this isn't going to get infected?
Don't worry about a thing.
Actually, you know, I kinda like it.
Would you pipe down?
Well done, you guys.
Thanks to you, we were able
to get to Capri safely.
Zucchero, who attacked us on the boat,
and the guy Mista handled
are both passed out on the boat.
No need to worry about them anymore.
Then let's hurry up and go to the place
where the ten billion lire is hidden!
Where did you hide it, Bucciarati?
A hidden safe at the bank?
Or maybe you buried it
in a cave on the island?
Could you wait just a bit longer?
Why's that?
Why are you so worried about the time?
Shh!
Hey, you guys. We're still
in here, so how 'bout it?
Can't you do the cleaning later?
Does your name happen to be Toilette?
Huh? What was that?
If your name is actually Toilette,
that would mean this is your house.
You can boss around anyone
you want in your own house.
But if that isn't the case,
you've got no right to boss me around.
Huh? Hey, wait, dumbass!
Didn't you hear me?
I said not to go in there!
Crack
Wh-What the hell do you think you're doing?!
You want a piece of me?!
What's going on?
A new enemy?
I'll kill you!
Wait!
Everyone, stop Narancia!
Why did you stop me?!
Could you be...
That voice...
It appears we've kept you waiting.
All of you, bow.
This is Mr. Pericolo,
one of the capos of Passione.
I came to accept the ten billion lire,
Bucciarati.
Episodio 09 The First Mission from the Boss
I contacted him as soon
as we reached the island.
Mr. Pericolo came all this
way to accept the money.
One of Passione's capos...
Thank you so much for
coming all this way, sir.
No, no. I'm the one who said I wanted to come.
All of you, lift your heads.
You must be the newbie I heard about.
Yes, sir.
Bucciarati's told me all about you.
Now that you've joined Passione,
you're basically family.
You're free to call me Mr. Pericolo.
Thank you, sir.
You, there. Sorry about earlier.
This one doesn't like being touched.
Sure.
You...
You mean, "Yes, sir!"
Mr. Pericolo,
why are you dressed up as a janitor?
There's a perfectly good reason
for this. I'll tell you later.
More importantly, you do have it, don't you?
The ten billion lire to hand
over to the organization.
Yes, sir. Right here.
What? What did you just say?!
He said it's right here!
Here?!
Bucciarati, where is it?
All I see are urinals...
Plop
I-It was inside the urinal?!
I mean, that's as safe as it gets, but...
Sucks to be the guys who've been
peeing there this whole time!
Yup... It's real.
This necklace alone is worth at least
seven or eight hundred million.
Bucciarati,
I won't bother asking how
you got this fortune.
All the organization cares about
is that you have the money.
Wait, you're already putting it away?
C-Could I just touch it a little?
Maybe even smell it?
The reality this fortune shows us is that
the owner is intelligent and trustworthy.
Congratulations, Bucciarati.
You've been promoted to the position of capo.
H-Hell, yeah! He's a capo!
Bucciarati's finally a capo!
You'll be taking over Polpo's
turf, now that he's dead.
You'll be overseeing the
gambling, money-lending,
and smuggling at the harbor, as well
as the restaurants and hotels in Naples.
Fifty percent of the profit will go to the
organization, and the other fifty will be yours.
That's amazing!
He earned authority just like that!
With Bucciarati's brains and popularity,
he'll be rolling in the cash in no time!
But the ball suddenly started rolling
as soon as this newbie Giorno joined.
Is he some kind of lucky boy or something?
By the way,
I know you just took over for Polpo,
but he had left one job unfinished.
Of course, you'll be taking on any
jobs that Polpo had, Bucciarati.
Are you okay with that?
A job that Polpo left unfinished?
It's a direct order from the boss.
The... boss?
The boss...
The boss no one's ever met?
An order... directly from him?
Correct. I'll tell you right here and now.
You'll be guarding the boss's daughter,
and risking your lives doing so.
That's all.
Daughter?
The boss...
Did you say "daughter"?
The boss has a daughter?
The boss we were eventually going to
track down and defeat has a daughter?
You'll start guarding her right now.
I've handed her over to you.
Handed her over?
Bucciarati!
Could that guy be...
No, not "guy."
She must be the boss's daughter!
That's her?
Do you mind if I go to the bathroom?
That's fine, Trish.
For now, stay by her side.
The order is already in effect.
Bucciarati.
Her name is Trish Una,
and she's fifteen years old.
"Una" is her mother's maiden name,
not the boss's family name.
Trish hasn't met the boss once in her life.
Bucciarati, as you're well aware,
no one knows who the boss is.
But of course, even the boss has a past,
especially when he was young.
Two months ago, a woman named
Donatella died of illness in Calabria.
A few days before her death, she asked
that a man named Solido Naso be found.
That man was Trish's father.
I'm sure she was just trying to look
out for her daughter's well-being,
but...
Naso doesn't exist.
Because that was one of the aliases
that the boss used when he was young.
Correct?
Beware of anyone trying to
look into the name Naso.
Anyone with any status in Passione
is very cautious about that.
Just trying to look into
the boss's past would mean
challenging the organization itself.
Word about Donatella eventually spread.
Word spread even more when it
came out that she had a daughter.
Of course, the boss
caught wind of this, as well.
The boss's decision was immediate.
Through a few other men,
he gave me the order
and placed her in my custody
soon after her mother's death.
The boss must've known immediately.
He didn't know she existed until now,
but he knew for a fact that
Trish was indeed his daughter.
And right after I took Trish into my custody,
we found out that someone was after her life.
If the boss's order had come
even thirty minutes later,
Trish most likely would've been
kidnapped by them, and then...
murdered.
Who is it? Who's after her?
People who have betrayed the organization.
We don't know how many of them there are.
They're trying to defeat the boss and
take over his drug trafficking routes.
Drugs...
They're under the impression that
Trish knows a secret about the boss.
They want information so that
they can defeat the boss.
But Trish is just a frail
little girl who knows nothing.
How long will we be guarding her?
One week... Actually,
it could even be less.
It's just until the boss finds those
traitors and gets rid of them.
Leave this island immediately
and hide her somewhere.
The only ones who know that Trish
is with you are the boss and myself.
Mr. Pericolo.
You said that order was supposed
to go to Polpo, correct?
Which means...
The enemies are Stand users...
I'd say that's a safe assumption.
They're most likely moving as a team, as well.
We don't yet know how many there are.
I don't have a Stand ability.
This is all I can do for you.
I'll contact you again if
I learn anything else.
Um...
M-Me?
Yes. Is it with you... um...
Am I going to be with you now?
Yes, that's correct.
But it'll be all six of us.
We will be risking our lives to protect you.
I see.
Then would you mind taking off that jacket?
My jacket? Why?
Just hurry up and take it off.
It's not as if I want to see
you shirtless or anything.
V-Very well.
I don't have a handkerchief,
so go buy one for me.
Also, some stockings and
Givenchy Blush No. 2.
The stockings need to be
reinforced at the thighs.
Get the latest issue of Italian Vogue, too,
and some mineral water.
I'd rather die than drink one
that's not from France, though.
When you're done gawking at the
scenery, go buy that stuff for me.
Guard the boss's daughter, huh?
So we suddenly have a connection to the
mysterious boss that I've been looking for.
This is definitely worth doing.
If we can see this through,
Bucciarati will be able to gain the
same level of trust that Polpo had.
But if we fail, it'll mean our lives.
All six of us are well aware of that fact.
What's your problem? Calm down.
I'm just trying to pet you.
At 9:25 this morning at Naples Prison, Polpo shot himself in the head.
Hey, come on.
Quit struggling! I can't read it. Jeez...
"At 9:25 this morning at Naples Prison,
Polpo shot himself in the head."
Well, damn... I was sure it'd be Polpo.
Who is it, then?
Who's the one guarding
Trish, who disappeared?
Find them
Well, then...
"Find them," eh?
But was anyone as reliable as Polpo?
Only a capo would be tasked
with such an important job.
And someone with Stand abilities.
Did anyone else like that exist?
Bucciarati
New Capo
Abbacchio
Mista
Fugo
Giorno
Narancia
We're just thugs right now,
but we're going to work
our way up the ladder!
If they attack us,
we'll kill them
Bucciarati
New Capo
Abbacchio
Mista
Fugo
Giorno
Narancia
We're just thugs right now
but we're going to work
our way up the ladder!
If they attack us,
we'll kill them
Pericolo
Has the boss's trust.
Just a capo.
Mysterious Boss
(Villain)
We're going to defeat the boss and
make a killing from his drugs.
Find them and get rid of them.
Protect my daughter!
Daughter(Trish)
15 yrs
The boss's daughter
must know something
about him.
We're taking her
hostage regardless
We were ordered to guard her.
Orders are absolute.
We'll guard her with our lives.
We're also bad,
but we believe it's morally
wrong to profit from drugs.
(We'll find out your
true identity one day)
Team of Traitors (Villains)
We don't know how many there are,
but they're definitely Stand users
Polpo's death brings
chaos to the organization
(The bow and arrow no longer exist)
And that's it for shopping.
Surroundings are all clear.
Let's see...
If I go this way and turn here,
I'll end up back on this street,
and then head in the opposite direction.
Okay!
Narancia, listen carefully.
That's a list of food and other
things you need to buy.
These are the keys to the car.
You can do this, Narancia.
I know you can pull it off.
Okay.
Listen carefully. No one knows
anyone is at this hideout,
not even the people at the winery
in the vineyard out front.
Once you're done shopping, try going in
circles on the same path over and over again.
Also try U-turning every once in a while.
Check to see if anyone's following you.
Then, come home after
switching over to the other car
that I arranged just in case
in one of the city's parking lots.
No one else knows that we're
guarding the boss's daughter,
but if someone's looking for us, the last
thing we want them to do is follow us.
Do you understand?
Someone needs to go shopping.
It's very important.
But we have to make absolutely sure
no one finds out about this hideo—
Jeez, I get it already!
Leave it to me!
Okay, now repeat all the steps I just
explained to you from the beginning.
Huh?
Once I'm done shopping,
I drive around in circles
in the vineyard out there—
Jab
Ow!
Wrong! Quit messing around!
Again, from the beginning!
Huh?
Um...
Drive around so I don't get dizzy—
Jab
Urgh! What the hell is your problem?!
Come on, Abbacchio!
Tell him to stop jabbing
me with the damn keys!
I'm older than him, damn it!
Letting him go shopping is a mistake!
You two will have to figure out whether
or not you should be jabbed on your own.
But with Narancia's Stand ability, he should
be able to stop anyone tailing him.
That's why Bucciarati
ordered him to go shopping.
So basically, that means I just need to make
sure I'm not followed back here, right?
By anyone who might follow me!
Something's wrong.
It doesn't look like anyone's following me,
but something feels off.
I've got a bad feeling about switching over
to the other car that Fugo prepared, too.
Huh?
Come on already.
Where exactly are you headed, huh, Narancia?
That came from below!
Hey, so, where are you headed?
You keep looking behind you.
Are you being followed or something?
Who the hell are you?! Get outta the car!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, talk about scary!
I'm the one asking the questions here.
Don't answer a question with
another question. That's rude.
Shut up! Get the hell out
of my car, you dumbass!
You're not leaving me with any choice.
My name's Formaggio.
I'm a member of the organization.
You already know that Polpo
died yesterday, right?
Yet everyone on your team just
happened to disappear at once.
Shit... He's bad news.
He shouldn't know the truth,
but he's definitely after us.
Right when I had something important
to discuss with you guys...
I-Is he a Stand user?
Narancia, I finally managed to
find you, but why are they gone?
Where's Bucciarati and the rest of your squad?
Who knows?
I have no idea where they are right now.
Did you check the
restaurants around here?
This car...
It's a rental, isn't it?
Bucciarati was the one who rented it.
If you didn't know that,
why the hell are you in this car?
Well?
I-I always drive around
in Bucciarati's cars.
I'm seventeen, so I don't
have my own car yet.
That's why I'm borrowing his.
Oh, yeah. Did you hear?
Apparently the mortician is trying to figure
out how the hell to cremate Polpo's corpse.
They can't figure out how to get
his body into the furnace.
They're just gonna have to chop him
up into tiny pieces, aren't they?!
Shut up!
Hey, you think so, too, right?
Huh?
What the hell? Th-There's no one here!
You actually fell for it.
Man, you're useless.
Say, Narancia, why are you guys
hiding somewhere when
a capo's funeral is going on?
I'm gonna make you talk
if I can't just follow you!
Now you've done it, you asshole!
You're gonna tell me all kinds
of things, right here and now!
You bastard...
Huh?
I'll murder you!
What the hell is that?!
Li'l Bomber!
So he's a Stand user... Tiny Feet!
Bada Bada Bada
Shit!
Look at how badly I'm bleeding!
How dare you?! How dare you?! How dare you?!
Bada Bada Bada
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
This is definitely not good...
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Th-This little shit!
I'll kill you!
Sh-Shit! He's out of his goddamn mind...
He's lost it and is shooting anything in sight!
And I'm stuck in this narrow
car with nowhere to run!
That's the most dangerous part of all this!
A-A bomb?!
Murder him, Li'l Bomber!
How do you like that?
And that?! And that?! And that?!
Are you dead yet?
Ow! Damn it!
Did we do it?
H-He's gone!
Did the blast blow him away?
But... there's not even a
shred of his corpse left!
Wh-Where did he go?!
Oh, come on... I'm right here.
I can make myself small.
That's my ability!
Tiny Feet... All the other guys
say this ability is worthless.
What determines if something is worthless
or not is how you use your brain.
That's how it is with abilities.
What the hell? I don't see him anywhere!
How the hell?! Damn it, where did he go?
Is he here?
The same thing happened when
he first showed up in the car!
Well, good luck in your search.
Where the hell did he just pop up from?
I'm gonna be buying some time here.
Now he's hiding somewhere!
A woman...
This bastard's bought stuff for a woman.
Stockings and blush...
And it's high-end blush to boot!
Who's he shopping for?
Is it for his mom or his older sister?
No... Chicks are super picky
about what they like,
so they buy fashion and
makeup stuff on their own.
The only chick who'd have
a guy buy stuff like this...
is a chick who can't leave
her place for some reason!
This is becoming more and more suspicious.
Looks like my gut feeling was right!
As I thought, without a doubt,
the one who was ordered to guard
the boss's daughter is Bucciarati!
In that case, I'll make sure I get Narancia
to show me where they're hiding.
My ability should start working
on him at any moment now...
Damn it... That bastard's definitely
somewhere around here...
I'm sure he plans to follow
me all the way back.
But...
I'm gonna find him and kill him!
I just have to make it back
without getting followed.
I'm going to follow the orders I was given!
Episodio 10
Hitman Team