Josuke, I'm about to go hunting.
Huh?
Come with me.
W-Wait a sec, Jotaro.
Did you just say "hunting"?
Does that mean...
We're gonna be hunting down
some chicks with nice bodies?
I'm a guy who's more into pure love,
so I've never done that.
I wonder if I can do it...
Akira Otoishi confessed yesterday.
Otoishi did?!
Before his identity was revealed,
he was using the bow and arrow.
He happened to shoot a rat with the arrow.
A rat?!
The rat didn't die after it was shot.
It writhed in pain and
freed itself from the arrow,
then ran away.
So even though it's a rat, this means that
it has definitely obtained Stand abilities.
I'm not sure what kind of Stand it is,
but we have to hunt it down
before something happens.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 16    Let's Go Hunting!
Wow, kewl!
Getting a small, quick rat into your
Stand's range will be difficult,
but by using the bearings, your range
will increase to about 20 meters.
This should be obvious, but it
won't work against a Stand.
You'll only be able to use it to defeat the user.
Try it.
What? I have to do it, too?
I don't know... My mind tends to wander
when ball-shaped things are involved.
The second one was so close!
Not bad. I'd give it 85 points.
But before our pursuit,
I'll give you a warning.
When dealing with living creatures,
you need to put composure ahead of speed.
If the rat enters your range and you miss,
it won't ever step into your range again.
So don't fire until you're positive you'll hit it.
I'm not trying to put pressure
on you, but remember that.
I'm feeling plenty pressured now.
Apparently, Akira Otoishi shot the rat
near this irrigation canal.
Given the area, it was probably a brown rat.
Brown rats can swim,
live anywhere, and eat anything.
The big ones reach about
20 to 30 centimeters long,
and some can weigh one kilogram.
They can jump about 2 meters.
Found it.
Aren't those a bird's tracks?
Their front paws have four digits,
and the back ones have five.
It's dragging something,
forming this S-shape.
This line was made by its tail.
It's a rat that's around 20 centimeters long.
I'm not sure how many,
but they're definitely here.
There's a tick on this leaf.
That means rats come through here often.
Without a doubt, there's a nest
deep in that drainage channel.
For now, we'll set a trap
here and video tape it.
That's one of those cameras that let you
watch while you're taping, right?
You're not using cheese for the trap?
It's a crumb of tempura.
Cheese is too extravagant for rats.
There sure are a lot of flies...
Jotaro!
Th-This is...
Rat corpses?
It's exactly what it looks like!
It's like the jelly from stewed fish.
Why the heck are you poking at it?!
It's flesh.
The flesh of these rats was melted
once, then hardened again.
And they died from having the flesh
under their skin melted.
What do you even do to leave
behind a corpse like this?
I'm not sure...
But we can probably assume it's the
work of the rat that we're after.
It used its Stand?
It killed the others and
made their territory its own.
Which means...
It's definitely making a nest at
the end of this drainage channel.
But the question is
if something capable of doing
this will just stay quiet.
Looks like the drainage
channel leads to that farm.
We might already be too late.
R-Really?
They have a chicken coop,
but there aren't any chickens.
There are no signs of life
at the house, either.
It doesn't look like they just went out,
and the front door isn't locked.
The rat is there.
And just as I feared,
it's likely that the people living
there have already been killed.
Let's go check out that house.
The rat will let us approach
within a certain distance,
because it's confident that no
slow human is going to catch it.
It's not expecting us to blast bearings at it.
That's how we'll get close
enough to nail it in one shot.
Found something.
Rat droppings.
Not made up of grass or grain, either.
It's meat.
They're heading toward this room.
Let's check it out.
Right.
What is that?
The sound of a refrigerator's compressor?
What the heck?
Does the refrigerator in
this house open on its own?
Has the magnet in the door weakened?
What?! There it is!
Damn it! It's right there!
That's what opened the refrigerator just now!
Can rats actually open refrigerator doors?!
Nah... Someone living here must
not have shut the door all the way.
And... Am I actually naïve
enough to believe that?
This rat is a Stand user!
Jo—
Jotaro's not here!
He went to the next room.
Great. Now our eyes have met.
Th-This is...
Did that rat do this?!
They're still alive...
Are you telling me that rat used
its Stand to turn the owners
into this, then preserved them in the fridge?
And it's eating them!
Damn it... Jotaro's not coming back.
That means I'm gonna have to kill this thing.
When dealing with living creatures,
I need to put composure ahead of speed, right?
If I don't get it in one try,
it'll figure out my range.
That's what he said, right? Damn it...
Talk about pressure!
From here, the table and chair
are slightly in the way.
I'm gonna make sure I blast this
bearing right into your forehead.
Stay right there for a bit...
Shit! It stopped eating.
If I move any more, it might run away!
I have no choice! It'll be an adventure,
but I'm gonna have to shoot from here!
It's moving! Now!
Crush
Yes!
It wasn't a fatal blow!
There it is!
That must be its Stand!
You're gonna try to attack me?
Don't underestimate me!
I'll get you with the next shot!
Crap! It's running under the table to get away!
I'm not going to let you!
Jotaro, what are you doing?!
The rat's here!
That shape...
Shit! It's a Stand that shoots something!
What should I do? Slap it
away with my bare hands?
But that's gross, so maybe not...
Which is it?
Did I hit it, or did I miss?
You bastard!
Yes! I nailed it!
I didn't hit it in the forehead, but I beat it.
That was close...
Jotaro, over here!
I got the rat! It's over!
Jeez. What were you doing?
You went missing at the most crucial time.
I felt totally stranded.
But wouldn't you know it...
I just barely made the bearing shot.
I wasn't trying to do a pun with "barely" there.
It had a Stand that shot
something like needles.
I bet if they hit you, they melt your flesh.
The people who live here got hit,
but they're still alive.
I can fix them with Shining Diamond.
If we don't take care of this by sundown,
we may have a problem.
Huh?
There's one more. I was just attacked by it.
Jotaro! Y-Your hand...
I was hit in the next room.
I could have dodged it...
Grabbing it to figure out the effects
of those needles was a mistake.
Just by touching the needle,
some kind of "Stand poison" courses
through you, melting even Stands.
Getting hit by five or six of those
would be enough to turn
a human into mush.
Thank goodness I dodged!
I'm lucky our personalities are so different.
That rat ran outside afterward.
It must've figured out that you
finished off the one in the kitchen.
I hate to ask, but I'm sort of waiting
for you to fix me up quickly.
O-Oh, right!
Damn it!
Why does there have to be another one?
Jo
Jota
Jotaro Ku
Jotaro Kujo
S
Sta
Star
Star P
Star Pla
Star Plati
Star Platinum
Hello, this is the Speedwagon
Foundation research team.
Hello, this is Jotaro Kujo.
Jotaro!
We've tried to call you several times already.
I was in pursuit, so my ringer was off.
Does it have to do with Otoishi?
Yes. Akira Otoishi hid the fact
that he had shot two rats.
Let me confirm.
It was two, and not three or four?
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
Good grief, Akira Otoishi...
Way to go.
It kills everything in its territory,
whether they are humans or its own kind.
It only cares about itself.
It's not a creature that should be
allowed to live on this Earth anymore.
Jotaro, wait!
How are you planning to chase
after a tiny little rat
that's run out into this giant field?
The author of Seton Animal
Chronicles, E.T. Seton, said,
"There is no animal that cannot be tracked."
Rats have a habit of not wanting
to go down an unfamiliar path.
Which means, without a doubt, it went back
toward that irrigation channel.
And if they don't eat constantly,
they will die from starvation
after about ten hours.
There... Those bite marks are new.
Yes! This is awesome!
We'll be able to corner it!
Take a look at this.
It didn't even glance at the bait in the trap.
It's on the video.
Its ear looks like a leaf that's
been eaten on by a bug.
Let's call it "Bug-Eaten" from now on.
Look at how cautious it is...
Unlike earlier,
we can probably bet that
Bug-Eaten won't let us
within 20 meters of him.
These are rifle rounds.
Just in case, I brought four rounds.
A-Actual rounds?!
Because of air resistance,
when round bearings fly
over 20 meters, the point
of impact goes off-course.
With the head of this round,
we'll be okay up to 70 meters.
Am I going to shoot that
with my Stand's hand, too?
I'm not confident about this at all.
Of course not. I guess I'll just have to do it.
Hold on...
Why'd you have to say it like that?
That kind of pissed me off.
I'm the one who took care of the other one!
Sure, it wasn't a perfect shot, but...
Right. So carry two rounds.
Huh?
S-So much pressure...
Be careful. There are leeches in this puddle.
What?!
Impossible...
What's wrong?
Be careful, Josuke.
The footprints suddenly disappear here.
What is this?!
Why'd the footprints disappear?
I know! It's under the dirt.
It must've dug a hole, then covered itself.
No!
This is backtracking...
I didn't think that rats did it, too.
Backtracking?
Backtracking is a special
instinct that wild animals have
in which they go back the way
they came to hide from an enemy.
In Japan, it's said that brown bears,
weasels, and rabbits do this.
But there's no record of
rats backtracking, too.
Does that mean, basically,
that the rat put one over on us?
Things aren't looking good.
With this terrain...
We might actually be the
ones who are being hunted.
I feel like something's staring at us.
We need to hide behind a rock.
Move calmly...
Bug-Eaten's Stand's attack
isn't too fast for us to see.
Don't miss where it's coming from.
If we can find where it's hiding,
we'll shoot it instead.
What the hell is this?!
Wha?!
The rat used the trap that we set for it?
Star Platinum, The World!
Good grief.
Don't panic.
I took out the needle before
the poison spread,
along with the flesh that it pierced.
Put a bandage on it.
And I figured out where the rat's hiding.
Halfway up the hill, near those three rocks.
You're amazing! Both the rat and you, Jotaro!
Am I the only loser this time around?
It's 60 meters away.
It doesn't look like it's going
to shoot more needles yet.
It knows that if it shoots too much,
we'll be able to pinpoint
its location and attack.
Stubborn little bastard.
Why are you complimenting the rat?
We need to do something.
Well said, Josuke.
We need to give it everything we've got,
or Bug-Eaten's gonna get us.
I'll give you all four rounds.
At this distance, it'll go up like a slider,
so aim one centimeter lower than the target.
Jotaro? What are you going to do?
I'm going to get closer
so it'll shoot the needles.
You're going to find out where it is, Josuke...
And then you're going to attack.
Wh-What?!
You're the only one who can do this.
Even if I get hit with one
or two of its needles,
I can have Shining Diamond fix me.
But Josuke, you can't fix yourself.
Give it all you've got, Josuke!
I-I need time to mentally prepare!
Star Platinum, The World!
Did you find it?
N-No... It moved right after it fired!
I'll try to get closer while
going up the side of the hill.
Look for the moment it fires.
The moment it fires...
Th-The pressure!
There! I see it!
What?!
That bastard calculated that I'd dodge
and then fired the needles at the rocks?
It ricocheted?
Jotaro!
Don't look at me, Josuke!
Aim at the rat!
Get it right when it's about to attack!
This isn't good.
I've got four rounds, but I won't
get any more chances.
If I waste any time...
Here we go, Josuke.
There! It's the same spot as before.
But it's hiding behind the rocks.
Damn it! If only it was looking over here...
But I've got to do this!
I'm just going to have
to hit that small target!
I'm suddenly feeling stronger.
I'm going to get you, you little bastard.
Josuke missed...
So you did look.
I thought you'd look if I missed,
and face your body this way.
Now I can target you for sure.
In the end, I wasn't a loser at all.
Call me Josuke Higashikata,
the man who deflects pressure!
The Stand rats that Akira Otoishi created...
Considering the destruction of
nature that humanity brought on,
I'm not sure how to feel...
But thankfully, Josuke's pretty reliable.
Good grief. We can finally relax a little.
Episode 17
Rohan Kishibe's Adventure