Seven years later, in the year 1888...
-London's East End, 1888-
...Jack the Ripper stalked the streets,
terrorizing the women of London.
And a feud between JoJo and Dio would
unleash a new horror into the world.
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 2: A Letter From the Past
He caught it!
The ball is intercepted by
the school hero, Jonathan Joestar!
Joestar, the mild-mannered, 195-cm giant
sprints for the goal with a roar!
Can he win his last game
before graduating?!
He's been tackled!
But he's still standing!
Two more fly in!
Three men are on him!
Incredible!
He's dragging them along in
his charge toward the goal!
What power! What determination!
He's a juggernaut!
And another tackle!
He's wavering at last!
There's the pass!
It's good!
Look who caught it!
It's Dio!
That's our Dio Brando!
Can he make it?
He dodges one!
And another!
He's done it!
He's free!
He shows off his lightning speed!
Try!
They did it!
They've won their final game!
JoJo and Dio! What teamwork!
What an amazing duo!
We did it!
That was some fine running!
Yeah, but it was all thanks to you.
Dio aims to graduate
with top grades in law.
JoJo has written a fine
thesis on archaeology.
This victory belongs to them!
They're the pride of our school!
JoJo, let's tell Father
about this right away!
How long has it been since
my dad adopted Dio?
I smile and act friendly, but I can't
think of him as a real brother.
Why not? He's both talented and kind.
But I can't forget
what happened seven years ago.
Dio, can you tell us about
your friendship with JoJo?
That's an embarrassing subject.
C'mon. We want to hear.
Well...
Friendship?!
Don't stand next to me
with your idiot grin!
Once I graduate,
I'll have no use for Sir Joestar.
I've spent seven years patiently
waiting and playing along.
Now that I am old enough to take it,
the Joestar fortune will be mine!
How are you feeling, Father?
Better, except for this cough.
The doctors want me in the hospital.
You should stay away
from the hospital.
Hospitals don't cure anyone.
They're only after profits.
I won't go. I feel better at home.
My chest pains are better,
and the swelling has gone down.
I'm getting better.
It was only a cold.
Why has it gotten this bad?
Oh, and congratulations
on your victory today.
You already heard?
An old college friend informed me.
Some friend!
We ran home to be the first to tell you!
I'm very pleased.
I'm proud to have such excellent sons.
You've come especially far, Dio.
Follow your dreams
after graduation.
I'll support you in every way.
You're family.
I am grateful that you have
lifted me out of poverty.
I'll keep striving to improve.
Only I know about it.
What purpose could this mask
have been created for?
But it belonged to my mother,
so it makes me think of her.
I hope one day I can solve its riddle
and stir up a sensation!
Oops!
Thank you again, Dio.
I must be getting old.
Climbing stairs really wears me out.
I just had a terrifying thought!
Dio is...
Dio!
What are you doing with that medicine?
What do you mean?
Have you always brought
Dad his medicine?
Yes. Why?
I came across an old letter
written by your real father.
It says here, I'm terribly sick.
I know it will be the end of me.
My chest hurts, my fingers are swollen
and my cough won't stop.
Those are the same
symptoms as Dad's!
What's going on here, Dio?!
What are you trying to say?
I'm having this medicine checked!
If you doubt that medicine,
you doubt our friendship.
Our friendship will be lost!
I can't look him in the eye!
It's because I haven't confirmed
my doubt yet.
JoJo, put the medicine back on the tray.
We'll just forget this foolishness.
Dio, swear your innocence
on the honor of your real father!
If you can do that, I'll do as you say
and forget all of this!
If my hunch is correct, his prideful
personality won't let him do it.
Swear it to me, Dio!
Swear?
Swear on his honor?!
Don't be absurd!
That bastard never had any honor!
You just proved my doubt.
Your reaction is unnatural.
I don't know what happened between you
and your father, but you killed him.
I'll defend my father, and my family!
So that's how it is?
I see what you've been planning!
You never had any love for me!
I won't let you near my father!
I'll analyze this medicine
and give it to the police!
Damn it! I was so close!
Was him finding out an omen?
No! I won't let a worm like him
interfere with my plans!
I have no use for a dead woman!
He pushed Mother to death.
Just thinking his blood
flows in my veins drives me crazy!
There's no turning back now!
Dad, I'm going to London for a few days.
While I'm gone, only accept
medicine from these doctors.
You can't trust my treatment?
Please do as JoJo says.
I don't know his reasons,
but I trust my son.
D-Dad...
He's getting worse.
He may need an antidote.
I have to finish JoJo before he
finds out about the medicine.
And it has to be a perfect crime.
This mask reacted to my blood
seven years ago.
If those spikes enter JoJo's brain,
he'll die instantly.
And it will look like an accident,
so no one will suspect.
JoJo, your curiosity will
be the death of you!
-London, two days later-
Whoa!
The university couldn't
identify the medicine.
Chances are it's Asian medicine.
That means...
Young man, that's Ogre Street,
the most dangerous part of London.
I know, but I have no choice but to go.
You can leave if you want.
Dio lived in London.
Asian medicine
can only be found here.
I'll find it, my evidence
and the antidote.
Another dead end.
That cat was eating a puppy!
Take him, Tattoo!
Use that knife of yours
to slice that snob to ribbons!
I see this street has earned its name.
This idiot just grabbed my knife!
All I have to do is yank
and you'll lose four fingers!
Try it. The instant you pull,
my foot will hit your
groin like a sledgehammer.
I can afford to lose a few fingers.
I'm fighting to protect my family!
That's far more than you can say!
Tell me where they sell
Asian medicine around here!
Hey, you!
You said you'd be fine
missing four fingers!
Don't try to bluff me, rich kid!
Let's dance.
I have to find that shop
no matter the cost!
Have you ever fought before?
You're only covering your head!
That went to the bone!
The knife threw me off,
but my hat still got you good!
He's a monster!
That was no bluff! He was prepared
to lose both legs, let alone fingers!
His will has overcome his pain and fear.
I never should have picked a fight
with a guy as tough as him!
What? JoJo went to Ogre Street alone?
I'm sorry, but yes.
Don't worry Sir Joestar with this.
Yes, sir.
I guess I won't need to use the mask.
Has he already died like a dog?
S-Stop!
I won't allow anyone to lay
a finger on that gentleman!
Gentleman?
Tell me something.
Why did you hold back on me?
A leg like yours should
have totally ruined my face.
I'm here for my father's sake.
So I realized you must have a family.
I don't want to cause them grief.
Is this guy for real?
He's completely naive!
But...
Yes, my friends are all fine, too.
He's a true gentleman to the core!
I like your style!
Tell me your name.
Jonathan Joestar.
You're looking for Asian medicine?
The man who sells it is as sly as a fox!
JoJo's been gone for three days.
He does what he says he will.
He's really grown into a man.
That is why I was so hard on him,
maybe too hard.
I'm sure JoJo is dead
in an alley by now.
Did he find any evidence?
Why can't I stop drinking?!
Just like that wretched father of mine!
Damn it!
Watch where you're going, numbskull!
Hey friend, check if that brat
left a pee stain on my coat!
Are you deaf, you snot-nosed punk?
You won't get away with that!
A disgusting insect like you has a lot
of nerve to speak to me like that.
What an excellent opportunity.
I'll try this on you before
I use it on JoJo.
What are you blabbering about?!
A live-body experiment!
What is that light?!
Was I hallucinating?
He's dead.
Just a boring little toy for torturers.
Impossible!
He's alive!
What is he?
Those teeth!
What incredible strength!
He's not stopping.
Does he feel no pain?
He shattered my shoulder
with just a tap!
I have to jump into the river.
So thirsty...
I don't know why,
but I feel terribly thirsty.
He's draining my blood.
What the...
So this is the mask's secret.
But...
No! I don't want the sun
to be the last thing I see!
The sun...
What's the matter?
Why is it dark in here?
JoJo!
I have proof of your devilish plot!
Next episode
JoJo, I have a final favor to ask.
This guy stinks worse than
a pile of puke!
- I'm throwing away my humanity, JoJo!
- Dio!
TOP	Chapter 3: Time With Dio