July 12th (Mon) 5:05 PM
Yoshikage... My son...
Where are you right now?
I'm sure you've probably changed your
face and name, and have hidden yourself.
How pitiful...  And yet...
Right. We need to find out about any
people who've gone missing recently.
Including those considered runaways.
Kira is probably hiding.
Do you think he'd commit
murders again in that state?
Serial killers like him can't easily
keep their impulses in check.
He will strike again.
Are you sure we don't need to do anything?
We haven't been able to find
a single clue about Kira yet.
That's what I was thinking, too.
But Jotaro said it was fine.
He said he'll have us move
when he finds something out,
but until then, he wants us
to continue being students.
I'd rather look for Kira than study.
We managed to corner him that one time,
so it should be pretty easy, shouldn't it?
Kisara
Drug
Yes. As long as I'm repairing my house,
I'd like to do some renovations, too.
Curses! He's actually taking pictures
of everyone to try to find him!
I guess I'll have someone come
by to give me an estimate.
Jotaro and all of his other Stand
users are doing whatever they want...
I need to make a new Stand user
to take care of those meddlesome bastards...
Hm?
That's...
There's no doubt about it!
Even though his appearance has changed,
our bond as father and
son bring us together.
There's no way I would mistake my own son!
I've found you, Yoshikage...
I'm gonna find out
who the guy disguised as my dad really is.
It can't be...
At this rate, those Stand users will...
I won't allow it!
I won't allow that to happen!
I will protect Yoshikage!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
July 15th (Thurs) 7:50 AM
I'm heading out.
I'm gonna be late...
And I've got class duties today!
Episode 31    July 15th (Thurs), Part 1
July 15th (Thurs), 8:02 AM
So tired...
I stayed up way too late last night.
I got plenty of sleep, so I'm
in top shape again today.
Look, Josuke.
Binoculars.
There's a pair of binoculars on the ground.
You're so easily intrigued by
things that are on the ground.
Don't pick them up. They're dirty.
What? Really?
I am not dirty!
Hello, Josuke and Okuyasu.
I-It was you? Don't scare
us like that, Mikitaka.
You're gonna give me a heart attack, damn it!
Oh, stop...
Don't get bashful.
It's not a compliment!
Though, yeah... You showed up at a good time.
There's something I wanted
to get straightened out.
The thing about you being
an alien is a lie, right?
You're just a Stand user who
thinks he's an alien, right?
Stop being ambiguous and
clear things up, damn it!
I have been clear from the beginning.
I am an alien.
Why are you talking like
that all of a sudden?
That's enough.
More importantly, what are you doing,
turning into binoculars
on the road like that?
Oh, yes. I wanted you two
to look at that thing,
so I was waiting here for you.
That thing?
That thing... The electrical
pylon right in front of you.
Electrical pylon?
That's not really an electrical pylon.
It's a remnant stripped of its
wires that's no longer in use.
When construction started on
Morioh's residential areas,
most of the cables got put underground,
so these weren't needed anymore.
What about it?
Are you trying to communicate
with some other planet?
There's smoke coming out of the
middle of that pylon, isn't there?
Huh?
Y-You're right...
Please take a good look at it.
H-Hey, it's a kettle!
What? In a place like that?!
It's, like, 20 meters off the ground!
Would you mind taking a look
about five meters higher?
What the heck is that?
L-Let me see, too.
There! There he is!
There's a guy up there! He's cooking!
What?! Let me see!
He must be living on that pylon.
He's actually making a living there!
He's fishing from the river,
and even has cucumbers growing.
That's really convenient!
I see! So it's basically a
self-sufficient dwelling.
Some people in this world
do very strange things.
Look out!
H-He's...
It's a new Stand user!
Yeah! I just saw him fly!
But what's a Stand user
doing living up there?
It would seem there's a need to
find out more about that man.
I can see them... They're finally here.
Are they interested in me?
Come on over.
It's been a while since
I've spoken to other people.
Look. It looks like he sees us, too.
Want to go over there?
Yeah, but be careful.
We still don't know if that
Stand user is a friend or foe.
July 15th (Thurs)  8:05 AM
Huh? D-Do you need something?
I'm in a bit of a hurry right... now...
Huh? Huh?!
July 15th (Thurs)  8:11 AM
Looking at it up close,
it's bigger than I thought.
You guys, stop right there!
Don't come any closer to this pylon.
Huh?
Move back a bit more.
I just relieved myself, so you need
to step back, or you'll be in trouble.
What are you talking about?
D-Don't tell me this is...
I told you so.
You'll get covered in feces and urine!
That's gross!
Gross? How rude!
I made it spray like that so I could
fertilize the wildflowers over there!
I like to recycle everything I possibly can.
On the right are Asiatic dayflowers,
mountain udo, and watercress.
They're all edible wildflowers!
Not to mention, if there
are wildflowers around,
I can catch wild rabbits
that come to eat them,
so it's killing two birds with one stone.
So you really are living up there?
Doesn't this pylon belong
to the electric company?
What are you talking about?
This is my house that I
bought with my own money.
I bought this abandoned
pylon for 100,000 yen
and made it my own ideal
self-sufficient house!
Bought?
For 100,000 yen?
That's right. Just 100,000 yen.
Because I'm self-sufficient,
I don't have to work at any company.
And even if I never leave here, I get all the
exercise I need by moving around the pylon.
Take a look at this spectacular view.
Huh? W-Wait a minute.
Even if you never leave? Just how long
have you been living on this pylon?
Let's see... About three years now?
Th...
Three years?!
I probably haven't touched
the ground in about a month.
H-Hey, Josuke. I had no idea that
an idiot like this lived in Morioh.
This guy isn't an enemy,
he's just a damn weirdo.
I don't think he's going to attack us.
True...
I guess, for now, we can just
head back and report to Jotaro.
But...
Something's still bugging me...
July 15th (Thurs)  10:15 AM
What's he doing?
Well, I guess kids take videos, too...
But since he's hiding behind that pillar,
it looks like he's doing the same thing I am.
He's following someone and
recording their actions...
Could he be recording someone here?
Hayato Kawajiri
"Hayato Kawajiri," huh...
There's something strange...
about this kid.
July 15th (Thurs)  7:33 AM
I'm home.
Silence
That's strange.
Josuke, you haven't left for school yet?
Josuke!
I'm hungry.
Josuke, that bastard... This is so rude!
How dare he take a bite out of my favorite
Kamakura Custar and then put
it back in the fridge?!
Not to mention, there should have been two left.
That kid seriously pisses me off.
July 15th (Thurs)  8:14 AM
Hey, something fell out of your pocket.
Is that a photograph?
Would you guys mind leaving now?
You don't have to pick it up.
I'll get it myself later.
It looks like a Polaroid.
What's he panicking for?
Seriously, it's okay! Just leave!
What?! You're...
Hey! J-J-Josuke!
You're Kira's dad!
I knew the ghost dad was involved in this!
So you've finally come in.
I've been waiting for this.
When you tell people to come in,
they become guarded and don't come in.
But if you tell people not to come in,
they get pissed off and come in.
You've finally stepped into
Superfly, Josuke Higashikata!
Wh-What?!
Well done, Toyohiro Kanedaichi!
Well done luring that idiot
Josuke into Superfly!
I commend you!
Something's not right! Come back, Josuke!
No, Kira's dad is right there!
The arrow's right there!
You bastard!
Why, you—
What?!
You see, when someone enters this pylon,
they can't get out until
the next person comes in.
If they try to force their way out, they
become a part of the pylon themselves.
That's my Stand, Superfly!
You fell for it, Josuke Higashikata!
Don't let him get away, Toyohiro Kanedaichi!
Josuke!
S
Su
Sup
Supe
Super
Superf
Superfl
Superfly
Toyo
Toyohiro
Toyohiro Kane
Toyohiro Kaneda
Toyohiro Kanedaichi
Josuke!
Damn it...
I said it was my Stand,
but Superfly isn't a Stand that I can control.
It's actually an independent Stand.
I can finally leave, now that
you guys have shown up.
Even I, its user, was held captive by Superfly.
Well, good luck living here in my stead!
That bastard!
He must've been working with
the guy in the photograph.
Okuyasu, is there anything that I can do?
You'll just get hurt, so stay out of it.
Your job's over.
If you could actually turn
into dynamite instead of
dice or binoculars and blow this
pylon up, things might be different.
That I cannot do.
I can't produce any strength
that isn't my own,
and I can't turn into anything
complicated like explosives.
But I'd like to be of some use.
Shut up.
I'm telling you that there's
nothing you can do.
Leave the dangerous stuff to us.
That bastard's starting to run
away because he's convinced
that he's got him trapped in there,
but he must not know who we are.
Hey. You gonna do this, Okuyasu?
I know you're up to it, too.
What's the big deal about this pylon?
Let's crush it, Josuke!
Yeah. There shouldn't be an
issue if I crush it and get out!
Watch it!
The hell? What's with their power?!
This thing's pretty sturdy.
But if we keep attacking it,
this pillar will snap in two.
And look. It looks like that
guy's about to fall off.
Y-You idiots! How can you
do something so terrifying?
Of course I thought about that possibility.
But haven't you noticed?
This pylon is draining your powers and
distributing them throughout itself.
Huh? What the hell is that idiot talking about?
Josuke, just a little more,
and you'll be out of there!
Here we go!
Hold up, Okuyasu. Listen.
Something's not right.
What's that weird sound?
It's the sound of all
the power you guys threw
into the pylon, moving throughout it.
What?
And think about this carefully.
You know that whole
"law of conservation of energy"?
Energy that's running around has to
be able to escape from somewhere.
So where's all that energy's gonna go?
It can't be...
Okuyasu, duck!
What?!
You can attack it all you want,
but all the attacks on the pylon are
just gonna come right back to you.
If you hit it, it'll hit back.
If you cut it, it'll cut back.
Just think about it.
No matter who comes around
with whatever kind of ability,
no one can destroy this pylon!
Okuyasu!
Th-This isn't good, Josuke...
I couldn't dodge it completely.
It ripped a hole in my side.
I guess I should've warned you about that.
And next, you're probably going to think
that if you defeat me, the user,
you'll be able to get out.
But that's futile, too.
This pylon is an independent Stand.
Even if I were to die,
this pylon would probably continue
to trap people inside for eternity.
That's what Superfly is.
Josuke...
For eternity?
But don't get too depressed about that.
You just have to lure someone
else in, Josuke Higashikata.
If one comes in, one can get out.
Just have some sucker take
your place and get out.
It's sort of like playing Old Maid.
It's like human society.
You just need to pass off the
old maid to someone else.
Am I wrong?
Indeed, if someone else is pulled in,
Josuke will be saved.
Huh?
What?
You should be the one to return,
then. Into the pylon...
you go.
You...
Mikitaka! When did you...
Who the hell are you?
Why were you an electrical wire?
When did you get there?
What the hell is that ability?
Why, thank you for asking.
You see, I'm an alien.
What?
Y-You actually can be useful!
Now's your chance.
Please step outside, Josuke-san.
Y-You bastard!
You have my praise, Mikitaka!
Josuke, hurry up and get out.
Get out of the pylon!
R-Right...
I did it!
You bastard! What the hell?!
The guy in the photograph didn't tell me
that Josuke had a friend like you!
I'm an alien, so I'm unaware of
this game called "Old Maid,"
but to suddenly trick Josuke and
tell him that he cannot leave...
It's like an adult beating a child at a game
on New Year's by tricking them.
This is why you should be the
one to remain in the pylon.
You will remain here.
After all the time I spent
living here, I ended up
with these thick calluses on my hands.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Take this!
It seems you're under the impression
that that's a part of me,
but that is incorrect.
That is not me,
but the pylon's wire that you
were hanging off of earlier.
Yeah!
All right! Now, go to the top
and come back out, Mikitaka!
You're the one who finally
stepped into this pylon.
Do you really think I'd let you escape?
I'm a man who has thought of nothing but
getting out of here every single day!
Did you forget?
This pylon will return whatever you do to it.
That wire's also a part of this pylon!
The angle at which the wire was cut
was made so it would return to you.
H-Have I been defeated?
M-Mikitaka! Hurry up and get out of there!
I can fix a wound like that!
Nope, he's not getting out.
I'm the one who's going to leave!
The direction and angle are perfect.
If you strike it, it'll strike back.
Mikitaka!
Y-You bastard!
I went through some trouble
getting out because of you,
but now I can get out easily.
I'm sure that's gonna hurt when
you try and pry those out,
but you'll have plenty of time to treat it later.
There are some medicinal plants down there, too.
You bastard! Do you think you can
escape just because you're out of there?
I'll chase you to the ends of the Earth, damn it!
Of course I can escape, and rather easily.
You guys haven't even been able
to find Yoshikage Kira, have you?
July 15th (Thurs)  10:42 AM
Who is that? I've never seen him before.
July 15th (Thurs)  8:14 AM
July 15th (Thurs)  10:38 AM
I'll find him out... no matter what.
Episode 32
July 15th (Thurs), Part 2