-England, 1868-
Hey! Look at that wreck!
Yikes! This guy died on the spot.
They must've slipped in the mud
and fell off the cliff.
But boy do these nobles
have some fancy clothes.
Look!
The woman inside is dead,
but the baby is still alive!
She must have protected it.
A baby?!
Who cares about a baby?!
What are you doing?
What does it look like?!
I'm taking their jewelry!
What's that?
What a creepy mask.
It's worthless to me.
Give me a hand!
Let's yank out their teeth!
They'll fetch a good price!
You...
You came to rescue me.
Thank you.
My wife...
My wife and son...
Are they all right?
They cr-- Uh, I'm afraid your wife
and the driver are dead.
But the baby is safe.
Perhaps this is fate...
My name is George Joestar I.
I must thank you for saving my life.
Please tell me your name
while I am still conscious.
He thinks I came to save his life!
What a fool!
It won't hurt to say my name.
Dario Brando at your service.
Mr. Brando, the Joestars
will not forget our debt to you.
-12 years later-
There's a good boy!
I'm off, Dad!
Take care, JoJo!
Let's go, Danny!
Dio!
Come here!
Dio! Are you deaf, boy?!
What do you want, Father? Medicine?
Idiot! I don't want any snake oil!
If you have money,
go buy me some booze!
JoJo, manners!
Sorry, Dad.
Check.
Fine.
Feeling smart now, kid?!
Stop! Give it back!
Hey, Erina!
Your daddy buy you this doll?
He makes a lot of money
for being a quack!
I know!
Let's peel her clothes off!
We'll see if it looks like
the real thing!
She cried!
Erina's a crybaby!
Knock it off!
Give it back to her!
Who're you?
Erina's friend?
I don't know her,
but I'll fight for her!
You dumb jerk.
Fighting 'cause she's a girl.
Huh? He's a total pushover!
How embarrassing!
Now our brave knight needs saving!
This guy's the only son of the Joestars!
The one thing I can't stand
is a rich kid!
You stuck up snob!
Have some of this!
Dio, my time is almost up.
Listen!
When I die, take this letter
to the Joestar mansion!
They owe me something big.
You're a smart boy. Go out there
and become the world's richest man!
Just stay on your own land, rich kid.
Let's go.
Are you --
Just leave me alone!
Go away!
I didn't attack them for your sake!
I want to be a true gentleman!
You were a lady in distress.
A true gentleman has to be brave enough
to go into a fight he knows he'll lose.
But one day,
I'll be strong enough to win.
You were ugly and sly.
You drove Mom to death.
You were a terrible father!
You want me to be rich?
Don't worry. I will be.
And I'll use any means necessary.
I'll start with this Joestar.
You pig!
No one will bring me down.
Jonathan Joestar.
This is a tale of two youths and
a stone mask that alters their fates.
Chapter 1: Dio the Invader
Who is he?
You're Dio Brando, right?
And you must be Jonathan Joestar.
Everyone calls me JoJo.
Nice to meet you.
Danny!
See him? That's Danny.
He's my dog.
Don't worry.
He doesn't bite.
What was that for?!
You'll pay for that!
So this is the Joestar heir.
He looks like a pampered brat.
We'll see who has it all
after I get through with him.
What's the matter?
What's going on here?
I'm sorry. The dog jumped at me.
It was a reflex.
Welcome, Dio.
You are part of our family now.
Everyone, I owe my life
to this man's father.
Treat him as you would JoJo.
Yes, lord.
Dio, this is your home now.
Live like JoJo does.
Thank you for your hospitality,
Sir Joestar.
You've both lost your mothers
and you're the same age.
You should get along well.
JoJo, forget about Danny, all right?
Yes, Dad.
I'm sure I'd be surprised if a strange
dog jumped at me, so I understand.
I do wish he'd apologize.
But we'll be living together,
so I have to be nice.
This way, Dio.
I'll show you your room.
Yes, sir.
Hands off!
No one touches my bags!
Keep your dirty paws to yourself!
Got it?!
I was trying to help!
No thanks!
I'll have a servant carry them.
Listen closely, JoJo.
I might be your guest,
but I won't take any lip from you.
I always come first! I'm number one!
No one looks down
their nose at me!
But I just want to be friends!
And another thing, I hate dogs.
They don't scare me.
I just can't stand their bootlicking.
So keep that dumb mutt
Danny away from me.
What's keeping you two?
Hurry along.
Yes, sir!
With Dio's arrival, JoJo's happy life
spiraled into misery.
That's another mistake, JoJo!
Look at Dio!
20 out of 20 correct!
JoJo, you call yourself a gentleman?!
Where are your manners?!
Clear JoJo's place.
No dinner for you.
Looking at Dio, I see I've spoiled you.
I've been a shameful father!
Dio's manners are impeccable!
What an oaf.
In this corner is Jonathan Joestar!
He's looking stronger lately!
And his opponent...
...has been changed.
All we know is his name!
He's the new guy in town!
It couldn't be!
Introducing Dio Brando!
You know the rules.
One hit to the face wins it.
Begin!
- Get him, JoJo!
- Take him down!
Look at those moves!
I've never seen the like!
I can't connect!
JoJo is better than I had expected.
But...
I'll show him how we do it in the
bad part of town, Booth Boxing style!
Eat this!
There it is!
JoJo is out!
It's not over yet, JoJo!
I'll jam my thumb in his eye
and follow through!
Did you see that?!
Dio!
Dio, that was amazing!
How did you do that?
It's just a new defensive technique
in boxing.
I'll teach it to you guys as a favor.
Really?
But don't teach it to JoJo.
He can't keep a secret.
- He can't?
- Thanks for the warning.
Why?
Why do that on purpose?
Loneliness will make a man hollow.
I'll turn JoJo into an empty husk!
Bit by bit, I'll steal his life.
When I'm an adult, he'll have nothing.
Damn that Dio!
This is awful.
It's like he's taking over my life.
Hey! Get a move on!
Hey! What are you doing?
Come here!
Let me join in on the fun!
Did you guys hear something?
Ignore it.
It's just a snitch.
What?!
Get back here! Who's a snitch?!
Let's split.
You're a snitch, JoJo!
You'll blab to anyone
over anything!
Squealer!
Hold on! Get back here!
I never squealed on anybody!
JoJo the squealer!
Dio! Dio did this!
He's spreading wild rumors about me!
He's trying to destroy me
for some reason!
Curse you, Dio!
Ever since he showed up,
everyone's turned on me!
Danny, you'll be my friend
no matter what Dio does.
Who was that?
I feel like I've seen her before.
My handkerchief!
Aha!
Thanks for the grapes!
I'll be here tomorrow!
Come see me!
She went off without a word.
Girls are so cute!
In that dark time, Jonathan's heart
was spurred on by love!
They quickly became friends,
and Jonathan was enchanted by her.
Erina.
Erina Pendleton.
She's an angel!
What are you doing, JoJo?
JoJo! You can't do that!
You're no good!
See you!
Bye bye!
Hi. Are you Erina?
You and JoJo look happy together.
I knew something was wrong.
He's been happy
where he should be miserable.
He did it!
That's our Dio!
He's got way more guts than we do!
He's my idol!
I want to be him!
Have you and JoJo kissed yet?
Not yet, eh?
Your first kiss was not with him!
It was with me!
Even if I stole it, the fact
that I kissed her is enough!
Their little romance is over!
He won't have a single
friend or lover!
Look! What is she doing?!
What is she thinking?
She's washing with puddle water!
Is she nuts? There's a stream nearby!
You wench!
You're just doing that to insult me!
Dio, you fool! Don't lose your head
over a dumb girl!
We're done here! Let's go.
Hey, Erina!
Erina, wait!
This isn't right. What happened?
Look at that sorry look on his face!
Go tell him why she ran away!
But I just couldn't bear
to see JoJo cry!
Why you...
What did you do?
What did you do to her?!
Dio!
I wouldn't use my name lightly
if I were you.
This ends now!
I won't let you hurt her again!
Your fight is with me!
So you heard about your darling Erina?
Now you want to take revenge,
with your fists, eh?
I won't let you insult her!
You're just twisted by jealousy!
You want more of what happened
when we boxed?!
I can't beat him.
But if I lose here, I'll have to spend
my life cowering in Dio's shadow.
But most of all,
I have to fight for Erina's honor!
I'm going to pulverize him.
And I'll do it fair and square.
That way he'll know beyond a doubt
he can never beat me.
Not in a fight, and not in life.
Come!
That's it! That felt good!
How could he grab me after that kick?!
How about some more?!
Dio!
I'm going to beat you until you cry!
How could rubbish like him beat me?!
You...
You have a lot of nerve, don't you?!
He's crying.
You filthy cur!
What's going on, you two?!
Dad!
Boys fight. That can't be helped.
But JoJo, you were beating
Dio while he was down
and unable to defend himself!
- That's not civil!
- But --
No excuses!
To your rooms, both of you!
You'll both be punished later.
What's that box?
Oh, well.
I bet a maid threw it away.
What's that?
Something's banging around.
Is someone in there?!
No! They're burning alive in there!
Erina...
Damn that Dio!
This is what you were aiming for!
Well, you got what you wanted!
The sight of him was too much to bear,
so we buried him quickly.
The police say a burglar probably
wanted Danny out of the way.
Dio...
Dio? He hasn't returned from school yet.
JoJo went to his room and slept.
After he woke, he thought about Danny,
the companion he had lost, and cried.
I evened the score by killing that mutt,
but I had no idea JoJo was so strong.
The more you beat him,
the tougher he gets.
My anger makes me vulnerable.
I have to fix that.
I must learn to cool my temper.
Seven years passed...
Next episode
Seven years later...
And Jonathan Joestar steals the ball!
I just had a terrifying thought!
You said you'd be fine
missing four fingers!
Our friendship will be lost!
I'll defend my father, and my family!
Chapter 2:
A Letter From the Past