All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
What the?! Something's coming!
I dunno what the hell that is,
but it's no ordinary human!
Polnareff!
But no matter! I'll kill him!
A playing card?
Welcome. Master Joestar,
we have been awaiting your arrival.
I am the butler of this mansion.
My name is D'Arby.
D'Arby?
Yes. I am D'Arby Younger.
I am the younger brother of
D'Arby Elder, whom you have
defeated beyond recovery.
Bam
You're the gambler D'Arby's younger brother?
Are you here to avenge your older brother?
No, not at all. I wouldn't even think of it.
Didn't my brother tell you
that the one who is fooled
and loses the battle is at fault?
I believe that to be true, as well.
It's my brother's fault for losing.
I don't bear a grudge at all.
My brother is my brother, and I am myself.
We are different people.
I am ten years younger than my brother.
I did respect my brother to a certain degree,
but we are from different generations.
My brother is old-fashioned.
He had to cheat and swindle to win.
He could only defeat those who were
either old-fashioned or amateurs.
I believe that Lord DIO also recognized this,
and that is why I am the one
he chose to be his butler.
What is the matter?
If you would like to fight me,
please, come into the mansion.
Everyone, don't rush in there carelessly.
We don't have much time.
Hurry up and take us to DIO.
Jotaro! Be careful! Something's coming out!
D'Arby Younger. His Stand, Atum,
suggests the God Atum.
H-Hey, he brought out his Stand!
Well, that's rare these days.
It's been a while since we faced someone who used their Stand out in the open.
So who is it?
Who shall be my first opponent?
He's so annoying!
Jotaro, beat the crap out of him!
Rumble
Let us make a wager.
The first blow Star Platinum uses against me
will be a left-hand punch.
His first attack will be a punch
thrown with his left arm.
Let us wager.
Whatever! It's all the same if you
hit him with everything you've got!
Do it!
Hurry up and hit him, Jotaro!
Bam
What? H-He dodged?
Such speed!
That's impossible.
Too bad. It seems I have lost this wager.
Just like my brother, I love gambling.
But I'm not very good at it.
As a reward, I shall take
you to an amazing world.
What? A hole...
Curses! It was a trap after all!
Jotaro!
Jotaro's falling into the hole!
Pull him out!
Oh, very well. You gentlemen may enter, too.
Wha—
Mr. Joestar! Kakyoin!
Wait! It would be too dangerous to follow them!
Avdol, can you hear me?
If you don't hear from us in ten minutes,
set the mansion on fire!
Got it, Avdol?!
Mr. Joestar!
Episode 40  D'Arby the Player, Part 1
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
This illusion... Are we
underground or above ground?
This wet feeling... This reality...
It's too convincing.
Just what is he trying to do?
Old man. Kakyoin.
Consider this mystery for me.
His Stand...
It knew without doubt that I was
going to throw a right punch.
Why do you think that is?
If we don't solve that mystery,
this guy will beat us.
Would you like something to drink?
Of course, the drinks are real.
They are also not poisoned.
Is this inside the mansion?
It is.
Where inside the mansion?
I cannot disclose that.
Is it below ground?
It could be.
Is this illusion being created by a Stand?
Yes.
Is this your Stand's power?
It is not.
Is it DIO's?
Whose is it?
That information is not necessary.
According to the Speedwagon Foundation's intel,
there are about two or three other Stand users.
Is that true?
That information is not necessary.
Looks like we're not getting any straight answers.
I could lie to you.
But I don't tell lies or trick others,
as my brother did.
So what are you getting at?
If we don't defeat you, we can't proceed?
Exactly!
That is indeed correct.
That needlessly polite attitude...
This man gets on my nerves.
Have you forgotten that it's one against three?
We're in a hurry, so all three of us will attack you.
Now, don't be in such a hurry.
Before that, let's have a look
at my collection, shall we?
Collection?
Though it pales in comparison to my
brother's, I also have a collection.
But one likes to hear compliments
about their precious collection
when showing it to others.
It can't be...
Dolls? Wh-What are these dolls?!
No, Kakyoin.
Given that we're dealing with one
of the D'Arby brothers,
those can't be ordinary dolls.
Squirm
D-D'Arby...
Talk to me. Please, talk to me...
Talk to me!
I'm so lonely...
Help me...
Oh my God!
They're alive! These dolls are alive!
You bastard! They're souls!
My hobby is to make dolls.
And I've had real souls inhabit these dolls.
I'm letting the cat out of the bag,
but this is my Stand's power.
My brother simply enjoyed his
soul coins, collected in little rows.
But that's rather simple and mundane.
I change their clothes and even talk to them.
For example,
her name is Sonia.
D'Arby! Oh, D'Arby!
I love hearing about her beautiful love stories.
D'Arby...
Isn't her skin beautiful?
She's so beautiful, I'm never
embarrassed to show her off.
Dr. Elliott is a murderer.
He's killed eight people.
I enjoy hearing about the
patients he murdered.
I made his glasses and stethoscope myself.
Oh, that's right! I must show you this!
The video game master from Japan, Tatsuhiko!
His IQ is 190, so he was formidable.
It wasn't easy to beat him and steal his soul.
Mama... Mama! Mama!
Both of you brothers are insane.
No, you're much worse than your brother.
You're pissing me off more!
You act like a gentleman, but you're scum.
You make me sick.
By the way, I'm sure you experienced
this when fighting my brother, but...
Human souls are indeed mysterious.
Once you admit defeat,
your soul's energy drops almost to zero.
I watch for that moment,
and then drag their souls out!
That is how both my
brother and my Stands work.
That's enough talk!
You're just pissing me off.
We'll hurry up and defeat you,
then move forward!
But you must listen!
Jotaro, you know you are
already under my control.
Earlier, Jotaro, when I read whether you were
going to use your left or right,
you were shocked, weren't you?
And how I read it is still a mystery to you.
At that moment, though subtly,
I was able to touch your soul.
What do you think I did when I touched it?
Bam
Wh-What?!
What is that?!
I left Atum's arm attached to your soul.
If I were to crush your right arm,
I'm sure Lord DIO would be quite pleased.
But in that instant, I would be
attacked by Kakyoin and Joestar,
and would be utterly defeated.
I don't want that to happen.
So how about this, gentlemen?
Why don't we play a little game
and wager our souls?
What?
If I admit absolute defeat,
I shall let go of his arm.
Good grief. Already under your control, huh?
True... But you're going to
regret tricking me, D'Arby.
I would absolutely love to hear you say,
"I will play a game and wager my soul."
But the first to play will be...
Kakyoin. I choose you.
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
You should fight me first.
You and Joestar are related by blood,
but you have no relation to Kakyoin.
If, after I steal the two Joestar souls,
Kakyoin lost interest in wagering his soul
and attacked me with his Stand,
it would be troublesome for me.
You're so full of yourself.
You seem to think you've already won.
Very well. I shall be your first opponent.
What?
Kakyoin!
It's fine. I feel confident.
I have experience with video games myself.
I'd like to challenge you to F-Mega.
And I shall wager my soul!
Atum
D'Arby Younger
I shall wager my soul!
Good.
Kakyoin!
You don't have to go first.
Yes, I do.
Since you have that thing attached to your arm,
it's likely you'd mess up the game's controls.
D'Arby, where is our guarantee
that if you lose, your Stand
will let go of Jotaro's arm?
Menacing
There's nothing wrong with the TV,
console, or game cartridges.
These are the same video games
you could find anywhere else.
I am not like my brother. I shall not cheat.
Now, let's begin.
Yes.
F-Mega!
Select your car.
First, please select your car.
Right.
So your machine is #28, eh?
Mine is #15, because I was born on January 5th.
Are you ready?
Enough pleasantries. Just go!
Race start in...
Five!
Th-The way he's pushing the accel button over
and over again at such a fast speed...
He's trying for a start dash!
Three...
Crap! I'm not going to be able to dash like this!
Two...
He's going to get ahead of me!
One.
Start!
He blocked me!
As long as I can keep this up, I will win.
It is impossible to get past me at this point.
And sadly, I, D'Arby, never make
mistakes with controls in a race.
You were naïve, Kakyoin!
What?!
I see you've played this game before, Kakyoin.
I don't need to answer that.
All right!
This is your chance, Kakyoin!
Hurry up! Get your machine
back on the course and start!
That technique...
It's not possible by simply
having experience in F-Mega.
Although he looks rather
anxious on the outside,
he has a very bold personality.
They're tied! They're right next to each other!
No. Kakyoin ended up on the outside.
If they hit a curve side by side,
the outside car is at a disadvantage.
355 kilometers per hour... 358... 360...
Only three seconds to the first corner!
It's possible to take the corner at this speed!
I'm going to bust through
that corner at full throttle!
Two... One!
At the same time!
They turned that corner at the
same speed and at the same time!
They're side by side!
I've taken a liking to you, Kakyoin!
You wagered your soul,
but you're not scared at all!
You rise above fear to work the controls.
Only people like you, who give me competition,
are worthy of being a part of my doll collection.
Noriaki Kakyoin thought to himself...
Me? Rise above fear?
Thanks. I've had training.
Six months ago, when I met your master, DIO...
When he planted the flesh bud in my brain,
I was trained to withstand fear.
That moment...
The moment I encountered DIO, honestly,
I was terrified of the beast he was.
I lost feeling in my legs,
every hair on my body stood on end,
and my body was frozen.
When I saw DIO and realized I couldn't move,
the paralysis made my hairs
stand even more on end.
My stomach convulsed, and I had acid reflux.
I nearly threw up.
As he looked at me, DIO said this to me.
His voice was gentle, as if speaking to a child.
Kakyoin.
There's nothing to fear.
Let's be friends.
I curse myself! After I heard that...
I was relieved. To be honest,
I felt relief from the bottom of my heart.
I thought I could stay alive!
But it was humiliating. I can't forgive myself!
Nothing could be more humiliating.
I couldn't forgive myself.
I cursed myself for giving in to him.
Jotaro saved me, and that was the
reason I went on this journey.
I will never return to being that
pathetic Kakyoin ever again!
D'Arby, that's exactly why I'm wagering
my soul with you in this challenge.
Three, two, one!
Again, at the same time!
The third corner!
That is why I, Noriaki Kakyoin,
will not make any nervous
mistakes with my controls.
I will show you that!
All right! The fifth corner!
Again, at the same time!
They're going through all
of them the same time!
K-Kakyoin... Damn you...
Next is the sixth corner!
Once you're through the sixth corner,
you'll see a speed tunnel.
As soon as you're through the tunnel,
you'll be able to go twice
as fast, up to 850km.
No matter what,
I must go through that tunnel!
But the tunnel is only wide enough
to accommodate one vehicle.
If they continue to race neck-and-neck,
one of them won't be able to enter the tunnel!
The sixth corner! Again, they were together!
The tunnel! I see the tunnel.
Kakyoin, don't let him push you out!
It seems you haven't realized yet, Kakyoin.
Are you trying to push me out?
Take a look at your #28's remaining power.
K-Kakyoin has less!
At the race's start,
you spun and were blown away
by my blocking maneuver.
Didn't you realize you had less energy after that?
Two seconds until the tunnel.
You're going to collide!
Let him have the lead!
Go into the tunnel after D'Arby!
I cannot!
If I let him enter the tunnel first,
my chances of winning are gone.
One second until the tunnel!
Kakyoin!
Grip
Whoa! He tilted his car!
I never guessed you'd enter on the tunnel's wall.
Y-You did it, Kakyoin! Mentally, you're winning!
Keep pushing through!
Shut up! You're distracting me.
He's ramming him!
I don't care how little power I have left.
I'll take this next turn, even if only a
hundredth of a second ahead of Kakyoin,
take the shortest course, even if it's
by a thousandth of a millimeter,
and get through this tunnel
even if it's but a moment faster!
No radar.
H-Hey, what's wrong?
I can't see the machines!
We have to get through the
tunnel in darkness from here.
What?!
Absolute darkness, where the
radar is completely useless!
There are eight curves,
one mine, and one cannon.
At the end of the darkness is the tunnel's exit.
One mistake and you'll hit the wall.
But my body has memorized the
timing needed to take the curves.
So has D'Arby.
That's the sound of taking a corner.
What's going on?! Where are they driving?
Who's going faster?
Three...
Two...
One!
Cannon!
Just for an instant,
I could see them in the
light of the cannon blast!
Kakyoin is just slightly behind.
I can see the exit!
They're coming out of the tunnel!
Gulp!
D'Arby is ahead!
He's ahead by a length!
I have won!
Next Episode Preview
I will never let down my guard.
You have less power than I!
I've grasped his soul!
Don't be ridiculous, Jotaro!
I know the rules of baseball.
It is impossible to back out now!
You should offer encouragement
at times like this.
Episode 40
D'Arby the Player, Part 2
This is pathetic.