All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I've got it.
I've figured out a way to reveal
what DIO's Stand truly is.
What?!
Rumble
Whenever Noriaki Kakyoin sees his
Hierophant Green, this is what he remembers.
Your little Noriaki doesn't try
at all to make friends.
It's not that the other kids don't like him.
He just doesn't open up to anyone.
As his teacher, I'm very concerned.
I'm his mother, yet I still
don't know why he's like that.
Ever since I was a child, I thought
that living in a city means
meeting a lot of people.
But even in an entire lifetime,
how many people meet others they can truly
understand, and who understand them?
My classmates' address books are
filled with their friends' names.
There must be about fifty friends in each.
Maybe even a hundred.
My mother has my father,
and my father has my mother.
But I'm different.
I'm sure rock stars and people on TV
have tens of thousands of friends.
But I'm different.
I probably won't ever have someone
who sees me for who I am.
Because I don't have a
single friend who can see
my Hierophant Green.
It's impossible for
those who can't see him to understand me.
Until I met Mr. Joestar, Jotaro,
Polnareff, and Avdol,
I felt that way all the time.
I wonder why I get goosebumps
when I think about Avdol and Iggy.
Perhaps because they were
the first friends I shared
a common goal with.
This journey to defeat DIO...
Even though it lasted only a few weeks,
they became friends I
could truly connect with.
Noriaki Kakyoin looks at
Hierophant Green and thinks:
I'll make him invisible to everyone,
just like he used to be.
Yes, to reveal DIO's true
identity and defeat him,
I'll make his presence completely disappear.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 46  DIO's World, Part 2
Hey, Jotaro!
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
That car's crushed to pieces.
Up there.
The old man and DIO are on the rooftops.
Only Kakyoin and Joseph are before me.
I see.
They split up so they could
attack from both sides.
So Jotaro and Polnareff must
intend to attack me from behind.
How useless.
This is...
Kakyoin's Hierophant!
Hierophant's barrier!
This is...
That's right!
Hierophant's barrier, which
activates when touched,
completely surrounds you for
20 meters in every direction!
Now I can sense both your
movements and The World's!
Take this, DIO! 20-meter
radius Emerald Splash!
You fool. You shall soon know
that The World's true power is, indeed,
the power to reign over this world!
Bring out your Stand, DIO!
The World!
Doom
What?! Kakyoin!
He was suddenly blown away!
Impossible!
Kakyoin!
Wh-What... just happened?
Did he beat me?
It's no use. I think my injuries are fatal.
I can't speak... I can't even lift a finger.
It's 5:15...
That means it's around midnight in Japan.
I wonder what my parents are doing.
Maybe they're already asleep.
I'm sorry for making you worry so much.
Noriaki Kakyoin's final thoughts
were not of his parents in Japan.
Though he cared deeply for his parents,
when his mind drifted to the final
question that puzzled him,
thoughts of his parents drifted away.
I can sense every movement of those
who touch Hierophant Green's barrier.
But DIO ripped apart the entire barrier at once.
Why wasn't it done strand by strand?
It was completely simultaneous,
without even a microsecond
of a time between them.
The entire barrier, over a 20-meter radius,
was ripped apart all at once?
How?
Without even the slightest delay...
How... all at once...?
How?
Kakyoin!
I-I can't let this continue! Hermit...
Joseph... You're next.
Don't you think taking the blood of a Joestar
would be just the thing to make
Jonathan's body completely mine?
DIO!
How could he hit them all with
no time passing between them?
Time passing...
Time...
The time!
I... I understand now.
H-How could this be?
There's no other explanation.
I-I have to tell them about this!
This terrifying truth... Somehow...
I have to tell Mr. Joestar...
At this rate, everyone will
be defeated.
How dare you do that to Kakyoin?!
I'll take that body back, for my Grandma Erina!
Erina? Ah, that country girl.
How foolish.
I shall drink your blood and kill you.
Joseph Joestar!
Die!
M-My final Emerald... Splash...
What?
He didn't even aim in the right direction.
I suppose he wanted to use up
the last of his strength to go out with a bang.
Impossible!
Kakyoin wouldn't do something
pointless at a time like this.
So why in that direction?
What does it mean?
Is he trying to tell me something?
It's a... message.
It's the best I can do...
Mr. Joestar...
Please understand.
Please, figure it out...
Kakyoin...
Noriaki Kakyoin
Noriaki Kakyoin has died.
— has died —
Hermit Purple!
And take this!
The sun's own energy, Hamon!
You old fool! Your Stand is the weakest of all!
I won't let you get away!
Kakyoin, why did you shoot the clock tower?
What was shooting the
clock tower supposed to tell me?
It must mean something important!
I-It's Mr. Joestar!
DIO's chasing after him.
Where's Kakyoin?!
Could it be, Kakyoin...
Were you able to solve the mystery
of DIO's Stand while all that was going on?
He destroyed the clock with Emerald Splash.
He destroyed the clock's hands...
He... stopped the clock?
I-Impossible! Could it truly be...
The true power of DIO's The World
is the power to stop time!
Take this, DIO! 20-meter
radius Emerald Splash!
The World!
Doom
This is The World.
But since time has stopped for you,
you can neither see nor feel him.
Die, Kakyoin!
You don't even realize that you've been killed.
There's no way for you to
even know what happened.
I understand, Kakyoin!
You died to send me that message...
and I've gotten it!
Hermit Purple
Joseph Joestar
It stops time?
It's a Stand that can stop time and keep moving?
That's too dangerous! Way too dangerous!
Calm down... Calm down and think!
I don't know the meaning of the word "panic"!
I need to think of something...
Some way to break through and defeat him!
H-He disappeared!
Wh-What's wrong?
Not going to hit me, DIO?
Weren't you going to drink my blood?
You've suffused your body with Hamon
to protect yourself.
Hermit Purple, infused with Hamon,
is like a high-voltage wire wrapped
around your body, isn't it?
You're quite the schemer,
you cunning old geezer.
The same goes for you.
You realized I was using Hamon
and made sure not to touch me.
Very attentive of you.
But I've figured something
out about your Stand.
DIO, though you can stop time,
it looks like you can only do so very briefly.
About three to four seconds, I'd say.
If you could stop time for any longer,
we would have all died back at your mansion,
and you wouldn't have had to chase us down.
So you understand how The World works? Hah!
I'll spare you a bit of praise for that.
It was Kakyoin who figured it out.
I won't let Kakyoin die for nothing!
And what of it?
What good does understanding
my Stand's power do for you?
What can your Hamon possibly do now?
Hermit Purple and Hamon!
Enough!
I don't need to touch the Hamon to attack you!
Hey, look.
That old guy fell outta the sky!
Santa! I bet he's Santa!
What were you doing on the roof?
Checking out some hot chicks?
Old man...
J-Jotaro!
Stay back!
Don't come near me!
Jotaro... What perfect timing.
But he's not quite in range.
I'll deal with Joseph first.
Jotaro! The secret of his Stand,
The World, is time!
It's a Stand that stops ti―
The World!
At first, I could only stop time
for a mere blink of an eye.
But as my neck wound began to heal,
I soon could stop it for two seconds, then three.
I can now stop time for five seconds.
It's strange to think of it as five seconds,
since it occurs when time is stopped,
but I have five seconds in which to act.
Eventually I'll get to a minute...
Then ten minutes, then an hour...
Then as long as I want!
It's quite exciting,
knowing that I will be able to stop
time for longer and longer...
Oh, that's right, Joseph.
You were using Hamon to protect your body.
Hamon gave me a little trouble
a hundred years ago,
but it's powerless before The World.
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Useless!
Halt
The grandson of Jonathan, Joseph...
You are now dead!
One more second...
Zero.
The World
Old man!
S-Stay back! R-Run... J-Jotaro...
D-Don't go near him.
K-Keep your...
d-distance...
Stay away... Stay away from him...
Y-You're no... match...
I've already taken care of Kakyoin, too.
Polnareff must be hiding somewhere...
Hah. But it doesn't matter.
You're next, Jotaro!
You bastard.
DIO!
Oh? You're approaching me?
Instead of running away,
you're coming right to me?
Even though your grandfather, Joseph,
told you the secret of The World,
like an exam student scrambling to finish
the problems on an exam until the
last moments before the chime?
I can't beat the shit out of
you without getting closer.
Oh ho! Then come as close as you like.
Too slow, too slow!
The World is the ultimate Stand.
Even without his power to stop time,
his speed and power
far exceed that of your Star Platinum.
So it's the same type of Stand as Star Platinum.
Not much range, but immense
power and precise movements.
I wanted to try a little test to find out
just how much more powerful The World
was, compared to your Stand.
Though it appears a test was hardly necessary.
Test? Is that what you call just patting me,
and not even enough to hurt?
Well, I guess you ripped my
20,000 yen pants, though.
Why are you Joestars so stubborn
about admitting defeat?
Hmph. I suppose I shall rise
to your silly provocation,
and test you just a bit more.
Shall we compare the speed
of our attack rushes?
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Next Episode Preview
I first experienced stopped
time half a year ago.
It began when everything around
me seemed to have stopped.
It will be The World's true power
that deals the final blow!
The World, stop time!
Episode 47
DIO's World, Part 3