All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Last time on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
It's her! That woman is the user!
Oh, my. What a forward, aggressive approach.
Smooch!
Oh my God!
Avdol, I forgot to tell you earlier,
but don't touch anything that
looks like an electrical outlet.
I'm afraid I've touched it, Mr. Joestar.
What?!
Two magnets, when close together,
will attract each other!
Mr. Joestar, this situation...
Yeah, it's extremely bad.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 30
Bast's Mariah, Part 2
Hey! Wait!
Damn it...
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
She went around the corner! After her!
Stuck
This is absurd! I can't believe
my body's become a magnet, too!
Calm down, Avdol!
We can't help that her power's taken hold of us.
Just think about fighting and defeating her Stand!
Where did that woman go?! Damn it!
I don't see her.
Anyway, we can't stay here like this forever.
Stand up slowly, Avdol.
Understood.
We managed to stand up.
N-Now, let's try to separate ourselves.
If we're stuck together,
that must mean twice the
magnetic force is affecting us.
Let's go to that fence, grab hold, and pull apart.
Here we go, Avdol. Use your core muscles!
Get a rhythm going!
Right, Mr. Joestar.
One! Two!
One, two.
Ah...
M-Mr. Joestar...
Th-This is very embarrassing.
Hey! What are you looking at?
We're just practicing a dance. A dance!
Y-Yes, dancing outside is truly the best!
Go away, damn it!
All right. Just a little more, Avdol.
One, two, and...
We did it! We made it this far without tripping.
I-Indeed...
Avdol, do you think you can slowly slide off of me?
Yes, I think I can.
All right...
I'll hold on to this fence.
Try to slide down my body,
and move away from my toes.
Since our heads are sticking together,
our heads and feet must have opposite polarities,
Positive
Negative
letting us separate there.
R-Right...
Y-Yes, just like that.
Wh-What's wrong, Avdol?
Th-This position...
Doesn't this look very risqué?
If anyone saw us, they might get the wrong idea...
N-No one's looking! Hurry up and slide free!
They brought even more friends!
H-Hey! Go away! Stop looking at us!
Hey! I said go away, you damn brats!
Avdol, hurry! Hurry up and slide off!
That's easier said than done...
This is not the role I've taken! I swear it isn't!
Fine, then I'll move!
M-Mr. Joestar, slow down!
Stick
Mr. Joestar, if you move like that...
I-It's the old lady from the hotel!
I thought you were a wonderful gentleman,
but to think you're into this sort of filth!
How dare you play with a woman's heart?!
You cheater!
Hurry! Hurry, Avdol! I'm starting to cry!
You villain!
Help me! Oh my God!
Wait... This is a misunderstanding!
We did it!
We need to stay apart, Avdol!
Your magnetism is growing stronger and stronger.
Curse you, damned fool! Go to hell!
There she is. It's that woman.
She's got some nerve,
just sitting there and smoking.
Avdol, approach her from that side.
Don't let her get away this time.
She seems like a strong woman.
She may have laid a trap for us.
N-No, Mr. Joestar...
It seems we've already fallen into her trap!
Bam
A railroad track!
M-My foot is stuck!
A-Again...
...we're...
...stuck together!
Son of a bi—
What is it, Mr. Joestar?
This sound... O-Oh, no! We can't stay here!
Avdol, use Magician's Red's
flames to slice the rails!
We need to get away now!
B-But, Mr. Joestar...
It's coming! The train's coming!
Hurry up and slice the rails!
I-I can't. If I were to slice these rails...
The train would derail, causing a
huge accident and killing many people!
That woman... How dare she...
Even if I tried to grab her with my vines,
she's out of my Stand's range.
But I can try using that post to pull us free...
I-It's no use! The magnetism's gotten stronger.
Mr. Joestar, keep pulling! You can do it!
I-It's coming! Pull harder!
What?!
Ker-thump
I've won.
Bast
Mariah
I've won, Lord DIO!
Now to kill Jotaro and Polnareff!
Good thinking, Avdol! You burned
through the railroad ties and dug a hole!
This is it! This!
This suits the image of Mohammed Avdol!
This is the role my character plays!
C-Clever little bastard...
You...
shit-eating bitches!
Magician's Red!
Swoosh
Hermit Purple!
Grab
I've got you!
Now, young lady...
I regret that I'm now going
to strangle you enough
to put you in the hospital for a week.
Your magnetism is rather troublesome, you know.
Boom
What are you imagining?
My chest didn't get bigger...
Your magnetism just got stronger.
This is what I had in my pockets.
The weapons I had in my pockets!
Mr. Joestar, duck!
Magician's Red!
Your magnetic force will keep growing stronger...
Until your bodies are crushed.
She's getting away!
No, she's not escaping.
She's keeping a certain distance between us.
I'm sure that woman fights by
staying neither too close nor too far.
If she gets too close to us, she'll be caught.
If she goes too far, the magnetism stops working.
This magnetism is the work of a Stand,
so it follows the rules of Stands.
Once the user is too far away, its power weakens!
What shall we do?
She said the magnetism would keep getting stronger.
Shall we flee until the magnetic force expires?
No. Even if we were able to
escape this magnetism,
it won't mean we defeated the Stand.
I, Joseph Joestar,
have strategically retreated from
fights in my younger days,
but I've never once abandoned a fight.
I'm going to keep fighting with all my might!
This is a map of the city.
Right now, we're here.
The woman is here.
If she continues down this road,
she'll loop around and head back this way.
We'll split up
and catch the woman here.
I won't think of her as a woman anymore.
I'll get her, no matter what!
After her!
Hey, look.
The rails have been cut...
People from the city have arrived.
I'm sure they'll report the damage
before the next train comes.
Let's go!
Seems like something's going on.
Someone cut the rail line!
Will the trains be okay?
They've stopped running for now.
Someone cut the rail line?
That's a pretty crappy thing to do.
Why would someone do that? Are they stupid?
You know, Jotaro...
I think people like that
will get what they deserve.
I spent three months' pay on this.
Let's get married!
Oh, my...
Huh? Wait, what?!
Huh?
They're chasing as fast as they can...
B-But they'll never catch me.
Stay calm. Gotta stay calm...
Looks like you can barely move now.
You won't be able to chase me anymore.
You think so?
I know these roads better than you do.
Look behind you.
It's a pincer attack!
We've finally cornered you.
Now, at the last moment, the tables have turned!
A pincer attack?
You still don't get it.
You think you've cornered me,
but it's you two who are cornered.
Look above you!
High voltage power lines!
Crap! Power lines are...
That's right. Power lines are magnetic.
You'll burn to a crisp!
Magician's Red!
Hermit Purple!
Avdol can defend himself
with his flames, just barely,
but you have no chance, Joestar.
My Bast's power is far greater
than your Hermit Purple's!
Woman, my flames will roast you!
Something's pulling me!
My whole body's being pulled!
Wh-What is this?!
I control flames that can melt steel,
but I can't defend myself from this...
My body is being crushed!
I can't keep this up!
Joseph Joestar, since this is the end, I'll tell you...
You were quite amazing.
We've only known each other for a few minutes,
but you are witty and canny,
and your experience gives you the
good judgment that young people lack.
You've got very charming looks, too.
Our ages are quite far apart, but I
might not have minded being with you.
Th-That's great...
Would you mind saving me, then?
Hmm...
You're a lot more powerful than my Hermit Purple!
I can't hold on much longer...
P-Please. Stop the magnetism!
Well...
Nah, I don't think so.
You're nowhere near as charming as Lord DIO.
I-Is there nothing that will convince
you to stop the magnetism?
No, not happening.
Sorry, but you have to die.
Even though I'm begging you?
You're much too persistent, you fool.
Then you've lost, young lady.
What?!
Sh-Shi—
Crash
We told you this was a pincer attack!
Magnets are attracted to each other.
Once you were between us, your luck ran out.
She can't hear you, Mr. Joestar.
It looks like she's passed out.
She's been crushed by the
weight and magnetic force.
I'm sure she's broken more than a few bones.
Now, then... Shall we go get some breakfast?
Certainly. I'm rather hungry
after all that running around.
It's already 9:00 AM.
Shit-eating bitches...
Ma
Mar
Mari
Mariah
Ba
Bas
Mariah
Bast
All
Mariah
Bast
All bones
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
admit
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
admitted
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
admitted to
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
admitted to hos
Mariah
Bast
All bones broken,
admitted to hospital.
Unable to Recover
(Must Retire)
Hermit Purple
Joseph Joestar
They're taking forever...
What the hell are they doing?
They're taking longer than
a woman getting dressed.
It's almost 9:00 AM...
They might have encountered an enemy.
Maybe we should go look for them.
Yeah. Good grief.
Come on, Iggy.
I know, I know. You're hungry, right?
So am I.
Menacing
Mariah is fighting with Joestar and Avdol.
I, Alessi, shall kill Jotaro and Polnareff.
Next Episode Preview
Now, little boy. Come with me to the
bathroom and take off your clothes.
Well done.
I'll help you take them off.
I'll apply some ointment.
Well done.
Is this really okay?!
Episode 32
Set's Alessi,
Part 1
Well done...