All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
So we finally meet,
DIO!
Congratulations, Polnareff.
You've avenged your sister,
and managed to travel from
the Far East to make it here.
If you want to give me a prize for that,
how about you give me your life?
I shall give you a chance.
Go down two steps,
and I'll let you join my side again.
But if you'd rather die,
then climb those stairs.
When I first met you,
I succumbed from the bottom of my heart
to your spell of fear and immense evil.
That was when I became a loser.
It's much scarier than death,
living with no desire but to do your bidding.
But right now, I don't feel any fear at all.
I feel only my will to fight.
Since I met Mr. Joestar and the others,
this journey of 45 days
and the death of my friends
have completely blown away my fear of you.
Is that so?
Then climb those stairs.
I see, Polnareff.
You've gone down the stairs,
which means you wish to join me, DIO.
Wh-What?! I know I just took a step up...
What's the matter? You're losing
your composure, Polnareff.
Doesn't one lose his
composure when he is afraid?
Or is it that in your heart,
you know you must climb up,
but you're so terrified that your body
subconsciously did the opposite and went down?
Impossible! I know I went up the stairs!
Wh-What did he do?! Is it his Stand?
I-It can't be...
DIO's Stand...
The World?!
Wh-What is...
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 45  DIO's World, Part 1
Polnareff, have you ever considered
why humans wish to live?
Humans live hoping to conquer
their anxieties and fears,
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
and attain peace of mind.
Seeking fame,
controlling others,
and acquiring wealth are all
done to achieve peace of mind.
Marriage and friendship are also pursued
as means of attaining peace of mind.
When humans say they wish to help others,
or that a thing is done for love or justice...
It's all merely to give themselves peace of mind.
To achieve peace of mind
is the goal of all mankind.
Now, given that, what anxiety could
you possibly feel toward serving me?
Any other peace of mind
will come easily if you do.
Doesn't challenging me, even knowing
that it may spell your death,
bring you anxiety?
I-It can't be! Am I subconsciously
submitting to him?
You are a very capable Stand user.
It's a waste to kill you.
Why not cut ties with Joestar and the others,
and serve me for eternity?
I can promise you peace of mind for eternity.
I can't go on like this...
Avdol, Iggy... Give me courage!
Y-You talk too much, DIO!
I've already died once.
I won't die again until I figure out
the identity of your Stand!
You leave me no choice.
Then you'll just have to die, Polnareff!
So that's The World? Bring it on!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
M-Mr. Joestar!
Don't worry, Polnareff.
DIO!
That was DIO, wasn't it?
We're going after him!
Before you go after him, let me say this.
I just experienced his Stand, just for a moment.
Actually, it wasn't so much an experience...
It was completely beyond my understanding.
I-I'll tell you exactly what happened.
I thought I was climbing the stairs
toward him, but before I knew it,
I was actually going down!
I-I'm sure you guys don't
understand what I'm saying,
and I don't know what he did, either.
I thought I was going insane.
It wasn't anything simple,
like hypnosis or super speed...
I experienced something much more terrifying.
Where are Avdol and Iggy?
Th-They didn't make it...
They died saving me.
I see.
Mr. Joestar, the sun is setting.
We must hurry.
You're right.
Hey, Nukesaku. What's above this floor?
A-A tower.
There is a single room at the very top.
Lord DIO stays there during the day.
Do any other staircases lead up to that tower?
N-No. These stairs are the only way.
All right. Lead the way.
So that's him.
The man we're about to face
is one I've never met,
yet one I've known for so long.
Yes. I have always known him.
I've known him since the day I was born.
The same goes for Jotaro.
He's not someone we have fond memories of.
Our Joestar blood always knew that
he was someone we would encounter
one day, someone we must defeat.
I have no regrets.
The journey we've made,
the events about to transpire...
I regret none of it.
What I'm feeling right now
tells me the side I'm on is white.
DIO's side is black.
Mr. Joestar and the others, too, are white.
Despite my injuries, I can
feel my courage growing.
I am on the white side,
the side of righteousness!
Once he steps out of the coffin, we'll attack.
But be careful.
There's no guarantee that he's in there.
Nukesaku, open the lid.
L-Lord DIO, I promise, I did not betray you.
It's because I truly believe in
your power that I led them here.
As certain as when you piss in a
strong wind, it'll get on your pants!
Please understand!
Shut up and open it already!
Make sure you kill these bastards,
Lord DIO!
He's going to come flying out!
Huh?
Me?!
I-I was the one inside?!
But I was the one that opened the lid!
Wh-What?! How?!
I never took my eyes off him!
Did any of you see the
moment Nukesaku entered...
No, was put into the coffin?
N-No... I was watching the whole time,
but when I realized it, he was already inside!
It's as Polnareff said!
This is not merely a trick or super speed!
We're in danger.
Something here is truly dangerous!
Run!
D-Damn it!
What are you doing, Polnareff?
Damn it!
What in the world was that?
I didn't actually see it, but it felt much
more powerful than any Stand
we've encountered so far.
It was like knowing a bulldozer is present
from the sound of its engine alone.
I felt it, too. It was incredible murderous intent!
It felt like someone stuck an icicle up my ass!
If we had stayed in there,
we would've been killed, one by one!
This is bad... This is extremely bad.
The sun's almost out of sight!
His time has come.
Don't tell me that we're
going to be helpless until sunrise tomorrow.
I'll telling you now, Mr. Joestar!
There's no way I'm going to run away now!
I agree with Polnareff.
I feel the same way,
but the situation has changed.
We've encountered his Stand, The World,
but we have no idea what it does.
When climbing a mountain,
if you don't know the route,
or where the summit is,
you are guaranteed to get lost. Guaranteed!
It's as inevitable as belching
after you drink a cola.
We know DIO will come after us.
He'll try to finish us before sunrise.
In that time, we'll have
the opportunity to figure out
his Stand's true ability.
We have to wait for that chance.
No! I can't run away!
Avdol and Iggy died for me!
I'll do underhanded things,
and even go to Hell itself,
but I will not run away!
Wait, Polnareff!
It's no use trying to stop him, old man.
Jotaro, tell us what you think we should do.
Polnareff is fighting him as he pursues him.
We'll fight him as we retreat.
That means
we'll be in position for a pincer attack.
Hey, you there.
I want to buy that truck. Sell it to me.
What'd you say? I need this to do my job!
What're you—
I'm flooring it, Kakyoin!
There you are, DIO!
Run away until sunrise? Like hell I can do that!
I'll finish you myself if I must!
If I don't know what your Stand is,
then even without that knowledge,
there are still plenty of ways to beat you.
I'll assassinate you!
Don't do anything rash, Polnareff!
I told them to leave someone
as stubborn as you alone,
but the old man and Kakyoin
insisted that I stay with you.
So here I am.
Jotaro...
Good grief.
The World
Ah, the automobile...
Its power and speed are impressive.
In my day, we had only horse-drawn carriages.
Hey! What do you think you're touching?
This car belongs to Senator Phillips!
Do you wanna puke from your eyes?!
My, my... Young folks are
so hot-blooded these days.
Ow!
Shut up and get in the front seat.
You're going to drive.
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Do you think you're going
to get away with this?!
No, of course he won't!
No one could get away with doing this to me.
I graduated high school and
college at the top of my class!
I was captain of my college wrestling team!
Even after I graduated,
I was respected and revered.
That's how I became a politician!
I have a villa on a thousand acres in Hawaii!
I married a beautiful model
who's 25 years younger than me!
I pay 50 times more in taxes
than ordinary people!
I've defeated every enemy that I've faced.
I'll eventually become president.
I am Senator Phillips!
Listen up, young buck!
You'll get life in prison for this!
You hear me? Life in prison—
I'll say it once more.
Drive.
Wh-Who the hell is he? He's going to kill me!
If I don't escape, he'll kill me!
If I don't escape, he will kill me!
Help... me?
Wh-What?!
I thought I jumped outside,
so wh-why... why... am I inside...
Why am I inside?
Floor it until you catch up to that truck.
If you fail to catch up to it, I'll kill you.
Y-Yes, sir.
Why inside?! Why?!
I know! It's because I'm a senator!
There's nothing a senator can't do!
The black atmosphere that emanates
from him is still close...
It's coming after us.
He's coming after us!
Can DIO tell exactly where you are, Mr. Joestar?
No. His body is that of my
grandfather, Jonathan Joestar.
We can sense each other due to something
like a strange wavelength between us,
but we can only tell that the
other is close, not where he is.
I couldn't tell exactly where the mansion was,
either, even though we were nearby.
All he can sense is that a Joestar is nearby.
He can't tell the difference
between Jotaro and myself.
He shouldn't be able to realize that
Jotaro and I have split up.
That's strange...
In movies, the engine always starts right up.
W-We're stuck in traffic.
Rush hour traffic in the
evening is bumper to bumper.
Go.
You say that, but I can't move forward.
The sidewalk is wide enough. Go.
The sidewalk?!
It's packed with people heading home from work!
That makes no difference. Go.
Y-Yes, sir!
Floor it.
Yes, sir!
It started. Hurry up and get on, Polnareff.
R-Right...
I've gone to such lengths for you!
You'll spare my life... You'll spare
this senator's life now, won't you?!
No.
I see! This is a dream!
A senator like me could never die this way.
It's a dream! A dream! Hooray!
There he is. Get closer to them. Closer.
If I'm not close, I cannot use The World.
He's getting closer. It's that car! DIO's in there!
Kakyoin!
Kakyoin's...
Take this, DIO! Emerald Splash!
Wh-What is he?!
He didn't so much as move from his seat,
but he managed to dodge with just one finger!
How about this?!
Even when I concentrated the Splash,
he dodged. D-Damn it!
When did he release his Stand?
Impossible! How could I not notice?!
He was a bit too far away.
He went flying out of The World's range.
Wh-What's happening?!
Would it benefit me in any way if I told you?
Keep your eyes forward and drive.
Careful, Kakyoin! You got too close to him!
I-I apologize. I-I couldn't help it.
A few months ago, he said,
"There's no need to make
yourself vomit from fright."
"Relax. Relax, Kakyoin..."
Damn it! Never again! I will never lose again!
Kakyoin, are you all right?
Did you see The World?
Yes... I attacked from around ten meters away.
If I had gotten any closer,
I would have been done for.
It's obvious that his Stand
has some terrifying secret far
beyond anything we can imagine.
But I've managed to figure out two things.
First, it can't attack over distance like
Hierophant Green and Hermit Purple.
It's a close-range power type, like Star Platinum.
Its range is about ten meters.
Second, it attacked with its fist.
So it doesn't use ranged attacks, like bullets.
If we can get within ten meters
of DIO without him noticing,
I think we may have a chance of defeating him.
We need to investigate carefully.
There's no such thing as being too
cautious when it comes to him.
That's strange. His car stopped.
Watch out! Something's flying at us!
Mr. Joestar!
What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I've got it.
I've figured out a way to reveal
what DIO's Stand truly is.
Next Episode Preview
I wonder why I get goosebumps
when I think about Avdol and Iggy.
Perhaps because they were the first
friends I shared a common goal with.
This journey to defeat DIO...
Show me your Stand, DIO!
Episode 46
DIO's World, Part 2