All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
"Which creature walks on
four legs in the morning,
two legs in the afternoon,
and three legs in the evening?"
The guardian of the pyramids,
the Sphinx, asked travelers this riddle.
The answer is "Humans."
Legend says that those who could
not answer were eaten by the Sphinx.
Thirty thousand kilometers from Japan,
Jotaro and the others have finally reached Cairo.
Cairo is immense.
Rather than searching aimlessly,
we should work our way from
the outskirts inward to the center.
We're finally here.
Jotaro and the others have arrived in Cairo.
But before the pyramid named DIO,
a few more Sphinxes stood in their way.
Welcome, foreigners. What would you like?
There's something I'd like to ask you.
We're looking for the building in this picture.
Do you know where it is?
Joseph and the others were exhausted.
Ever since their arrival,
they had searched constantly
for the building in the picture.
These are spirit pictures that
Joseph managed to take of DIO's mansion.
DIO had moved to a new hideout,
and the Speedwagon Foundation
had lost track of his whereabouts.
Where is DIO?
If they are unable to find
him in the next few days,
Holly's life will come to an end.
Sirs, this is a café. Please order something.
Four iced teas.
Nope, I don't recognize it.
Cairo has a population of six million.
There must be two to three million buildings.
Will we be able to find him?
There has to be someone...
Someone has to know where it is.
This building, huh?
I can't tell from just a picture...
Sorry, it doesn't look familiar.
I see. Sorry to bother you.
No problem.
Come on. Let's continue our investigation.
I know that building.
What?!
No doubt about it. It's that building.
Spread
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 34  D'Arby the Gambler, Part 1
W-Was it you who just said that?
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
I just heard someone say
they know this building.
Yes.
I did indeed say that I know where
the mansion in that picture is located.
What? Really?!
That's great to hear!
Yes! We're pretty lucky to have
found someone who knows
where it is just from this picture.
Where? Please tell us! Where is it?
Are you asking me to give
you the answer for free?
Y-You've got a point. Sorry about that.
I'll pay you ten pounds.
So, where is it?
I love gambling.
I'm a sucker for cheap thrills.
I can't get enough of them.
Well, you could say that
I make my living gambling.
Do you like gambling?
I'm not sure what you're getting at.
If you don't like gambling, just say so.
I'm asking you exactly what you mean by that.
Well... Would you make a
silly little wager with me?
If you win, I'll tell you
where that place is for free.
Wager? I'm pretty confident
when it comes to wagers,
but we don't have time
to play poker right now.
I'll give you another twenty pounds,
so please just tell us.
The thing about gambling is,
you can do it with anything.
It won't take any time at all.
For example,
look over there. See that cat?
Now, why don't we bet on which
smoked fish that cat will eat first?
Right or left?
How about it? It's silly, but thrilling.
Hey! You're really starting to annoy me!
Just take the thirty pounds,
and hurry up and tell us!
Polnareff, that's not the way to
ask someone for information.
Okay, fine! Then I'll make a bet.
I pick the one on the right!
Good! Now it's getting fun.
Then I shall wager on the left.
Hey, now...
Hey, Jotaro. Isn't he rather suspicious?
Yeah... He might be an enemy Stand user.
But he might just be a compulsive gambler.
If he does anything even remotely strange,
plow through him with Star Platinum.
Got it.
By the way, if I lose,
what am I supposed to pay you?
Like, a hundred pounds?
I don't need money.
How about your soul? I'll take your soul.
What?
What kind of joke is that? Cocky bastard.
I want to hurry up and
get the hell away from him.
Your answer?
Yeah, okay, sure. That's fine.
Oh? The cat has taken
notice of the smoked fish.
The right.
The kitty's going to the right.
If I were a cat, I'd pick the bigger one.
The one on the right looks bigger!
You saw it.
It first took the left,
then the right, and then ran.
I win.
Hey, you lost, Polnareff.
What are you going to do now?
I'm getting sick of asking
around about that building.
Now, then. As per our agreement,
let's have you pay up.
Huh? Pay? Pay what?
Your soul.
That is indeed what you just wagered.
Your soul!
I am a Stand user that steals souls!
Gambling makes it easier for the
human soul to leave its vessel.
It is my Stand's power to
steal it at that moment!
What?! What's going on?!
Grab
Polnareff!
Hold it! Don't kill me. It's too late!
If I die, Polnareff's soul, which is
in my Stand's grasp, will also die.
Polnareff!
H-Hey!
H-He has no pulse.
He's dead! Polnareff is dead!
Polnareff!
This is Polnareff's soul.
This means I've already gotten rid of one
of the people trying to get in Lord DIO's way.
Even if he was just a fool.
It's a little overdue,
but allow me to introduce myself.
My name is D'Arby.
D-A-R-B-Y. There's an apostrophe after the D.
The Stand that steals souls
from those who lost a bet...
The one that suggests Osiris.
By the way, this is my cat.
Y-You bastard!
Don't screw with us! A bet? It was just a scam!
A scam?
Listen. If you've been scammed,
the one who failed to see through it is the loser.
I believe gambling is just like relationships.
It's all about fooling the other.
The one who cries loses.
Are you going to kill me with your bare hands?
Very well. Do it.
If you want this soul to die, as well.
Listen here.
You will not walk away from this in one piece.
Do you remember what you
were doing on the night of
September 22nd, 1984 at 11:15 PM?
What are you talking about?
I remember.
Around that time in California,
I was gambling with an American
man named Stephen Moor,
and he said the same thing you just did.
This is him.
The one below is Moor's father,
and his wife is right next to him.
If you want to get Polnareff's soul back,
you have no choice but to continue
gambling with me.
Th-This man is a demon...
He's planning to take us, one by one.
What will you do?
If you're scared, you can go home...
And leave Polnareff behind.
Well, have a drink and think
about it long and hard.
How about some chocolate?
M-Mr. Joestar, what are you trying to do?
Have you heard of surface tension, Barbie?
It's D'Arby. My name is D'Arby.
It's the force that's keeping that drink
from breaking the surface, correct?
What do you plan to do?
The rules are simple.
We'll take turns putting coins in this glass.
The one who makes it overflow loses.
Hey, old man...
Y-You can't mean... Mr. Joestar!
I'll wager my soul on it!
Osiris
D'Arby Elder
I'll wager my soul on it!
Good!
What?!
Impossible! P-Please don't! He's a con artist!
I won't let him cheat!
I'm the one who chose the method of this wager!
Jotaro, make sure he doesn't cheat.
Okay! That's fine. I shall take this bet.
But first...
Do you mind if I inspect the glass and coins?
Of course, you have that right.
You also have the right to
make sure I'm not cheating.
First, will you guarantee that if you lose,
you will return Polnareff's
soul, no matter what?
I am a gambler. I do have my pride.
If I lose, I always pay up.
I won't lose, though.
Very well. You can go first. Put in a coin.
Mr. Joestar!
Just leave this to me.
I'm an expert at this trick with a glass and coins.
I'm not easy to beat when
surface tension is involved.
It should fit about eight or nine more coins...
As long as I can remain calm
and my fingers don't shake.
May I put in more than one coin at a time?
If you can do it all at once.
Well, then...
F-Five?!
Hey, I think I saw a little wave there.
Quiet!
Don't touch the table.
It's your turn.
Your guts are quite impressive,
to put in five at once.
I'll go with one.
That was too close.
The old man...
He has cotton between his finger and the coin.
Liquid is dripping from it.
He's squeezing it out and adding to the alcohol.
And you wanted me to watch for cheating?
You scoundrel...
Not bad.
No more will fit!
Even one more and the
drink will spill over! I've won!
It's not a scam if you're not caught!
That's what he said himself.
This is bad for my heart.
I thought it was going to spill...
Now it's your turn, Obie.
It's D'Arby. Don't mistake that again!
My name is D'Arby!
It's not Obie or Barbie!
My apologies.
He's screwing up his name on
purpose to make him agitated.
That old man...
He's a gambler at heart.
Let's continue our wager.
It's your turn to put in a coin, D'Arby.
There's a shadow, so this angle is difficult.
I'll put it in from the right side of the table.
You may put it in from wherever you like.
Though because of my cheat,
it's already at its limit.
He can't put any more in,
no matter what he tries.
It'll overflow if he even touches the surface.
You're thinking that this glass's
surface tension is at it's limit.
That it's impossible, right?
But that's not true...
I-Impossible! It can't be!
There's no way it wouldn't overflow!
What do you mean,
there's no way it wouldn't overflow?
As you can see, it went in.
He made no suspicious moves
that could've been cheating.
I was watching with Star Platinum.
He put the coin in fairly.
There's no doubt about it.
B-But I made sure!
I made sure that it would
overflow if one more was added!
Why? There's no way one
more could have gone in!
So how?!
Go ahead, Mr. Joestar.
Hurry it up.
Or are you trying to wait until it evaporates?
I-I can't believe it.
Mr. Joestar!
Joestar acknowledged in his mind
that he'd already lost the bet!
That's why his soul emerged.
I, D'Arby, have won this bet!
Polnareff, I'm sorry.
Holly, I might not be
able to save you, after all.
Mr. Joestar!
Old man!
That's two!
Now, then. Let us continue gambling.
As long as you two don't abandon
these two and run away with your
tails between your legs, that is.
You bastard!
You don't learn, do you?
If you kill me, these two souls will die, as well.
Damn it!
Avdol, stop!
Hey! If you're going to make trouble,
I'll have to ask you to leave!
Shut it. Stay out of this.
Yes, sir!
You realized it too late, Jotaro.
Is there something wrong with the glass?
This is how one more coin went in.
There was a tiny bit of chocolate
on the bottom of the glass's outside.
Before they started the game,
he asked to inspect the glass and coins,
and that's when he stuck it on.
I believe you were aware that
if it's not discovered in time,
you can't call it cheating.
Wh-What do you mean?
How is a bit of chocolate
the reason the coin fit?
It's melted now,
but until a moment ago, it was
solid at the bottom of the glass.
He used just enough so we wouldn't notice,
This side will spill
Glass is tilted
but the glass was propped up so it would tilt.
Once it melted, the surface became level.
Surface tension becomes equal
It melts
Even though the surface tension was at its limit,
he made it so at least one more coin would fit.
Wh-What?!
B-But...
Could chocolate actually melt
with such convenient timing?
He melted it using the sun's heat.
I didn't notice.
He went to the right side of the table
so the sun's rays would directly hit
the glass and melt the chocolate.
Fine.
D'Arby, get your trump card ready.
We'll finish this with poker.
J-Jotaro!
Rumble
How interesting!
Poker is one of the games I'm best at!
Poker? This man just beat Mr. Joestar!
I-It's too dangerous!
I know.
He's not violent,
but he's still more dangerous than
any other Stand user we've met so far.
But...
I can't afford not to do this.
Next Episode Preview
Draw three.
I'll draw two.
He's not doing anything suspicious, and yet...
Cheating is all about finding a mental blind spot.
There's only one joker.
Well, then, Jotaro...
Very well. I'll wager my soul.
Episode 35
D'Arby the Gambler, Part 2