All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
What the hell is that?
Why didn't Avdol's flames sense him?
Where are you, Avdol?!
Avdol...
has been disintegrated. He is dead.
You two are next.
I must correct your arrogant belief
that you can defeat Lord DIO.
One by one... In order...
I shall scatter you throughout
my dimension of darkness.
You're lying...
Saying that
you killed Avdol...
Don't lie to me!
Wh-What?
I hadn't heard
that Polnareff's Stand was so fast,
or could attack at this distance.
Look over here, damn it! You piece of shit!
Slice
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 43  The Miasma of the Void, Cool Ice, Part 2
What was that?
Just when I thought the illusion had gone away,
I heard the sound of a wall
breaking somewhere in the mansion.
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
Could it be Avdol and Polnareff?
Damn it! I know I hit him, b-but he's not dead...
They suddenly shrank and
disappeared into their dimension.
The user and the Stand both...
Avdol... God damn it.
You're... You're the one who said...
Polnareff! Iggy! Look out!
You said if something happened,
we had to think of ourselves first.
You said you wouldn't save me.
You liar!
Ever since India, all you've done is
meddle in other people's problems!
Avdol! You should have just left me alone!
If I hadn't crouched down just then,
I would have been killed.
Is fate telling me to live on?
Is Avdol's will telling me to fight?
It's too dangerous to stay in this room.
Let's move, Iggy!
Grar
Up there, Iggy!
Go upstairs! Up those stairs!
That's the exit! That's the door we came in.
But we can't go out that way.
Avdol sacrificed himself to save us.
Because he believed that we could defeat DIO.
I can't betray the trust of someone like that!
Running away now is what a loser would do.
I'm not running away.
I'm running to get to that bastard, DIO!
Let's run straight to him!
And I thought they'd go for the exit. So close...
I'm impressed that he managed to injure me.
It is indeed true that Polnareff
has a mindset that allows him
to conquer fear and face danger.
Without a doubt, I will corner
and kill him. Without a doubt...
My Stand is far stronger than he is.
The inside of his Stand's mouth
is a dimension of darkness?!
I can't even imagine what that dimension is like,
but it lets him get close without any
sounds, smells, or other signs of life.
But how...
How am I supposed to beat that guy?
H-He cut us off!
He's nearby.
He's here!
Iggy, watch my back!
I'll watch yours.
He can't come through without
breaking a hole in the wall.
What I do know is that
the moment he shows himself
from that dimension of darkness
is when we'll have our chance to kill him.
Come at me, damn it! I'll cut you in half!
Right now, my Chariot is incredibly fast.
Because of how angry I am at losing Avdol!
What?! H-He's in the crack under my foot?!
Chario—
Grar
My foot!
First, I've taken your foot,
so you won't be able to run around or escape!
Bastard!
Whoa, there.
Mr. Joestar! The sound of another wall breaking!
Yeah, there's no doubt about it.
Avdol and the others are in this
mansion, and they're fighting.
Hurry! We have to find them!
You managed to hide during
the confusion, Polnareff.
But it's no use.
With that foot, you can't go far.
You're probably under some rubble nearby.
You are powerless before me.
Without a doubt, I will defeat you.
Now, where are you, Polnareff?
What's all this noise, Cool Ice?
L-Lord DIO!
Please be careful!
Polnareff and that dog are hiding nearby.
Please leave this to me.
You need not personally trouble
yourself with this, Lord DIO.
The fake DIO we made using The Fool tricked him.
Usually, I'd feel guilty about attacking
someone from behind like a coward,
but since that's how you killed Avdol,
I don't feel even a shred of pity!
It's exactly how you deserve to die!
Do it, Iggy!
Cream
Cool Ice
Do it, Iggy!
Break through his scapula,
and split him open to the hip,
like a mackerel!
No! Damn it!
He figured it out!
Sunlight streams through this room's windows.
The real Lord DIO would never
leave his room to enter this place.
Iggy!
The real Lord DIO told me he trusts me,
and that he would leave this to me!
So, no matter what happens, he would
never descend to this second floor!
Shit! He's going to kill Iggy!
Iggy will be swallowed up by
that dimension of darkness!
You shitty little mutt! How dare you?!
You made me destroy an image of Lord DIO!
Wh-What the hell? He punched him!
He didn't use his dimension of darkness!
He punched Iggy across
the room without killing him!
Of all things...
Even if it was a fake Lord DIO made of sand,
how dare you make me strike him?!
I'll kick you to death, you bastard!
It takes but an instant to be swallowed
by my dimension of darkness!
That is not enough time for my anger to wane!
This is all your fault! You!
You're the one who has angered me!
This is all your fault!
Learn your lesson!
How's that?! Learn your lesson!
How's that? How's that?!
S-Stop...
Cool Ice isn't right in the head.
This is overkill.
He's mad that he had to attack DIO's image?
His mind itself is the dimension of darkness!
His mind is the black abyss
that rips everything apart!
Lord DIO said
that we cannot underestimate
the power of human resolve.
But you're no more than a filthy dog!
You don't have resolve,
or a proud soul, or anything like it!
Stop...
How's that? And that?
How's that? And that?!
Stop it, Cool Ice!
Bam
I will end this, Polnareff!
Damn it!
He disappeared!
But...
Iggy!
Our fake DIO made of your sand Stand failed,
but your sand gave me a hint.
I've figured out a way to read his movements!
I can see him.
I can see the route he's taking!
Serves you right! I've got you!
You bastard!
When you use your dimension to move,
you have to swallow up whatever's in your path.
So swallow this! Swallow the sand
and head this way, you shithead!
And when your rotten, stinking
mouth appears, that's when
you're going to crumble!
I hit him head-on! Hell yeah!
Your other weakness, Cool Ice,
appears when you try to confirm my location.
You've got to poke your head out
of your dimension of darkness,
or you can't see what's outside!
Suck on that!
Suck on my sword until you die,
you piece of shit!
Y-You bastard...
I pierced your brain stem
through your throat, damn it!
Hurry up and die! You're mortally wounded!
Just hurry up and die!
Die, Cool Ice!
I will not die.
I do not have time to suffer pain.
Whatever it takes, I will kill you!
Whatever it takes, I will swallow up Iggy
and kill Joestar and the others!
I can die after that!
You bastard!
A wise move. You've pulled your sword free.
This time, I will send you to hell!
Is this the vile arm that stabbed me?
You bastard...
Damn it! I had no choice
but to shove him away!
Shit!
Oh, no, you don't!
I cut it! B-But this isn't good...
Grar
Damn it! He got my leg. I can't move.
But I don't have time to
think about pain, either.
And I was so close to finishing him, too!
This guy is just...
He's obsessive!
He's crazy, but he's completely
obsessive about serving DIO!
I can't let that overwhelm me!
I can't die until I kill you, either!
That bastard! Here he comes!
Take this!
Grar
I-It's no use. I cut him, but he
swallowed the tip of my sword!
It's impossible to attack him when
he's in his dimension of darkness.
I'm just going to get being swallowed up.
He's swallowing up everything
in his path. God damn it!
Bastard... Since he knows I could attack him,
he's decided to just guess where I might be
and strike anywhere and everywhere!
He's got good instincts.
At this rate, he'll hit me for sure.
I have to pull back Chariot.
D-Damn it... Iggy's losing blood like crazy.
A bunch of broken bones are piercing his lungs...
Talk about reckless... The walls are disappearing.
N-No... I had the wrong idea!
This isn't instinct. His moves are calculated!
He's moving around in circles,
and the circles keep getting smaller.
He's on a path like a cyclone...
No, like a mosquito repellent
coil, closing in on me!
Even if he doesn't show up
to see where I am, he'll hit me eventually!
I'm caught in his trap.
A-Am I going to be able to dodge him with this leg?
I-I've got to dig through the floor and get away.
It's no use. I don't have enough time!
He's coming at me!
I somehow managed to dodge...
But he's going to keep closing in,
like a needle on a record.
In about five more rounds, he'll be here!
Now, here's the question...
How am I going to dodge when
I have this hole in my leg?
Pi
Pick
Pick one
Pick one of
Pick one of the
Pick one of the th
Pick one of the three
Pick one of the three fol
Pick one of the three follow
Pick one of the three following
Pick one of the three following choi
Pick one of the three following choices.
Ans
Answer #1
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The
Answer #1 The ha
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The hand
Answer #1 The handsome
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Po
Answer #1 The handsome Pol
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polna
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
Pick one of the three following choices.
su
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
sudd
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
sudden
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly th
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thi
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thin
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly think
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a coun
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a counter
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a counterattack.
Ans
Answer
Answer #2
Answer #2  His
Answer #2  His fri
Answer #2  His frien
Answer #2  His friends
Answer #2  His friends wi
Answer #2  His friends will
Answer #2  His friends will co
Answer #2  His friends will come
Answer #2  His friends will come sa
Answer #2  His friends will come save
Answer #2  His friends will come save him.
Ans
Answer
Answer #3
He
He won't
Answer #3
He won't be
He won't be able
Answer #3
He won't be able to
He won't be able to dodge.
Answer #3
Re
He won't be able to dodge.
Real
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reali
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reality
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is c
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is cru
Answer #3
He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is cruel.
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a counterattack.
Answer #2  His friends will come save him.
Answer #3 He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is cruel.
I'd like to choose answer #2,
but I can't count on it.
Pick one of the three following choices.
Answer #1 The handsome Polnareff
suddenly thinks of a counterattack.
Answer #2  His friends will come save him.
Answer #3 He won't be able to dodge.
Reality is cruel.
There's no way Mr. Joestar and the others,
who entered the mansion ten minutes earlier,
would show up in the next couple of seconds
like American comic book heroes—ta-da!—
and save me at the last minute.
For all I know, Mr. Joestar and the others
are struggling in their battle, too.
Looks like answer #1 is the only option.
Chariot! Pull me out of the
circle as hard as you can!
Damn it! Pull me faster!
I-It's no use!
Grar
Despair! The answer he's been left with is #3.
Answer #3
Reality is cruel.
My Silver Chariot is a Stand
that cuts things with a sword.
Now that I'm so badly injured,
it doesn't have the power to pull my weight.
Damn it...
You wreck! Keep still, you idiot!
If you move or use any more
of your Stand's power,
your broken bones will pierce further
into your lungs, and you'll die!
What are you trying to act
all tough for, you idiot?!
Are you trying to save me
so you can die along with me?
I'm the one who's going to look cool saving you!
You have to survive and warn Mr. Joestar
and the others about this bastard.
The important thing is to defeat him!
Avdol saved me, but you
don't need to save me, too!
If we all die, it's over!
One more time around,
and he'll come right to me.
The answer is #3.
Reality does not forgive.
Looks like his obsession... wins.
So long, Iggy.
Next Episode Preview
This blood is not your doing.
It is Avdol's.
I don't know the details.
I have really bad luck with friends...
Not to the likes of you!
It happens every time.
I only realize it after they're gone...
Episode 44
The Miasma of the Void, Cool Ice, Part 3