All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
It should be about time.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 25
Iggy the Fool and Geb's N'doul, Part 1
Wh-What's that?
They're here.
It's a helicopter!
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
You don't have to state the obvious.
We can see that.
That's a helicopter from
the Speedwagon Foundation.
They're looking for a place to land.
Speedwagon Foundation?
Your old friends who are taking
care of Mom back in Japan?
Yeah, that's right.
Don't tell me we're going
for a ride in that helicopter.
No. As much as I'd like to,
the crew aren't Stand users.
If we were attacked, they would be at risk.
Then why is that helicopter here?
They've brought us a helper.
What? A helper?
He has a few personality issues,
so it's taken a while to get him here.
Mr. Joestar!
It's impossible for him to
come with us on this trip!
There's no way he could be helpful.
Do you know him, Avdol?
Yeah, very well.
Hold on. If he's a helper,
that means he's a Stand user, right?
He's the Stand user whose Stand
suggests the card called The Fool.
The Fool?
Hah! That card sounds like an idiot.
We're lucky that he's not our enemy.
You wouldn't be able to beat him.
What'd you say, you asshole?
You'd better watch your mouth.
It's the truth.
And what's with the hand? That hurts.
Sounding all high-and-mighty and shit...
Knock it off already.
The helicopter landed.
Mr. Joestar! Thank goodness you're safe.
Thanks for coming out here. I appreciate it.
So...
Who's the Stand user?
I'm asking which one of you is the Stand user.
Is it you?
No, it's not either of us.
He's in the back seat.
The back seat...
I don't see anyone there.
No, he's there.
Hey, hey, hey!
You say he's there, but where is he?
Is he really short or something?
Get the hell out here! Come on!
W-Watch out!
Hm?
What's this sticky stuff?
Please, be careful!
The helicopter ride was rough,
so he's in a really bad mood.
Don't get close to him!
I told you, he's got some personality issues!
Polnareff, you can't win.
And I'm asking where the hell he is—
Whoa!
H-H-H-H-H-He's...
...a dog!
Don't tell me this dog is....
Yes! He is The Fool Stand's user.
His name is Iggy.
He loves to tear out human hair by the mouthful.
We don't know where he was born.
When even the dog catchers in
New York couldn't get him,
Avdol was able to find and finally capture him.
Oh, I just remembered.
While he's ripping out hair, he likes to...
fart in the human's face.
He's kind of vulgar.
God damn it! You're gonna pay for that!
Damn you...
Chariot!
Th-That's...
So that's The Fool.
We met an orangutan Stand user
off the shore of Singapore, but...
Who the hell do you think
you are, you stupid mutt?!
Don't make me cut you in half!
Slice
What the?! It's like it's turning into sand...
I-I can't cut it!
Now it became solid and swallowed up my sword!
That's...
Simply put, it's a Stand made of sand.
Yeah... And the simpler they are,
the stronger they are.
I'm not sure if I could hit it.
Hey! Help! Do something about this dog!
Sorry, Polnareff,
but I'm not about to get
my hair ripped out, too.
You monster!
Do you have his treats?
If we didn't, we wouldn't
have been able to make it here.
Stop! Help me!
His sense of smell is incredible.
What is that?
Coffee-flavored chewing gum.
It's Iggy's favorite treat,
and he'll do anything for it.
Mr. Avdol! Keep the box hidden from—
Oh, no! He got the box!
He loves coffee-flavored chewing gum,
but he still won't let down his guard for anyone.
At least take the paper off first.
There's no way he could actually help us.
Good grief.
Damn it...
My beautiful hair's been thinned...
You stupid bastard!
While he's eating the gum, he should be fine.
Let's get the supplies out now.
Here's some food and water for your trip.
Oh, thank you.
There are medical supplies
and a change of clothes, too.
Also, a new camera, for taking spirit pictures.
TVs don't work so well for spirit photography.
Oh, I know.
Hey, you guys.
I see. It'll make a nice memory.
Avdol! Hurry up with the gum!
But you're already such good friends, Polnareff!
Mr. Joestar, we'll be taking our leave now.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
About my daughter...
How is Holly doing?
Give it to me straight.
Well, sir... I hate to say this,
but I'm afraid she's not doing very well.
Her energy is fading,
and her life remains in danger.
According to the doctors from
our Speedwagon Foundation,
she'll be lucky if she survives
for another two weeks.
There's no time.
Damn it...
Also, we have some information for you.
According to the report, two days ago...
Nine mysterious men and women
gathered in a building that DIO
is believed to be hiding in,
and then they all departed together.
DIO and nine others?
We don't know who they are.
The person who reported this was killed,
and the mansion had already been cleared out.
We were unable to locate
the nine men and women.
Any further investigation of
this matter is impossible for us,
since we are not Stand users.
Were they new Stand users?
Hold on.
Any remaining Stand users with Stands that
suggest Tarot cards...
Excluding Hol Horse's Emperor,
the only card left is The World.
I had thought that The World
would be DIO's Stand, but...
Avdol?
I-I don't know.
I have no idea. Nine of them?
Apparently, DIO's head hasn't
gotten used to its new body yet.
DIO is very proud, so there's
no way he'd flee from Cairo.
It would appear that he's trying
to stop us from reaching Cairo.
Good grief. There's only two
weeks left, and nine of them...
We might end up a little tired.
We'll be off, then.
Please have a safe trip.
Thank you. Take care of Holly.
That dog...
It noticed the presence of the Great N'doul, eh?
Damn. So close.
I was almost able to get it.
I guess I need more practice.
The Nile Ue Ue Fly, eh...
It's because of this fly
that Joestar and the others
were able to pursue Lord DIO this far...
The Fool
Iggy
Mr. Joestar, can't you
do something about this?
Why is that shitty little dog sitting in
the seat while we're stuck in the back?
It's so cramped, my back hurts.
You'll have to wait until the flavor from his
beloved coffee gum fades.
Once that happens, I'll throw
a new piece of gum into
the back so he'll go there.
Then you can change seats.
All right, all right. Calm down! Damn it...
Wh-What the hell?!
L-Look! Over there!
Th-That's...
The helicopter!
The Speedwagon Foundation helicopter
that flew off earlier is down in the sand!
There's no sign that it was attacked.
It's like it just fell to the ground.
It couldn't be!
Be careful!
It's very likely we'll be
attacked by the enemy's Stand!
Look! It's the pilot!
He's dead...
There are marks where he
clawed the helicopter's side...
This is horrible.
Approach carefully.
Something could be hiding there.
It's water.
So much water...
It's coming from the pilot's mouth...
No, from his lungs.
There's even a small fish.
He drowned in the middle of the desert!
What on earth?
H-Hey...
The other one's over here.
He's alive!
Are you all right? Get a hold of yourself!
What on earth happened?
Wa...
Water...
What? You want water?
Polnareff, hand me that canteen.
Right.
Here, get a hold of yourself.
Here's some water.
Drink slowly.
No! The water's going to attack!
What?!
I-It's the enemy Stand!
The enemy Stand is inside the canteen!
D-Damn it!
The Speedwagon Foundation crew wasn't
part of this fight,
but they were still attacked!
Avdol, did you see what kind of Stand it was?
I only saw a hand.
But it's still inside the canteen!
I haven't seen it leave.
Who could it be?
They mentioned that DIO
gathered nine men and women...
Is the attacker one of them, then?
Jotaro, locate the enemy's body.
I'm looking for it right now.
But...
The enemy's body isn't anywhere I can see.
I even looked for something like
that stupid mirror The Sun had.
But it seems the enemy is
operating from very far away.
Polnareff, attack the canteen.
Huh? Me...?
Th-The pilot's head was completely
sucked into that tiny little canteen.
So if I poke a hole in that thing...
Hell no!
Kakyoin! You're closer!
You should just hit it with an Emerald Splash!
I don't want to.
Don't try to make someone do
something you won't do yourself!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
No means no.
Well, I say that I don't want to do it, either!
Th-This is...
Kakyoin!
It's the water!
It had already left the canteen,
along with the blood!
It's not that the Stand was
inside the canteen...
The water is the Stand!
It got Kakyoin!
I-It got Kakyoin's eyes!
Polnareff! Stop panicking!
Bring out Chariot and defend yourself!
Crap. It's going to get Polnareff, too.
What's going on?
It attacked the pilot's corpse!
No, not the corpse. The watch.
It attacked the watch's alarm.
Sound! It attacks by locating sounds!
Sounds?
Shit! Polnareff!
It's coming for you this time!
Run to the vehicle!
I-It's so fast!
Hurry, Polnareff!
It cut me!
Hermit Purple!
It soaked into the ground...
The enemy can detect sound
through vibrations in the ground.
It can move freely around underground,
without being seen, and before we know it,
it can attack us from behind,
or through the bottoms of our feet.
And its user is able to remain far away.
They all got onto their vehicle.
He must have realized that I,
N'doul, was finding them with sound.
Too bad figuring that out
won't do them any good...
H-How's Kakyoin?
It's not good.
He may have been blinded.
Let's drive.
We have to get him to a doctor immediately.
But if we move, it'll attack.
We can't be careless.
What?!
These footsteps... It's the dog.
That dog...
It left the car before my attack.
It anticipated my Stand's attack.
It seems that dog is going
to be a problem after all.
The tires are in the water! Shit!
It's no use. We're being pulled in!
We're going to slip!
Move further back!
Helper! Come on, damn it! Help, already! Hey!
That accursed dog...
It must also know that I'm
only four kilometers to the west.
What should I do...
I'll have to take care of the dog first!
How careless can you be?!
You stupid dog!
No, I'll leave the dog alone.
It doesn't appear that Joestar
and the others can control that dog.
If it's just going to sleep, it's harmless.
Now, without hesitation...
It's so sharp!
It cut the front tires in half!
Go even further back!
S-So that's what it's trying to do...
Shit! Everyone hang on!
Rumble
Next Episode Preview
I can hear it! I can hear it!
Don't make a sound.
He can smell where the
enemy's going to attack next.
The water started chasing Jotaro!
If we can just find their body,
there's a good chance we
can defeat that fearsome Stand!
It's Iggy.
Episode 26
Iggy the Fool
and Geb's N'doul,
Part 2