All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
So my The World's power and
precision are both superior!
I've seen enough. I'm satisfied.
I will end you now!
I have decided that
I will show no mercy when
fighting one of the Joestar bloodline,
but will kill them instantly!
The way to end you is with
The World's true power!
The World! Stop time!
The World!
Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless! Useless!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 47  DIO's World, Part 3
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
With this, the Joestar bloodline will finally end.
My archenemies, who dared to
make an appearance in my destiny...
Farewell!
Wha—
What?
He just moved!
He... Impossible!
His finger just moved!
I-It can't be.
It can't be!
They're... the same?
So it's the same type of Stand as Star Platinum.
The World and Star Platinum
are the same type of Stand?!
Can he see me?
Or is he moving his hand subconsciously?
Time's up.
Bam
Could you see me?
I asked if you could see me, Jotaro!
Who knows?
I don't know what you're talking about, DIO.
Very well! It doesn't matter!
It doesn't matter if you can see me
during stopped time or not!
If you can move the same way as my The World,
let me see you moving!
Yes, it was six months ago
when I first stopped time.
In order to test out my
Stand's power and speed,
I had one of my servants
fire a shotgun at me.
As I went to catch the pellets...
For a moment,
it looked like everything had stopped.
That's when it all began.
At first, I thought it was an illusion.
Trained boxers and those who are in accidents
feel each moment as if it were
several seconds or minutes...
I thought it was something like that.
But The World was able to step
around the pellets that hung
suspended in stopped time.
And...
It could grab the pellets!
It's not an illusion!
Lord DIO!
You will surely be able to control time!
You must believe with more conviction
that you can move within stopped time!
It must be like breathing.
Like being able to snap an HB
pencil in half with your fingers!
You must believe it's a perfectly
natural thing for you to do.
What's most important is
to recognize it as such.
You must believe that
it's natural for you to do it!
You are the emperor of this world!
It's only natural for you to control time!
Clang
And then one day, I felt the wheels of time
truly enmesh themselves with The World.
It was like a beam of light
piercing the darkness.
It truly was a magnificent feeling.
I, DIO, had truly surpassed
all forms of life and all Stands!
And now, I can stop time for five seconds,
and longer and longer intervals each time!
Jotaro! I shall see just
how powerful you truly are!
The World! Stop time!
You had placed that magnet on me.
When we were testing each
other's strength earlier?
It looks like a magnet taken
from a wallet or pocket planner.
You completely fooled me.
I can't take my eyes off you for a second.
But!
If you're using a trick like this,
that proves you can't move during stopped time!
You only added a few more seconds to your life!
This time, you will...
Die, Jotaro!
Zwoosh
Bagoom
What?!
H-He... really can move!
Only for a moment, but he can move!
The magnet wasn't to trick me
into thinking he could move...
But to trick me into thinking he couldn't,
and lure me closer!
You must believe it's only natural
that you can stop time!
Of all things, this descendant of the Joestars
has invaded my world of stopped time...
I could move for a moment... Just a moment.
But...
Good grief.
It was only enough to get one punch in.
You. Woman.
Fetch my leg from over there.
Hurry up and fetch it!
Behave like a flight attendant,
bringing a drink
and caviar to a first-class passenger!
I guess I have to bash your head to pieces,
or it'll be like nothing ever happened.
You've already recovered your energy.
Because that hole I put in
your gut is closed up now.
Your eyes followed me in
the world of stopped time...
So you truly can see my movements, Jotaro.
Seems so.
Kakyoin did quite well for you.
Because he figured out the
secret of The World's powers,
you were able to figure out that you
could move during stopped time,
and so, you were able to invade my world.
Which makes me think...
Just how long can you move
within my world of stopped time?
Two seconds? Three?
Or perhaps you can move five seconds,
just like me, and you're just
pretending that you can't? And so on.
Well? How about it?
This isn't good.
I could move longer with some practice,
but right now, a moment is the best I can do.
I believe that you can only
move for a moment now.
But since you have invaded
my world of stopped time,
it would not be wise to
underestimate you by getting close.
Even when I still have an
overwhelming advantage.
Therefore, Jotaro, I've decided how to kill you
such that it doesn't matter
how long you can move!
You've gone pale.
When you saw these knives,
you realized that you face a more
horrific fate than that geezer Joseph.
Bastard!
How the hell does he come
up with stuff like this?
He's dangerous.
You cannot escape!
The World!
Five more seconds!
Once time begins to move again,
I wonder if even your Star Platinum
can manage to deflect so many knives.
Four more seconds!
Being able to see this must be
all the more terrifying, Jotaro!
Three more seconds...
Just two more seconds...
Is that all you can do?
This proves that you really can
move only for a moment.
One more second...
Zero.
It's over.
I'll add one more, just to be sure.
To be frank, I'm relieved that
I could defeat you so quickly, Jotaro.
I never thought you would be
able to enter my stopped time.
As I see it, those machines known as
automobiles are useful devices,
but because everyone has one,
the streets become too crowded.
Only I, DIO, should have
power over stopped time.
Good grief.
Throwing all those knives...
Now my valuable uniform is full of holes.
I stuffed my clothes with magazines
just in case he tried throwing anything...
But I didn't think he'd throw
that many knives at me.
Playing dead and waiting
for a chance to strike is the
best chance I have right now.
I need to figure out how
to knock off his head...
Otherwise, he won't die.
I'd better play it safe.
The Joestar bloodline has
proven itself rather lucky.
He might be trying to
trick me by playing dead.
I must end him beyond
a shadow of a doubt!
By...
chopping his head off with this!
This is truly the end for you,
Jotaro!
Die, DIO!
The World
Die!
Polnareff!
The World! Time has stopped...
So it's you, Polnareff?
And time will move once more.
Too bad, Polnareff.
With just a moment more,
and with just a tiny bit more force,
you could have torn my brain
apart with your rapier.
B-Bastard! This is impossible...
You cannot assassinate DIO.
Joestar's Egyptian tour group
will be no more, once I finish you.
Damn it. Polnareff's going to get killed.
I wanted to play dead as long as possible,
until I could land a blow to his head, but...
It would be easy for me to keep
Polnareff's head on his shoulders.
But DIO won't enter
Star Platinum's attack range.
It'll end up like it did last time.
I have to make sure he
doesn't realize I'm alive.
As long as he doesn't know for sure,
my chance to get close to him will come.
Talk about irony.
I tried my hardest to move
inside his stopped time,
but now I have to try my hardest
to stay completely still.
Farewell, Polnareff!
Jotaro, you...
You're alive... or you're coming around.
Dont move! We're the police!
We have guns pointed at you!
Put your hands up slowly.
All right. Perfect timing.
There's something I'd like
you to shoot with that gun.
Shoot the man lying on the ground over there.
You can shoot his leg, his torso...
Whatever you like.
Come on. Be sure not to miss.
Perhaps I was just imagining
that sound I thought
I heard coming from Jotaro.
What a sick thing to do...
But now DIO's attention
is on me, not Polnareff.
Right now, he's suspicious as all hell.
He'll try to make absolutely
sure that I'm dead.
This is when things get really dangerous.
The sound of his breathing...
I don't hear it. He's not breathing.
Then what about his heartbeat?
This is damn tough...
If I black out, I really will die.
It won't even be funny...
If I die because I used my
Stand to stop my own heart...
His heart isn't beating. He is definitely dead.
I thought he was still alive,
but it was just my imagination.
Just in case, I'll lop off his head
so that I can truly rest at ease.
All right, Jotaro?
Rumble
What?!
Stop time!
The World!
I went through hell there...
But even if you stop time,
I'm still going to blow your head off, DIO.
Wh-What? It can't be...
Finally...
Finally, I was able to bash his head in.
But that bastard DIO is a monster
Menacing
who survived a hundred years
at the bottom of the ocean.
I can't believe he's dead yet.
It's too soon to relax.
I'll kill you...
Wh-What is this? Impossible! M-My legs...
I can't move my legs.
I can't stand!
I have a headache... a-and nausea...
How could this happen? Me, DIO, feeling sick?
My head's been destroyed, so I can't get up?!
Damn it! I have to do something!
I covered you with gasoline
so I can track your smell.
I feel bad, kicking a guy
when he's down, but...
Nah. I don't feel bad about this at all.
My friends and a lot of innocent bystanders
are dead because of you.
The World!
If I can...
If I can get to that place...
Time... Time will move once more.
He put his ear to the ground
to listen for cars coming near.
But...
I can't let him get away!
Screech
That place... That place!
If I can just get there...
This place is taken. You can't escape.
Give up, DIO.
The World! Sto—
You fell for it, Jotaro!
This is my escape route!
You have lost in the battle
of wits against me, DIO!
Doesn't this street look familiar?
This street... I-It can't be...
That's right.
It was my escape route to take
the blood of Joseph Joestar!
DIO, you bastard!
Next Episode Preview
Jotaro...
This trip was truly fun, wasn't it?
Joestar blood suits me so well!
This is the greatest high!
There's one simple answer.
Episode 48
Long Travels, Goodbye My Friend
You're going to...