All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
He's got such a strong face,
and yet he died in an instant.
Well, the end of someone's life is
usually a pretty sudden curtain call.
It's probably normal to die without
being able to say goodbye.
It may seem like I'm talking as
though I know everything, but...
Polnareff! Please, don't let him get to you!
Do you still not understand?
Mr. Avdol told you not to fight by yourself!
And you ignored that...
You wanted to get revenge,
even if it meant dying with your enemy.
Mr. Avdol followed you because that
worried him, and this is what happened!
So what am I supposed to do?
We need to fall back for now.
Avdol was cruelly stabbed in the back.
My sister was killed without resistance.
You want me to hold these
regrets inside and run away?!
Don't fight them when we don't
even know how their Stands work yet!
Don't fight a battle that will kill you!
That's what Mr. Avdol was trying to tell you.
Hey! Come on, li'l Pol Pol.
Why, you...
Polnareff! Slowly come back towards me.
We're going to use that
truck to get out of here.
Y-You're telling me to hold it in?
A-All ri—
Hey, Polnareff.
Bam
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 11:
The Emperor and The Hanged Man, Part 2
Avdol died for you.
I think that means you owe him.
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
He might not have died, if not for you.
Y-You bastard.
Where's your real body?!
Polnareff, calm down!
But there's no need to be sad.
Actually, you should be happy...
Since you'll be together again soon.
You'll die, and then you can be with
those two fools in the next world.
Your little sister was really cute, Polnareff...
Once you're reunited with your
sister, you should ask her
about exactly how I killed her!
Polnareff, don't let him provoke you!
He wants you to attack!
Bastard!
Your Chariot cannot cut my Hanged Man.
I am within a mirror.
Your Stand can't enter a mirror. That's why!
You mad?
I bet you're mad.
Hey, Hol Horse. Fire away.
Let's put an end to this idiot.
Aye aye, sir.
Die!
Emerald Splash!
What?!
What? He shot...
...Polnareff!
Kakyoin, was it? Not bad.
That's out of my Stand's range.
Even if I hit him from here,
the bullet wouldn't hit with much force.
Mr. Centerfold went after them, eh?
He must really want to finish off Polnareff.
S-Sorry, Kakyoin.
I-I...
I thought I didn't care if I died,
so long as I could avenge my sister.
But I understand now...
I understand how Avdol felt.
I won't let his feelings go to waste.
I'll fight to keep living.
Do you really understand?
Yeah.
Crack
Take this instead of a handshake as
proof that we've made up, Polnareff.
Right. Th-Thank you, Kakyoin.
When they come after us again,
we'll defeat them together.
Avdol, you...
At that moment, I'm sure that
I stabbed him with the sword.
But my strike didn't land.
There was no resistance.
Even after breaking the mirror,
his Stand, Hanged Man,
still attacked from the shards.
He'll attack my reflection
from within the mirror.
My Stand can't go inside a mirror...
How am I supposed to attack him
if he's in some kind of mirror world?
Damn it!
Polnareff, you keep talking about
"inside the mirror" and "the mirror world,"
but there is no world inside a mirror.
This isn't some fantasy or fairy tale.
What are you talking about?
You saw it, too, didn't you?!
You can only see him in a mirror,
and when you turn around, he's not there.
Yes.
But what you see in a mirror
is just a reflection created by light.
You don't have to tell me that!
Listen! I'm talking about
what's going on right now.
If there are such things as Stands,
there could be a mirror world, too!
There isn't.
Look, you...
I think that fact is what will let us
solve the mystery of Hanged Man.
If Stands can defeat other Stands,
then there's still something
we don't know about his—
Polnareff! He's inside the
plating on the steering wheel!
What?!
He's caught up to us!
Look out!
A-Are you okay, Kakyoin?
I-I hit my chest, but I'm fine.
What?
Chariot!
Slice
Kakyoin! Get away from
anything that's reflective!
Damn it... I got it. I just saw it.
He's going from mirror to mirror!
He moves by jumping from one
reflective surface to another!
He traveled all this way
by reflecting over and over!
Reflecting?
That means he's actually light!
The true nature of his Stand is light?
Kakyoin! He was just in the car's bumper!
He's going to reflect off of the
car's bumper and into something else.
Don't go near anything that's reflective.
And take anything off
your body that reflects!
Take off the buttons on your uniform!
Mister, are you guys okay?
Want me to bring some medicine or something?
Hey! Kid! It's dangerous, so get out of here!
Hey, your car's totally messed up...
Hey, you're bleeding.
What?!
Are you okay?
Th-That asshole!
He's in the kid's eye!
Hey, kid. Don't look at us.
Huh?
I told you not to look at us!
Stop following me with your eyes! Damn it!
Huh? But you're hurt.
I'm fine! See? Perfectly fine!
So go look over there!
But you're bleeding...
Look over there, you brat!
Damn you, Centerfold!
What are you going to do?
You wouldn't stab this cute little kid's eye out
with that sword of yours,
would you, Polnareff?
Polnareff!
I finally got you.
You can't run anymore.
Not unless you stab the kid's eye out.
What a coward! This is unforgivable!
Hey, Kakyoin.
You don't say things like
that in this kind of situation.
Listen! In situations like this,
you've got to say something more
like this before you get your revenge.
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff.
For my sister's honor, and so that
my friend Avdol can rest in peace...
I'm going to hurl you
into the depths of despair, Centerfold!
Forgive me, kid! I'll buy you a caramel later!
There's sand in my eye!
Slice
Bam
P-Polnareff, he's in your eye...
I don't really understand the principle,
but he essentially moves at the speed of light.
A speed that you wouldn't
normally be able to see.
But I knew that if the kid closed his eyes,
the next place he'd move
to would be my own eye.
I see...
Hanged Man can only exist
within the world of reflections.
When one world is about to be destroyed,
he has to move to something
else that's reflective.
So...
As long as I can read his trajectory,
he'll be easy to cut with a sword.
His real body is over there!
You bastard. Finally...
Finally!
We finally meet...
Centerfold!
My name is Jean Pierre Polnareff,
and I've seen through your Stand's secret.
It's a Stand of light that
moves at incredible speed.
There's no way I can catch it.
But if I know where it's going to go,
and I slash its trajectory in that moment,
I can slash you, too!
If Kakyoin and Avdol hadn't shown up,
I probably wouldn't have figured that
out and you would have killed me.
Polnareff! He's not the
man with two right hands!
That's not Centerfold!
Wh-What?!
Polnareff!
Emperor
Hol Horse
Polnareff!
Over here.
Bam
You fool!
I'm Centerfold.
You...
He's just a drifter that
happened to be in town.
I just used a knife to give him
the same wound I have.
You totally fell for it!
Coming close to him
without knowing what I
looked like was a big mistake!
You bastard!
Take this! My Emerald—
Hey, hold on a sec.
Take a good look around you.
Hey, gather 'round!
These guys say they'll give you money!
What?!
They'll give us money for nothing!
Thank you!
You have such big hearts!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
Please give us money!
Have you figured out what's going on?
You say you've seen through my Stand?
You fool.
I've known about my Stand's
weakness for quite some time.
If there are lots of reflective surfaces
so you can't find its trajectory,
it has no weakness!
Don't look! Don't stare!
Don't stare at us!
You can't run anymore.
What are you going to do? Blow everyone up?
You sacrificed your youth to hunt me down...
And you're going to fail before you finish?!
Talk about a lonely, boring life.
Meanwhile I, Centerfold,
will continue to have cute girls
like your sister all around me,
and live a fun, happy life!
Come to think of it, your sister
was really good at sobbing...
You can die now.
Wh-Why, you...
Polnareff, that's not what you say here.
When taking revenge,
you shouldn't say, "Why, you..."
You say this.
My name is Noriaki Kakyoin.
To avenge my friend, Avdol,
and so that the soul of my friend
Polnareff's sister may rest in peace,
I will have you pay with your life.
I'll give this gold coin to whoever picks it up.
It's so shiny, you can see your face in it!
Now I see, Kakyoin.
Looks like all of their eyes
are focused on one point now.
Yeah.
We know the trajectory that
Hanged Man will have to take!
Merci, Kakyoin!
The moment!
Rip
Hold it!
It won't open!
Looks like you're the one who's
really good at sobbing, Centerfold!
Well, you're about to fall to Hell,
sobbing the whole way down.
But there's one thing I can't rely on
the guardians of Hell to do for me.
And that's...
To turn you into a pincushion!
I've been waiting years for this moment!
I'll leave the rest to King Yama.
So this is the true Hanged Man...
He was rotten to the core.
I got my revenge.
Hanged Man
Centerfold
Hold it!
I finally caught up with you guys.
Why are you walking so slow?
If you're gonna run,
run like your lives depend on it.
Right, Mr. Centerfold?
Better say your prayers. Your lives end here!
So act like this is the end and come at us!
Show us what you've got, damn it!
Right, Mr. Centerfold?
Hey, are you listening, Mr. Centerfold?!
I don't think he's listening anymore.
He's rather busy right now...
Since he's being sentenced in Hell!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Don't try to pull that nonsense!
Bluffing won't work on me!
There's no way you can beat him!
Even I don't stand a chance
against the invincible Hanged Man!
Polnareff, your jokes suck.
That piece of shit's body is about
two or three thousand meters that way.
Want to take a look?
Okay, I will!
Hey! You're running away?!
I-I don't stand a chance!
I'm at a total disadvantage by myself!
I'll run for now and wait
for the next opportunity!
I'm the type whose power only shows
when I'm paired with someone else.
Being #2 is better than #1!
That's Hol Horse's philosophy of life!
Got a problem with it?!
What?!
Mr. Joestar! Jotaro!
We already know about Avdol.
Though it was a simple funeral,
his body's been buried.
The one who stabbed Mr. Avdol in the
back was the man with two right hands,
but the cause of death was Hol Horse's bullet.
What shall we do with him?
I'll give him his sentence.
Death!
Wha?!
Please run, Sir Hol Horse!
Sir Hol Horse!
What's with this woman?!
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm always thinking of you!
That is my reason to live!
Please run! Hurry!
You bitch! Let go of me!
What are you thinking?!
Jotaro! Kakyoin! Don't let Hol Horse get away!
Too late.
Huh? Oh...
Well said, baby!
I'll gladly accept your
feelings and keep on living!
I'm running away because I love you, baby!
Forever!
Why, you...
Come back here!
Ah...
Don't "ah" me, you bitch!
Polnareff, that woman was
just another one he was using.
And he no longer had any intention of fighting.
We have no time to deal with him.
Avdol is gone.
But we have to hurry ahead.
It's already been fifteen
days since we left Japan.
Damn it...
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
All right! Let's resume our trip to Egypt.
Listen up! In order to defeat DIO,
our hearts have to be as one.
We can't go off on our own!
That's when he'll come after us.
Got it?
Let's get a move on!
Good grief.
Next Episode Preview
The city of Varanasi is coming into view.
Murderer!
I am the culprit!
I am Joseph Joestar! An American!
What?!
I love you.
Hey... doesn't that sort of
look like a person's face?
Episode 12
The Empress