All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
I'm sure it's quite the shock,
dying because your sister ate you.
When a man wishes from the heart,
all of his greatest weaknesses come to light.
You didn't even think about how unnatural
it is to bring someone back to life.
You want to believe that the one you loved
is still alive somewhere on this Earth.
You hope that they'll suddenly pop
in tomorrow and say, "Good morning."
By the way...
You said something about a third wish,
but you've already made
your third wish, haven't you?
You don't mean...
"Bring Avdol back to life."
Hail 2 U!
Zam!
No... He's...
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Avdol!
Episode 22: Judgment, Part 2
Av... dol...
My fingers... fell apart.
Polnareff!
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
This is your fault...
Because of you, I... I...
Ended up like this...
Avdol... I... I made you...
I...
I'll have you pay for this, Polnareff.
With...
your body!
I'll get better if I eat, right?
Right?
Brother!
What's the matter, Brother?
S-Stay away! Stay away from me!
Both of you... Return to the ground, please!
Why? You're the one who brought us back.
It's your turn to enter the ground!
I-I was so freaked out that
I forgot to summon Chariot.
I was so caught up in my wish
that I forgot to use my Stand...
Get away from me, please!
Get away from me!
What?!
"Please"? Nope! You don't have any wishes left.
I've already granted your three wishes.
You don't get any more.
Stop!
Hail 2 U!
Make sure you cry and scream
all you can before you die.
You're in this island's backwoods.
Your voice won't reach the shore.
No one will come to save you.
I-It's no use. I'm done for...
I'm going to die. I'm beaten.
Sherry...
Avdol...
Even though they're just clay dolls,
it's not so bad being defeated by them.
Avdol, just like you said, you died because of me.
I have no complaints about
whatever happens to me.
What...?
Are my eyes so blurry that I'm seeing double?
It looks like there are two Avdols.
Of course there's only one clay doll.
If I'm seeing things, I guess that
means death is really close now.
Not to mention how much I'm bleeding...
It makes sense that I'd hallucinate.
Then... I guess I'll die.
I'll have to tap out early.
Goodbye, Mr. Joestar, Kakyoin, Jotaro...
I pray for your victory.
Avdol, for you...
I'll atone in the next world...
What?! Impossible!
I knew it! There is another Avdol!
My eyes weren't playing tricks!
Besides the clay doll Avdol...
There's another Avdol!
Magician's Red!
Impossible! He should have been dead!
He was stabbed by the Hanged Man, Centerfold!
He should be dead...
Tsk, tsk.
Mohammed Avdol!
Yes, I am!
Bam
I-Is it really you?
Tsk, tsk.
Rumble
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
I-Is it the real you?
Polnareff, you haven't matured a bit.
You're still going on
about your sister without
thinking of the consequences.
Impossible!
There's no way you can be alive!
I was told that after you were stabbed in the back,
Hol Horse blew your brains out,
and you died on the spot.
Indeed, I was shot. Right in the forehead...
But because I was stabbed
in the back, for a moment,
my face was looking up.
Meaning, the bullet grazed me.
I guess this is what you call a blessing in disguise.
Hol Horse's bullet only scratched my skin and skull,
so it never reached my brain,
and wasn't a mortal wound.
But I did completely lose consciousness.
Cameo of the Judgment card, was it?
I'll give you Hell!
Hell 2 U!
The third wish... Just the third wish...
It's real.
It came true.
Judgment
Cameo
Mohammed Avdol is alive.
This bad news...
Shouldn't you hurry and tell DIO and your
other Stand user buddies about it?
Shouldn't you, Cameo?
That's right! I have to tell them!
I have to let them know!
Mr. Joestar, Kakyoin, and Jotaro!
This is, indeed, very surprising news.
But I can turn that news into this:
Judgement's Cameo not only
killed the idiot Polnareff,
but also killed Avdol,
who was actually still alive!
Oh! I shall change it into good news!
Magician's Red!
Whoa, there.
Avdol!
This Stand is rather powerful...
Be careful! It's not just power.
He's got speed, too.
Avdol, is that all you've got?
It looks like I'll be able to
share my good news after all.
May fortune...
be with you both!
What?!
Hail 2 U!
Brother...
No. My Sherry...
Sherry... died.
You're...
just...
a clay doll!
Brother...
Polnareff.
My apologies. I take back my
statement that you hadn't matured.
No, you were right.
I should be the one to apologize.
This battle has been decided.
Avdol! Tell me your three wishes!
I shall grant them for you.
Before you die for real this time!
Go ahead! Give it a shot.
You get three wishes.
Bastard! He's making fools of us!
Avdol, ignore him.
You don't have to make any wishes.
Avdol, are you listening to me?
No...
Make it four.
Wha?!
What?
Wishes. I mean wishes!
I wish to make the three wishes into four.
Tsk, tsk.
You can't be serious...
Are you denying my wish?
Cameo, you're the one that offered!
I will have you keep your promise!
You still insist upon this futile contest of power?
Such a weak kick.
What?!
Yes! Awesome!
Tsk, tsk. My first wish was
to make you scream in pain.
It came true.
I-Impossible! You're strong!
You're much stronger than earlier!
The wound left after I was stabbed by the
Hanged Man hasn't completely healed yet.
I was guarding that wound earlier,
so I couldn't use all of my strength.
Wha—
I was finally able to stand again
just three days ago in India.
I was able to take a plane here,
so the trip was very easy.
Nothing less from you, Avdol!
Now, my second wish...
To make you scream in fear!
And my third wish...
To make you cry in regret!
Th-That bastard! He's running away!
Wait, damn you!
Shh. Be quiet, Polnareff.
With that kind of power and speed...
It is the rule of Stands that the
user must be somewhere nearby.
Is he here?
He should be hiding very close by.
Could that be—
Shh!
The user is hiding beneath the ground?!
Damn him! What should I do with him?
He had the nerve to use my sister,
so I'll show him Hell!
Hell 2 U!
Bastard!
Grind
I'm gonna drop all sorts of things in there...
Like dirt, sand...
A spider...
And ants...
And a match.
Bastard! I'm not done yet! Not yet! Not yet!
Hey, Polnareff.
I do believe nature is calling.
Shall we engage in the
timeless ritual of male bonding,
and take a piss together?
Tsk, tsk.
Huh?
I somehow made it.
C'mon! Laugh, Polnareff!
Laugh! Laugh, Polnareff!
Avdol... Did your personality change?
You weren't a guy who thought up
perverse stuff like this before.
It's not because you were shot in the head, is it?
Come now, aim for it!
Right!
Please forgive me!
My fourth wish. That is...
To not listen to your wishes.
Magician's Red won't forgive you.
Not happening.
Bam
Ba-dum-tss!
Magician's Red
Mohammed Avdol
Hey! You'll never believe this, guys!
Who do you think I met?
Polnareff! We were worried about you!
Where did you get those wounds?
Were you attacked?
Who cares about my wounds?
Listen! Don't be shocked, Jotaro!
Don't let your back go out in shock, Kakyoin.
Who do you think I met, Mr. Joestar?
Behold and rejoice!
Tum-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That bastard Avdol was alive!
Doo-do-doo!
Well, let's go.
I'll help you carry your luggage.
Hey, Avdol.
It's been a while. How are you?
Avdol, is that wound on your back all right?
It's fine. A bit stiff, though.
Hey...
Has it really been two weeks?
Thank goodness we're all still okay.
Hey...
Jotaro, you still wear all that stuff?
Don't you get hot?
W-Wait a minute, you guys!
Hey! I said wait, you assholes!
Hey, what's the deal with that attitude?!
A guy who was dead came back to life!
What the hell?! Why are you
having normal conversations?!
Oh, Polnareff, I'm sorry.
When I said I buried Avdol in India...
That was a lie.
Casual
Wh— Wh— What?!
It was Mr. Joestar and Jotaro who tended
the wounds on my head and back in India.
Y-You assholes knew that Avdol was still
alive in India, and you didn't tell me?!
You, too, Kakyoin?!
I only found out the day after.
But we couldn't let the enemy know.
And since you have such a big mouth...
Pardon. Since you can't lie,
I suggested that we keep it a secret from you.
If you'd let the secret slip,
Avdol couldn't have recovered in peace.
We were planning to tell you
as soon as we knew he was safe,
but we had no idea you'd run into him first.
Oh, yeah, Avdol!
Your dad is on this island!
Let's let him know you're here!
Oh, that was me in disguise.
Wh-What?!
Th-Then you guys... That was all...
Go away!
No one comes to see me with good news!
I don't want to hear it!
Avdol's death was not your fault.
Did you have to go that far?!
How dare you guys leave me out like that?!
Hey, now. There's no reason to cry.
I'm sorry. I didn't think you'd be this hurt.
I'm sorry, Polnareff.
There's a reason I came to this island in disguise.
A reason?
It was partially so the enemy wouldn't find out,
but I also had Avdol do a little shopping for me.
A little shopping?
It was a very conspicuous purchase.
So I disguised myself as a
rich Arab when I bought it.
Now, everyone, we're gonna ride that and leave!
Polnareff, cheer up already. Come on.
It's almost here!
Wait, what's almost here?
There's nothing—
What?!
A submarine?!
That's right. From here, we'll ride to Egypt in this!
Y-You're kidding! You really
bought something like this?!
Next Episode Preview
How about this glistening design?
A submarine, huh...
Perhaps a refreshing white would be best.
Hurry up and make some coffee.
I just don't know which one to pick.
Kakyoin, why are you taking that cup?
Hello? Oh, is that you, Joseph?
Episode 23
The High Priestess, Part 1