All rights for this production are reserved to the copyright holder, and distribution
is permitted only to its intended audience. Unauthorized reproduction, screening,
display, or modification of this program's content is strictly prohibited
by law, and violation is grounds for criminal and civil prosecution.
Previously on Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
A Stand has manifested
from Ms. Holly, as well!
You will not reach Lord DIO!
But if we fail to meet DIO within fifty days...
Someone I know has this
exact mark on their neck...
What?!
Kaboom
I've decided to go to Egypt with all of you!
If I go after DIO,
I'll be able to find the
one who took my sister's life!
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Stardust Crusaders
Episode 6: Dark Blue Moon
The loathsome curse of DIO...
Even the Speedwagon Foundation's doctors,
who have the latest medical technologies,
This story is fiction. The characters, groups, places, laws, and names
used in this program have no connection to any existing in real life.
stand powerless before DIO's curse.
Egypt
In order to save Holly, Jojo and
crew head toward faraway Egypt.
Japan
Hong Kong
Hanoi
In order to avoid danger,
Bangkok
Ho Chi Minh
they travel by sea rather than air,
heading first to Singapore.
Singapore
To get from Hong Kong to Singapore,
we'll be on the water for three full days.
Well, let's relax and keep our spirits up.
But seriously, guys...
Can't you do something
about those school uniforms?
You're going to continue
our journey wearing those?
Isn't it ridiculously hot?
Well, we are students...
And students should behave as students.
But I suppose that sounds like a stretch...
Hmph.
Hmph! Japanese students are such stiffs.
I see... so this is Bushido.
Once you clear your mind,
even fire seems cool.
But you know, girls won't fall for stiffs like you.
Let go! Let go of me! You big lug!
Shut up!
Damn it, let me go! Let me go!
What a little brat.
Hey, what's going on?
I thought we agreed there'd
be no passengers on our boat.
Let go!
I'm sorry. It's a stowaway.
This brat was hiding in storage down below.
A stowaway?
Come at me if you're gonna!
I'll kick your balls in!
I'll turn you in to the naval police.
What? The police?!
P-Please. Let me go!
I just want to go see my dad in Singapore.
I'll do anything!
You can work me as hard as you want!
Let's see. What should I do?
Should I let you go?
What should I do?
P-Please!
Ow!
I'm not gonna let you go after all. Hell no.
First, I'm gonna go let the
Captain know, so come wit—
Whoa! He jumped in! Talk about energetic.
Is he planning to swim to shore from here?
What should we do?
Just leave 'im.
I'm sure he dove in because
he's a confident swimmer.
Th-This isn't good!
Sharks gather around these parts!
This isn't good!
Hey, you brat! Come back!
Get back here! It's dangerous!
There are sharks!
Those waters are shark-infested!
Huh?
Crack!
Good grief, you little brat.
You're...
A girl?
And a little runt of one, at that.
H-How dare you grab my chest like that?!
Damn it!
Good grief.
J-Jotaro! Below you!
Something's attacking from underwater!
It's not a shark! It's really fast!
Jotaro! Hurry!
Hurry and swim to the boat!
I-It's too far.
If it's at that distance, leave it to me.
Hierophant Green!
I-It disappeared! It's a Stand!
That thing is a Stand!
A seafaring Stand...
I don't believe I've ever
even heard of such a thing.
This girl... Sh-She couldn't be...
Could she be that Stand's user?
Could she have led Jojo into the
shark-infested ocean on purpose?
Wh-What's with you jerks,
all glaring at me like that?!
I don't know what's going on,
but do you want a fight?!
Don't underestimate me! I'll take you on!
One-on-one!
Face me, one-on-one!
You little shits!
She can't be serious.
Maybe we should toss
her back into the ocean.
Don't be rash.
If she was really an ordinary stowaway,
she'd have been eaten by sharks.
I've already checked the
ten people on this boat.
I don't know who it could be,
other than this girl.
Isn't there a way we can
find out who she really is?
Hey, how's DIO doing?
DIO? What the hell is that?
Don't act like you don't know,
you little brat!
You damn punks!
Do you want to talk to me,
or do you want to get stabbed?
Which is it?!
This demon's blade is telling me that it wants
the blood of its 340th victim already.
What's so funny, you stupid grunt?!
Grunt?
You know, I really don't think it's her.
Yes, but...
So is this girl our stowaway?
Captain.
I'm pretty harsh when it comes to stowaways.
O-Ow... Ow...
You may be a girl,
but if I go easy on you,
we'll just get more and more stowaways.
We're gonna hold you in
one of the rooms below
deck until we get to port.
Captain, I'd like to ask you something.
You've verified the identities of
all ten of the men on board, right?
Of course.
All of them are veterans
who have been on this boat
for over ten years.
I'm not sure why you're so worried about that.
By the way...
I request that you refrain
from smoking aboard this ship.
What did you plan to do with the
ashes and butt after you're done?
Were you planning on throwing
it into the beautiful ocean?
You're a guest on this ship,
but I'll have you follow her rules,
Mr. Outlaw.
Got it?
Hold it.
If you're going to put it out, just put it out.
Don't be a condescending
prick about it, you jackass.
Hey, Jotaro! Don't be rude to the captain!
You're the one at fault.
I'm very aware that I'm being rude.
He isn't the captain... I just figured it out.
He's the Stand user!
Wh...
What?!
Sta... nd?
What might that be...?
That's inconceivable, Jotaro.
Captain Dragon came recommended with
verification by the Speedwagon Foundation.
He's someone we should trust.
There is a 0% chance that he's a Stand user.
Hold on, a Stand? I have no
idea what you're talking about...
Jojo, random guesses will only
make things more confusing!
Do you have any proof, Jojo?
I've found a way to differentiate
Stand users from other people.
What?!
That is...
If a Stand user inhales even a
little bit of cigarette smoke,
a vein pops up on the tip of their nose.
What the hell are they all doing?
You can't be serious, Jotaro!
Yeah, I'm lying.
But it looks like we've found the idiot.
Menacing
Jotaro, how did you know he was suspicious?
Actually, I didn't think he was at all.
Huh?
But I planned to try this
with all of the men on board.
You're cold. Damn, but you're cold.
You're right. I'm not the captain.
The real captain is already sleeping with the
fishes at the ocean's bottom back in Hong Kong.
Then you can sleep at the bottom of Hell!
Grab
Damn it!
Splash
I-I can't move...
Trouble on the water!
Lies and betrayal!
The Moon card, which suggests
fear of the unknown.
Its name: Dark Blue Moon!
If I tried to take five of you at once,
even I'd break a bone or two,
so I was going to hide my identity
and take care of you one by one...
But if you've figured me out,
I guess I have no choice.
I'll have to take on all five of you!
Getting my hands on this girl is a sign
that my luck is changing for the better!
I'm going to jump into these
shark-infested waters with her.
Of course, you guys will end up following us in.
If we fight in the water,
where I have the advantage,
I can beat all five of you.
Don't underestimate me by taking a hostage!
Don't think that I, Jotaro Kujo,
will be shaken by this!
Underestimate? No, this is a prediction!
I hear that your Stand,
Star Platinum, is pretty damn fast.
I'm not trying to brag,
but my Dark Blue Moon
is pretty fast in the water.
It can swim more elegantly
than any fish in the sea!
Why don't we test them out?
Follow me... if you're prepared to
choke to death on all the seawater
you're about to swallow.
Crush
H-He attacked faster than we
could fall... That's impossible...
You're the only one who's
going to choke on seawater.
Avdol, say something.
You tried to out-predict me, a fortune teller...
...but it's ten years too early for you.
Star Platinum
Jotaro Kujo
He's drifting away.
He sure talked up his Stand's powers,
but it looks like he was just an idiot.
Jotaro, what's wrong?
Hurry and lift up the girl!
What's wrong, Jotaro?!
D-Damn it... I'm being pulled in...
Th-These are...
Acorn barnacles!
The crustaceans called acorn barnacles!
They're all over Star Platinum's
arm and on the side of the boat!
He's still planning on fighting.
He attached them to me earlier,
when I hit him.
They keep multiplying!
My Stand's strength is being drained...
H-He suddenly disappeared.
The captain, he's nowhere to be found!
Jotaro! Bring in your Stand!
I can't,
which is why I'm sweating way
more than I want to right now!
Jojo!
Jotaro!
Shoom
Jojo!
C-Crap!
Th-This isn't good!
Welcome! Welcome!
So you've finally come to where
Dark Blue Moon reigns supreme,
the undersea realm.
It's a bad idea to underestimate me, boy.
Even in the ocean,
the Stands can still communicate, so go ahead.
Try to sound all cocky, like you did earlier.
Go ahead, boy!
So what do you want to be?
Tell me what kind of fish dish you want to be.
Fish cakes? Or maybe sashimi?
I'll make a meal out of your Stand.
You fool... You're trying to sound tough, boy,
but inside, this is what you're thinking:
"How long can he stay underwater?"
"I can probably last about two minutes,
but can he last longer than me?"
Let me answer you.
My lung capacity is three times
greater than a normal person's!
And I've trained them.
My best time underwater is
6 minutes and 21 seconds!
I'm sure you're getting dizzy
just hearing that number.
And!
Dark Blue Moon's fins are
underwater cutters that move
sharper than a ship's propeller!
Before you get overconfident again,
take a good, hard look at your Stand!
The acorn barnacles I attached to it will
keep absorbing your power to propagate.
I'm sure you can feel your power draining away.
Trying to run away by swimming back up?
Take a good look around you!
Haven't you realized that
Dark Blue Moon has been
creating an underwater whirlpool, boy?
Swim! Swim!
It's gonna get harder to breathe,
and your power is still draining!
But it's too early to kill a
self-absorbed little brat like you just yet!
I-It's been too long!
He's still not coming up!
A whirlpool!
There's a giant whirlpool!
Where the hell is Jojo?!
Let's go save him!
Th-These are scales!
Th-That guy's Stand has
scales as sharp as razors!
There are countless scales
swirling in that whirlpool.
He wasn't bluffing when he
said he could beat all five of us.
That whirlpool is like a watery ant lion pit!
It's very possible we could all die if we dive in.
H-His scales?
And now I'm going to guess
what you're thinking next!
"In a whirlpool, only one spot stays still."
So mundane!
"It's the center!"
"If I jump into the center
where he is, I can attack him."
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
If you think you can hit me
with that punch of yours again,
come at me.
Come at me with your worthless Stand,
its power drained by the acorn barnacles.
See if you can manage an attack
that's even sharper than these
underwater cutters, boy!
C-Curses... It's too reckless to act.
It's Jojo!
I could see Jojo in the whirlpool!
This isn't good!
He was limp!
Limp? He wasn't struggling at all?
That might be a good thing.
What?
How dare you say you were
going to turn me into sashimi?!
The one that's going to be
sliced up like sashimi is...
Star Finger!
Wha...
Slice
The one who was turned
into sashimi was you, after all.
Blub, blub, blub, blub...
What's that? I can't hear you
very well since we're underwater.
Speak up!
But your power was being drained...
You let yourself go limp on purpose
to concentrate your power in your fingers...
Th-That's what you were thinking...
Nope. What I was thinking was...
If you pissed yourself when you lost,
it'd be gross since we're in the water,
old man.
Jojo!
That's my grandson for you!
Well done, Jotaro! Hurry and come u—
Th-That captain had
planted some bombs after all!
Damn it!
Hurry up and get the emergency boats out!
We'll signal a nearby boat for help!
Dark Blue Moon
Fake Captain Dragon
Have some water.
We've sent signals for help,
so someone should be here soon.
I don't know what in the world is
going on, but who are you people?
We're hurrying along a journey, just like you.
Though you're on a journey to see your father,
while I'm on one for my daughter.
Pbbt
Hey! That's our precious water!
How dare you spit it out?!
N-No... E-E...
E-E-E-E-E...
Everyone, look!
Next Episode Preview
What is this boat?
The ramp's down, so why
hasn't anyone shown their face?
There are no signs of life.
I'm all sticky from the salt water...
So that's what this means...
You think you've won...
Episode 7:
Strength