July 15th (Thurs)  4:43 PM
It's open. Come in.
Rohan-sensei?
Where...
Over here, Koichi.
Rohan-sensei!
What's wrong? You wouldn't explain
anything over the phone...
I'd like you to help me.
I'm being attacked by an enemy Stand.
What?!
A S-Stand? Where is it? Where?!
It's on my back. It's possessed my back.
Your back?
Um... Your back is being attacked?
Yes. It's a very dangerous Stand.
I'm not sure what I should do.
Could you show it to me?
I cannot.
But if you don't show it to me...
If I show it to you, it'll kill
me and transfer over to you!
Hurry up and burn them, okay?
See? It's talking! It's this thing, Koichi!
Huh?
Why are you hiding it?!
Did you call me over here
just to mess with me?
What are you talking about?!
I already told you. If I
show you my back, I'll die!
But you're always messing with me, Sensei.
So that is what's going on.
No! I'm being serious right now!
There's a corpse upstairs!
Huh? A c-corpse?!
Um... What are you doing, Sensei?
Climb over me, and go ahead.
Please, please, go ahead. Please!
Seriously, what's with you?
Well? Do you believe me now?
It's gone!
That's impossible...
Right here, Koichi!
Look, Koichi! This is Masazo Kinoto!
He had the life sucked out
of him, and he dried up!
Wow, that's amazing. You did
a great job making that.
But this is no time to be
joking around, Sensei!
The Stand users made by the old man
in the picture are really after us.
So I rushed over here, thinking that
something might've happened to you, too!
What?
Then this thing...
Anyway, just be careful.
Bye.
W-Wait, Koichi!
I asked you to come because
I knew those shitbags
Josuke and Okuyasu wouldn't believe me!
You have to believe me!
We're friends, aren't we?!
Koichi!
Don't be down, okay?
Even though this has gotta hurt...
I, Rohan Kishibe, have never
faced such humiliation...
You bastard. You'll regret this...
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
July 15th (Thurs)  5:25 PM
Lately, my nails are growing fast again.
Episode 34    July 15th (Thurs), Part 4
Too fast.
That woman running her fingers through
her prized, well-cared-for hair...
Congratulations. You get to live longer.
I'll hold off on picking you right now.
Until I can completely blend into
Kosaku Kawajiri's lifestyle.
So, every time I leave,
my dad, like, totally follows me in
secret, or comes snooping around.
You're going out at night too much.
And whose fault is that?
I got super pissed off, so I totally stole
something in front of him on purpose.
And then I went straight to your place.
Seriously? They've probably got
the cops looking for you now.
Hey... What are you touching my bag for?
What's wrong?
Don't worry about it. It's nothing.
What are you, a pickpocket?
A groper? What a joke.
Morioh. Morioh.
Oh, crap! This is Morioh.
Come on, we're getting off.
Ow...
What the hell?
Watch where you're going
when you get off the train!
Hey, did you see that? He had
a bowling pin nail clipper.
A bowling pin nail clipper, in this
day and age... What a geek.
July 15th (Thurs)  5:07 PM
Do you have the pictures?
Hey, where are you going with the pictures?
Morioh Grand Hotel.
That's the only place I can go now.
To where Jotaro is? It doesn't
matter where you go, okay?
Just give up and burn the pictures.
Well done...
Even though you don't know who could
be watching from which window.
This is dangerous.
There, you see? Every street has an intersection.
See? There's no way you can cross.
Someone will see your back for sure.
The road's just going to get wider,
and there will be even more people.
So let's just not go! Okay?
There's no way you can cross.
You think so?
Masazo Kinoto came all the way to my house.
He must have crossed an intersection, as well.
I just have to figure out how he crossed it.
And he did it... like this!
Stick
This is ridiculously embarrassing,
but I can make it to the station this way.
Yeah, not bad, Rohan Kishibe.
But you've forgotten something.
When Masazo Kinoto was crossing,
I didn't interfere with him!
Hey, jackass! Why are you walking so slow?
The hell did you say?!
See?
Er, hey! Turn around!
What?!
You're the one forgetting
something, Cheap Trap.
Masazo Kinoto didn't have this...
He didn't have Heaven's Door!
Cannot turn around
for one minute.
What?!
All right. Now I should have no problem
walking so that no one sees my back.
You'd better be prepared, you bastard.
Wh-What?
There's no way you're going to make it.
You're the one who's going to die
with your dick all shriveled up.
Just keep running your mouth.
Your only ability is to talk.
And that's been sealed.
Wh-Wh-Who the hell do you
think you're talking to?!
July 15th (Thurs)  5:32 PM
Looks like there aren't any
big intersections for a while.
Hey, can you use your Heaven's
Door ability on animals, too?
Yeah, if the animal has any intelligence.
So that means if an animal sees your
back, I can transfer over to them, too!
Even easier than humans, huh?
True. I have to be careful of these guys, too.
I hate cats.
They glare at you.
Hey, move!
What?! It can't be...
So one of these guys just has
to glance at your back, right?
My ability is only to speak.
But, you see, humans aren't the
only ones that I can talk to.
I'm the one who called them here.
They hate you.
I just told them that you
love killing cats and dogs!
Get him!
Heaven's Door!
I-It's no use! There are too many!
I won!
3 Freeze!
These animals didn't do anything wrong.
So scram, all of you. Shoo.
Th-That Stand is...
Koichi!
What?!
I thought that you might
just be messing with me,
but I was still a bit worried, so I went back,
and you were still acting
weird, Rohan-sensei.
Even outside your house, you were
walking with your back to walls,
and crossing the street with your
back to someone else's, all by yourself.
So you really do have an
enemy Stand on your back.
That's exactly what I admire
so much about you...
You truly are my friend.
It's on your back, right?
I just have to remove the
enemy from your back, right?
Reverb, 3 Freeze!
Heavy...
Y-You did it!
Aren't you a bit naïve?
I'm not sticking to your back with
strength, but with my ability.
Trying to forcibly remove me from your back
means that you'll destroy your back.
Thud
Huh?!
Go ahead and tell Koichi, okay?
Hurry up and tell him!
R-Rohan-sensei?!
K-Koichi...
I'm very moved that you came
here, and very grateful...
But I'd appreciate it if you'd withdraw Act 3.
You can't see it, but my back is
starting to rip ever so slightly...
Act 3! Undo the 3 Freeze!
S-h-i-t. Understood.
R-Rohan-sensei! A-Are...
Of course I'm not okay, Koichi Hirose!
This damage is your fault, isn't it?
Do you get it now?
There's no way to get rid of me.
Peeling me off your back, Rohan,
means that you'll be peeling
away your own back!
Hey...
You're just going to wear yourself out.
Either you'll pass out from
exhaustion and damage first,
or you'll go crazy and kill yourself...
No matter how great the Stand,
they can't defeat me
if my only ability is to talk!
Okay?
The Stand on your back... Just what kind of...
Large Vehicles
Cannot Pass
Through
What kind? Do you want to see?
You want to see what kind of Stand it is?
Fine...
I'll show it to you.
R-Rohan-sensei...
Looks like you've finally lost it!
I guess you finally realized it's
no use going to Jotaro, either!
Jotaro?
I wasn't heading there in the first place.
I was heading here.
I was so happy to finally make it here
that I couldn't help but laugh.
What are you yammering about?
You finally showed your back to someone!
I'm now going to possess Koichi Hirose!
Th-This place... That post box...
Cheap Trap, you turned around here.
Even if you didn't turn around because
you knew what this place was,
because of your ability, you had no
choice but to look Koichi's way.
Wh-What?!
The alley where Reimi is, where you
can't turn around, no matter what!
It's true that if any Stand tried to get
rid of you, no matter what it was,
you'd return the damage to me.
But there was something that
could grasp only you...
Something that'll only take
those who look back.
Something that'll only take your soul!
Let go! Okay? Let go!
Where do you think you're taking me?! Hey!
The afterlife.
I don't know if Heaven or Hell actually exist,
but just in case, I'll write it in for you.
Going to Hell
It wouldn't do anything except talk,
but that was one intense Stand.
Koichi, if you hadn't come,
I wouldn't have made it here,
and it would have killed me.
But since I was so focused on that thing,
I had no idea we'd end up here.
Reimi!
Did you take these pictures, Rohan?
I did.
Something bothers me about them...
Hayato Kawajiri
Kosaku Kawajiri
Family of 3
C
Ch
Che
Chea
Cheap
Cheap T
Cheap Tr
Cheap Tra
Cheap Trap
Masa
Masazo
Masazo Kinoto
July 15th (Thurs)  6:04 PM
So, like, Mika
got her boyfriend to buy her
some expensive brand earrings.
Buy some for me, too!
Next time.
What do you think you're
doing in my apartment?!
Hey, get the hell out!
Hm... A one-room apartment...
I am Yoshikage Kira. Would you be
kind enough to tell me your name?
My nails are quite long, aren't they?
Look how long they are.
Is there anyone who can actually
stop their nails from growing?
There isn't.
Just as no one can stop
their nails from growing,
you cannot stop the destiny
you were born with.
I believe I asked for your name...
M-My boyfriend... What did you do to my—
Don't answer a question with a question!
Didn't they teach you in school not to
answer a question with a question?!
I'm asking you what your name is!
M-Minako! M-M-Minako!
Minako...
Your parents gave you a beautiful name.
I like it.
Minako, I have a request.
It would make me happy
if you would hold these.
I want you to cut my nails with
these geeky nail clippers.
You've never cut someone else's nails?
There's a first time for everything.
Be careful not to cut them too short.
Help... Please...
Help... Forgive me...
Forgive you?
Now, wait a minute.
I'm not angry or anything.
This is something I enjoy.
I chose you because you
suited my taste, as well.
I was born with these tastes, so I'm just
trying to act positively about it.
Positively...
It sounded like you were asking
your boyfriend for some earrings.
Here, he left these for you.
It's a present.
You're very good at cutting nails.
I like that about you, too.
And you are truly adorable
when you don't talk.
What to do, Minako...
I want to take you home with me,
but bringing you into the
Kawajiri home would be risky.
Still, this is refreshing...
This is truly refreshing!
Th-The man and woman he
followed from the station...
He killed them and made them disappear!
That's... Hayato.
What is he doing in a place like this?
This is the opposite direction
from the house and his school...
What's that?
I didn't lock the door...
Hayato... He...
It couldn't be.
He's not human... What is that
thing that's disguised as my dad?
There's evidence that they've been back here.
And there are blood stains on the floor.
Did he finally make his move?
July 15th (Thurs)  8:36 PM
The thing in Hayato's hand
was definitely a handy cam.
It doesn't seem to be in
this room right now...
Hayato...
He's been acting weird
ever since the other day.
I have to find out what Hayato was doing.
I have to find out for sure.
C-Calm down...
I have to calm down and gather my thoughts.
First, this videotape...
Should I show it to someone?
I can't show it to Mom!
Mom totally trusts him.
Should I show it to the police?
Would they believe that a person got
blown up and then disappeared?
More importantly, he's not human...
Could the police even
catch someone like him?
No... Does anyone even exist in
this world who could catch him?
What should I do?
Mom and I are going to be killed eventually.
What am I supposed to do?!
Do you mind if I join you...
in the bath, Hayato?
It's been a while.
I-I'm gonna head out now.
Oh, come on.
We're family, after all...
Wh-What does he want?
I'll be in trouble if he finds this tape.
I'm sorry, Hayato, but could
you let go of the bucket?
I want to draw some water and wash my body.
I-I'll wash your back for you, Dad!
That's a great idea.
But I'll wash your back first.
You're the one who got in first.
I'll wash yours first, then we can switch.
Now, sit down.
What's the matter?
You seem to be sweating quite a bit.
Did you get get too hot?
Y-Yeah...
Then why are you shivering?
Isn't it strange to shiver if you're overheated?
You're tickling me, Dad!
You should know that I've
always been ticklish!
You're... right.
You've always been ticklish, Hayato.
I-I'll wash my front...
I see. So you'll do it yourself.
By the way, I just remembered...
This evening,
I was around the Jozenji area that's
in the opposite direction from home,
and I saw you.
Huh?!
With a video camera!
What were you doing?
Now I know for sure!
This little brat was watching!
This is awful... I thought I'd
peacefully fit into this household...
I've had nothing but misfortune this year.
What an awful year.
Killing this brat will draw attention
to myself, and that would be very bad.
But since he saw that, I have no choice!
I just turned one of the strands
of this brat's hair into a bomb.
If I just cause a slight explosion on his head,
it'll just look like he slipped
and hit his head on the bath.
That's a common accident in our society.
You're going to die.
Die, brat!
Are you going to kill me, too?
Even though I've got video of you...
I'm even videotaping you right now!
What?
I've been suspicious of you this whole time.
Your different shoe size
and the fact that you were practicing
your signature are all on tape!
I've got other tapes, too!
I even took a video of the cat-like
plant you've got in the attic!
I'm the only one who knows
where the tapes are!
But if something were to happen to me,
I'm sure someone would find that place.
What?
Don't you dare lay a finger on me! Got it?
You little shit! You dare threaten me?
I won't let you touch my mom, either!
Episode 35
Bites the Dust, Part 1