You Are Here
Koichi...
Over here, Koichi.
Ah! R-Rohan Kishibe!
Come on, now. You don't have
to put up your guard like that.
It's not like I'm going to harm you.
Besides, when I read you with Heaven's Door,
I actually felt a lot of admiration for you.
I have a feeling we have a lot in common.
Don't you think so?
Uh...
You see, there's something
that I wanted to ask you.
I lived around here from when I was
a baby up until I was about four.
I wanted to find the place where
I lived then, for nostalgia's sake.
It's also a manga artist's job
to remember their childhood.
But the memories would be from
when I was three or four,
so I don't remember much.
Oh...
What I wanted to ask you
about is this town map.
It's quite bizarre.
Look.
Convenience Store
Owson
Kisara
Drugstore
Soba Shop
Arisugawa
Tailor
Tanaka
You Are Here
Soba Shop Arisugawa, Kisara Drugstore,
and the convenience store Owson is how
the shops line up from the right.
Huh?
Now look at the actual shops.
From the right, it's Soba Shop
Arisugawa, Kisara Drugstore, and...
Owson on the left...
Huh?
The road between Owson and
the drugstore isn't on the map.
How lazy of them.
Koichi, will you come with me for a bit?
I'd be very grateful if you'd
show me around here.
Huh? Well, I, uh...
Even after I, Rohan Kishibe,
have asked so courteously?
I see.
So you're not even willing
to walk ten or so meters.
You're so selfish. Jeez...
Just five minutes, okay, Sensei?
Just five minutes!
Episode 17    Rohan Kishibe's Adventure
Isn't it bizarre?
This road isn't on this 1/3000 scale map
of Morioh published by
National Map Publishers.
Huh? Sometimes if you find errors in maps,
they'll give you a bookstore gift certificate.
Ugh...
Jeez, this map is infuriating.
Look, Koichi.
Yonemori
These houses that say "Yonemori," "Honma,"
and "Onodera" aren't on it, either.
Honma
Numakura
Onodera
This map is filled with errors.
Two or three bookstore
gift certificates won't cover this.
Rohan-sensei..
Looks like an empty house.
Rocky
What a strange place.
It doesn't look like anyone lives
in these four or five houses.
Even the electricity to the
vending machine's been cut.
Huh?
That post box...
This is where we first turned.
How strange...
How did we end up back
where we started again?
But we turned right, left,
then right, so how...
It's possible that we're being
attacked by someone's Stand.
Huh? Stand?!
Koichi, would you have
Reverb fly up to the sky?
I see!
If it looks down from above,
we'll see which way to go.
Reverb Act 1!
What's the matter?
Th-There's something there.
Something touched it up in the sky.
I didn't see anything.
But something definitely touched it!
Are you two lost?
Want me to show you the way?
A girl!
That girl's a Stand user!
Heaven's Door!
Don't even give her a chance to speak!
Victory to the swiftest!
Boom
Now we're safe.
She won't be able to harm us.
That's amazing!
I-It looked like a drawing
leaped out just now...
I guess that means I've matured a bit.
Though it wouldn't work
on lame people like Josuke,
who don't like my manga.
We're on the same wavelength.
She's not a Stand user.
She's just a normal girl.
Huh? Sh-She's not an enemy?
Right. You can't hide
anything from Heaven's Door.
She's Reimi Sugimoto, age 16.
Her address is 3-12, Kotodai, Morioh.
It's right over there.
She doesn't have a boyfriend.
Her measurements are 82-57-84 centimeters.
She has a mole on the
side of her left nipple.
She had her first period the
September after she turned 11.
The first time she kissed a boy,
he forced his tongue into her mouth.
Hey! Hold on a sec, Rohan Kishibe!
If that girl's not a Stand user,
then I won't allow you to
read any more about her!
All right, all right.
Don't get so angry.
"She'll forget everything
that just happened." There.
Want me to show you the way?
A lot of people get lost around here,
since all the alleys looks alike.
We'll be fine if you could
just tell us which way to go.
No, no. You won't understand
if I just explain it to you.
I'll show you the way, so follow me.
Want one?
No?
Could you just grab the other end, then?
Snap
Aw, you're going to get dumped by some girl.
What are you talking about?
It's Pocky fortune-telling. How the
Pocky breaks tells me your fortune.
You're selfish, aren't you?
And you have a tendency to mess with people.
That's why you'll get dumped.
Did you hear that, Koichi?
She's completely off!
She called me selfish!
If we're going to play that game,
I know a thing or two, as well.
Light pink nail polish means you're
a coward when it comes to love.
You let true love slip away
at the crucial moment.
Huh?
No way...
This is a psychological test,
not fortune-telling.
Other than love, there's something else
scaring you right now, isn't there?
Apparently,
a murder took place at this
house about fifteen years ago.
A murder?!
Murder...
No one lives there now.
Do you want to hear about it?
I heard this from the old
lady who lives next door.
The night of the murder,
while the girl who lived here
was asleep in her bedroom,
she awoke to a "drip, drip" sound
coming from her parents' room.
She wondered what the sound was,
and called out to her parents,
but there was no reply.
But the girl wasn't that scared, because...
Her beloved dog was by her side.
Beloved dog?
Yes. He was a big guard dog.
Even in the dark, if she put
her hand underneath her bed,
he would whimper and lick her hand.
She felt safe because Arnold was with her.
But she heard the dripping sound
go on for more than ten minutes...
Finally, the girl decided to
find out what the sound was.
And then...
She found her beloved dog Arnold dead,
hanging from the coat rack.
His blood was the dripping
sound that she heard.
Suddenly, she heard a voice
from under the bed say,
"Your hand is so soft and cute,
Miss. Whimper, whimper..."
"I already killed your parents." And then...
The girl was killed, too!
I-Is that a true story?!
Did it sound like one? It was just
payback for trashing my nail polish.
Whew...
Th-That stuff is bad for my heart... Jeez...
Drip
Wha—
That's...
Yes... That girl was me.
Both Arnold and I are ghosts.
G-Ghosts?
What my Stand, Heaven's Door, read
were memories from when she
was alive, so I couldn't tell.
You two walked into the place
where I died fifteen years ago.
I guess we're on the same wavelength.
This is the border between
the living world and the next.
Re
Rev
Rever
Reverb
Ko
Koichi
Koichi Hiro
Koichi Hirose
Let's get out of here, Koichi!
I-It's no use!
Use Reverb, Koichi!
Have it fly into the air and find the way!
She must have been what
touched it in the sky earlier.
Just have it fly up already, Koichi!
Wha—
What?! There's suddenly a wall in the sky!
K-Koichi, Reverb is touching the ground.
Huh?! Ah, what?!
Y-You're the one who went
flying up into the air.
There's only one way out of this place.
And I know where it is.
H-How are we supposed to fight a ghost?
Please don't possess us!
Hey, hold on. Stop treating
me like a vengeful spirit.
What did I do to you?
You're the ones getting all scared on your own!
I'm not the one who trapped you in here.
This is the border between
this world and the next.
You two have strange powers.
They're called Stands?
I wonder if that's how you ended up here.
You're not our enemy?
You really don't trust people, do you?
I think I'm what they call a bound spirit?
I became a ghost that can't leave here.
For fifteen years, I tried to speak to
various people who ended up here,
because I needed to tell someone.
But you're the first ones that
I've been able to talk to this much.
I told you I'd tell you how to get out of
here, and that's what I'm going to do.
After I finish the story, that is.
Story?
The rest of my story from earlier.
Before I could see the murderer's face,
I was stabbed in the back with a knife.
It was late at night and dark,
and I was desperately running away.
The murderer hasn't been caught yet.
He's somewhere in Morioh.
That's what I wanted to tell someone.
He's blended into this town.
Wait. Are you telling us because...
I'm not asking you to catch him.
But I want you to tell someone...
Someone who can catch him, like the police...
Whoa, whoa. Why should we have
to do something like that?
Rohan-sensei!
It's fine. I just want to say the rational thing.
I do feel bad that you were killed...
But why should we have to find
the murderer just because of
your personal grudge and suffering?
I think, as a ghost, you'd be better off
cutting your ties to this world
and passing on into the next.
Do you even know how many boys and
girls have disappeared from this town?
Huh? No.
It's eight times the national average.
I'm not saying it's all of them, but at least
some of them are being killed in secret.
By him.
W-Wait a second!
Are you saying these murders
are still happening?
Hey! Don't make baseless claims like that!
You just said you didn't
see the murderer's face!
So how would you know that?
The souls of the murdered
fly above here all the time!
And they all have a wound just like this.
H-How cruel... It's so long and deep...
I can't talk to those souls
going to the next world,
but I've seen them many times.
I know what he's into! I know!
These murders have been going on for
fifteen years here in Morioh,
where I was born and raised.
It's frightening, and it wounds my pride.
When they catch the murderer,
my beloved Morioh
will be known nationwide as a
town where a murderer lived.
But we have to stop the
murderer as soon as possible!
Even now, he's targeting someone,
and I can't do a thing.
Who's going to be killed next?
If you, the living, don't take
back this town's pride and peace,
who else is going to do it?!
I don't know if you understand
what I'm saying, but...
I'm done talking now.
A-All right. I'm very shocked.
But... Still, we have to do something.
Hmph. Stop being such a
goody-two-shoes, Koichi.
It's just going to be trouble.
But it might be good to go after
the murderer and interview him.
I might be able to draw a
really interesting manga!
Is the exit this way?
If you think he's a good person
deep down... well, you shouldn't.
He's pretty gray when it
comes to being trustworthy.
Hey, are you listening?
All right. I'll lead you to the exit.
Huh? The exit? Where? Where is it?
If you turn left past the
post box, it's right there.
Yay!
Don't rush!
There's a certain rule you have
to follow to get past there.
A rule?
Once you pass the post box and turn,
you'll be able to see the
exit about 20 meters away.
No matter what happens,
until you get there, promise
me that you won't turn around.
What? Why?
It's the rule for passing
from this world to the next.
Even Arnold understands that.
Well, I guess we can promise to do
something even a dog can handle.
What happens if we turn around?
Our souls will be pulled into the
next world, which means you'll die.
Don't be frightened!
Just don't turn around. Simple, right?
R-Right when we passed the post box...
Something shot between our
legs and went behind us!
Don't turn around!
Just keep walking slowly and calmly.
R-Rohan-sensei, something is following us.
I know.
Something's there...
Something is right behind my head!
Don't worry about it!
There's always something trying
to make you turn around.
But as long as you don't
turn and look at it,
it can't touch you, so just
keep your wits about you.
N-Now a warm liquid is dripping down my neck...
You're almost there! That light is the exit.
What?
Huh?
Th-The exit...
But I can't take it any longer!
Rohan-sensei, let's run!
Don't panic!
It's going to try to trip you.
You're safe now.
You got through it.
You can turn around from there.
That was so scary! I'm so relieved!
That was a lie, Koichi!
That wasn't really me just now!
Huh?
Impossible...
Not yet. Don't look back yet.
This didn't happen when I was by myself.
They didn't try to trick me!
Koichi!
Hmph. I don't really get it,
but we just can't look, right?
You're lucky you're with me, Koichi.
Heaven's Door!
You won't be able to see,
and you'll be blown away.
Crash
Boom
Calm down, Koichi.
I'll write that you can see again now.
The road between the convenience
store and drugstore is gone.
W-We made it back...
We'll always be here.
Until the murderer's caught.
The day that Arnold and I turn around to go
where my mom and dad are will be
when the pride and peace
of this town are restored.
Until then, I can't leave here.
If you ever need to ask me anything,
come by any time.
We can see each other any time,
Rohannie and Koichi...
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
for listening to what I had to say.
That girl had some nerve, calling me "Rohannie."
She was getting too friendly.
But... Reimi Sugimoto, huh...
There's something admirable
about how that ghost lives.
She's been fighting for fifteen years,
alone, for the sake of the living.
Zero Clues Found in Family Massacre
Sugimoto
Family
Grave
Sugimoto
Reimi
There it is! Sugimoto Reimi, age 16.
Not that I doubted her,
but now I've got some clues.
Ah, could you be...
Rohan Kishibe, who became a manga artist?
You know me?
Rohan, you were only four,
so it's no surprise that you
don't remember that incident.
Your house at the time was very near theirs.
The night of that incident,
your parents had urgent business
they had to attend to and
were forced to leave...
So they left you overnight
at the Sugimoto household
because you were all very close.
That night, Rohan, you were staying
overnight at the Sugimoto household.
And you were the only one to survive.
I was... there?
Sugimoto
Family
Grave
When the police found you,
you kept crying and repeating
the same thing over and over.
"Reimi snuck me out the window."
Reimi saved you before you
could be found by the murderer.
That little girl... No wonder
she acted all friendly with me.
I can't read my distant memories nor
my fate with my Stand, Heaven's Door.
If you happen to wander down this path,
do not turn around, no matter what.
Morioh Landmark 6
"The Path Where You Can
Meet a Girl's Ghost"
How to get there: Take the #11 bus
from Morioh Station and get off
at the Kotodai Shopping District.
It will appear between the
convenience store, Owson,
and Kisara Drugstore at 2-chome.
Warning: Most people won't be
able to see it, but if you happen
to wander down this path, do not
turn around, no matter what.
I really met a ghost!
The girl in that picture is Reimi!
Okay, we get it.
So, I researched her,
I said I believe you, didn't I? Right, Okuyasu?
and she was also a student
at Budogaoka High School.
She's cute... She's my type.
I wish I'd been born fifteen years sooner.
We should eventually go meet this ghost, too.
But, Koichi, if we tell Jotaro
or Old Man Joseph about this,
they're probably going to ask one thing.
"Is the murderer a Stand user?"
W-Well... I don't know...
Then we'll just have to let the
police and the courts deal with it.
B-But there's a murderer in Morioh!
I know. And that's why I'm saying that
Jotaro and the Speedwagon Foundation
won't just go after a normal murderer.
Calm down.
He's managed to escape from the
almighty police for the past fifteen years.
It's not like we'd run into him right away,
like we'd hailed a taxi cab.
Let's stay calm and look into this carefully.
So what did Rohan have to say?
The same thing as you, Josuke.
Hey, look out, Koichi.
Don't cross the road when
you're all spaced out.
S-Sorry...
Originally, Morioh was a resort filled
with villas that belonged to samurai.
My ancestors were among them.
But we were ruined during
my grandfather's time.
All that's left is the house that I live in now.
And I'm stuck working a trivial office job.
Hey, what did you do with the
imported wristwatch I bought you?
Ah, it's in your bag. That's right.
It was a little too big for you.
Let's get it fixed tomorrow.
What's wrong? Why are you acting so shy?
Now... Watch your step.
Let's enjoy this weekend to the fullest.
Just the two of us.
You just dripped something...
How rude you are.
You need to clean that up yourself.
I can't remember what your name was,
but that's all right.
Well done. You cleaned it all off.
Now, then...
Let's make dinner together.
What's the dish that you're best at?
Kira
Episode 18
Shigechi's Harvest, Part 1