Arrow, where are you headed?
We're going to shoot him, too?
That young man will be the
sixth new Stand user...
But that should be plenty.
I'll be able to kill anyone who tries
to get near my son, Yoshikage!
Ting
What?!
Ow.
Wh-What's the meaning of this?
The arrow chose him, but it was deflected.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 27      I'm an Alien
That's all the information
we were able to gather.
Profile
Yoshikage Kira
It appears he's done a good job of disposing
of all evidence of his crimes up to now.
Yoshikage Kira...
What do you look like now,
and what is your name?
Where are you?
Summer...
There are many more tourists around town now.
Yeah...
I doubt that he'll be able to stay put.
I'm sure he won't be able
to resist making a move.
The summer season is finally upon us.
On July 1st, the beach and rivers in
Morioh were opened to the public.
There are hordes of tourists
from the capital and S City,
making the town even livelier.
Relaxing at a summer villa,
camping, fishing, yachting...
There are many fun activities
to find here this time of year!
How are you all going
to enjoy your summer?
Yes, many fun things...
I'm sure he has
many fun things to do, too.
People live while hiding what's
deep in their hearts from others.
But...
Is there anyone who has
been able to hide their true
self from others forever?
Damn it!
I want to show that woman
the true Yoshikage Kira.
I want her to hear how
I feel deep down inside...
That I want to take your
slender neck into these hands
and strangle you to death.
When my nails are growing,
I become unable to suppress my urges.
I just need to be patient until it subsides.
I'm still not able to perfectly
mimic his handwriting.
Kosaku Kawajiri
Kosaku
Josuke Higashikata... Jotaro Kujo...
It's because of them that I'm in this mess.
Um...
Uh... What... are you doing?
O-Of course. It should be obvious.
You were reading a book.
Um, I poured some tea for you.
I know you probably think that's rare,
b-but if you'd like some...
If you don't want it, that's fine, too...
Oh, look at the time.
I think I'll go to bed...
Open up your heart to that woman.
Show her your true self,
Yoshikage Kira.
D-Darling?
Crap. Opening up is a bad idea.
They'll find out.
I'm sorry I startled you.
H-He was trying to undo
the buttons in the back?
"I'm sorry I startled you"?
Not at all! All of your actions lately
have been exciting me to no end!
And they make me feel thrilled! I...
I've fallen
in love with you.
J-Josuke, l-look over there.
What the heck is—
Is this... Could this be...
T-Terri Funk—
It's a crop circle!
Yeah! A crop circle!
Th-That's amazing!
I can't believe one of these
showed up in a field in Morioh!
Something's not right, Okuyasu.
Take a closer look at the middle of that thing.
Something's really wrong here!
You're gonna go in?
We don't have a choice!
Be careful.
Yeah.
I-Is he alive?
He's got a scratch on the back of his neck,
but I think he's just unconscious.
Hey, wake up. Are you all right? Hey!
I've never seen him at our school.
Oh, looks like he's awake.
Where...
Where am I?
Where?
You're right in the middle of
a field in Budogaoka, Morioh.
Is this Earth?
Last night, I suddenly felt ill.
I then lost consciousness, it would seem.
It's past eight, so I was unconscious
for thirteen Earth hours.
He totally tried to pull one over us!
Damn! I can't believe you tried
to pull such an elaborate prank!
Man, you sure got me!
You're a really funny guy!
So you made a crop circle and waited
under the grass until someone came by?
Amazing! That's amazing!
I can't breathe! My stomach hurts!
Stomach Medicine
That's so stupid!
What school do you go to?
School?
We love guys like you!
My planet is in the Magellanic Clouds,
but it has been destroyed.
I came to Earth to find out
if it's a suitable place to live,
and if the people are nice.
That's enough of that.
If you take the joke too far,
you're going to ruin your own brilliant idea.
Here, have a tissue.
Thank you. That was quite delicious.
W-We should really get to school.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Let's go.
That guy ate the tissue.
He's a guy who takes jokes too far.
The ice cream shop's closed!
And it's our only comfort on Monday mornings...
It can't be helped.
Let's give up for today.
Would you like some ice cream?
Well? Do you want some?
Yeah, but the shop's closed,
so there's nothing we can do.
There's no reason for you to give up.
I just happen to have two.
We can call it a trade for the tissue earlier.
Earth seems like a very nice place to live.
It's cold...
Wh-Why did you have
ice cream cones in your bag?
Are those ice cream cones not good enough?
That's not what I'm asking!
Who the hell are you?
I believe I told you that moments ago...
Ah! You want to hear me introduce myself?
It must have slipped my mind.
My name is Nu Mikitakazo Nshi.
I am 216 years old.
My occupation is a spaceship pilot.
My hobby is having pets.
I'm even currently carrying
a house mouse in my bag.
It is very happy when I pet its back.
This guy's a Stand user.
There's no doubt about it.
Let's kick his ass, Josuke!
Calm down, Okuyasu.
Do you really think a Stand user
would say that he's from
the Magellanic Clouds?
Th-Then what the hell is with him?
There, there, there.
I have no idea.
We're gonna have to investigate.
Don't eat that ice cream.
Huh?!
So you're 216, you say?
Yes.
Hmm...
And your occupation is a spaceship pilot?
Why do you keep copying me?
So, what?
Are you trying to say that you're an alien?
An alien!
An alien! Yes!
I should have used that word to begin with.
I'm an alien.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Then, like, your... flying saucer?
Could you call over your spaceship?
You can, right?
Of course.
But, sadly, as it is currently on standby
in space, 1,500,000 kilometers away,
it would take about three days.
I can't bring it immediately.
Are you going to call it
with that watch of yours?
Oh, how did you know?
But this is a secret between us.
Please don't tell anyone of this.
This guy is totally messed up in the head.
He wasn't joking earlier at all.
He's a delusional, crazy bastard.
Should I punch him?
You always want to throw punches first.
Let's take it a bit further, just to be sure.
Do you have, like, a ray gun and, like,
an ultra hyper anti-gravity
device in your bag?
Of course I do.
But I didn't come to Earth to fight,
so I left them in my spaceship.
Aw, come on. If you're an
alien, show us something.
And your blood wasn't even green.
Yeah. Alien blood is always green.
Do you two doubt me?
Hey, calm down.
You finally got it? You moron!
I don't mind going along with pranks,
but I don't have time to deal
with delusional freaks like you.
You didn't have to just come out and say that!
Shut up! It's better to be up-front!
What? Is there a fire somewhere?
Wh-What the hell?
This sound... I don't like this sound.
This sound...
Stop this sound!
I don't like this sound!
I'm allergic to it!
Make it stop!
Josuke, this guy's dangerous!
Let's go. We shouldn't mess with him.
But don't you think
leaving him like that is a bit cruel?
He said he's allergic to that sound,
right? Just leave him be.
I'm leaving, Josuke.
H-Hey!
Damn it, Okuyasu.
H-Hey, you okay?
No... Please,
take me somewhere I can't hear this sound...
Wh-What?!
Please take me away!
A-Are you actually...
I have a power that allows
me to turn into anything.
H-Hurry... I feel like my head
will split open amidst this sound...
Please...
I'll turn into sneakers, so please,
wear them and take me with you!
In return, I'll do anything for you!
Are you a Stand user?!
Whoa! Y-You're super fast!
With your powers plus my powers,
our speed and jumping strength are doubled.
Are you seriously an alien?!
T
Te
Ter
Terr
Terra
Terra V
Terra Ve
Terra Ven
Terra Vent
Terra Ventu
Terra Ventus
Mi
Miki
Mikitaka
Mikitaka Haze
Mikitaka Hazekura
What the hell?!
You...
You can't see this?
He can't see it!
He's not a Stand user.
Then what the hell is this power?
Who the hell are you?!
You're rather persistent, aren't you?
I told you earlier that I was an alien...
Hang on a sec.
L-Let me sort this out in my head.
Anyway, you saved me by
taking me away from that.
The people on my planet can't
stand the sound of sirens.
It's a wavelength that aggravates our nerves.
I'd like to do something for you
to thank you for saving me.
Shall I turn into a fan and fan you?
Or maybe a back scratcher
so I can scratch your back?
Whoa, it's not like I saved you because
I wanted something in return...
You'll really do anything?
Please! Do it! Thank you!
Shopping
Catalog
What would you like me to do?
C-Can you turn into anything?
Like something light, or multiple
numbers of something?
Yes. I can turn into almost anything.
However, I cannot turn
into complicated machinery
or anything more powerful than me.
I see, I see. Got it. I like you!
So you're going to thank me, right?
Yes.
I-I...
just had a brilliant idea.
It's an idea that'll make everyone happy.
Happy?
Yeah!
See, I managed to make some
money from a lottery ticket,
but my mom found out and
froze the account I put it in.
Once she finds something like that,
there's no convincing her.
It sucks not having any
money for the summer season.
Shopping
Catalog
And so...
Can you turn into this? This thing.
What is that?
They're dice!
I'll make some money using these,
then I'll split it with you,
and everyone will be happy!
What do you do with those?
Huh? You don't know what dice are?
I-I'm sorry...
You don't have to apologize.
It's really easy. I'll show you.
These are tools that people
who like games really love.
They're hard, and they have six sides.
This divot represents the number one,
and it has them from one through six.
Ah, yes. I think I'm starting to understand.
So when there are five divots,
it's the number five, right?
Well done, alien!
And three divots represent a three.
Yes! Try turning into one.
Understood.
That was simple.
What are you talking about?
You're way too big.
You're only supposed to be about this big.
Also, you've got five on two sides.
The numbers on a die are from one through six.
The numbers on one side and its
opposite side should equal seven.
Oh, pardon me.
How about this?
Th-That tickles!
Hey, don't laugh. Dice don't talk.
Huh?
Come on.
I-I'll do my best.
I'm a bit nervous about this, but...
Yes, you're good! Very good! This is perfect!
I'm getting excited!
Rohan Kishibe, I hope you have
some money waiting for me!
I-I can't breathe...
Oh, look who it is.
What does Josuke Higashikata want with me?
This is a rare occurrence.
Did you get more information concerning Kira?
No, not exactly...
Um, well...
Are you done with work today?
I was wondering if I could have
a peek at your next chapter...
What are you plotting?
Just spit it out.
D-Damn...
I can't hide anything from you, Rohan-sensei.
All right, I'll tell you the truth.
Please! Play Cee-lo with me!
Cee-lo?
To be perfectly honest,
I have no spending money for the summer.
Well, I have 30,000 yen.
It's my life savings.
But...
Nowadays, 30,000 yen is gone
after you make one or two trips
to an amusement park and get some food.
So all that's left is to make
more money, or go flat broke.
Wagering on the thrill!
Isn't that what youth is all about?
That's what I think! Don't you agree?!
Look, I'll be straight with you.
I've always disliked you.
So why should I have to play Cee-lo with you?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sure you're not hurting for spending money,
so you have no reason to play.
But... All right.
Huh?! You'll do it?
I don't dislike games, and this seems fun.
Come around to the back.
Thank you, Rohan-sensei.
The shooter rolls 3 dice into the bowl
This will result in paying double
This will result in winning double
The larger number wins (here, the 6)
Do these rules work for you?
No arguments here.
Chips cost 1,000 yen each.
And when you roll the
three dice into the bowl,
if even one spills out,
you lose then and there.
Got it.
All right. Let's tape the rules up here.
Okay, let's do this!
Wait.
We won't be using your dice.
Huh?!
We'll be playing with these
dice I had in the house.
U-Um, is there something wrong with my dice?
No idea. There's just something
that I don't like about them.
And...
I did say this seemed fun,
but I wasn't talking about Cee-lo.
I meant that it'd be fun taking
your 30,000 yen from you.
When you lose, you'd better pay up for real.
It doesn't matter how well
acquainted we are, Josuke-kun.
Yes! Those dice are the ones
that the alien turned into!
I snuck them into your house ahead of time!
I'm such a villain.
It won't be much, but I'll be making
some money off of you, Rohan-sensei.
Now, let's roll to see who goes first.
I rolled a four.
Yes!
All right, you go first. Go ahead and roll.
Ow!
O...
O-Ow! I accidentally hit the table.
Hurry up and bet and roll your dice.
R-Right...
I-I'll start off with two, I think,
so that'll be 2,000 yen.
Okay, here's two.
If I roll a one, a two, and a three,
I'll have to pay double,
so I really need to make sure
I don't get one, two, and three.
Better not get a one, two, and three!
Not a one, two, and three!
I-I'll go really lightly on the first roll.
Just to test the waters...
Here we go... Lightly.
How's that?!
Huh?!
What?
A-An omen...
Triple sixes, AKA "omen."
Josuke wins five times what
he wagered from Rohan.
S-Stupid! You're not supposed
to start off with that!
E-Er, I mean...
I meant that was some stupid luck!
A triple six, meaning you have
to pay five times my bet...
It almost seems like I'm cheating!
Hmph. It seems you've already earned
10,000 yen in spending money.
Let's continue the game.
I can't believe my luck myself...
It's my turn next.
I want to get back what I just lost, so I'm...
going with ten.
Ten?
All right! Go!
One, two, and three. The wager is doubled!
The shooter rolls 3 dice into the bowl
This will result in paying double
Rohan has to pay Josuke double what he wagered.
This is too much! This is way too much!
Does that alien not know
what "holding back" means?
Crap... He's totally suspicious of me!
Episode 28
Highway Go Go, Part 1
Highway Go Go Part 1