July 15th (Thurs)  10:43 AM
Who is that? I've never seen him before.
Hello. My name is Kinoto.
I'm the architect you called.
I came to estimate repairs from the fire
and any renovations we might do.
Oh, right. We made plans for you to come by.
Heaven's Door!
Sorry that was so sudden,
but I've been quite cautious lately.
Yay! I got work!
Gonna make some money!
Rohan Kishibe seems like he
has a lot of money,
so I'm gonna make a fortune.
Hopefully I can
overcharge a little bit.
He was born in 1970 and
is a first-class architect.
His name is Masazo Kinoto.
I see.
Looks like he is indeed the one I called.
He's not a Stand user or an enemy.
Hm?
I don't like anyone looking at my back.
I don't want anyone to see my back.
It's not like I have acne, scars, or a tattoo,
but I never want anyone to look at my back, ever!
I can't seem to get a girlfriend. What should I do?!
I have no idea what that's about,
but I guess everyone has
strange concerns and fears.
But it seems like he's safe
to allow into the house.
Though there was that incident
with the Janken kid, too...
Just in case, I'll write in
that he can't attack me.
Huh? Did I do something just now?
No. Please, come in. Let's discuss the job.
Is something the matter?
The room that caught fire
is the one facing the yard.
If you don't come in, we can't
discuss what to do about it.
Oh, please, go ahead. I'll follow you.
Huh?
Now, please, go ahead.
July 15th (Thurs)  9:06 AM
Episode 32    July 15th (Thurs), Part 2
Of course I can escape, and rather easily.
You guys haven't even been able
to find Yoshikage Kira, have you?
You guys haven't seen my face.
Doesn't my name seem fake, too?
I mean, it's Toyohiro Kanedaichi.
Wh-What the hell?
Are you wearing something over your face?
The fact that I thought about leaving here
means I also planned on getting away.
Well, I'll be leaving now.
Y-You bastard!
Please don't come in, Josuke.
I'll remain with this pylon.
What?! What the hell are you talking about?
This all started because I found it,
and this happened because
I turned into a wire
and climbed all the way up here.
I can be useful, too.
I wanted you guys to be proud
of me, and that's why I did it.
Even though Okuyasu told
me to stay out of it.
I got what I deserved.
Please don't worry about me.
If I think of it as if it were
the inside of a spaceship,
it seems quite spacious.
You're pretty weird, but also brave.
Though it really doesn't
matter to me who stays here.
As long as I get to leave,
that's all that matters.
You guys can decide the rest for yoursel—
No, you're the one who'll be staying.
The only time you'll ever get
to hear the word "goodbye"
is when you hear us say it!
J-Josuke!
Y-You bastard!
Since you cut this, I was able
to fix it and climb back up here.
Impossible...
Mikitaka, could you hold on
for another ten seconds or so?
After I beat the crap out of this guy
and drag him back into the
pylon, I'll fix you right up.
Don't fall, Josuke!
Of course I won't fall.
I just said "impossible," but that was wrong.
Let me rephrase that and say, "you fool."
All I wanted to do was leave this pylon.
I wasn't planning on killing anyone...
But now I'm going to have
to knock you off of here
just so I can get away, you fool!
Shut up!
Shining Diamond...
It looks like a very powerful
Stand when you see it up close.
But do you really think you can
lay a finger on me when I can walk around
the top of this pylon with my eyes closed?
I'm guessing its range is about two meters.
Watch it!
Hey, you dumbass! Quit fooling around!
Josuke, move away from there!
It's already been cut with the knife!
He's already cut up the pylon!
That was a dirty trick!
But it's not a speed that my
Shining Diamond can't dodge.
What are you smirking for, you bastard?
Are you that happy about
me kicking your ass?!
I know every nook and cranny of this pylon.
I know exactly which angles to cut
to make the energy come
flying from any direction.
Just like one who's played
billiards way too much,
I know it all too well!
Billiards?
Jo...
Josuke!
You said it wasn't a speed that
Shining Diamond can't dodge, right?
But do you know which direction
it's going to come from?
I wonder how many more shots it just fired.
They're reflecting off of the beams now.
Here they come!
Josuke!
It's coming from behind, too!
This is exactly why I said, "you fool."
That alien or whatever over there
bravely said he'd stay behind with the pylon.
You should have just listened to him.
Then you wouldn't have to die.
B-Both of his arms?
He won't be able to dodge
the next attack like that.
Here comes the energy to finish you off!
It's going right for...
By the way, Okuyasu,
did you happen to see from there how many
of this guy's attacks I smacked
away with Shining Diamond?
Huh? Yeah, I saw.
I'm pretty sure I saw you smack four of them.
What? Did you just say, "by the way"?
Four of them, huh?
Well, that should be enough.
Four shots should be plenty.
What are you two talking about?!
You said they were reflecting.
You said the Stand's energy was reflecting
like billiard balls to attack me.
What about it, Josuke?!
My Stand is Shining Diamond.
I'm sure the old man in
the photograph told you,
but its power is to fix things and
energies that have been destroyed.
Fix... Did you say "fix"?
What are you saying you fixed?!
Are you saying that you actually had
the chance to fix something just now?
You idiot!
You fixed the energies that were reflecting
and returned them to where they originated.
Josuke, I thought you were defeated,
but I guess you had already won.
I-Impossible...
It looks like the line you were supposed
to say was "impossible," after all.
I'm really sorry.
I started living on this pylon
because I disliked other people.
But the old guy in the photograph
said that if I could trap
even one Stand user here,
he would look after me so I
could live in the outside world,
and I ended up going along with it...
Please! Will you let me
go back to this pylon?
I never want to leave here again.
I want to stay in here forever.
I'll never think about leaving
the pylon ever again.
New Morioh landmark:
the guy who lives on a pylon.
Morioh Landmark No. 9:
The Guy Who Lives on a Pylon
He lives completely self-sufficiently,
but if you bring him salt or snacks,
he'll be happy and let you
take pictures with him.
He's a bit shy, so he wears a mask
and won't tell you his real name.
More importantly, about the
old guy in the photograph...
Did he say anything?
Like where his son, Yoshikage Kira,
might be, or anything else?
Is there a Stand user named
Koichi here in Morioh?
What about Koichi?!
Listen, the old guy in the photograph
just happened to randomly
mention it when he was talking.
I didn't ask too much about it,
and he didn't go into detail.
Well, what did he say about Koichi?!
He said that he's been eliminated.
What?!
It seems the old guy in the photograph
had already found his son
Yoshikage Kira's whereabouts.
He said it wasn't just about
protecting his son anymore,
and that he was going to
start attacking, as well.
And this morning, a brand new Stand user
eliminated a Stand user named Koichi...
That's all he said.
July 15th (Thurs)  10:58 AM
Hmm... This is rather...
Whoa! Th-This door will be about 800,000 yen!
And the design is from the
Victorian and Edwardian eras!
It uses materials made in England, too...
This is going to cost quite a bit.
He said he didn't want
anyone to see his back...
Was he acting like that on his
way to my house, as well?
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Please, before it gets cold.
Oh, don't mind me.
July 15th (Thurs)  11:16 AM
I need to control myself...
Not yet...
Sh
Shi
Shini
Shinin
Shining
Shining D
Shining Di
Shining Dia
Shining Diamo
Shining Diamon
Shining Diamond
Jo
Josuke
Josuke Higashi
Josuke Higashikata
July 15th (Thurs)  10:20 AM
I hope they're able to find Koichi safely...
July 15th (Thurs)  11:37 AM
Damn it! He's nowhere! Not at home, school,
or anywhere!
Koichi! Koichi!
Where are you, Koichi?!
I'm not giving up!
I'll find you, whatever it takes, Koichi!
That's what's going on.
So I was wondering if you would
use your sense of smell
and tracking abilities to help me find Koichi,
Yuya Fungami.
I'll fix your injuries. This is a trade-off.
A trade-off?
You can't be serious, Josuke!
Don't underestimate me!
You're the one who put me in this
condition, and I'll never forgive you!
Do you think that my pride would
actually allow me to help you?
I guess it's a no, after all.
I thought it was useless to begin with.
Well, see you around.
I don't have time to waste.
Wait, huh?! You're gonna
back off that easily?
W-Wait a second, hey!
Come on, haggle with me a little more.
Okay, fine! I'll help you out!
Come on, now, jeez...
If I keep acting tough,
I'll just be in the hospital longer.
The only one losing out is me.
I can't be nice to my girls
with my body in this condition,
so I'm getting worried and lonely lately,
thinking that they might leave me.
This all happened because I got
into an accident to begin with,
so I've got nothing against you.
So hurry up and fix me up, will ya?
These injuries are killing me!
I already fixed you up using Shining Diamond.
Huh?
You know...
I really am a hot, beautiful guy.
Saying that I resemble a Michelangelo
sculpture would be putting it lightly.
But you know, I think my eyes are
a bit droopier than before...
Can your Stand actually fix me up 100%?
Stop complaining!
More importantly, just how well
does your sense of smell work?
Let's see... I mean,
I don't want you to think of me
like some hunting dog, but...
Sniff
For example, I can tell that three girls
are walking up the hall right now.
This smell is Reiko, Akemi, and Yoshie.
They're my groupies.
And I can also tell they're coming
here from the pachinko parlor.
Yu! How are you feeling?
Ah, Yu! Yu is out of bed!
Yo.
Are you all better, Yu?
Yu!
There, there, my cute little kittens.
You're Josuke!
What the hell are you doing here?
Looking for an ass whooping?
Hey, stop. I have nothing
against Josuke anymore.
More importantly, you guys were
just playing pachinko, right?
Huh?
How did you know?
Your skirts reek of sweat around the ass.
The only reason you guys
would sit on a vinyl chair
for a long time would be pachinko.
Akemi, you have chocolate?
You won at pachinko, didn't you?
You're right! You're amazing, Yu.
Here, these are for you.
As you can see,
I'm the man I am because of these girls.
You fixed my injuries, so I'll help you out.
You said you're not like a hunting dog?
You're more than that, Yuya Fungami!
July 15th (Thurs)  12:05 PM
What's the matter?
The floor upstairs is also burnt, right?
I'll give you an estimate,
so please, go ahead.
What's with him?
Why does he go to such
lengths to hide his back?
What's going to happen if I see it?
I-I want to see it!
At this point, I can't help wanting to look!
Even if it means tricking him...
Oh, it itches... It itches...
But I can't quite reach it.
Would it be rude if I asked someone
I just met to scratch my back?
That's fine...
July 15th (Thurs)  12:38 PM
This is it.
This is where we found just
Koichi's bag lying on the ground.
Koichi's house is less than two minutes away.
How did this new Stand user attack
Koichi and take him away
on his way to school?
No one saw him.
Josuke...
Our deal doesn't include me fighting, right?
You just want me to track, right?
I don't have to fight the enemy, right, Josuke?
Why are you asking that now?
You were already being followed.
It's that man.
I smell the same scent
as Koichi from that man.
He has something of Koichi's on him!
What? That bastard over there?
Wait! Come back here!
You bastard! What did you do to Koichi?!
M-Mom?
Mom!
This is definitely my mom.
She's unconscious, but she's alive.
I was watching from here,
but I couldn't tell...
When did he change into Josuke's mom?
I heard that Jotaro can
stop time for two seconds,
but this is nothing like that!
Jotaro wouldn't be able to bring in
a random person from nowhere!
If he had come after me directly,
I wouldn't have minded
just knocking him out...
But that bastard went after my mom...
Guys like that are unforgivable!
Guys who play dirty tricks like this!
Yuya! Where is he?
Where'd the bastard disappear to?!
If you were touching him and don't know,
then how would I know?
B-But he's still here, Josuke...
He's nearby. His scent hasn't cleared yet!
Hmm... Yuya Fungami, huh?
It's a bit surprising that
his nose works that well.
Though I was fine with getting caught
when I started following him, anyway.
I was planning on bringing out
Josuke's mother, either way...
In order to observe Josuke.
Observe...
My Stand, Misterioso, observes.
Misterioso carefully observes
Koichi Hirose and your mother, as well.
July 15th (Thurs)  7:37 AM
That kid seriously pisses me off.
I'll just eat his pudding, then!
Josuke! So you were still home.
You're here, right?
These are
your panties
Everyone feels fear.
It's no use trying to hide your
feelings or expressions of fear.
The fear that lies deep within one's heart
can never be erased...
No matter who you are.
Wh-Who are you? How did you get in here?
I just figured it out now by watching you,
but you seem to have a habit of
swallowing your saliva when
you're scared, don't you?
Everyone shows some kind of subconscious
sign when they're scared.
A habit displayed when they're truly scared...
Have you never realized it?
I'm asking you who you are!
I'm not giving you any money!
Get the hell out of here!
Do I look like a burglar to you?
I don't want your money.
Actually, I'd prefer to pay you.
After all, I'm having so much fun right now.
I'm having such fun with
the attention you're giving me.
The fact that you're giving me
attention out of fear, that is.
Gulp
Oh? You swallowed again, didn't you?
See? You just swallowed again!
That's definitely the sign that you're scared!
And once the sign of your fear is discovered,
my Misterioso completes
its invincible attack!
I was able to turn Tomoko Higashikata,
Tomoko
Higashikata
as well as Koichi Hirose, into paper with ease!
Koichi
Hirose
When I slightly startled
Koichi on his way to school,
his sign of fear was blinking twice.
I could tell immediately.
Yuya, I'm asking you where
the scent is coming from!
No matter how tough Josuke
is, I thought that he'd
be scared if I brought out
his mom all of a sudden, but...
Sure enough, I saw Josuke's sign.
Josuke definitely bites his
lower lip when he's scared!
Ba-dump
The next time Josuke gets
scared and shows that sign,
Misterioso will eliminate
Josuke from this world!
Yuya, you keep looking at my mom.
Could it be...
Is it this jacket? Is there
something inside the pockets?
I don't know what kind of Stand
it is, but is it in this pocket?
Oh? Is he going to bite his lower lip?!
Come on, bite it!
Yuya, answer me! Is he in here?!
Damn! Looks like he's not scared yet.
Josuke, I didn't promise to help you fight.
I only promised I would track.
Going any further is way too dangerous.
I accepted this deal because
you fixed my injuries,
but only a fool would put
himself in danger after that.
I'm sorry, but that guy is too creepy!
Then I'll have to see for myself.
There's nothing in there.
Both pockets are empty.
Other than this piece of paper...
The scent is no longer in the pocket...
Could it be...
Don't! If I were you, I wouldn't
unfold that piece of paper!
Episode 33
July 15th (Thurs), Part 3