Jeez...
Damn it, this pisses me off.
Now, where did I put it?
Anjuro Katagiri, a.k.a. Angelo.
He's become the most awful and
disgusting criminal in Japan's history.
He's repeatedly committed murders
ever since he was 12.
His last murder...
Milkman! Watch your step over there!
...was lower than dog shit.
In March of 1994,
he happened to meet three 14-year-olds.
He raped and murdered two of them.
Did you step in it?
Yes, it appears so.
Seriously, it pisses me off.
Letting their dog shit in front
of someone else's house...
I'm really thinking of keeping it
and putting it in the owner's
pocket tomorrow morning.
Um... I left your milk over there.
I'll be off now.
You...
You're not the usual milkman.
Yes, I'm just covering this morning.
Huh...
Because the third boy was from a rich family,
he demanded a ransom.
That's what led to his arrest.
I might just be picky, but the
seal on this milk's lid is broken.
Huh?
Is it?
Yeah, right here!
Oh, yeah...
See? It's broken, right?
Yeah. Sorry about that.
I'll be going now.
Thanks.
Good day.
Damn that bitch!
Glob
That woman's pretty watchful.
If that woman or her brat,
Josuke, drank this milk,
my Stand, Aqua Necklace,
could have possessed them!
Another one? You just keep going, don't you?
When the police infiltrated the area
where the boy was being held,
they found a truly horrific sight.
The boy was dead, and his privates
had been chopped off and
nailed to a pillar near the corpse.
Why the hell didn't you
clean up your dog's shit?
On top of that, you just threw your
cigarette on the ground, didn't you?
Don't get cocky!
Because those who get cocky...
can just swallow my Stand and die.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 2  Josuke Higashikata! Meets Angelo
So it seemed like that Stand
had possessed the robber...
Or rather, it was just in his body.
It didn't attack me.
Was Angelo nearby? The guy in the picture.
No, I didn't see him.
Damn it, my hair's not setting right.
Listen up. That Stand's power is weak,
but it can be controlled remotely.
It's the type that can somehow enter people.
I'm heading to your house now.
Huh? Right now?
Don't eat or drink anything until I get there.
That includes tap water.
Don't shower or use the bathroom, either. Got it?
Hold on a second. I haven't
told my mom about you yet.
My mom's pretty tough, but it seems
that she still loves Joseph Joestar,
and cries when she thinks about him.
She'll know who you are with one look.
Josuke, where did this picture come from?
This is the milkman from earlier...
Do you know him?
Hey, Josuke. What's wrong?
Crap! I was too late.
I just saw that thing go into
my mom's mouth from the coffee!
Hello? Josuke? Hey! Josuke!
Josuke, you want some coffee, too?
Yeah, sure. Could you put in
some milk and sugar for me?
Milk and sugar, right?
Do-
Boom
Josuke? Was it milk and sugar?
Yeah.
Hello? Jotaro?
I caught that Stand, but...
What?
What should I do with it?
How in the hell...
Be careful. Angelo should be watching
over your house from somewhere.
Don't take your eyes off that Stand.
I'll be right there.
Angelo,
Criminal
Condemned
to Death,
Escapes
There's no doubt that Angelo was
able to escape prison and death row
because he used his Stand.
But I still don't know the specifics
of that Stand's power.
Dead ball!
And that's the game!
The game ends with a dead ball!
There, there.
You little shit!
Josuke! You need to get going,
or you'll be late!
I'll kill them both!
That little brat and his hot mom!
Yup!
I need to either get the cap off
or break open this bottle, somehow...
He's...
I'm home. You really feel it when
you work the night shift at my age.
Higashikata...
Come to think of it, it's the same name.
So this is Officer Higashikata's house.
I haven't seen him since I was 12.
Talk about memories.
I know everything about you!
Freeze.
Josuke, why aren't you at school?
Are you allowed to take
your gun home, Gramps?
Oh, shush! Answer me.
I-I'm going! I'm just waiting for someone.
You fool. This is just a model gun.
You scaredy-cat.
I guess I win the first round in our
weekly contest to scare each other.
Yeah, yeah. I lose.
Hm? What's wrong? You're not
even trying to argue this time.
Nothing. Mom already left.
You should go to bed.
You're tired, aren't you?
Now, our next story.
News Bureau
7 Bodies Found In Park
The number of strange deaths occurring
due to the center of the eye or ear
being destroyed has risen to
seven as of this morning.
The police are trying to get to the
bottom of these bizarre deaths,
which have only occurred in Morioh.
They're trying to determine if they
were caused by illness or accident.
I've heard about this.
It definitely reeks of foul play to me.
I can't help but feel like someone really
dangerous is hiding in this city.
Gramps...
Morioh's masterpiece, beef tongue in miso.
He's here...
I know you well, Higashikata.
After you finish your night shift,
you always enjoy a shot of brandy.
Josuke, grab the bottle and get in the car.
Let's take it somewhere isolated.
Right.
G-Gramps...
Josuke Higashikata, this is all your fault!
It's all your fault for not
keeping your eyes on me.
You got too cocky!
It cheers me up
when I see cocky guys step
into the depths of despair!
That was close! That power is incredible...
You're still being cocky!
I'll kill you, whatever it takes!
You hear? Whatever it takes!
Gramps opened the cap on the bottle.
But there's nothing to worry about.
It's just a minor wound. My Stand can easily...
All fixed.
It can't be...
He should wake up.
My Stand can heal wounds.
I've done it lots of times since I was a kid.
I even fixed my friend's broken bone...
Hey, Gramps! I'm gonna be mad
if you're messing around.
Did you really fall asleep because
you had the night shift?
You don't need to try to scare me anymore!
Gramps! Gramps!
Josuke...
The wound's been completely...
It can be said that humans live by destroying.
In the midst of all that, your power
is kinder than anything else.
But once a life is taken,
it doesn't come back.
No matter the Stand, it can't bring it back.
For 35 years, he protected this
city as a police officer.
He sensed the danger here,
and when he heard news about
murders that sounded like Angelo's work,
he had the eyes of a man who
was protecting his city.
Angelo has killed many.
There must be several bodies
of people from this city
that haven't been found yet.
There's no reason for his murders.
It's a hobby to him.
And he'll keep killing, I'm sure.
He's probably going to start
by killing you and your mom.
I'll...
I'll protect this city and
my mom in his place.
No matter what happens.
A
Aqua
Aqua Ne
Aqua Nec
Aqua Neck
Aqua Neckla
Aqua Necklace
An
Anju
Anjuro
Anjuro Kata
Anjuro Katagiri
The funeral has ended,
and his uniform hangs in the closet.
And behind it, the shoes, socks, shirts,
and pants of a middle-aged man,
who would say, "What? This is what I like,"
are neatly folded and lined up.
But eventually, they will
probably be disposed of.
Because, despite his daughter
not wanting to throw them away
since they hold such dear memories,
no one will ever wear them again.
Josuke probably doesn't
want to see anyone right now.
Everything but canned drinks
and foods is dangerous,
so don't consume anything else.
How's your mom?
I had her go to a relative's
house after the funeral.
Good idea. She can come back
after we kick Angelo's ass.
I'm not pissed off or anything.
I just got a little worked up for a moment.
I'm calm. Completely calm.
Calm, huh?
Well, this is your furniture,
so it's up to you if you want
to take out your anger on it.
By the way, that scar on your lip...
That's from when I punched you.
Can't your Stand heal your wounds?
My Stand can't heal my own wounds.
What if his Stand enters your body and
starts tearing things up from the inside?
I'd probably die.
If it invades me, I lose.
You're gonna try to trap my
Stand in a bottle again?
That ain't happening again, Josuke.
I know your powers very well now.
Tomorrow, or the day after tomorrow...
I'll wait patiently for my chance.
— 3 Days Later —
He's come this close to see what's going on...
But these past three days,
he hasn't made a single move.
What's he waiting for?
It's raining...
Rain?
What the hell?
I thought something seemed odd about you.
So you're a Stand user, too?
Well, whatever. I've been
waiting for this moment.
This house is now mine!
You guys can't leave while it's raining!
Josuke!
He was just here all of a sudden,
boiling the water.
He's twisted the faucet, too.
Angelo's Stand has entered the house.
He wasn't waiting for you to drink the water.
He was waiting for it to rain!
His Stand can move in the rain... No.
It can move freely in liquids.
Josuke! Stay away from that kettle!
The steam is him!
This is just great.
We can't capture him in the bottle.
Stay away from the steam.
If you inhale that, you're in trouble.
Get out of the kitchen.
About that... It seems like it won't even
do any good to get out of here.
Angelo has already made
several holes in the roof.
So it's dangerous to go upstairs,
obviously, or outside.
This is just great...
I never would have thought a power
that uses water could be this terrifying.
He's pretty smart.
What's so funny? We're trapped.
Hey!
I mean, Jotaro...
The guy who killed my Gramps is this close.
This is just great!
Now, then. Let's finish this.
Now, Josuke...
How would you
slip out of this situation?
Slip out?
I wouldn't quite word it like that.
I would break out!
Hurry, this way!
The wall's going to go back to normal.
Good grief.
Well, we've blocked the steam...
The humidifier!
Josuke!
I've won! Just as I thought, Josuke!
I knew you'd break through the
wall and come into this room!
Shit!
When horse races or test answers
end up exactly as I expect,
I can't help but feel lucky from the
bottom of my heart and laugh.
It just bubbles out!
Josuke!
What Angelo just said is wrong, Jotaro.
Josuke?
Even when things end up exactly as I expect,
I don't feel like laughing...
Not when it comes to Angelo.
That's...
Got it. Sorry, it's a bit gross.
I shredded up a rubber glove
and swallowed it beforehand.
I see. It appears the user's body is over there.
Sh-Shit!
So you're...
...Angelo.
Damn it!
Y-You guys aren't going to kill me, are you?!
Sure, I'm an escaped death row inmate.
But just because I was found
guilty by Japanese law
doesn't mean you guys have
the right to judge me!
Josuke! I killed your grandpa,
but you have no right to kill me!
If you kill me, you'll end up
a cursed soul, just like me!
Don't go telling people what
they can and can't do.
M-M-My right hand! My hand!
No one's going to execute you.
Not me, and not Jotaro, either.
You're not going to be executed,
and you're not going back to jail.
Josuke, I'll leave the rest to you.
Wh-What do you plan to do
with me, you bastards?!
Repent for eternity, Angelo!
For all of those you killed,
including my Gramps!
You're gonna live forever in the
city my Gramps protected.
The Angelo Stone.
Morioh Landmark 1
The Angelo Stone
Directions  One minute's walk from Morioh Johzenji Street Bus Stop #3
The Angelo Stone is known as a landmark,
and a place where lovers meet.
It's admired by the people of the city,
despite its creepy appearance.
He really is pretty crazy.
Good grief...
Episode 3
The Nijimura Brothers, Part 1