This is Morioh Radio.
Your host, once again, is me,
your neighbor, Kai Harada.
Now, then...
Look at those smooth spokes
shining as they spin!
Last week's topic was, "The King of Terror is
supposed to come from the sky this July.
This mountain bike was a gift to
celebrate me getting into high school.
What are the citizens of
Morioh going to do?"
Getting new stuff is always exciting.
All right, let's get to the replies.
This one's from "RIP Big Bro."
I'm not gonna be able to take
the bus to school for a while!
I wonder what happened to his big bro?
O-Ow...
Wh-What the heck?
There's a bag in the middle of the road.
I-It can't be! The thing in that bag was...
Wh-What am I gonna do?! I ran it over!
I-I couldn't help it!
It was in the middle of the road!
There was nothing I could've done!
Precisely.
You're not the one at fault here.
That was just an unfortunate accident.
The guy who put the kitten in a bag
and left it in the road is at fault.
Talk about a terrible thing to do.
W-We have to treat its injuries!
It's no use.
You don't hear it crying, do you?
It's dead.
What's your name?
My name's Tamami Kobayashi,
and I graduated from
your school two years ago.
That's a nice bike.
You a first-year?
Y-Yes. My name's Koichi Hirose.
Ah, high school, eh? Takes me back.
Things were good back then.
Well, have a seat, Hirose.
Huh? B-But...
Just shut up and sit down.
So... I've got an idea.
I'll bury that cat for you,
so give me a little money. Okay?
Hey! Are you listening?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Hey, now. Quit messing around.
It's true that this wasn't your fault,
but are you planning to do
nothing about killing my cat?
Did you say it was your cat?
That's right.
Y-You put the kitten o-over there?
That's not the problem anymore.
I'm asking you if you're really
gonna do nothing about it and go.
You're the one that killed it, bro.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 6  Koichi Hirose (Reverb)
Hey, you're feeling guilty, right?
If your heart could be freed
from the shackles of guilt by paying some cash...
Wouldn't it be better to just pay up?
Right?
Money
Wh-What's this lock-looking thing?!
It's heavy!
Huh? You can see that?
Then this should go even faster, Hirose.
Th-This is a Stand!
A Stand's inside my body!
Hey, Josuke.
Isn't that Koichi standing over there?
Yeah, that's definitely Koichi.
That kid hangs out with shady-looking
characters all the time.
But he looks like he's having fun.
I met a guy named Keicho Nijimura
about four months ago,
and obtained this ability.
I had no idea what was going on,
but man, I was happy.
I figured that if I could
use this ability properly,
it could support me for the rest of my life.
Now...
Come on, cough it up.
These shackles won't come
off if you don't pay up.
I-I don't...
have any money.
Huh... You looked away just now, didn't you?
W-Well...
I-It's heavy!
I can't even stand anymore!
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
It's not nice to lie, you know.
You felt bad about lying, didn't you?
The more guilt you feel,
the bigger the lock becomes.
These shackles are the weight of your sins.
It's automatic.
Even if I'm sleeping, or if you try to
run far away, it's never coming off.
All right? If you get it,
then show me your wallet.
Come on.
What the heck? You should have just
given me this in the first place.
You have 7,000 yen!
Th-That's for buying sneakers
for gym class today.
Sneakers?
Go barefoot!
What are you doing over there?
J-Josuke and Okuyasu!
A grown man trying to threaten
a high school kid for money?
Try getting a job to earn your money.
Now, look! You little boys stay out of this!
Oh, we can't do that.
Not when there's some smelly trash
around, using some petty Stand.
We've got to take out that trash properly.
Hey...
This seriously isn't coming off.
Whoa, wait... You guys can see it, too?
Just how many of you can see that?
That's what I want to know.
But right now, that doesn't matter.
Would you kindly take that lock off of him?
Hey, you little brats!
Don't underestimate me!
I'm not playing games here!
Sinners must pay for their sins.
That's the rule of society.
Or what? You're going to
pay me instead of Koichi?
Then I'll let you off the hook.
Money's money to me.
Oh? You're gonna try to get money from me?
Just try it, damn it!
Wait! You just took 7,000 yen for me!
That was the fee for lying to me!
Huh?!
You're trying to pay for that poor
kitten's life with just 7,000 yen?
That just won't do.
I'll take about five hundred grand for that.
Five hundred grand?!
Come on, five hun—
Shut up, you little shit!
O-Okuyasu!
Hey, don't push it.
Shut yer trap, you dumbass.
We told you to give his 7,000 yen
back, so give it back, you dipshit!
Slip
O-Ow! My front tooth!
Wh-Why the hell did you wobble around
and fall over on your own?
On my own? That's so cruel!
How dare you say that after hitting me?!
My front tooth's gone. You're so cruel!
H-Hey, wait a sec... Are you okay?
Wait, Okuyasu...
Don't feel any guilt toward him!
H-He did it on purpose!
Front teeth are pretty expensive, you know...
Since I don't have insurance.
Wh-Why, you...
Whoa, now! Don't try anything funny with me.
If anyone who's got my lock on them
tries to damage me in any way,
it goes right back to that lock.
Y-You bastard...
Hey. Is the kitten that
you said Koichi ran over
this thing?
A s-stuffed animal?
Here, let me see. I picked
up your front tooth for you.
It's all better.
It's gone!
Yay! My heart feels so much lighter now!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Hey, aren't you forgetting the 7,000 yen?
All right! I'll give it back.
Once the money's down, hurry up
and get out of here, dumbass!
I-I'm saved... Ah!
Th-The bills... H-He took them!
He took the big parts that
the bank would exchange!
Th-That bastard...
Unforgivable! Even if it's not my money.
Damn. I was only able to get 7,000 yen.
Don't think you're gonna get away with that.
Just you wait.
Aw, man...
My day started off with something
terrible, so I was down the whole day.
I'm home, Police.
Hey, you alive? Woof, woof.
I'm home.
I've heard all about you around town, ma'am.
They say you're beautiful, kind, and so refined.
You can't be serious.
I wouldn't lie!
Really?
Of course!
Wh-Why is he in my house
rubbing my mom's shoulders?!
The
The Lock
Tama
Tamami
Tamami Koba
Tamami Kobayashi
Y-You!
What are you doing here?!
Oh, Ko, you're back. Hi!
I-I asked you wh-what you were doing here!
This gentleman delivered
the money you dropped.
Huh?!
Seven thousand yen.
You must've been in a hurry.
Th-This money... You told her you found it?
That's right. You ran into Mr. Kobayashi
on your bike today, didn't you?
Wha...
I made sure you got your money back, Koichi.
A-And you should have!
Ko, why are you so worked up?
Ma'am, this is hard for me to say,
but it appears that I dropped my wallet
when we ran into each other, too.
It looks just like this one.
Which means our wallets got swapped.
Do you understand what I'm saying, ma'am?
Y-Yes, though that seems very unusual.
But I guess it's possible.
So I'd like you to tell Koichi
to return my wallet to me.
It had about five hundred thousand yen in it.
Please tell him to give it back to me.
What?!
F-Five hundred thousand?!
So that's it!
I see your scheme now!
K-Ko...
Don't panic! He's a con artist!
They're all lies!
Oh, that's right.
I can prove that our wallets got switched.
Last night, I had a
hamburger combo at Jonny's.
And... Oh, yes. I added an
order of onion gratin soup...
So I believe the total on
the receipt was 1,833 yen.
It should be tucked away
in the wallet Koichi has.
K-Ko!
N-No! Mom, please believe me!
This is a trick!
You did this earlier, didn't you?!
And then you went out of your
way to buy a similar wallet!
I hate to say this, but your son, though
I'm sure it's just a phase, is pretty rotten.
Don't you feel guilty as his mother
for raising a son like that?
Stop!
M-Mom!
I finally did it!
Now the weight of her guilt
won't allow her heart to be free.
I'm gonna take you for everything you've got.
First, I'll take this house's land, title, and seal.
What a great house this is.
Koichi,
is something wrong?
Sis!
Wh-What?!
Earlier, when she brought me tea,
I made her spill some on my hand,
and then acted like it really burned.
She kept apologizing so much.
She was so cute and sexy.
So she's a third-year at a girls' school?
R-Ripe for the picking.
A-A-Awesome!
How dare you?
You won't get away with this! I won't let you!
What the hell?
What's up with that puny egg thing?
What the hell is that?!
Mom, Sis, please leave the room for a while.
Ko, what's happening?
Please, don't ask any questions now.
Hey! K-Keep that thing away from me!
Your mom and sister leaving the room
doesn't change the fact that
th-they're my hostages!
I won't let you harm my mom or sister.
J-Just try it, Koichi! Just try!
Take the locks off of them!
If your mom sees you beating
the crap out of me,
her guilt is just gonna grow more and more!
I told you to take them off!
Don't underestimate Tamami
Kobayashi, you pissy little shit!
L-Like hell I'll take them off!
Crack!
Huh? What?
That didn't hurt.
Huh?
Smack!
Whoa! What's this?
The sound is impressive,
but it's actually super weak!
What the hell is with your Stand?
It doesn't have any speed or power at all!
How dare you scare me
like that, you dumbass?!
I'll show you that a Stand's strength
comes from how strong you are mentally!
Crack!
Which means your mental strength is zero!
I'm gonna make sure you pay dearly for this!
S-Something strange is
going on with his cheek!
"Cr-ack"?
It looks like a manga sound effect.
Crack!
Wh-What the heck? I hear a
weird ringing in my ears!
Like the sound I heard when I got hit...
Smack
What the hell is this writing on my arm?!
I-It won't come off!
Smack!
Crack!
W-Wait... Th-These sounds that
I hear coming from inside me...
Your Stand did that?!
Damn it! Get rid of this sound!
Smack
Boom!
Smack!
Crack!
It's the sound.
My Stand makes the sound
resonate from inside his body.
C-Come to think of it, there was that famous
Basho Matsuo poem I learned at school...
So quiet and still
The shrill of the cicadas
Seeps into the rocks
"So quiet and still,
the shrill of the cicadas
seeps into the rocks."
Smack!
Crack!
Boom!
Damn it! I totally fell for it!
If you take the locks off my mom
and sister, I'll stop the sound.
If you keep resisting,
even I don't know what will happen to your body.
Stop this sound!
Dogyaa
Stop being stubborn and take off those locks!
Damn it! How dare you do this to me?!
Smack!
Crack!
Boom!
Dogyaa!
Like I could threaten and con if I was
afraid of a little brat like you!
The "Tama" in my name means "ballsy"!
I'll show you just how ballsy I am!
I'm not scared of some knife!
Don't take me lightly!
I'll show you how terrifying I can be!
The true fear of the locks!
Ow!
What?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Make the cut shallow, and scream like hell!
Toss!
"Toss"?
What was that scream?
What's wrong?
Ko?!
I-It's not what it looks like!
C-Crap!
Yes!
K-Ko! How could you do
something so terrifying?!
No, Mom! t's not what it looks like!
No!
Sis!
I win! You lose!
Hurry up and stop this sound, Koichi!
If you don't stop this sound,
your mom won't be able to
bear the weight of her guilt.
When humans can't bear the
weight of their sins anymore,
they think they'd be better off dead.
I-I can't... anymore!
Mom!
I can't live any longer!
Stop acting tough!
Hurry and stop this sound! Are you
gonna let your mom kill herself?!
No, I won't stop the sound.
I'll do the opposite, and make more sound!
Believe in me!
What?!
!em ni eveileB
Believe in me, Mom!
Believe in me!
Believe!
Mom!
Believe in me!
This is a matter of the soul!
Like hell she'll believe you!
Mom...
He's right... If I, his own mother,
won't believe in him,
then who will?
Koichi's always been a nice boy.
He would never hurt anyone
or take their money.
Yes!
Sh-Shit!
Mom!
D-Damn it!
Usually, they'd never believe...
My parents would never believe in me!
Gulp...
It was just a joke!
Ko, it was all just a joke!
Take the lock off my sister, too.
It's already off!
We can't do anything to harm her beauty, right?
I was only kidding about taking your house!
I even gave back your 7,000 yen,
didn't I? Right? Right?
Please forgive me!
I'll do anything, Master Koichi!
What? You'll do anything?
Yes, Master Koichi! Anything!
I'll be your underling!
All right, then...
Make sure you bring me five
hundred grand by tomorrow.
It's a joke. It's only a little joke.
Th-That didn't sound like a joke!
H-Hey, Okuyasu! What the
hell is going on here?
Allow me to carry your bag to school!
You're seriously going to carry it?
But of course!
Master Koichi! You're a true man among men!
Oh, stop it.
Hey, Okuyasu!
Don't ask me! I'm not smart, remember?
Episode 7
Toshikazu Hazamada (Show Off)