I swear I'll save you,
so wait for me, Rohan!
So it learned my scent?
It's going to chase me forever,
and as soon as it touches me,
it'll suck out my nutrients?
Yes!
That thing can't go faster than 60km/h!
This bike'll have no problem beating that.
But how the hell am I
supposed to find the user?
I guess I'll sort out everything
I know about him first.
First, why did he set up
a trap inside the tunnel?
It would have been easier to
ambush us from the roadside.
Second, I think there's more
to his sucking out nutrients.
There's got to be a reason for that tunnel.
I've got to check out that tunnel!
I need information about
the Futatsumori Tunnel!
Koichi!
I need to call Koichi and have
him use Reverb to find the user!
Now, now. What's the matter? There, there...
All right. There should be plenty
of distance between us now.
Where's my card?
Y-You can't be serious!
Why'd it suddenly appear?
I ran away at 80km/h,
and it was going 60km/h.
Even doing simple math,
it should have taken another
two minutes to get here.
That thing is a Stand.
It can appear and disappear freely...
He managed to make it appear
somewhere near where I am,
and now it's going to accurately
attack me by following my scent!
S-Sixty kilometers...
Wh-What?!
Shit! A baby carriage!
What's the matter with you?
You're so fussy...
If I slow down, I'm gonna die.
Rohan will die, as well.
Sorry, but I'm gonna have to ride through.
I have to just bust through!
But, Shining Diamond!
Fix.
Good!
I'll never be able to make
a phone call like this!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 29     Highway Go Go, Part 2
Listen up, Yoshioka.
In one minute,
you will receive a very
important call on your phone.
This is a deal worth one billion!
You'd better not mess this up!
I'm counting on you, Yoshioka!
Y-Yes, sir! Please leave it to me.
This is it! This cell phone!
It just happened to show up
at the perfect time. Lucky me!
I will do my absolute best!
Talk about a silver lining!
Hello?
Huh?
Gah! One billion yen!
Did that happen when I grabbed it?
My silver lining just broke!
If you hate me, just hang up on me!
H-How can you say that, Minayo?
Say it! Ask her to marry you!
Minayo, will you m-marry—
Man, I think I might be lucky today.
Huh? What? What is it, Akira?
Talk about good timing!
Hello, Hirose residence.
Koichi!
So that's what's happening.
If I don't find the user,
I'm gonna get killed.
I think it's a guy who has some kind of
obsession or grudge with that tunnel.
Are there any incidents
involving that tunnel?
Th-There is. It's in the
paper from two days ago.
I saw the news on TV, too.
Some thug on a motorcycle was driving drunk
and crashed into the tunnel's entrance.
John Doe is unconscious and in critical
condition with injuries all over his body.
He's undergoing intensive care
at Budogaoka Hospital now.
Sounds like he's a victim of the Stand, too.
Anyone else?
W-Wait a sec.
When I saw the scene of the accident
on TV, there was blood all over.
Th-That Stand is one that
sucks up nutrients, right?
This sounds like a different injury.
Isn't it possible that the John Doe
who's in critical condition
could be the Stand user?
He needs nutrients from other
people to heal himself...
What? I-It's the ocean!
If I keep going straight, I'll be in trouble!
I need to turn somewhere, or I'm
gonna plunge into the ocean!
That corner!
I'll have to take it going more than 60km/h!
Hello? Josuke? What's wrong?
Koichi! Keep me on the line. Don't hang up!
Here I go, damn it!
Crap! I might crash!
No.
I can do this right now.
I can make this turn.
I will make this turn, damn it!
Yes! I made the turn!
Did you see how I hung in there?! Take that!
Wh-What?!
The ocean's on this side, too!
No Entry
It's Morioh Harbor!
Shining Diamond!
Now for the crumbled wall...
Fix it!
Th-That was close...
It was trying to head straight toward me,
so it couldn't see this wall.
Like a mosquito that can't see a screen,
it's following me by scent alone.
It doesn't have the ability
to think or plan its attacks.
Its only goal is to take nutrients from me.
The theory that this guy's the critically
injured patient makes sense.
Everything fits together.
Josuke!
Koichi, the hospital!
That John Doe must be the Stand user!
Find out his name for me.
Got it.
But, man, this situation is heavy...
H-How am I supposed to get out of this?
How far did he go? That little shit Josuke...
When this arrow wanted to
pierce a motorcycle thug
who was about to die after an accident,
I was wondering what the
hell it was thinking, but...
This is amazing! Just amazing!
Who would have thought he would
create this amazing Highway Go Go?
A Stand ability is all about
the user's mental strength!
The hungrier someone is,
the stronger they are!
No one can defeat the power of a man
so hungry to heal his own injuries.
But I really would have
loved to see Josuke die!
What should I do? What should I do?
A culvert!
I'm glad I found a culvert
that drains into the ocean,
but it just keeps getting closer and closer.
H-How am I going to get out of here?
Wh-Which way should I go?
Um... The ocean is behind me,
which means it's also to my right.
The ocean is definitely bad news.
The left is the way I came from... I think.
Wh-Which way do I go now?
I think the left might be the ocean,
but if I go to the right...
Th-There's the middle, too...
Wh-What's happening?
I'm pressing the gas, but
the speed keeps dropping...
I-Is it breaking down?
Wh-What?! It's not broken?
Then why am I losing speed?
I'm gonna stop!
I-It's coming!
Could it be...
Am I out of gas?
Man, don't scare me like that.
I'm just out of gas...
Then there's no problem at all.
I thought it was some
major malfunction that even
Shining Diamond couldn't fix.
This isn't a problem.
There'll be no problem escaping this.
Still no problem.
I can fix this with no problem.
And the motorcycle, too, of course.
I can't get too relaxed
since that thing teleports,
but gasoline is not a problem.
But it seems
that I do have a problem after all...
I'm lost!
Wh-Which way is the hospital?
H
Hi
Hig
High
Highw
Highwa
Highway
Highway G
Highway Go
Highway Go G
Highway Go Go
Budogaoka
General Hospital
Pardon me. I'm in a huge hurry.
I'd like to know which room
the young man who caused
the motorcycle accident at
Futatsumori Tunnel is in.
What's his room number?
Please tell me!
Now, listen...
Can you not see what's written there?
Huh?
Visiting hours are over for the day
If you need an eye exam,
you can come in after 9:30 AM tomorrow.
Um, I'm not actually here to visit him.
But there's a reason I need to know his name!
Please, tell me!
Didn't you hear me tell you to go home?
Worthless brats like you are such a bother.
You seem pretty short for
a motorcycle gang member.
Do your feet even reach the ground?
Jeez.
Act 3...
Okay, Master! Let's kill da ho!
Beeetch!
O-Oh, no!
That was close...
These medicines costs 50,000 yen a bottle.
Huh?
They're heavy?!
They're going to fall!
Hey, you! Help me! Hold me up!
Um, by "Hey, you!" did you mean me?
Yes! Who else is here?! This is really heavy!
Well, yeah, but still...
You did just tell me to go home.
Not to mention, I'm so short,
I don't know if I can reach.
Are you going to get in trouble
with your boss if those break?
Then you're going to be like,
"Oh my gah!" Isn't it?
All right, fine! I'll tell you!
He's in room 525!
Yuya Fungami is in 525.
Take that elevator to the fifth floor!
Huh?
Josuke!
Koichi...
Did you find out where he is, Koichi?
Room 525! His name is Yuya Fungami!
It's room 525!
Thanks, Koichi!
It's on the fifth floor!
Hurry and get into the elevator!
Sh-Shit...
I-It just keeps coming in!
Koichi! Reverb Act 3!
You really are a guy I can
count on. Thanks, Koichi!
But 3 Freeze can only attack
one place at a time.
The rest of them are following Josuke!
There it is! Room 525!
I'm finally here!
The vent!
You bastard!
It's only a few more
meters to the room...
This distance is a pain!
I'm just gonna cut through
and kick your ass!
Damn it!
I'm going to get there, no matter what!
I'm going to get there
and kick your ass...
Who the hell is that brat?
This is Yu's room!
Don't mistake it for your own, you dumbass!
Don't worry about him.
You okay?
I thought it had been a while
since I got nutrients from that
first guy in the tunnel, but...
So you're the second one I've
been chasing around, huh?
I'm surprised you really made it here.
I'm a little shocked, actually.
Yu, you know this guy?
Huh?
Nah, I don't know him,
and I don't give a shit.
Great job, Highway Go Go.
I've healed up quite a bit.
If I can get nutrients from two or three
more guys with abilities like his,
I'll be fully recovered.
Hey!
We told you not to lay your lazy ass down there!
And I just told you not to worry about him!
More importantly, come over here
and give me some attention.
Little ol' me can't even move yet.
I really have to take a piss.
My bladder's super full.
Ooh! That's my job!
We promised we'd all take turns doing that!
It's my turn this time!
What? No, it's me!
I don't care who it is.
Just hurry up and bring the
urine bottle and help me go.
Okay!
Then I'll...
Hey, Akemi.
That peach is rotten.
Peel a different one.
How can you tell it's rotten?
Why? Because it reeks.
It totally smells rotten.
From over there?
You've got a point.
I think my nose suddenly
got much more sensitive.
Oh, you're right... It really is rotten.
One of you three is on your period, right?
Am I wrong? Someone's
on her period, right?
Huh?
Ha, so it's you, Yoshie!
Looks like I was right.
And one of you is also really
pissed off right now, huh?
When you get mad or excited,
your body releases adrenaline,
and I can smell it.
What the hell are you mad about?
Is it you, Reiko?
Huh? I'm not mad.
We're all really happy that
you're feeling better, Yu.
Yeah, we're super happy!
There's no reason for any of us to be mad.
Hey, hey, something's not right.
It totally reeks of someone being pissed off.
Don't lie to me.
Which one of you is mad?
It's me!
I'm the one who reeks of all that adrenaline!
Impossible!
You should be completely dried up by now!
How the hell are you standing?
That's because...
You were drinking my IV fluid?
It wasn't much, but I replenished myself.
Release Rohan, the guy you're
holding captive in the tunnel!
You fool!
Highway Go Go still remembers your scent!
Yu!
You three, don't move!
My name is Josuke Higashikata.
My Stand's name is Shining Diamond.
Though its target range is small,
it can throw punches faster than
a ho-hum speed like 60km/h.
I've never actually measured it,
but if it gets closer,
it can go about 300km/h.
Hey, stop! Wait!
M-My spine is still broken.
My arms and legs are still
broken and I'm bedridden.
I'm critically injured!
And you're saying that you're
going to hurt pitiful ol' me?
All right, my bad.
I'll free the guy in the tunnel.
I think he's still alive.
If you replenish his nutrients,
I think he'll live...
S-So...
You wouldn't do something
as cowardly as kicking
an injured person's ass, would you?
That's not something a man would do!
Yeah! That's cowardly!
Oh, I see.
It's true that I probably
wouldn't feel too great if
I kicked an injured person's ass.
It's definitely not manly,
and it pains my heart.
Right? The guilt will stick with you
forever if you kick my ass.
I thought about that, so I already fixed you.
Huh?!
Eh?
Can you move?
You can, right?
Your wounds are all healed up, aren't they?
Th-They are...
Right.
I figured if I fixed you up first,
it wouldn't be cowardly at all, would it?
Yuya Fungami continues his hospital stay.
If he ever tries to use Highway Go Go
again to try to heal himself,
Josuke threatens to kick
his ass over and over.
I feel so refreshed.
I feel like it's New Year's morning
after I just put on a fresh pair of underwear.
Yu!
However, it's rather enviable
that he gets to be nursed
back to health by his fangirls.
Meanwhile, Rohan...
Josuke Higashikata...
U-Um, look, Rohan-sensei,
a lot's happened, but I, uh...
Why did you heal me?
Huh?
You meddlesome brat.
I would have rather die
than be saved by you.
Not to mention, you stepped into the
enemy's trap after I told you to run.
How stupid can you be?
Wha—
Just so you know, I don't consider
this a favor I need to return.
...apparently still doesn't
get along with Josuke.
Also...
After all this happened,
Koichi Hirose took his dog for a walk.
H
Hi
Hig
High
Highw
Highwa
Highway
Highway G
Highway Go
Highway Go G
Highway Go Go
Yu
Yuya
Yuya Fun
Yuya Fungami
Ah, that cat's a British Blue.
Where'd you come from, little kitty?
Episode 30
Cats Love Yoshikage Kira