Caesar was the son of Mario Zeppeli,
the best furniture maker in Naples.
Mario was a proper Italian,
dedicated to his family.
To Caesar, he was the ideal man.
When Caesar was ten,
Mario left without a word.
They were motherless, and
distant relatives stole all they had.
Caesar became delinquent
and grew to hate his father.
I bet he's living
carefree with some woman!
I'll find and kill him!
He threw away his youth
and his future.
He committed theft, arson, assault
-- anything short of murder.
Even mafiosos feared him.
Hey, you're Caesar, right?
What's your last name?
I don't have one!
Then you aren't Italian.
Italians are proud of their families.
Never holding back, he started
fights by using a wrench.
With his foe stunned,
he finished them off!
Though he didn't know it,
he was already using Hamon.
Then, at age 16 in Rome...
No mistake. It's him!
Caesar felt he might murder his own father.
However!
W-What is that?!
That's a diamond, all right.
Boy, don't touch that stone!
You!
W-What's this wall doing?!
S-Stay back. It's a trap!
The events of 50 years ago
were unknown to Caesar.
Will, Caesar's grandfather,
had died tragically.
Mario had taken up his torch,
trained with Hamon and
discovered these ruins.
He searched the world for a way
to defeat the monsters within.
But Caesar was totally unaware of this.
Y-Young man, I ask you a favor.
Speak with a woman in Venice
named Lisa Lisa.
She is the only one who can stop them.
Perhaps because Caesar had grown,
Mario did not recognize his son.
Fa...
Caesar's father had left to keep
his children safe from all this.
Father!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 20: Young Caesar
I see.
Caesar's misunderstanding led to hatred.
But that became pride in
his father and his family.
So Caesar picked up
where his father had left off.
He wants to avenge his father.
Forgive me, Caesar.
I didn't mean to speak ill
of your family.
If you want to go in there
despite it being a trap,
then you must have a way
to beat Kars.
I've changed my mind!
If you're going in,
then I'm right behind you,
Caesar Zeppeli!
One set of footprints leads in.
W-Who was that?
I swear I saw someone.
Am I seeing things?
No, that's not an illusion!
What the hell is that!
Caesar?
He vanished!
But I know he's here.
He's within a few steps.
Does Kars have a new trick?
No, the sun is too strong.
He can't be outside!
The cat stance, an element of kung fu.
Caesar has never heard of kung fu.
But he relaxes his limbs,
ready for attack from any direction.
For him, it is a reflex.
Caesar!
What are you doing?
Going in alone is madness!
Stay back, instructor!
I can't move, let alone go inside.
Something is hiding in the entrance!
What's that?
I can't see a--
A-A single footprint.
He jumped!
He's coming from above!
I-It's...
...Wamuu!
Instructor Meshina!
What the hell? That was Wamuu.
Are he and Kars in there together?
But how can Wamuu come out
during the day?!
He does look ghostlike somehow.
Where is that smart-talking upstart?
JoJo...
I hear he's learned much.
Where is the man who killed Master Esidisi?
Wind. Wamuu can control the wind.
That's why he's transparent.
Air is coming from
those pipes in his chest.
It's slightly visible
because of water vapor.
I've got it!
He's cloaking himself in vapor
from those pipes.
It's refracting the light.
It's like a suit that bends light,
protecting him from the sun!
That's why he's transparent!
So JoJo isn't here.
You're Caesar, the bubble-user, right?
Just by looking at you,
I can see you've also learned much.
Very well. You are worthy
of death at my hands!
We'll see who dies!
I feel like I did when I was poor!
Just like when you killed my father!
I'll use my viciousness to destroy you!
Don't think your wind
will just blow my bubbles away!
Some bubbles go through wind!
I've updated
my grandfather's Hamon Cutter!
Bubble Cutter!
High speed rotation
turns the bubbles into disks!
Hamon ensures they won't pop!
The wind protecting you
is just air to them!
Instead of defending you...
...it'll suck them in!
His skill with Hamon
is more than I bargained for.
Now, Hamon-user!
Hold it! I won't let you go inside!
Gliding Bubble Cutter!
Now, while you're off balance...
...I'll give you a Hamon kick!
But Caesar was in for a shock!
If you are tripped, you try not to fall.
Especially if you need
to escape the sunlight.
But Wamuu was different!
He bent backwards!
He's not just an immortal monster!
With senses like that,
he's a fighting genius as well!
But my Bubble Cutter
must have damaged him severely.
The advantage is mine!
I have a way to beat you indoors!
My nerves are honed to a razor edge.
I can even feel differences in the air.
I have the itch like when I was poor.
My breathing is normal.
I'm not sweating.
Perfect Hamon conditions!
Instructor Meshina!
Taken off your coat, have you, Wamuu?
Caesar and Meshina aren't here!
Are they already inside?
T-That's...
What happened?
Take this, Wamuu!
Bubble Launcher!
I said that won't work!
Bubble Cutter!
Running?!
I won't run or hide!
Bubble Cutter!
You're dead, Wamuu!
Gliding Bubble Cutter!
Wamuu!
No more games!
It's over!
Divine Sand--
Stop and look around!
My Bubble Cutters are now
Bubble Lenses floating in the air!
Lenses?
And that hole you knocked in the wall
is like the open shutter of a camera!
The lenses send sunlight...
...into the hotel!
Huh?!
You can't move!
You're film! A frozen image!
You're totally exposed!
Trying your barrier again?
I won't let you!
I'll finish you off
with a direct Hamon blast!
One point...
...at one moment.
A tiny blind spot.
Caesar's body created a shadow
at one point!
Wamuu didn't lose his chance!
He showed Caesar once again
that he was a fighting genius!
Wind power!
Divine Sandstorm!
S-Such destruction!
I-It couldn't be!
It's Wamuu's Divine Sandstorm!
So that means Caesar is...!
You had grown so much.
I am satisfied.
I haven't had such a fight in ages...
...warrior of Hamon.
And it was a close one, too.
If my wind didn't have the strength
to blow away your lenses...
...I have no idea how I could've
stopped the light.
And if Lord Kars, who cannot use wind,
had met you here first...
...and met your power...
Even if he had won...
...he would've been in worse shape
than I am now.
Don't.
You will not fight again.
My Divine Sandstorm
has shredded your body.
Stop. The battle is done.
You have no more Hamon.
See?
You've almost bled out.
That means you have no hope.
Stop.
Goodbye.
Your life has ended.
What?!
My lip ring with the antidote. Why?
I-I'm...not afraid to die.
But I am a proud member
of the Zeppeli family.
It is in my blood.
Something like this might mean nothing
to an inhuman monster like you.
My father didn't recognize me,
but he sacrificed his life to save mine.
My grandfather gave his Hamon energy
to JoJo's grandfather before he died.
It's tradition. I have to do something.
I can't let my life's flame sputter out.
This is the Zeppeli family spirit,
from the past to the future!
It's the human spirit!
JoJo, this is the last of my Hamon!
Take it!
That's Caesar!
Did you hear that?
Yes.
Caesar can't be...!
Caesar!
He made a bubble from his blood.
He must have used
all of his Hamon to make it.
He saved it for this, for his friends,
rather than using it on me.
I'll let it go.
It's not because I'm sentimental.
His talent as a fighter was real.
He has my respect as a fellow warrior.
I will hold you forever
in my memory...Caesar.
A man as splendid
and as fleeting as a bubble.
T-The place is a wreck.
A Divine Sandstorm did this.
And Caesar was caught in it.
A bubble...
C-Could it be...?
No!
It's Caesar's bandana!
And...
A ring! Wamuu's lip ring!
This Hamon energy feels strange!
W-Whoa!
I haven't called Caesar's name
since we got here.
It was because I was scared.
If I cried out his name
and there was no response...
If there was only silence...
That's what scared me.
I wouldn't accept it.
So I didn't call him.
But now I know.
The Hamon in that bubble
told me everything.
Right here, moments ago...
...Caesar died.
Caesar, you bastard.
You were a showoff till the end.
Leaving a gift like this...
Caesar, where are you?!
Where are you sleeping?!
I'll find you! I'll dig you up! Caesar!
JoJo!
This isn't the time to search or grieve.
What?!
There are two of them and two of us.
Even numbers.
But all that trail of blood says
Caesar hurt Wamuu badly.
We're in enemy territory.
Let's go and finish it.
JoJo, come on.
Take the antidote, then we'll hunt them.
T-That heartless...
Not even a single tear for Caesar?!
Coach Lisa Lisa...
...your cigarette's backwards.
She's our coach,
she has to keep a cool exterior.
I know she wants to cry
much more than I do.
He treated her like a goddess,
and knew her much longer than me.
I have to hold my feelings back.
Caesar, I know you thought
I was self-centered.
But sometimes I understand
how others feel.
I might be learning.
But I'll fight them like the devil!
Your spirit rests with me!
Blood...
It's blood.
That's where Caesar fell.
Caesar...
Caesar!
They're in enemy territory.
Kars and Wamuu are near.
But the two couldn't help themselves.
JoJo called Caesar's name.
Lisa Lisa's tears flowed freely.
But their cries were only answered
by cold silence.
Caesar was gone.
The silence confirmed the fears
of JoJo and Lisa Lisa.
Though his body had died,
his soul lived on.
Rest in peace, Caesar Zeppeli.
Next episode
I'm in a bad mood.
I'll hug you to death!
We fight tonight, under the full moon.
You have no tomorrow.
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
Chapter 21: A Hundred Against Two