The battle for the Red Stone!
JoJo versus Wamuu...
...in a chariot duel!
The match will begin when the moon
reappears from behind that cloud!
What a life I have.
Why does Wamuu get all the fans?
One lap is 960 meters.
These horses can make a lap
in one minute.
Look at that column.
Each lap, a new weapon
will hang from that column.
Weapons?
The one who reaches the column first
will be able to wield that weapon.
For the first lap...
...it's a giant sledgehammer!
That thing could smash
through a chariot!
If Wamuu gets his hands on it,
my situation will go from bad to worse!
But if I get it first, cover it with oil
and fill it with Hamon...
...victory will be mine!
I expect an excellent,
fulfilling fight from you, JoJo.
The moon is at the cloud's edge.
Soon its light will shine upon us!
JoJo, what are you doing?!
It's almost time!
I know, I know!
The start is the key!
I have to check the rubble
under my wheels.
Hey, Wamuu, it looks pretty bad down there.
You gonna clear that up?
JoJo, hurry and climb on!
JoJo!
Start!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 22: A True Warrior
Start!
What the...?
L-Lord Wamuu is having trouble starting!
His wheels are stuck!
JoJo did it!
That clever devil.
Bastard, you were at work
while we looked up at the moon!
You cheater!
Rotten cheater!
I never thought I'd be called
a cheater by you!
When your life's on the line,
there are no rules!
I don't mess around
when it comes to survival!
Beep beep!
He's nearing the column!
JoJo will reach the hammer first.
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Wait till I get my mitts on you!
Gotcha!
I'm going faster than I thought!
No!
JoJo!
Y-Yikes! It got caught on my ring!
B-But now this fight is in the bag!
What luck!
You can have the hammer.
That was my plan from the beginning.
Wamuu has some sort of plan.
Show me your fighting genius!
A little oil and some Hamon!
Bring it on, Wamuu!
Wamuu slowed down.
This is a fight to the death,
not a race.
The proper usage of your weapon
and your horses is the key.
Okay! Now I'll just move in and
whack him with my hammer!
JoJo, you can't slow down now!
You have the hammer,
so I'll grab something else.
So, Wamuu, are you ready
to get slammed by this thing?!
He was so happy with his hammer,
but now look at his face!
H-He sure thinks b-bigger than I do!
No! Speed up and get away, JoJo!
Too late!
Now you have to abandon your chariot!
He fell? I guess the fight ends early.
What will JoJo do next?
JoJo!
I give a 90% chance he'll be crushed
by my vampire horses.
There's a 5% chance he'll break left...
...and a 5% chance he'll go right.
Now what will our cunning warrior do?
M-My hammer.
Where's my hammer?!
His hammer? Did he hit his head?
A hammer won't save you now!
He mustn't dodge.
If he does, Wamuu will stop and finish him
with a Divine Sandstorm!
But JoJo ran straight at Wamuu's horses!
Yes, JoJo! Quick thinking! That'll work!
He struck the harness
between the horses!
The horses ran on, and JoJo used
the hammer to send himself skyward!
U-Unbelievable!
The hammer's length
kept him from being kicked!
In your face!
And now to give you a good whack!
He's gone! Where'd he go?!
Wamuu is always a step ahead of JoJo.
R-Right! These guys can hide
inside others!
That was close!
H-His boot!
It saved him!
If he wore a different kind of shoe...
Luck's on my side!
This hammer got caught on my ring.
Luck is part of being effective!
Now look at yourself!
Your own power has trapped you
inside of that horse!
Here we go!
Here's Hamon for you
and your horse, Wamuu!
The fool! He doesn't see!
Look out, JoJo! Stay away from Wamuu!
Inside there, Wamuu's hands are free,
and speed and shaking are no issue.
That means...
Nobody has survived a direct hit!
Caesar didn't!
You are caught in my Divine Sandstorm!
Even with just half a lap
around the arena,
it was a fight full of twists, eh?
But in the end, Wamuu was the better
thinker and the better fighter.
Next up is the battle
between you and me.
To be honest,
I prefer not to fight women.
Wamuu dislikes it even more.
Even so, all Hamon-users
must be exterminated.
Drink that for a painless death.
You seem to be mistaken.
JoJo and Wamuu aren't done fighting.
L-Lord Kars, look over there!
Huh?!
Lord Wamuu's arms look like
they're about to fall off!
M-Madness...
How did that happen?
W-Wamuu! What happened to him?!
It's JoJo!
He survived! He's up!
He's just fine!
W-Well, I did it again.
That Divine Sandstorm hit him directly!
H-How...?
Directly?
JoJo was cunning enough to make
it look direct.
He's an absolute genius of trickery.
I don't know if I should praise him.
Take a closer look at Wamuu.
I-I see...
He wrapped Hamon-filled reins
around Wamuu's arms.
Wamuu's Divine Sandstorm was hobbled.
Wamuu was sticking his hand
out of the horse.
I knew he'd stick his other hand out
to use his Divine Sandstorm.
And I had the perfect counter!
Look at Lord Wamuu's face!
He's sweaty and pale!
Where is he looking? He looks vacant!
W-What should we do?!
It's lap two!
B-But Lord Wamuu can't grab
a weapon like that!
Can Lord Wamuu fight on?
It's no surprise.
Wamuu was struck with Hamon
in the middle of his attack.
The confidence he built over millennia
has crumbled.
The quiet intensity his victories
gave him has vanished.
It was surely a shock for him.
But it matters not!
Put out the next set of weapons!
Lord Kars gave the order!
We must obey his command.
For the second lap
both warriors get crossbows!
Each comes with two balls for ammo!
The faster warrior chooses
the large or small bow!
S-So now there's two weapons,
a big one and a small one?
Lisa Lisa, let me say
what's on your mind.
Wamuu's mind is in no state to fight.
So why is Kars deploying weapons
with such confidence?
It makes you nervous, right?
Here's why.
It's because Wamuu is a true warrior.
Top athletes use a psychological
technique called the switch comeback.
When pressured by shock, failure or fear
they can flip a mental switch
and bring out their fighting spirit.
In desperate situations,
a ritual is needed.
This is Wamuu's!
W-What the...?! What is he doing?!
Lord Wamuu!
Look at his eyes!
He poked them out!
I foolishly relied on my eyes
because I could see.
JoJo exploited my weakness.
Now I will use this horn
to see wind instead of light!
He flipped his switch
by removing his eyes.
Wamuu is now psychologically invincible.
Now he can sense the wind with his horn.
He sees air better than light.
W-What was that all about?
That won't psyche me out!
We lost Caesar!
Your eyes are nothing compared to that!
Which crossbow--
--will you take?
Why ask? You know the answer!
The big one, of course!
I need more power!
That one does have power.
Yeah, lots of power.
N-No! I can't draw this thing!
S-So tight! Can I even bend this string?
You got greedy!
Even a normal crossbow
takes a lot of strength to draw!
You got greedy!
So greed got you back!
I'll use the first ball
to get a picture.
Now I see the range.
The next shot won't miss.
Damn. How can I shoot back?!
Lord Wamuu, blow him to smithereens!
Let us feed on whatever remains!
J-Just as I thought.
The wind stirred up by the fire
makes it hard for him to see.
This is the spot!
He's underestimating Wamuu.
H-Hey, what's Lord Wamuu doing?
He's turned away from the flame!
JoJo is staying opposite Wamuu
and near the flame.
He's giving away his position!
He's banking his shot
like a billiard ball!
Wha...?!
He hit me from behind!
I was looking at the terrain
as we circled.
I wanted to find a wall
I could use on you!
C-Can't breathe!
It lost momentum,
so it didn't pierce the skin.
But he's spitting up blood,
which means organ damage.
Finish him, Wamuu!
But JoJo is a wily one.
Be on your guard!
Has he set a trap?
My crossbow cocked itself
when it hit the ground.
I can't let him know that!
I can't kill him from this far.
Closer. Come closer.
N-Now!
He has!
Almost! Almost!
His shot went wild, though.
I should commend him for fighting
until the very last.
Here I come, JoJo!
S-Stay away!
D-Don't get any closer!
Go away! Leave me alone!
Please, just spare me!
You cur!
Huh?
He's throwing rocks!
What a pathetic loser!
Go down like a man, little worm!
Wamuu...
...here's what you'll say next.
Do not dishonor our fight, JoJo!
Here!
A bat could fly between those stones.
But what about you, Wamuu?
A-An iron ball c-came from behind!
B-Bastard!
Looks like I did it again.
Wamuu, I used the shot you fired
at me earlier.
The arena went quiet.
Everyone was silent.
There wasn't even a moan.
Wamuu's wound was
like a Jack-o'-Lantern's sneering grin.
The iron ball carried
a small amount of Hamon.
The wound began to fester.
Wamuu's damaged arms grew worse.
There would be no more
Divine Sandstorms.
I-I have to r-resume my Hamon breathing.
A kick after faking a fall?!
You're just lashing out in pain!
Rebuff Overdrive!
JoJo won! Wamuu won't get up again!
W-What has become of the great Wamuu?
I have fallen into such a sorry state.
A body that lived for 12,000 years
is reduced to this.
H-His arms!
His arms are gone!
It is not my way to give the enemy
an easy victory.
My wounds are my flesh.
My losses are my ability.
I will use all of this to claim victory!
His arms!
He fired his severed forearms
from the hole in his chest!
What the...?!
C-Can't breathe!
I can't use my Hamon breathing!
T-That wind.
It's flowing toward Wamuu.
This is my ultimate mastery of wind.
Ultimate mastery? No!
Stop, Wamuu! You cannot do that!
The wind is going into those pipes!
My ultimate mastery:
Atmospheric Rift!
Next episode
You recreants!
No matter what the method...
Kars's stance...
You crossed a line
you shouldn't have crossed.
I alone always stand on top!
Chapter 23: The Warrior of Wind