-Tibet, 1863-
You have endured our training
for three long years.
You can run for dozens of miles
without losing your breath.
You will soon be ready for the training
we call the Celestial Gate.
However, I tell you again, Zeppeli...
...if you continue your training, you
will not be able to escape your doom.
The time for turning back is now.
You can still start a new life.
Master Tonpetty...
...please read the waves
of my life once more.
When am I destined to die?
Where am I destined to die?
What would you do if you knew?
I have a purpose in my life.
I cannot set it aside.
I want to know in order to
fulfill that purpose.
I will accept everything
when I know when I will die.
I will be satisfied.
Very well, if you feel
you are prepared...
...I will tell you.
In an ancient, hidden chamber
that reeks of death...
...a child will open the way.
In order to release a chained
young lion into the future...
...you will burn your own wounds
and after, a cruel death awaits you!
Baron Zeppeli...
Be careful, Baron!
Here I come, JoJo!
In order to release a chained
young lion into the future.
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 7: The Inheritor
This collar won't budge!
And Tarukus hasn't shown off any of his
tricks for fighting in this room.
That worries me.
Come, fools! You want to hit me
with some of your Hamon?
You cowards won't be able
to lay a finger on me!
What's the matter? Scared stiff?
Well done, Baron Zeppeli!
Try this, Tarukus!
Tornado Overdrive!
H-He just...!
Above me?
No, the chain is coming from below!
You're both right!
I call this the Hell Heaven Snake Kill!
I'll strangle you both to death!
I-I can't breathe.
My Hamon won't...
Jo...
JoJo...
Lord Dio, I have executed
both of them as you ordered.
Th-This is...
This is just too cruel!
Jonathan!
Still alive, even with
a broken neck, are you?
Allow me to finish you.
Jo...
JoJo...
The other one is still alive, too?
My ultimate...
My ultimate technique
is now yours, JoJo!
JoJo, please, take up my torch!
Ultimate Deep Pass Overdrive!
JoJo, I have given you
all of my life energy.
B-Baron...
B-Baron Zeppeli!
I'll grind both of you into paste
beneath my boot!
Y-You...
Jonathan pulled Tarukus off the ground!
Baron Zeppeli's Hamon
healed his broken neck!
Idiot, you think you can yank that open?
You, a pathetic human?
I couldn't pull apart that steel
even with the power Lord Dio gave me!
You'll pay, Tarukus!
Jonathan!
W-What the...?!
You are utterly twisted by your madness.
You willingly sold your soul to Dio.
S-Such strength!
His body can barely contain his power!
Jonathan received Baron Zeppeli's power
and it has synergized with his own!
Tarukus, I will allow nothing of you
to remain in this world.
I will banish your evil spirit!
Drown in the depths of history!
Enough talk, you little brat!
Your little trick didn't work!
It's over!
Baron Zeppeli!
Baron Zeppeli...
I can't...
I can't believe this.
Without you...
Without you, what will we do?
JoJo, you fool!
Have you lost your wits?
This is no time to grieve!
Now...
Now you are...
Now go.
Defeat Dio.
Destroy the mask.
Baron Zeppeli!
I...
I am satisfied with my fate.
When I was young, I was married.
But I abandoned my family
to pursue the mask.
Even so, I am satisfied with my fate.
I accept it completely.
In the end, I passed along
all of myself.
JoJo...
...you are my hope.
Baron Zeppeli...
You feel like both a son
and a best friend to me.
And now I will live on...
...within you.
The 19th century novelist
William Thackeray wrote this:
To love and win is the best thing.
To love and lose is the next best.
So JoJo took up his mentor's
life's quest as well as his spirit.
Farewell, Baron Zeppeli.
P-Please...
Please spare the life of this child.
Let me confirm your desire, madam.
You will give your life to us,
but we must not touch your child.
Is that right?
Please, leave my child alone.
You move me to tears. Okay.
I, Dio, swear that
neither I, nor any of these
servants will harm your child.
However, all of them bowed to their fear
and gave their souls to me willingly.
It would be better for both you
and your child to join us.
You would have no worries.
There would be no hate between you.
Please, just spare this child!
Just this child...
Okay, okay...
My sweet baby!
We won't harm the child, as I promised.
Instead you do it yourself.
It is a tragedy of your own choosing.
Jonathan's expression has changed.
His face is darker.
And I am the same.
We must endure our sadness and anger.
We cannot grieve until Dio has fallen!
Jonathan, Dio said he would wipe out
the town in one more night!
Zombies will create zombies,
breeding like rats!
What is happening down there?
Is Wind Knights Lot still alive?
Is my sister all right?
Let's hurry.
Mr. Adams!
Poco, why are you
wandering about at this hour?!
Mr. Adams, is Sis all right?
Is the town all right?
Is she all right?!
You really think she's all right?!
She's furious!
She'll lock you in the
barn when you get home!
I guess the town is safe.
Let's move!
Thanks, Mr. Adams!
A child!
I want to drink the fresh,
warm blood of a child!
He's already been turned!
Can you escape this speed?!
It looks like it is too late.
That's correct.
The outskirts are infested with zombies.
Another one?!
My name is Dire.
A kick, but why so slow?
Try this! Thunder Split Attack!
H-He's incredible!
A normal man would pull his head back,
but he head-butted me instead!
Wait, Jonathan Joestar!
I am human.
Forgive me.
I wanted to see
how well Zeppeli has trained you.
Did you say Zeppeli?!
I did. He is a dear friend who has been
through 20 years of trials with me.
Indeed.
I am Straizo.
Look at this.
A letter...
It's from...
...Baron Zeppeli!
He sent that letter to request our aid.
He wrote about the location of the mask
and the man who bears it.
This is our master, Tonpetty.
A pleasure to meet you.
You're Baron Zeppeli's teacher,
Master Tonpetty.
Where I come from,
shaking hands is not a custom.
We greet each other this way.
And where is Zeppeli now?
I see. Zeppeli has passed.
Even if we had come earlier,
his fate would not have changed.
But this Dio's power is overwhelming!
His wicked might is quite extraordinary.
This town is now mine
and it took less than a single night.
Next episode
You fell for it, fool!
I will show you no mercy!
I'll feel no guilt for killing you!
Come, JoJo!
Chapter 8: Blood Feud - JoJo & Dio