Rome, Italy
What do you call this?!
You expect me to eat spaghetti
with ink in it?!
Well sir, this is
spaghetti al nero di seppia.
It is made with fresh squid ink,
so it is black.
Huh?
It's quite tasty, sir.
Yum! Well isn't this a treat?
I like it! It's good!
This hotel is going to the dogs.
They'll let anyone in these days.
Signorina, this is a gift for you.
Oh, it's lovely!
My pretty thing, when you remove this
at night before bed, please think of me.
Oh, no! Did that stuck-up snob
really just say that?!
It's sweet enough to make
my teeth hurt!
I'll put a spell on it.
Make her fall to my love charm.
I can't stand guys like that!
And spread your magic to her lips.
That insinuating little dog!
I see his game!
It's a travesty!
Here we go.
A little Hamon prank.
These will wrap around his
face and stick for a while!
Th-This can't be!
I-It's Hamon!
He used Hamon!
Excuse me, you have a call from a
Mr. Speedwagon, Mr. Caesar Zeppeli.
Mamma mia! I'll be right there.
Wh-What the...!
That skirt-chasing Casanova
is the Zeppeli we're here to meet?!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 14: Elite Ancient Warriors
The Speedwagon Foundation, founded 28
The Speedwagon Foundation's
Washington headquarters
years ago through Speedwagon's fortune.
It furthers science, medicine,
archaeology and more...
...for the benefit of all humankind.
But it has a deeper purpose.
To find the secrets of the stone masks!
We're using UV lights.
Put on your masks, please.
Introduce the snake!
The snake was absorbed!
Santviento isn't dead!
He's defending himself somehow!
He'll awaken in the darkness.
Impossible! How can we kill him?
He feeds on masked vampires,
and he's immortal!
But be at ease, Mr. Speedwagon.
As long as he's under these UV lights,
he won't be able to move.
That's right.
What a relief.
Let's take our time
and research a way to stop him.
These were taken in the cave where
we found Santviento.
Look carefully.
Their horns are all different!
If the one on the bottom is Santviento,
who are the others?
According to von Stroheim, the Germans
found another Pillar in Europe.
Is that true?!
They are in a vertical line.
That could indicate the ranks
of the Pillar Men.
Von Stroheim told us to meet a man in
Rome, so JoJo and I are going.
That man...
...is the grandson of Will A. Zeppeli,
Caesar Zeppeli!
So where are you from?
Shall I take a photo of you
with the fountain?
The birds in this country
sure are friendly.
Can't say I like the men, though!
Come, now! You've been introduced,
so why can't you be civil?!
Allow me to be frank, Mr. Speedwagon.
My grandfather died tragically
fifty years ago.
My father took up his torch
and hunted the mask.
We Italians have the strongest
family bonds in the world.
We are proud of tradition.
I am no different.
But what about that man?
You say he knew nothing of his
grandfather until recently!
Such irresponsibility!
I'd watch what I say, if--!
Hold on, Caesar!
I kept everything a secret from JoJo!
Even so.
He fought Straizo and
one of the Pillar Men.
So I wondered how tough he was
and waited for him.
I saw what he could do with Hamon
and was disappointed.
His Hamon is simply not enough!
His victory against the Pillar Man
was blind luck for sure.
I will never work with him!
Caesar, he hasn't trained with Hamon!
It's too late, old man.
I'll show you with a good thrashing.
That won't happen.
With your Hamon, you couldn't
even beat this girl.
Then you couldn't even beat a pigeon!
Are you making fun of me?
I love to make fun,
but I won't be made fun of!
H-He gave this girl a Hamon kiss.
I'll say it again.
You couldn't even beat this girl.
S-Should I stop them?
No, even if it's hard on him,
if he can't get through this...
What did I tell you?
My grandfather only died because
your grandfather got in his way!
I can't accept someone of
your bloodline!
Caesar, that's too far!
Y-You...
You couldn't leave it at just me,
you had to insult my dead grandfather!
I have a technique
sure to eliminate the Pillar Men.
My Hamon Bubble Launcher!
My gloves and clothing are coated
in a special soap mixture!
I'll blast you back home, Joestar!
I'm impressed you're still conscious,
but your Hamon won't break you out.
And look at that,
your breathing is ragged.
Enjoy your stay.
Now you'll say, Signorina,
I will lift my Hamon spell.
Here, signorina,
I put a Hamon-filled pigeon in her mouth
while I was being choked.
I knew you'd kiss her again
to remove your Hamon.
I'll say it again.
You couldn't even beat a pigeon!
What a day.
Who does this jerk think he is?
Does he have to grandstand
just to sit down?
He really ticks me off.
If I had a technique like his Bubble
Launcher, he wouldn't be so proud.
I have to come up with something.
But working at it would be a hassle.
I'll show him what's what
with a card game.
What are you up to, JoJo?
Deal the cards normally.
What do you mean?
I told you to deal normally!
No tricks!
Wh-Whoa-oa!
Oh, no! I've been caught!
Well, you can't beat me without
resorting to sly gimmicks like that.
So what is this mirror
on your shoe for, eh?
You want a piece of me?!
Bring it, rube!
Caesar!
It's been eight hours.
What are you waiting for?
What am I waiting for?
Here's your answer!
What's this?! A German soldier!
It looks like we're clear.
The Germans guard the Pillar Men.
He'll get us in to see them.
You're serious?!
Germany and Italy have an alliance!
And the Germans want to do
scientific research on my Hamon.
You're Englishmen, but
you're allowed to see the Pillar Men.
You can thank my
painstaking efforts for that, JoJo.
Mr. Speedwagon, we have
many questions.
Let's work together
to stop them before they wake.
Hey, Mark.
How is your girlfriend back home?
Well, she's...
Th-The truth is...
...I'm going home
to get married next week!
Really?!
Mamma mia! Congratulations!
I was his wingman when
he picked her up!
Hey, keep your eyes on the road!
Stop nuzzling the wheel!
By the way, JoJo...
...do you have a girlfriend?
Of course not.
No girl would want to
date a guy like you.
It would be easier to find Nessie!
This guy really thinks he's hot stuff!
I'll come up with a killer technique
and teach him a thing or two!
Look! Something's strange!
Wh-What's going on?!
Calm down! They're under UV lights!
They can't move.
Take care and look into it.
Yes, sir!
The death of von Stroheim's team
was an important lesson.
We have to cut the Pillar out and
put it in a bunker in Germany.
What's happening?
There's a shadow, so I can't tell.
Take a closer look.
I-I hear something.
His horn!
H-He couldn't be...!
He's awake!
Bring out more UV lamps!
Yes, sir!
H-He's blocking the UV light
with blood and brain matter!
The world has changed while I slept.
I can see how
in these paltry inventions.
H-He spoke!
Do you think you can hold me
with your feeble lights?!
Our hands!
They're stuck together!
Wamuu!
Awaken, my masters!
The famous Mouth of Truth
was a secret entrance all this time?!
This place is so unearthly!
Caesar, have you tried Hamon
on the sleeping Pillar Men?
Hamon is only useful on the living.
It has no effect on stone.
It won't work unless they are awake.
Hey, where are the guards that
are supposed to be here?!
No one's here! It's too quiet!
You're too loud.
T-This isn't right.
There should be a guard posted here.
What?
Whoa!
Hey, I just stepped in something!
It's the grossest feeling ever!
What the heck is it?!
Th-They're...!
The husks of soldiers!
Th-They're all dead!
No way!
Hey, Dutch! Don't run off!
Something's out there!
Wh-What is that?!
This can't be! Th-They're...!
Awake!
Get out of there, Mark!
Mark!
Caesar... Caesar!
They didn't even notice what happened
when one of them bumped into Mark!
It's like when a man
steps on an ant while walking!
It is night outside, Wamuu.
Yes, Lord Kars. What is your plan?
Searching for the whereabouts
of the Red Stone of Aja, of course.
All we need is the Stone and
the Mask will be complete!
But Master Esidisi, the human world
has changed much over the years.
Long ago, the Emperor of Rome
had the Stone.
But that age has ended, I am sure.
Then we must find out
where the Stone has gone.
They say the Emperor
cherished the Stone.
I am sure humans
still tell stories of it.
I shall find the Stone.
We have time.
For now, let us go outside and
observe the changes in the human world.
Wamuu!
What are you doing, worm?!
Stay your hand, Esidisi!
I apologize, Lord Kars.
Wamuu, I know how you hate
when someone enters your shadow.
I forgot how you reflexively attack
anyone who does.
It has been 2,000 years, after all.
I have offended you, my lord.
Punish me as you see fit.
No, there is no reason for it.
It is that very fighting spirit
that lets me rely on you.
The fault is mine
for entering your shadow.
Forgive me, Wamuu.
Lord Kars...
We go, Wamuu.
Yes, lord.
Caesar!
Kill me! Kill me now!
Mark!
I-It's starting to hurt.
I-I'm so scared.
I was numb at first, but the pain...!
Please kill me now, Caesar!
Mark!
There's nothing we can do!
We can't do anything to help him.
We're powerless!
The hopelessness is overwhelming!
C-Caesar...
You...
Thank you, Caesar.
Mark!
He was just a young man.
Just an ordinary man.
He loved his family.
And his girl.
And his country.
He was a normal,
hardworking young man.
He was just a kid!
Caesar!
JoJo, stay out of this!
This fight is mine!
I have to do this myself!
Next episode
Oh, I'm tired of talking.
I told you to continue!
He's spineless!
The Hamon tribe.
This is my Divine Sandstorm!
Chapter 15: A Hero's Proof