You bastards!
Don't turn your backs on me!
Time to face my Hamon Bubble Launcher!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 15: A Hero's Proof
Th-This couldn't be...!
Great! He's a nuisance,
but at least his Hamon works!
You're surrounded by my bubbles.
Here's the bombardment!
H-He popped your Bubble Launcher!
Those wires on his head
didn't pop my bubbles.
It was the wind they created.
That means those wires are
anti-Hamon weapons!
They know the principles of Hamon!
- Wamuu -
They've met with Hamon before,
over 2,000 years ago!
- Esidisi -
- Kars -
What is happening
to the air around them?
No, Caesar! Get down!
Wh-What the...?
Close your eyes!
That wasn't just wind,
it was the aftermath of a vortex!
Caesar!
The Hamon tribe.
I thought we eliminated them all
2,000 years ago.
But here they are in Rome,
waiting for us to awaken.
Damn...you...
You killed my dear friend.
You think losing an eye will stop me?!
Wh-What's so damned funny?!
The Hamon tribe
always says the same thing.
It was the same when we crossed from
the western continent as it is now.
You think losing an arm
or an eye will stop me?!
How dare you take my friend's life?!
That's why we laugh.
Y-You monsters!
Let's go. We must find the Stone.
G-Get back here!
You're running away?!
Your throat and lungs are your
weak points.
We know that if you can't breathe,
you can't use Hamon.
Now I'll say what I've always said.
Come and face me again
when you are stronger, boy.
When we meet again,
I want to admire your strength...
...before I utterly destroy you.
It seems there are no other Hamon users.
Let's move.
Here! Look here!
Don't go and overlook me, now!
He only cut your eyelid.
Your eyeball is just fine.
Take your little Bubble Launcher
and hang back.
I'll take care of this.
JoJo!
It's time to show off the brand new technique
I've worked so hard on.
What?!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Joseph Joestar,
the guy who mopped the floor with your buddy.
I call this the Hamon Clacker Volley.
I start off by filling
these clackers with Hamon.
Oh, no!
JoJo, what are you doing?!
This is no time for foolishness!
My friend just died!
You're completely senseless!
Me? I'm dead serious.
Caesar, you mourn
the loss of your friend.
I feel your pain and anger.
But more than that, I can't stand
egotistical jerks like these guys!
I'm not an expert yet, but see
what you think of my Clacker Volley!
I hate to say it, but my Hamon
is still weak.
But I can use these steel clackers to
break your skin
and fill you with Hamon.
That should even my handicap.
Pretty good, right?
Take this!
Let's go.
This is absurd.
Perhaps humans have regressed
over the years.
Regressed?
Perhaps so.
JoJo, stop monkeying around!
You just tossed metal balls at them!
JoJo might be serious. He'd be fine
if he was facing a street punk.
But these guys are
way out of his league!
It's silly enough to make me cry!
Blast it! Nobody here
takes me seriously!
Hold it, big guy!
You're gonna get hit!
Don't.
Human lives are short enough.
Do not rush to die.
Spaghetti al nero di seppia looks bad,
but it's a real treat.
You need to try my Clacker Volley
before you judge it!
The clackers vanished!
I've been working on the railroad,
All the live-long day.
L-Look!
Gotcha! Still fooled?
If you don't get it...
...let me show you!
Take this!
Those moves are impossible!
And he's even faster than Santviento!
The clackers didn't even touch him!
I admire your weapon, courage and idea.
This is becoming fun.
Thus...
I'll give you one minute.
I bestow on you a single minute
to fight the mighty Wamuu.
JoJo!
As you see, I've cut your wrist.
Your wound gives you one minute
of consciousness to stop the bleeding.
Give me everything you've got!
Here is what I say to the Hamon tribe.
Here is an hourglass
measured in blood.
Wamuu, we'll be outside.
Boy, go pick up your weapon.
Huh? What was that you said?
Go pick up your weapon?
Is that what you said?
I don't need to do that.
There's no need to go pick it up.
That was my Clacker Boomerang!
One minute is all I need to end you.
Make fun of me, will you?
I'll smash you to pieces!
Then I'll fill you with Hamon!
Very well.
Hit me all you like.
You are the first person
to scar my face.
And so I bestow upon you
this honor before you die.
You say no one has ever
hit your face before?
Big words!
You didn't even notice
when you killed Mark!
I'll make you regret
holding your nose so high!
Look out! He's up to something!
That arm of his isn't broken!
Th-This is gonna be bad!
It was wise of you to jump back.
I let you hit me to punish myself
for my lack of caution.
But that has ended.
JoJo, finish him now!
My ultimate technique.
The Divine Sandstorm!
I-I'm in trouble!
He spins his left arm clockwise!
And his right arm counterclockwise!
JoJo is caught unaware, and Wamuu's
fists seem to grow before his eyes!
The space between his fists becomes
a destructive vacuum!
The whirling creates a microcosm
of wind and sand!
H-He ripped through that marble pillar
like a piece of old cloth!
I've never seen such power!
JoJo...
That was my Divine Sandstorm.
Jo-JoJo!
No, stay back!
Mr. Speedwagon, you have to run!
I'll do something to hold him back!
The blood in my eye threw off my aim.
But it was enough, even when you
hid behind the pillar.
Dead already?
Ordinarily, I would ignore
humans like yourselves.
But you witnessed my shame,
so I must be rid of you as well.
Prepare yourselves.
I'm imagining things.
H-He couldn't be...!
U-Unbelievable. He's trying to escape!
Playing dead like that.
He's got no shame!
I can understand leaving me,
but Mr. Speedwagon?
He's spineless!
That guy is the
biggest menace I've seen!
My breathing is out of control.
I can't use Hamon!
All that's left is my specialty.
All I can do is run!
Look at our dismal hero!
JoJo is on the ground,
forced to play dead.
And he's about to
leave Speedwagon to his fate!
Even so, JoJo will remain
the worthy hero of this tale!
Here's why!
Still alive, are you?!
You coward.
You thought you could
trick me and escape?!
I only needed to fool you
for a dozen or so meters.
I just wanted to get to this minecart.
So you only acted like a coward to lure
me over and let your friends escape, eh?
And you fell for another of my tricks.
Get out of here now, old man!
Caesar, you too!
JoJo...
That chivalrous bastard...
I've sure painted myself into a corner.
I need to come up with something.
Can I get a break?
An unbending hero!
Only when JoJo loses the will to fight
will he lose his status as a hero.
JoJo!
Damn him!
He's far more injured than me!
He may put on a foolish act,
but he takes his fate seriously.
He knows he has to beat those monsters!
You speak quite brashly
for one in such a terrible state.
You're a tough one.
Weak-spirited, but tough indeed.
How are you so tough?
Do you have bricks for brains,
or do you have another trick for me?
You want to know?
Don't tell me.
Is it something stupid like going into
the mine and using explosives on me?
Oh, no! He knows!
Or do you plan to pull the brake
and send the minecart flying?
Something like this?
H-He did it again!
The time on your wristwatch
is almost up.
There is no chance you'll survive this.
You have no more tricks.
But tell me this.
Why don't I see defeat in your eyes?
You want to know?
You really want to know?
Forget it. I'll just kill you now.
If you give me a month,
I'll become strong enough to beat you.
What was that?
Give me a month and I'll outdo you.
I'm the first person to scar your face.
If I put my mind to it,
my potential is limitless.
No, never mind what I said.
Well, finish me quickly.
It's an honor to be killed
by a warrior like you.
Continue.
Oh, I'm tired of talking.
Make it painless, Wamuu.
I told you to continue!
JoJo is still okay!
You have a long life ahead of you.
You'll have to carry the shame
of being scarred by a human.
The only way to fix that is by beating
me in a fair fight after I've trained.
What? Don't feed me your lies, JoJo.
I've hooked him! Just a bit more!
He called me a coward when I ran.
Using a word like that means
he's the proud warrior type.
I can use that against him!
I'm rather new to fighting.
But if I train with Hamon for a month,
I know I have the talent to beat you!
I was the first human to hit your head,
and I carved a hunk out of it!
But you have a chance to kill me
before I grow into a real threat to you!
Why you...?!
Wamuu.
Master Esidisi.
His minute is up.
Why do you let him live?
Crap, we've got company!
Master Esidisi, I've grown fond of
this wielder of Hamon.
I-I got him!
JoJo!
I agree to your proposition.
You say you'll be stronger in a month,
so I will give you a month to live.
You won't kill me?
That's right.
We'll fight again?
This is a bad idea. You'll regret it.
Yes! I'm safe for now!
However...
I need to ensure that
you will not simply run away.
Wamuu, will you use
that old thing again?
The Wedding Ring of Death.
I will put this ring around your aorta.
Wh-What are you doing?!
The ring will start to
dissolve in 33 days.
Inside is a virulent poison.
The ring cannot be removed.
Any attempt will break
it, releasing the poison.
You have only one way
to avoid the poison.
Fight and defeat me within 33 days
and take the antidote from my lip ring.
JoJo!
Till death do us part.
A true wedding ring.
Midnight in 33 days at the Colosseum.
I'll be waiting, JoJo.
You guessed wrong
if you thought you'd escape.
I don't imagine we'll fight,
but here's a little gift!
I'll put it around your windpipe!
My heart and throat!
Mine is a different poison from Wamuu's.
The antidote is in my nose ring.
Kars, do you want in on this?
Nonsense.
We are immortal.
A worthy opponent is a rare thing
that gives our lives meaning.
I can see why you do this.
But our goal is to obtain
the power of the Red Stone of Aja.
Do not forget that, you two.
Let's go!
JoJo, grow strong and
overcome my Divine Sandstorm!
H-Holy smokes.
A wedding ring?
That's a black joke
if I ever heard one.
And now I've got two of them.
Do I look like a bigamist or something?!
Well, at least Speedwagon
and Caesar are safe.
There's no sense in moping about it.
JoJo.
You damned fool.
Despite your blood loss, you pulled
a bluff a card sharp would be proud of.
Good show.
Let's study Hamon together.
We'll grow stronger.
You and me both.
Next episode
I only said one month as a bluff!
Step through those doors and you'll see.
Coach, no!
I won't hold back because you're a girl!
Welcome to Venice!
Chapter 16: Lisa Lisa, Hamon Coach