Using Caesar's bandana,
JoJo barely defeated Wamuu.
Next, Lisa Lisa faced off against Kars.
Von Stroheim and Speedwagon
appeared suddenly with help.
However, in a cowardly turn,
Kars used a double to fight.
He sprang out and
stabbed Lisa Lisa in the back.
JoJo and Lisa Lisa are in
the greatest peril of their lives!
Kars, you bastard!
I hope you rot in hell forever!
JoJo doesn't know.
He doesn't know that
that woman is his own mother!
Don't let go, JoJo.
It's a forest of crystal spikes below.
She'd die instantly.
K-Kars!
Your soul is as rotten as a pumpkin
left in a field that even flies won't visit!
Shout at me. Grumble at me. Insult me.
While you're holding that rope,
that's all you can really do.
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 24: The Ties that Bind JoJo
JoJo! Lisa Lisa!
JoJo doesn't realize
his mother's life is in his hands!
Mr. Speedwagon, we should tell him!
No.
Why not?!
It's not the time.
Von Stroheim, are you done
with the vampires?!
We have to help JoJo!
Give me a break!
You think we can get rid of them
in just a minute or two?!
Get out of my sight!
It's no good. They need more time!
JoJo...
Careful, the rope will slip
if you don't watch it.
While you're holding the rope,
your hasty feet can only move so far.
He kicked Kars,
but Hamon didn't flow into him!
W-We're in a real fix!
Looks like your Hamon is running dry.
You might have just enough
for one last, all-out attack.
I'll just stroll up to you and take
your life like I'm plucking a flower.
Kars!
It's true I might have barely enough
in me for one final attack.
I'm not exactly confident.
But even so, I've come up with a plan.
It's something to make you choke!
Do you want to know what it is?
I won't tell you!
Hey!
You're not tying any ropes together!
This is a match!
What do you think I'll do with it?
Wh-What is JoJo up to?
He set his scarf on fire!
Before this fire burns me,
I'll use all I've got
left to send you packing!
The fire is a gamble!
It's a risk to motivate me!
I seek life within death!
JoJo...
An act like that...
...is just desperation!
Don't toy with me.
You're just dodging around
in order to catch your breath.
I'll say it again:
I want to kill you at my leisure.
I won't play king of the apes!
Come on, now! I need to breathe!
Who cares if I look silly?
Listen.
I can cut Lisa Lisa's rope
whenever I please.
And if you dodge again, I will!
Is that all right?
Should I cut it?
You want me to do it?
You don't, do you?
Don't!
You ran before. Now come to me, slowly.
If you want me to cut the rope,
stay where you are.
The coward!
What's your choice?
Is your life more precious
than this woman's?
Here's my choice!
I don't know what you're planning,
but if I cut this, you'll fall as well!
You fool!
JoJo!
Lisa Lisa!
Idiot. That's two birds with one cut.
What the...?!
He...!
This rope is connected to JoJo!
When did he do it?!
He didn't have the time!
When he first kicked, he let himself
be cut along with the rope!
While he lit the match, he secretly tied
his leg to her rope and made a loop.
He needed a distraction.
So he set his scarf on fire.
And then to tie the ropes together,
he let Lisa Lisa be cut down on purpose!
That cunning devil!
Now you're holding me and Lisa Lisa up!
You deceived me, JoJo!
I never thought I'd hear that from you!
It seems you like tricking,
but you hate to be tricked!
You may have lived
for over 10,000 years.
But to compete with my skills,
you need another decade!
Kars!
Your time is up!
Hamon Overdrive!
D-Did it work?
T-That was the last of my Hamon.
I'm burned out.
I don't have any Hamon left.
I-It got into him!
Yes!
He did it! He hit Kars with Hamon!
Off you go!
You...
Look! Kars fell into the crystal spikes!
He's finished! See?
Hamon will travel right up his arm!
You're weak! Your time is up!
Even we could finish you now!
He's trying to spook us.
All right! Let's eliminate him for good!
Bring out the UV amplifier!
Yes, sir!
Coach Lisa Lisa...
Kars said he didn't quite kill you.
I don't think he hit anything vital.
If we act quickly,
I'm sure you'll live through this.
It's finally over.
It is. I'm glad.
Hey, Mr. Speedwagon?
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why did Granny Erina tell JoJo
his mother died when he was little?
Why does Lisa Lisa
hide her past from him?
Smokey, that's...
Granny Erina told me not to ask you,
but I have to know!
She's his mother.
Keeping that from him is awful.
Smokey...
JoJo and Granny Erina are my friends.
They saved me from crooked cops,
even though I was just a thief.
That's why I'm here!
I'll do all I can to help.
All right, Smokey.
I'll tell you.
You did take good care of Erina
while I was away from New York.
But promise not to tell JoJo!
This is a Joestar family issue.
It's not our place to talk about it.
The name Lisa Lisa is an alias.
Her real name is Elizabeth.
She was raised by
a Hamon-user named Straizo.
She and Erina's son, George,
fell in love and got married.
George and Elizabeth had a son.
You know him as JoJo.
JoJo's father George was
a member of the Royal Flying Corps.
Aviation developed rapidly
during the First World War.
George was among the first
brave pilots to fly into battle.
He stood out as a hero
even among the Royal Flying Corps.
However...
...a gut-wrenching horror from the past
came back to haunt the Joestars.
Fifty years before, Dio had created
blood-sucking zombies.
Straizo, myself and the others
thought we had exterminated them.
But one had escaped, hid within society,
and lived for decades undiscovered!
He was a cunning, intelligent creature.
He created no spawn.
He ate even the bones and hair
of his victims, leaving no evidence.
And by some wicked twist of fate...
...he worked as a commander
in the Royal Flying Corps!
T-The Royal Flying Corps?
With JoJo's dad?
The same.
George uncovered his secret.
He had listened well to Straizo and me.
But ultimately,
George was an ordinary man.
He had character and talent,
but he hadn't trained with Hamon.
Before he could unmask the commander,
he was discovered and attacked!
His message to Straizo wasn't in time.
George's death was covered up
as a nighttime plane crash.
Straizo and I found this suspicious,
and eventually found the truth.
That night, I told Elizabeth
as she held an infant JoJo.
Instead of showing grief...
...she flew out of the house!
She was a genius with Hamon,
but her emotions consumed her!
She was witnessed
when she killed the commander.
The military didn't know
about zombies or Hamon.
They concluded that Elizabeth
had attacked their beloved commander,
killed him, and burned his body.
Soon she was known around the world
as a murderer and national traitor.
We used all the Speedwagon Foundation's
resources to cover her trail.
Elizabeth had to leave England behind
without even a word to her son.
Erina knew what had happened,
and she had a request.
When this child grows up
and asks about his parents...
...please tell him they both died.
This child...
And so Elizabeth became Lisa Lisa.
Why?
Why is it that way?
At least say his mother is alive!
I know painfully well why.
Erina lost her husband and son in
the battle between Hamon and the masks.
But thinking of her grandson, of JoJo...
...she didn't want Hamon in his life!
Lisa Lisa is the same way!
Such a tragic family.
Such a miserable fortune.
But now...
Now JoJo...
JoJo used Hamon
to save his mother's life!
Mr. Speedwagon...
Now there's no reason
for Lisa Lisa to hide.
JoJo knows about Hamon,
and he used it to save his mother!
True.
But it's not up to me.
We have to know how Erina
and Lisa Lisa feel first.
But...
Colonel!
We're ready to fire!
Right! Aim it right at him!
We will have the honor
of executing Kars!
Prepare to die, Kars!
I can't tell you how good it feels
to order this myself!
Don't, von Stroheim! The mask!
The Stone is in his mask!
UV light will help him!
D-Damn it!
Stop! Don't fire the UV amplifier!
N-No!
I-I didn't see him holding the mask.
I didn't see him put the Red Stone in!
Dear God...
Kars...
Next episode
The ultimate life form...
He can manipulate life at will!
Is there no way to stop him?
Kars, the Ultimate Thing, is born!
Chapter 25: The Birth of a Superbeing