Wind Knights Lot, a valley town
surrounded by sharp cliffs.
Built in the Middle Ages
to train knights...
...it now serves as a prison
where inmates mine for coal.
Farms and fishing give the town life.
Its population including prisoners: 517.
A terrible doom will soon visit them!
Two stars fallen from the heavens
Swallowed by waters swirling
light and dark
Their ripples move outward,
pulled toward each other
The sun will guide the man
who walks the path of honor
And for the man who follows
his ambition...
...a sacrifice awaits
With pounding heart
and burning will
With thundering fists
And overflowing bravery
He steps forward, free of doubt
A fate determined by his blood
JoJo!
Chapter 5: Knights of Darkness
Everyone is hard at work.
Things still appear peaceful.
But I know Dio is around here somewhere.
What happened?
Um, well, Speedwagon
has been begging me for a while.
So I thought I'd help him create
just a little Hamon.
And my finger kind of slipped.
I'm terribly sorry, Speedwagon.
W-Why...you...
It's a kid, sir.
Rather spry for such
a young cutpurse, eh?
Why are you just standing there?!
All of our money is in that bag!
That little devil!
A grab and dash in a single move.
Let's see...
I think he can serve us as a guide.
H-He's not sinking!
JoJo, if you're up to your knees,
you need to build up more Hamon energy!
That was a nice sound, JoJo.
Your Overdrive
passed through perfectly.
Do you think this is the spot?
No, a couple steps to the left.
I'll bet two pounds on it.
It shocked me!
Nice catch!
H-Huh? What's going on?
Who are you?
Something's wrong with the boy.
Did I use too much Hamon?
The boy is not the only thing
that's wrong.
Look around.
This is...!
A graveyard!
Looks like we were the ones
nicely caught in this trap.
The boy was under
some sort of hypnosis.
Jonathan, above you!
The sun is gone.
Time for your lives to go with it!
Dio!
T-They're crawling out!
I-I've been preparing myself
for this moment.
But I can't help being dismayed.
I'm sweating here!
That arrogant monster is
right there in the flesh!
He repaid Sir Joestar's love
with bloody betrayal!
I won't let him get away with it!
So that is Dio.
I see. He and his zombies
can't operate during the day.
So he hypnotized the boy and lured us
to an arena where he has the advantage.
A man of such guile
must not have the mask.
We have to destroy him somehow!
Zombie knights!
What's your name?
P-Poco!
All right, Poco.
Hang on tight!
Let's move, JoJo!
Yes, sir!
Zoom Punch!
Wow!
Dio Brando...
We've never met before.
But I say this to the mask
that has awakened you.
We meet at last.
Hey, baby!
Do you plan on fighting from that perch?
Come on down!
You're a cocky one for an insect.
I am the pinnacle of life.
A new being that will create the future.
I am incapable of sinking
down to a human level.
I've never felt such malice!
He already fancies himself a tyrant!
This is the only scar that has yet
to heal after my fight with JoJo.
Come, conjurer!
Let your blood salve this wound!
How many lives have you taken
to erase those scars?
How many slices of bread have you eaten?
Dio!
Baron Zeppeli!
I will handle this.
You're going to suffer!
Solar Hamon, shine on me!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
He did it!
His Hamon is flowing up Dio's arm!
How feeble!
I-It's freezing!
No!
Zeppeli was it?
Your energy comes
from the flow of your blood.
So if your blood vessels are frozen,
you're powerless.
Know that I have absolute control
over my body.
I vaporized the moisture in my left arm.
When it vaporized, it sucked up heat,
flash freezing your arm.
And now!
Buffoon!
I'll smash through your arm
and your skull like a vase!
Dio, I'm ending your madness!
I feel Dio's wicked blood
flowing through his hand.
I'll take that as a compliment.
But you did quite well to stop my fist.
I must say I'm impressed.
JoJo!
JoJo, if I were you,
I'd keep my hands to myself.
Take this, Dio!
Once your arm is frozen,
blood will no longer flow through it!
Your Hamon energy will not work!
H-He's too strong!
He's five times as strong
as both of us together!
No! He'll freeze JoJo's arm
just like mine!
I can't let JoJo be hurt!
Baron Zeppeli!
T-This can't be!
S-So cold!
It's so cold it burns!
My skin is peeling
like I touched cold metal!
Baron Zeppeli's arm!
Without circulation, it will rot!
He can't be stopped without
solar Hamon!
Can we stand against him?!
Hamon?
A breathing trick?
If you want to huff and puff...
T-The ground is shaking!
...then you should trumpet
a fanfare in my honor!
Tarukus! Black Knight Blueford!
This fight is beneath me. Arise!
Make their screams
a fanfare dedicated to me!
W-Who are these creeps?!
Poco, run and hide!
In the 16th century, an ill-fated queen
was slain by Elizabeth I.
You, fierce knights who
served Queen Mary Stuart!
Settle this!
I leave the extermination
of these pests to you!
Enjoy.
He lifted and crushed that boulder
with just one finger!
Those two zombies are moving for JoJo!
T-There's no way he can handle both.
If I had a little circulation...
Then what?
I could heal my arm a bit.
Is there some way to thaw my arm?
Baron Zeppeli, you need to
heat up your arm, right?
Y-You have a plan?!
How about this?!
Speedwagon!
In the Arctic, people treat frostbite
by putting the wound inside a seal!
Zoom Punch!
Your blood is mine!
H-He's draining my blood!
Speedwagon, I...
I didn't come here
to slow you and Jonathan down!
If he can drink blood through his hair,
I can send Hamon up it!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
It's not working!
Is this bloodsucker weakening my Hamon?!
I didn't give you enough credit.
I thought you'd be the type to flee.
I apologize.
I'll accept your apology
if we live through this.
I-I need to get my arm
into fighting form and fast!
That sight chills me
more than your arm did!
That blade makes
Jonathan's 195 cm frame look tiny!
That sinister black hair!
Those faces!
They have secrets!
I can read people,
and those two have secrets for sure!
Every Englishman knows the legendary
knights Tarukus and Blueford.
Even history bows to my will!
Long ago, around 1565, two queens
fought in a war of royal succession:
Queen Elizabeth I...
...and the beautiful,
23-year-old Mary Stuart.
The great knights Tarukus and Blueford
were her loyal vassals.
The pair had lost their families
and Mary accepted them with warmth.
Even the strongest man seeks respite,
not in romance, in something larger.
The pair found that in Mary.
They swore to honor her,
even if it meant ending their lives.
But one day, Mary's husband
Lord Darnley unexpectedly died.
Seeing a chance, Elizabeth blamed
Mary for Darnley's death.
The land turned against Mary,
and she was caught and imprisoned.
Tarukus and Blueford fought to free her.
Elizabeth bargained
with the two thorns in her side.
Turn yourselves in.
If you do so, I'll spare Mary's life.
There is no reason to refuse her offer.
I have no regrets.
The two were arrested...
...and executed.
Here are a few words as a parting gift:
Mary is already dead.
You were deceived.
See that lying over there
like a pile of rubbish?
That's your Mary.
You vile fiend, Elizabeth!
You betrayed us!
With my final breath I curse you
and all of your descendants!
I lay my curse upon you!
The knights were beheaded.
It is said that Tarukus's neck was stiff
with fury, and took several axes to cut.
Blueford's hair coiled around
his executioner's feet...
...digging into his killer's flesh.
And the story of their delusion
gave me goose bumps.
These legendary heroes cursed the world.
I dug them up and gave them life!
I turned them
into unstoppable revenants!
We swore fealty to Lord Dio!
We have come to end the world!
Death to everyone!
S-Such hatred!
Their scorn has been amplified!
Dio's made heroes into monsters!
Can JoJo overcome this delusion?
Hamon that burns in my left hand!
Scarlet Overdrive!
A-Astounding!
I-I had forgotten!
Much rides on Jonathan's shoulders!
His father's death
and his hope for the future!
And the hope of us all!
This boy has some skill.
He's perfect for warming up
after a 300-year nap.
This one's flesh belongs to me!
I'll gnaw on his yummy cartilage!
Another zombie!
This is no place for pawns.
W-What speed!
Lord Dio, this young man
has a great deal of spirit!
I ask for the pleasure of
drawing the curtains on his life!
As you will.
Tarukus, stand aside.
Black Knight Blueford, a supreme fighter
and utterly without mercy!
You can practically feel the pride
and skill flowing from him!
This is so strange.
I learned about him in school.
And now he's coming
to kill me.
I have to steady my breathing
and relax my muscles!
O-Oh, no! He's got both arms
behind his back!
Which will he attack with?
Or will he kick?
No! He uses his hair!
N-No!
You've got a keen eye
if you dodged my hair's Danse Macabre.
I'm enjoying this.
Jonathan!
This is bad!
He can't breathe down there!
He won't be able to use Hamon!
We have to go help him!
T-Tarukus!
Damn! We can't even help Jonathan!
It's already over.
He can't touch Blueford underwater.
My supervision is no longer needed here.
I'll now turn Wind Knights Lot
into a town of zombies!
Just one more night, then they will
spread through England like a plague!
I-I need to breathe to create Hamon!
Just one breath!
Now swim for the surface, boy.
You can't breathe down here,
and my armor weighs me down.
I won't use my sword.
This is a duel between heroes!
You need to make your move
before you drown!
Can I make it to the surface
before he does?
What are my odds?
As death threatened to take JoJo,
his explosive inner reserves awakened!
An ordinary man, his lungs screaming
for breath, would swim upward.
But not JoJo!
Instead, he turned and swam
deeper toward the bottom!
W-What is he thinking?
Hmm? Danny won't let go of your toy gun?
It's because you're trying
to take it away.
Change your thinking.
Try giving it to Danny instead.
Wind Knights Lot is a coal town.
That means the ground sunk long ago.
There!
There should be air trapped
under the rocks!
I found it!
With just one breath,
my blood's beat has returned!
I-Impossible!
The tables have turned on you!
Hamon will travel even better down here!
Underwater...
Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
Next episode
Blueford is a mess!
I'm a master of slaughter!
This pain is nothing.
You will be destined to die.
Life Magnetism Overdrive!
Chapter 6: Tomorrow's Pluck