The spines of this mask can pierce
a human brain.
But they haven't the power
to pierce our immortal brains.
We need more power.
Oh, what's this?
It's called a Red Stone of Aja,
a rare and beautiful gem.
It refracts light billions of times,
making it strong and pure.
Its power is miraculous.
But it is not enough!
This tiny stone doesn't
give the spines enough strength.
To complete our mask,
we need a flawless Red Stone.
We need a super Aja.
Once we have it...
...we will conquer the
sun, and become the final,
perfect step in evolution.
The masks were invented by
the most intelligent among them, Kars.
Kars and the others crossed the
Atlantic in search of a super Aja.
Suzie Q.
Yes, Madam Lisa Lisa, here it is.
Thank you.
In my hand is a perfectly flawless,
natural crystal.
A super Aja!
You had a Red Stone of Aja?!
The Pillar Men wiped out
the warriors of Hamon.
But this Stone narrowly escaped them.
I am its current guardian.
Caesar, I know how you must feel.
The stone masks killed our grandparents,
along with countless others.
And we've met its inventor, Kars.
Smash it!
Smash the Red Stone!
If you break it,
they'll cry like babies.
I cannot do that.
Why not?!
There is a legend that they
cannot be defeated without the Stone.
Why the heck not?!
I don't know.
But I perform my duty as guardian.
JoJo, Caesar...
You must take a final examination.
A-A final exam?!
Caesar, you must defeat Meshina.
JoJo, you must defeat Loggs.
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 17: The Deeper Plan
Are you ready, Caesar?
I'm more than ready!
It's almost dawn.
It's always darkest before dawn.
Now where on earth
is Loggs hiding?
I have to stay sharp.
I have a score to settle with him.
Is that Instructor Loggs?
H-How horrid!
I-It's unnatural!
Instructor Loggs!
H-He's dead!
E-Esidisi!
So you came to Venice, to this island.
To think that the woman guarding
the Stone is just an island over.
His lungs were pulled out.
Lungs are vital for Hamon-users.
It had to have been one swift kick.
The tyrannical Loggs.
You yelled at me for three weeks.
To be honest, I hated you.
I thought I would finally
get back at you for all you did.
But watch me from up there,
my instructor.
See the fruit of your torture!
Hey, Esidisi, it's six days early,
but I'll take it now.
The antidote in your nose ring is mine!
Out of my way.
I don't have time to deal with you.
Time? You have way more time than me!
That was sharp.
I think you've grown smarter.
But when somebody
looks at me like that...
...they're asking to die.
I'll tell you once more.
Get out of my way!
Touch me and you'll lose half your body!
Make me!
What's this?
Well? Get me out of your way!
I only move
if there's dog poo in my way.
His Hamon is breaking through my skin!
He's learned much control
in just three weeks.
However!
I must say your new skill surprises me.
But you're still far from ready
to fight against me!
I met and devoured countless
Hamon-users like you 2,000 years ago!
If I twist and break your finger off,
you'll never use it again!
Like this!
You finally noticed?
Your arm is wrapped up
in a fine silk thread.
It's soaked in vegetable oil
so it conducts Hamon well!
I was aiming for your neck,
but there was no chance!
H-How did you do it?!
I-It's...
It's a little morbid for my tastes.
First blood goes to my instructor
and me, Esidisi!
2,500 years ago, a man in China
wrote The Art of War.
He said this:
Victory is decided
before the battle is fought.
That means laying strategies
while your opponent is unaware.
I skipped school a lot.
But Granny Erina made sure
I studied history!
You may have lived a long time,
but you don't have a head for strategy!
Take this!
W-Why you...?!
Oh? Are you mad?
Are you upset that
I disintegrated your arm?
Get upset! I'm far more furious!
Because of that ring you put in me,
I haven't slept right for weeks!
I can't take it!
I just can't take it!
W-What's he doing?!
H-He's bawling!
I thought he'd blow his top for sure.
This Esidisi is full of surprises.
T-This is embarrassing.
He's throwing a tantrum!
My poor arm!
Some things are creepier
than anger.
I'll finish him quickly.
Ahh, I feel better now.
My emotions get out of control.
When I'm about to lose it,
I calm down by crying for a while.
You referred to Sun Tzu, right?
I know him, too.
Long ago, I journeyed to China.
All war is deception.
To fight is to delude.
Anger your enemies to
lure them into mistakes.
That's what you're planning, right?
I won't fall for it.
But JoJo, I really am shocked
at your improvements.
I admire your Hamon.
I've longed for a worthy opponent.
W-What are you doing to his arm?!
It's a bit thin,
but it will grow thicker in time.
H-He's too much!
He was crying a minute ago!
Oh, JoJo, I believe I've frightened you!
Admit it, you're scared of me!
I-I can't read him!
I've always read my opponents
and used their feelings against them.
But Esidisi's personality is beyond me.
Am I the one being read, here?!
W-What's happening to Loggs's body?!
I-It burns!
H-His body is boiling!
How in the...?!
An animal's temperature rises
when it moves or fights disease.
I can bring my blood to 500 degrees
and shoot it out.
I sent my boiling blood into him
when I took off his arm.
Wamuu can control the wind
with his Divine Sandstorm.
But I am a master of fire.
Heat is my domain!
Your power to utterly destroy a body
is astounding.
But I can see you're just
trying to scare me by doing it!
Try a Clacker Volley!
My Hamon isn't like it was a month ago!
I really did frighten you.
Your emotions caused you to attack
recklessly and too soon, JoJo.
My veins will inject boiling blood
into your head and turn it into stew!
This is why I am called
the Burning King!
JoJo...
Take this, Caesar!
Bubble Launcher!
Stop! That's enough!
If we continue,
one or both of us will die.
No, I hate to admit it,
but I'd be the loser.
I have trained here
ten years longer than you.
But your Hamon burned off all the hair
on my right arm.
What can I do
after being shamed like this?
You passed your final exam
with flying colors.
You're more interested in your
good-for-nothing friend's exam, Caesar?
I am only this strong because
I didn't want JoJo to outpace me.
And both of us are going to survive
our upcoming battle.
I'll say this, JoJo seems
lazy and impudent.
But he's good deep down.
You're bad at making friends,
but when you do, I guess it's true love.
T-That's...!
Esidisi!
That was a clever dodge.
T-The mask protected me, but...
H-Hot hot hot hot!
Damn his blood!
Blast it! These sexy lips
finally come out from under the mask,
and you just burned them, bastard!
JoJo, on the surface
you make witty banter.
But in your head,
you're planning, aren't you?
You turned pale, JoJo!
Did I hit the mark?
Was that a bull's-eye?!
My next plan...
I-I'll use the string!
I'll act like I'm dodging.
But I'll run a string along
these spikes while I move.
I can't let him catch on.
Once he steps inside the string,
I'll wrap him up, then use Hamon!
T-That laugh means trouble.
C-Could he be reading my plan?
No, that's impossible!
Here's the Burning King's Prison!
How long can you
keep avoiding my attacks?
So you noticed at last.
Why is my hat shrinking?
You're caught in my web!
My hat is 100% wool.
It conducts Hamon just fine.
Oho?
W-Why are you smiling?
Is there a reason?
Your next line is,
I'll wipe that smirk off your face!
B-But that's my trick!
A web? Look around you!
I am the one spinning a web!
I knew about your little plan all along!
JoJo, what did you say?
Victory is decided
before the battle is fought, was it?
True, true.
True, true, true!
How very true your words were!
But my plans were the ones to go
deeper and decide victory!
My veins have given you some new holes.
Now I'll fill them all
with my burning blood.
You'll look like a lovely birthday cake
covered in candles!
He's on a knife edge!
H-He won't make it!
Caesar!
Judging from what I can see,
I assume Loggs is dead.
If JoJo falls,
Esidisi will come after us next.
JoJo's too far away for us to help now.
It hurts, but we have to think about
Lisa Lisa and the Stone.
Now, let's prepare to move.
JoJo...
Let me hear your screams
as you twitch and writhe in despair!
You laugh as I hold you
on the edge of death?
Has the fear driven you mad?
Well...
My arms are folded and
my eyes are closed.
This is a victory laugh, Esidisi.
You lost today because
you snoozed for 2,000 years.
I lost?! You say I've lost?!
Oh? You don't get it?
You can't read me?
You don't understand
you've already lost?
You said your plans went deep,
but mine went even deeper!
Humans have been progressing
for the past 2,000 years.
In the 18th and 19th centuries,
sleight of hand became entertainment.
I'm a huge fan of it.
Illusion is my thing!
B-But I cut those strings!
How are they still whole?!
My rope magic worked!
I laid my trap so that even if
the string was cut, it would be safe.
Cutting here
leaves the white string whole.
A simple trick.
Now you'll say, My veins will move
faster than your pathetic Hamon!
My veins will move faster
than your pathetic Hamon!
Feel the beat of my Hamon Overdrive!
I can't... I can't...
You're a human...
I... I-I am the highest life form!
I won't be beaten!
That's it!
You've pushed me too far!
Esidisi's body is leaking
some kind of energy!
Is it the energy from
millennia of life?
Die already!
Die with the power you stole
from thousands of innocents!
My instructor, I must thank you
for torturing me.
Grazie, Loggs!
Santviento turned to stone
and only feigned death.
But even Esidisi's bones were destroyed.
Why is he different?
Maybe it's just because my Hamon
became stronger.
He's dead now, and I have
one of the antidotes I need.
I guess it reminds me of snot
because it's dripping from a nose ring.
But I have to drink it.
All right! I think it worked.
The ring around my windpipe is gone.
So, now I'll go see
Caesar and Lisa Lisa.
I think I used my head too much.
My shoulders are sore.
Six days until
the ring around JoJo's heart dissolves.
Next episode
How about the white one?
Wait until we cross!
But I really do like this design.
I'll eradicate them.
Which to choose?
Damn it! I can't hit her!