N-No!
I-I didn't see him holding the mask.
I didn't see him put the Red Stone in!
Dear God...
Kars...
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 25: The Birth of a Superbeing
He stood up!
Stand your ground!
German soldiers are not cowards!
The ultimate being?
Madness! No creature could
ever become perfect!
Kars...
Look at his arm!
It's still smoking!
The Hamon will ruin him!
He'll melt where he stands!
He might have put the Red Stone
into the mask,
but he is still utterly the same!
And he'll die like that!
Fire the UV amplifier again!
We'll end him for sure this time.
Hurry it up!
Sir!
What's going on with him?
What is he staring at?
L-Look!
See? Over there!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Am I seeing things?
His hand turned into a squirrel!
It's kind of cute, actually.
Look out!
It's dangerous!
Stay away from that squirrel!
The squirrel!
Get out of here! Hurry!
Unbelievable!
He can manipulate life at will!
Hooray!
The sun is rising!
The vampires...
The sunlight will take care of Kars.
We're saved!
It's no good. He's fine!
He's still standing, even under the sun!
This is a nightmare! It can't be!
This looks like our doom!
A perfect life form combines
the abilities of all other life forms.
It combines all life into one.
But this...
Breathtaking. Such beautiful radiance.
That light is the most
wonderful thing I've seen.
And now I have conquered it.
H-He's invincible!
He has no weaknesses!
Even Hamon won't work on him!
He's immortal! Unstoppable!
No one can beat him!
He is complete!
Kars, the Ultimate Thing, is born!
T-This is my fault.
I let him put on the mask
with the Red Stone in it.
Is... Is there no way to stop him?
Are we humans destined to die,
to become food for him?
No, I have a plan.
What was that, JoJo?
Hold her.
Yeah...
I have one last plan.
A final plan?
Yeah, I save it for last.
What is it?
JoJo, d-do you mean that final plan?
Listen up!
Do it till your last breath!
Do what until my last breath?
Run away!
I knew it!
Hamon-users mean nothing to me now.
But you...
Wamuu and Esidisi need to be avenged,
and I must celebrate.
JoJo, your death...
...will be dedicated to my birth!
He's catching up!
Pipe down!
I'm trying to think up with something!
Keep quiet!
JoJo's going out there to save Lisa Lisa
and the rest of us!
But it's useless! No plan of his could
overcome what Kars has become!
He's coming! Hurry!
Hey, Smokey!
I don't think you understand,
so I'll tell you something!
There's no reason for you to be
running with me!
Kars is after my blood alone!
He thinks killing me is the best way
to ring in his new life!
JoJo, there's something
you have to hear!
Lisa Lisa, your coach, she's your...
He's here! He's here!
Speedwagon, is he...?
Is he really the perfect being?
Yes, the power of the Red Stone will
make him into the ultimate life form!
A perfect being is: One, invincible.
Two, does not age.
Three, will not ever die.
Four, has the abilities of all
other life forms, and outperforms them.
In addition, it is like a Greek statue,
a model for beauty.
T-There's no way to stop him now.
He has no weakness at all!
Humans can't kill him,
not with Hamon or even the sun!
JoJo!
Smokey, your path ends here!
Tell me about it later!
JoJo!
That won't save you.
Let's see who's stronger, Kars!
That's...!
One of our warplanes!
JoJo!
The feathers are
as hard as armadillo shell.
They are coated in an oil
that deflects bullets.
Naturally, their hardness makes them
weapons as well as shields.
His feathers are like knives!
This looks bad!
But...
I got on this plane
to get away from you!
JoJo!
All he can do now is run!
Fly, JoJo! Fly!
That's all we humans can do now.
Current speed: 240 km/h.
No matter how evolved he might be,
he's still just an animal.
I'm safe for now.
I guess he can't keep up
with a plane for long.
The fuel!
Two hours left.
So I can run away for two hours.
Does that fool think he can run
from me for even a moment?
You'll never land safely now.
You won't stand on the earth again.
JoJo! JoJo!
Do you read me? Respond, JoJo!
Hey, Speedwagon!
JoJo! Grabbing that plane
was a smart move!
The Germans and I will do what we can
to help you get away!
Do you have a chart?
It's right here.
Good. Maintain radio contact.
I'll give you the plan.
What?!
First, give us your current position.
JoJo, do you read me?
What's wrong? Hey!
JoJo, respond! JoJo!
Yeah, I read you.
But Speedwagon, no technique
or weapon will work on Kars.
You said he was immortal.
Yeah, I did.
Your plan to run is all we can do.
Listen up, old man.
I have a different idea.
What idea?
Now JoJo, don't do anything rash!
Just keep away from him!
We won't be able to stop him later!
No! Don't even think
of doing something on your own!
Just listen to me, okay?
He's the ultimate being on earth!
But he's from Earth.
This planet gave him life.
And it might take him back!
What do you mean?
How would the Earth take him back?
Magma!
Magma, the hottest thing on earth!
I'll drive him into the lava
at Isola di Volgano to kill him!
D-Don't! You've risked your life
more than enough times!
Let us and the Germans handle it!
Listen to him, JoJo!
Don't be crazy!
Kars will kill you!
Sorry, I can already see the volcano.
The time is now!
Mr. Speedwagon...
It's happening again...
Jonathan's father,
Jonathan and George...
The men of the Joestar family
all led short lives.
I don't want to lose you, too!
Please stop, JoJo!
For Lisa Lisa's sake, too!
Lisa Lisa is your mother!
What was that? Say again!
What is that noise?
This is insane!
Piranhas?!
What the hell?!
They're chewing up the plane!
How did they get in?!
Kars's feathers!
They transformed!
Damn it! My parachute!
You little bastards!
Wh-What now?!
JoJo!
What's going on? Respond!
JoJo! JoJo!
You're brainless.
That parachute is like a spider's web
trapping you, JoJo.
You're just a little butterfly.
I'll take my time killing you!
What?!
I-It's a dummy!
Kars, I'm not going down
without a fight!
You're going with me into that volcano!
JoJo!
Damn you!
Lunatic!
Granny Erina, you told me about
my grandfather once.
You said he sank into the Atlantic
with his lifelong foe to save you.
I hate to sadden you again.
But I guess
this is the Joestar blood in me.
Did you really think I couldn't get away
before you hit the ground?
Kars!
You're dying alone, JoJo!
W-What the...?!
Kars, this plane will be your coffin.
You!
Von Stroheim!
How and when did you get in there?!
I wasn't sure you could handle it alone!
It was cold in this pontoon.
But you came.
But it's time to jump, JoJo!
What do you mean jump?
But I don't even have a parachute!
Listen to me and jump out of the plane!
JoJo, respond!
Say something! Anything!
Just talk to me, JoJo!
JoJo...
Von Stroheim...you crazy bastard.
You're even crazier than me!
B-But I have to thank you.
Y-You look all right,
but what about Kars?
Did Kars take a lava dive?!
You...worms...
Next episode
Did you say Hamon Overdrive?
Bless our mother earth!
Don't you wish to purge your fears?!
JoJo!
Farewell, everyone.
Chapter 26: The Ascendant One