The poison rings in JoJo's chest and
neck cannot be surgically removed.
Before the rings dissolve
and the poison is released,
JoJo has to defeat Wamuu
and take the antidote!
Venice, Italy
What a disaster!
I only said one month as a bluff,
but they took it seriously!
I should've said one year!
Hey, JoJo...
Quit screwing around!
Start thinking!
I-I am thinking!
But there's no point
in thinking too hard about it.
Not only for me.
You'll get depressed, too, Caesar.
JoJo, you need to at least learn to do
what I am about to do.
The water isn't falling!
JoJo, catch!
Hold it like that.
That's all? Piece of cake.
Here's what went wrong.
The strength of our Hamon
is about equal.
But you always release it
in a burst from your palm.
That's why the water exploded.
But I was releasing Hamon
from the tip of my finger alone.
Just one point.
Using one point creates a vibrating skin
that holds the water.
Scattering Hamon like you do
wastes energy.
A squirt gun with a smaller hole
shoots farther. Got that, chump?
Listen, JoJo. You have to train
to control your Hamon completely.
That is why we came to Venice,
the home of my coach!
Oh, no!
The two words I hate the most are
effort and work!
31 days until the rings dissolve
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 16: Lisa Lisa, Hamon Coach
What's this?
I thought Venice was a tourist town.
Why would a master of Hamon be here?
Excuse me.
We want to go to Air Suplena Island.
Gondolier, are you listening?!
He's standing on a floating oar!
W-Who the heck is this guy?!
What the...?!
You'll get it now!
I don't know who you are,
but you're going to pay for that!
You can use Hamon well enough
to stand on water, hmm?
A woman?!
C-Coach!
She is called Lisa Lisa.
No one knows her true name,
her history, or where she learned Hamon.
But she will be our coach
for the next month.
I still have to make you pay
for hitting me with that oar.
I won't hold back because you're a girl!
I tested your talents
and found them superb.
I'm impressed you can walk on water
without training.
However!
You must be prepared to die
if you want to master Hamon in a month!
S-She's made a high bar!
What the...?!
Joseph Joestar, you will wear that
breathing correction mask at all times.
I can't--
Use rhythm. With proper rhythm,
you'll have no trouble.
But if you fail to maintain rhythm,
the mask will begin to suffocate you.
You will learn to run 100 kilometers
with the mask on!
Take this stupid thing off right--
I-I can't breathe!
Your training has begun.
I'll take it off for meals
and tooth brushing.
JoJo, just maintain your rhythm.
It'll be like wearing a Halloween mask.
Y-You're gonna get it, you--
I have one more thing to tell you.
I am not teaching you
so that you can save your own skin.
I am forging warriors
that can destroy our enemies!
Y-You witch.
You want another round with her?
I don't hit women.
Now, Caesar, JoJo...
...welcome to Venice!
Sheesh.
I respect her skill with Hamon,
but I'd never marry a girl like that.
She's kinda cute, though.
Bow to her!
What? Why is a playboy like you
so polite to her?
I respect my coach like my own mother.
I won't tolerate rudeness toward her.
Air Suplena Island is 30 minutes
northeast of Venice by boat.
Compared to the city,
it is dark and mysterious.
But the island's beauty
matches Lisa Lisa perfectly.
This is our new training ground!
That entire island is my home.
We have to prepare to face death, eh?
Just how will we train?
I see.
You're safe, and so is my grandson.
I couldn't be happier.
Tell Granny about the poison rings
and I'll beat you senseless!
I can't tell her. How could I?
This is the prologue,
we call it Hell Climb Pillar!
W-What?!
What's this about?
C-Coach, are we really starting
with Hell Climb Pillar?
I haven't ever attempted it.
Hell Climb Pillar has claimed
many trainees' lives.
If you cannot overcome this test,
you have no right to be here.
Hey, don't keep this a secret
between yourselves!
What the hell is this Hell thing anyway?
Step through these doors and you'll see.
Coach, no!
Th-This is...
...oil!
It's flowing down this pillar.
It's 24 meters to the top.
Climb using only your hands.
There is no other exit.
If you can't climb,
you'll die down there.
We have to get up this slippery,
24-meter tall pillar?!
30 days until the rings dissolve
A test of endurance using Hamon,
the grueling Hell Climb Pillar!
This is bad.
I can barely cling to the pillar.
Moving my fingers even a bit
is exhausting.
Falling off of this pillar just once
would leave me
with no energy to climb!
We'd starve and die!
JoJo and I both!
JoJo, the longer it takes,
the harder it will get!
Hurry and climb!
N-No!
I have to worry about myself!
I lost control just by talking.
This is ridiculous!
I just got here!
She knows I don't have
the power to climb this bloody pillar!
Damn her! Just tossing
us down here like that!
She's lost my respect after all!
I've always been nice to girls.
But I'll come up with some way
to torture her later!
Bloody hell!
A lot of trainees died
trying to climb this thing, huh?
Are you sure they weren't simply too stupid?
Using anything but Hamon
is an insult to the pillar!
Hell Climb Pillar loves only Hamon
and rejects all else!
Never forget that!
Wait! Hold on, Lisa Lisa!
I mean, Coach!
Y-You won't really let me die down here
if I don't have the power to climb up.
It's my first day here.
This is just a test to fire me up.
You'll pull me out later, right?
Such cold eyes!
A look like that means
she'll really let me die!
Blast it all!
Who do you think you are?!
You being cute just makes me
even angrier about this!
Twenty-eight hours later.
Caesar is at 15 meters.
JoJo is at zero meters.
The rings will dissolve in 28 days.
More than a day has passed
and Caesar's only made it that far.
I shouldn't be worrying about others,
but he's struggling.
The fingers supporting him
look like they're about to come loose!
His Hamon is about to run out!
Fight, Caesar!
He's about to fall again!
He's on his fingertips!
Caesar!
W-Whoa!
W-Wait a minute.
Were his fingertips always like that?
He wasn't about to fall off at all!
He was...
A squirt gun with
a smaller hole shoots farther.
N-No way!
I-I'll give it a shot!
Let's solve a Hamon mystery!
Is this it?
I did it! I'm sticking!
My Hamon is sticking!
I thought having your hands
flat supported your weight.
It's odd, but the opposite is true!
Hamon concentrated into the fingertips
is much stronger!
What a simple puzzle! I've got it!
Now that I understand,
I just have to climb.
So how will I torture that awful woman?
Looks like JoJo's got it.
Another 24 hours have passed.
Caesar is at 18 meters.
JoJo is at 16 meters.
The rings will dissolve in 27 days!
Now I know why Caesar slowed down
so much at 18 meters.
The pillar widens out as it goes up.
This is where it gets hard.
The pillar is as mean as that woman!
Three hours later.
Caesar is at 19 meters.
JoJo is at 18 meters.
Oh? What's that?!
I-It's a crack!
And it's big enough for my fingers!
Hooray! Time for a break!
What luck!
Yes! Now I can catch my breath!
W-What was that?!
It felt like a switch!
W-What's happening?!
No!
Hell Climb Pillar loves only Hamon
and rejects all else!
Watch out! Something's coming!
Crap! I turned something on!
Even climbing this thing
might be too much.
H-How can we get past that?!
A sheet of oil shoots out at
the 20 meter point of the pillar!
The high-pressure stream
cuts like a razor!
W-What's up, Caesar?
A-Are you mad at me or something?
S-Sorry, Caesar.
But I know any sane person
would've tried to rest there.
Whoever made this was twisted
to set a trap like that!
I wasn't looking at you
with blame, JoJo.
It was worry.
Can my Hamon get me through
that razor-sharp barricade?
There's one way!
W-What the...?!
He's sticking with his feet!
Caesar!
Hamon to attract and repel!
My Hamon is focused at my feet to stick
I have to control two opposing types
of Hamon at the same time!
I-I did it!
I hate to say it, but JoJo
can't yet control two types of Hamon.
He can't get through!
S-Spectacular!
I'm glad Caesar found a way through.
But I'm not sure
I can perform a stunt like that.
Nine hours later.
Caesar reaches the top after 61 hours!
C-Coach!
JoJo can't take any more!
Stop the oil, please!
Knowing JoJo, he'll attempt
some try-or-die stunt any second now!
But will he make it?!
Hanging around like this
is getting me nowhere.
If he tries to break through,
that oil will split him right in half!
Even if he's blasted away,
he'll just fall and starve to death.
Coach!
To hell with it!
I have to try or die!
Here goes nothing!
Don't, JoJo! Just stay there!
The beat of my Hamon cuts like a knife!
JoJo!
JoJo... He...
He's using Hamon
to slide along the oil sheet!
The oil loses momentum as it shoots out.
And so!
He used the speed of the oil
to jump on top of it!
He didn't fall!
In fact, he's up three meters!
No one has ever
climbed the pillar that way before.
Turning his weakness into strength,
he's quite clever.
I-I made it!
But it's not over yet.
I'm on the wall.
But its overhang is even worse
than the pillar's.
I'm completely exhausted.
There isn't even a meter to go, damn it!
I-I can't control...
...my breathing any longer.
C-Caesar!
Don't misunderstand.
I wasn't mad at you earlier.
Coach, please forgive me
for saving JoJo like this.
That's fine, but aren't you
exhausted, too?
I forgot!
Don't let go, please!
Caesar!
Ten seconds later, after saying
Don't let go, 13 times...
...JoJo reached the top!
Hold it, Miss Lisa Lisa.
While I was clinging to the pillar
for my life, I was thinking.
How am I gonna get back at her?
Shall I strip you bare,
or pinch your nose till you cry?
I thought he was easygoing,
but I guess he's the vengeful type.
Which will it be?!
I-I did it! I'm holding water in a cup
while it's upside-down!
Marvelous!
In only three days, he's learned
how to control Hamon!
JoJo's talent is incredible, but Coach
Lisa Lisa's training is even more so!
Coach!
I-I'm impressed.
G-Give me more training, please!
You'll see. I can overcome anything!
Forget it.
I guess he's easygoing after all.
Believe me, I have many activities
ready for you.
I'll impress you into the ground.
Yes, ma'am!
The next three weeks
will be harder than this warm-up.
And who are you, sneaking up on me?
Wh-Who are these guys?
The water is like pudding!
These two are my servants and
your instructors, Meshina and Loggs.
I-I couldn't even begin to do that.
Do you want to learn?
I asked if you want to learn.
O-Of course I do!
I have to!
Do you?
Then come here
and take a good, close look.
Tell us your names already!
From here on, we're gonna...
...forge you into real men!
Breathe! If your breath is strong,
your muscles will be, too!
You have to breathe ten times a second!
T-This sucks!
Inhale for ten minutes,
then exhale for ten minutes!
If you can, the mask comes off!
Th-This is crazy!
Seven days until the rings dissolve!
Next episode
You must take a final examination.
We need more power.
He's good deep down.
This is unnatural!
I can't take it!
Chapter 17: The Deeper Plan