JoJo...
S-So you're JoJo?
Listen up, JoJo.
Santviento, the Pillar Man, uses the mask
to turn men into vampires.
He makes them stronger
so he can eat them.
He's a grave threat!
He must be destroyed!
Careful, JoJo!
Tag!
You spoke a minute ago, right?
Hello! How are you?
Happy! Fun! Nice to meet you, man!
Now together, Santviento!
Three, four!
Happy! Fun! Nice to meet you, man!
From the silent depths
The pillars awaken from ages-long sleep
Crimson blood
Summons the valorous to stand up
If inherited love is called fate
Then take another step with smiling eyes
Mystify the darkness, dodge in a blink
Avoid the blade,
find an opening and strike
Conviction tested
opens the way to the future
Like a bloody storm
Hot like a bloody stone
Destiny written into your veins
The undying bonds of honor arise
Take hold of them
Chapter 13: JoJo vs. The Ultimate Being
Happy! Fun! Nice to meet you, man!
JoJo, stop fooling around!
JoJo, what are you doing?
Well, I have a theory that
he's not a bad guy after all.
I'm testing it out.
I think it's wrong to assume
someone is evil.
Don't be an idiot!
Look at these dead soldiers!
Nonsense! You reap what you sow!
You experimented on him
and blasted him with guns!
Besides, Speedwagon, I came here
so that I can get you back to New York.
I have no reason to fight.
Now, everyone!
Happy! Fun! Nice to meet you, man!
What's this guy's problem?
He's just ignoring me.
I'm a bit upset.
Fine. I'll just stick my foot out
and trip him!
W-What happened?
Th-That was the strangest sensation.
This is new to me.
What is this tool?
He spoke!
He really does understand!
Somehow he's mastered our language!
A-Amazing!
He's pulling it apart like
an expert watchmaker!
Soldiers need hours of drilling
in order to do that!
H-His intelligence is incredible!
So bright.
This light is also new to me.
We weren't the ones observing!
It was him watching us!
Listen here, pal!
If you can understand,
then respond!
Knock, knock!
Watch out, JoJo!
You begin to irritate me, primitive.
What the...?!
Rib Blades,
also known as Fighting Ribs.
Maximum reach: 132 cm
Maximum pressure: 825 kg/cm2
Capable of turning in
any direction!
JoJo!
Sparks?
What is this human?
My body didn't absorb his.
He flew away.
His leg also appears fine.
I have never seen such a human.
Is he a unique specimen?
Or all humans of this age the same?
It appears that human is unique.
JoJo, this is horrible!
Old man...
You bastard!
Let go of the old man!
Now I feel like fighting!
I'll have you mounted in a museum!
Humans have also evolved somewhat.
I'll flood you full of Hamon!
The Hamon is making that blood...!
It's not working!
My Hamon is running off of him like rain
from a raincoat and into that blood!
His skin is acting like a ground
just like Straizo's scarf!
My body and his body repel each other.
M-My hand...
...it's...
...still there.
Just a little joke.
I rolled my wrist forward
in the nick of time!
But this is a serious pickle.
He's immune to Hamon!
What should I do?
No, he's not!
Hamon works! It's protecting you!
It keeps his body from eating you!
Fool! What do you do
when you eat a blowfish?
You kill it, remove
the poison parts and eat!
It will be no different for Santviento!
Well this is a perfect mess!
I have to think of something fast!
I need an escape plan at least!
Absolutely not!
You can't let Santviento get out!
He's a danger to mankind!
Shut up! Don't talk like
you didn't have a hand in this!
And you think I need more pressure?!
I'll send Hamon right into his body
through this knife!
His skin is bending like rubber!
But can you dodge this?!
Here's Hamon in your eye!
This is a surefire hit!
Wha-What?!
Even his eyes are like rubber!
No! JoJo, get out of there!
JoJo!
He won't be able to breathe after
being hit there!
He seems to create energy in
his blood through breathing.
But while unconscious,
he's an ordinary human.
JoJo! Use your Hamon breathing!
Breathe, damn it!
Use your Hamon breathing!
JoJo!
This is the end!
I have to use the self-destruct!
For the Fatherland!
For eternal glo--
Hold it, von Stroheim!
No need to panic!
I took a big gamble.
Attacks from outside are no good.
So I'll send Hamon into him
while he eats.
JoJo!
I was waiting for him to try this!
This is perfect!
Enjoy your Hamon treat!
I-I get it now.
After entering that foul body,
I understand its digestive process.
Each of his cells uses digestive fluid
to dissolve the cells of his prey.
That's why he appears to
absorb his opponents.
I'm only safe because I sent Hamon
into him as he tried to dissolve me.
But your Hamon was too weak!
It wasn't enough to destroy Santviento!
Chunks of his body
are trying to reform!
Straizo did something like this,
so I figured you would do the same!
Von Stroheim!
Pay attention!
Does sunlight hurt him?!
Y-Yes!
Joestar, it was written
on the walls of the cave!
Sunlight will hurt him!
He made the masks to conquer the sun!
What are you doing, Joestar?!
That door leads outside!
I'll destroy you with sunlight!
He's running out of breath!
He'll lose control of his Hamon!
He hasn't trained with it,
so the battle has tired him!
Cease this foolishness, primitive!
JoJo, use your Hamon breathing!
If I could breathe,
I wouldn't be so tired!
Damn it!
I've had more than enough of you!
I'm dragging you up these stairs
so you can do some sunbathing!
What the...?!
Heavy... I feel so heavy.
Wh-What's happening?
Meat Invade, also known as Foul Flesh.
Bits of Santviento are attacking!
They're draining me!
Y-You son of a...
Keep moving...
I never expected such a human
to be born while I slumbered.
Leave the rest to me,
Rudol von Stroheim!
It's just this door, right?
I believe I can handle that for you!
Von Stroheim, you...
Cursed peasants.
Just a few centimeters more!
A meaningless struggle.
This is trouble.
Joestar, could you do me a favor?
What is it?! I'm trying to think!
Be quiet!
Listen to me!
You see the axes on the wall?
Can you reach one?
Use one to chop off my leg!
Wh-What?!
Use an axe to hack off my leg!
Then I can reach the door!
B-But...
You're really asking me to do that?!
Just do it! He's starting to reform!
Don't ask me! I'm not a doctor!
I'm a proud servant of the Wehrmacht!
I am prepared to do my duty!
I would proudly give a few legs
for the sake of the Fatherland!
Do it now, Joestar!
Quit fussing!
If you want me to chop, I'll chop!
I want you to chop!
I figured he was all hot air, but when
it comes down to it, he's got real guts.
We think differently,
but I respect your courage.
Forgive me!
How do you feel now that
you're in the sun?!
Did we do it?
Wh-What?!
He's crawling into the wound in my leg!
Get out of there!
This is a shock!
Von Stroheim is safe and Hamon-free!
Santviento is inside me!
What a fearsome creature!
What tenacity to live!
If he's inside von Stroheim,
he is safe even in sunlight!
S-Such horror!
This is horrifying!
Do you know what frightens me, Joestar?
My leg doesn't hurt.
In fact, it feels quite pleasant!
Von Stroheim!
Hold on!
Y-You won't...
Joestar!
You've seen what Santviento,
the ultimate being, can do.
There is no hope for me.
I'll use this to destroy both of us.
But I must tell you something
before I die.
So listen up, you annoying Englishman.
The Wehrmacht did not awaken Santviento
because of military curiosity alone.
What?
Why so suddenly?!
Listen!
It is your destiny to hear this!
Recently the Wehrmacht discovered
another Pillar hidden in Europe!
W-What?!
Von Stroheim, are you serious?!
That means Santviento is not unique.
The Pillar Men have slept for millennia
and we seek their fantastic powers!
Soon, they will awaken.
If a weakness other than sunlight
cannot be found, all is lost.
That is why we had to
experiment on Santviento.
Events fifty years ago have
destined you to fight the Pillar Men!
Joestar, your Hamon is too weak
to overcome them!
Go to Rome! Someone awaits you there!
It is a man Speedwagon knows well!
H-He's trying to control my body
and make it hide in that well!
But soon I'll open myself up
and let the sun shine in!
Von Stroheim, you can't...
Human greatness is in proudly
facing down one's fears.
The words of the
Greek historian Plutarch.
Farewell...
...you annoying Englishman!
Don't do it! I still have questions!
Damn that crazy soldier!
Putting on a show like that...
Santviento!
Get out of my way!
If you don't, you'll die, JoJo!
Steady your breathing.
Use your Hamon breathing.
Move it! You were doomed from the start!
A-And now you'll say,
I see through you, primitive!
It's high noon.
The sun is above and reflecting off
the water. That'll cook you good.
Try jumping into the well after thinking
about the movement of the sun!
I'm not letting you fall into the water!
I-I'm alive thanks to the sun.
It's turned him into a solid statue!
Next episode
My grandfather died tragically.
Then you couldn't even beat a pigeon!
Bring out more UV lamps!
Awaken, my masters!
Chapter 14: Elite Ancient Warriors